<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 07:37:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomic-Scale Tailoring of Ni-Rich Cathodes for the Development of Commercial Li-Ion Batteries: From Laboratory to Market]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of the Li-ion battery industry has promoted the development of breakthrough materials and systems; nevertheless, achieving desired performance through sophisticated designs within well-established systems has also become essential. Here, it is demonstrated that precise control of the lithium-to-transition-metal (Li/M) ratio serves as a commercially viable lever to tune the voltage profile of Ni-rich cathodes. This arises from the combined effects of Ni defect at Li sites...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Intensity Statin versus Upfront Equivalent-Dose Combination of Moderate-Intensity Statin with Ezetimibe Following Acute Myocardial Infarction (ROSUZET-AMI): protocol of a multicentre, open-label, randomised non-inferiority trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: High-intensity statin therapy is recommended as a first-line strategy for lowering low-density lipoprotein cholesterol (LDL-C) levels in patients with acute myocardial infarction (AMI). A combination of moderate-intensity statin and ezetimibe at an equivalent dose to high-intensity statin may achieve similar LDL-C reduction with fewer side effects. This study evaluates the long-term efficacy and safety of this approach, initiated following AMI, compared with high-intensity statin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunomodulatory Properties and Ameliorative Effects of <em>Pediococcus inopinatus</em> in an Animal Model of Inflammatory Bowel Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) is a chronic gastrointestinal disorder associated with dysregulated immune responses and gut inflammation. In this study, lactic acid bacteria were isolated from various types of skate kimchi, and 100 strains were screened for their anti-inflammatory activity. WiKim0108 demonstrated potent suppression of nitric oxide production and proinflammatory cytokines (IL-1β, IL-6, TNF-α) in lipopolysaccharide (LPS)-stimulated RAW 264.7 macrophages without cytotoxic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stem Cell R&amp;D in Korea: Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow - A Paradigm Shift from Therapeutics to Bio-Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memantine modulates neuroinflammation and motor coordination in a Parkinson's disease model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memantine, an NMDA receptor antagonist clinically approved for Alzheimer's disease, has been implicated in modulating neuroinflammatory responses beyond its anti-excitotoxic actions. To explore its potential relevance in Parkinson's disease, this study evaluated memantine's effects in both LPS-activated microglial cells and a synucleinopathy mouse model. In BV-2 cells, memantine elicited a modest but measurable attenuation of TNF-α and IL-6 secretion, which was accompanied by downregulation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Posture-dependent cerebrospinal fluid flow measurement in the optic nerve subarachnoid space using multi-delay 2D interslice saturation MRI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have indicated that CSF dynamics within the optic nerve subarachnoid space (ONSAS) may play an important role in the progression of optic diseases. Yet, as common optical tests are limited to the ocular structures and cannot probe beyond the optic nerve head, direct evaluation of CSF dynamics in ONSAS remains challenging due to limited imaging methods. In this study, we propose a non-invasive MRI method, inversion-recovery alternate ascending/descending directional navigation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase 1 Study of IMC-002, a Next-Generation Anti-CD47 Antibody, in Advanced Solid Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: IMC-002 demonstrated favorable safety/tolerability at doses of 5-30 mg/kg every 2 weeks. RP2D was defined as 20 mg/kg every 3 weeks. Preliminary anti-tumor activity was observed, with a CBR of 33%.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proficiency test for gamma-emitting radionuclides in seawater: A case study from South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Following the release of Advanced Liquid Processing System (ALPS) treated water - radioactive contaminated water purified to regulatory safety limits for all radionuclides except ³H - from the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Plant, the need for reliable marine radioactivity monitoring has become critical. This study describes a proficiency test (PT) program organized by the Korea Research Institute of Standards and Science (KRISS) to assess the analytical capabilities of six domestic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of an LC-MS/MS method for Tirzepatide, a dual GIP/GLP-1 receptor agonist, in rat plasma for application to a pharmacokinetic study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A sensitive and rapid liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry (LC-MS/MS) method was developed and validated for the quantification of tirzepatide, a dual agonist of glucose-dependent insulinotropic polypeptide (GIP) and glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) receptors in rat plasma. Tirzepatide was extracted from rat plasma by protein precipitation using methanol. Chromatographic separation was achieved using a peptide C18 column with gradient elution of water and acetonitrile containing 0.1 %...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical injury history increases pulmonary susceptibility to PM2.5 inhalation: Toxicological evidence for risk assessment in a neglected vulnerable population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Environmental health risk assessments typically prioritize vulnerable populations such as the elderly, children, and individuals with respiratory diseases. However, individuals with a history of chemical-induced lung injury are rarely considered, despite potentially heightened sensitivity to air pollutants. Therefore, this study investigated the pulmonary health risks of particulate matter (PM) 2.5 exposure in a chemical lung injury model, reflecting realistic exposure conditions. Mice were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Depressive episode and treatment outcomes in elderly individuals with tuberculosis: A prospective cohort study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In elderly individuals with tuberculosis, depressive episodes are associated with functional impairment, suicidal ideation, and poor treatment outcomes. Routine mental health assessments at tuberculosis diagnosis may help improve clinical outcomes in aging populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Advances in Modulating the Crystallization Dynamics of Sn-Pb Mixed Perovskites for High-Efficiency All-Perovskite Tandem Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A deep understanding of Sn-Pb mixed perovskites is critical for the development of highly efficient all-perovskite tandem solar cells that surpass the radiative efficiency limits of single-junction devices. However, the rapid crystallization and intrinsic instability of Sn-Pb mixed perovskites often lead to crystal lattice defects, compositional inhomogeneity, and poor film morphology, which significantly reduce both device performance and stability. This review systematically examines the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptions of Effective Nursing Handover Education: A Mixed-Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that nursing curricula should integrate standardized communication tools, simulation-based training with authentic cases, and learner-centered strategies. Enhancing situational overviews, interactive environments, and formative feedback could contribute to improved handover competency and ultimately improve patient safety outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing Deaminated DNA to Modulate mRNA Translation for Controlled and Sequential Protein Expression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Messenger RNA (mRNA) offers transformative potential in vaccines and therapeutics for a range of intractable diseases. While considerable efforts have focused on enhancing protein expression levels to improve efficacy, comparatively little attention has been given to regulating the rate and timing of protein expression. Given that sudden antigen bursts can overstimulate immune responses and pose serious risks in susceptible individuals, precise control over translation kinetics is essential for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Hall Resistivity Anomalies in Epitaxial SrRuO<sub>3</sub> Thin Films by Mo Doping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Magnetic transport properties are essential for probing the interaction between charge and spin dynamics. Those include the anomalous Hall effect (AHE) and topological Hall effect (THE), which are useful in the development of spintronic devices. SrRuO(3) (SRO) offers an ideal platform for investigating the Hall effect, induced by robust ferromagnetism, and can be further manipulated by tuning the spin-orbit-coupled band structure near the Fermi level. In this study, we investigated how Mo doping...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chiral Acoustic Phonon and Conservation of Pseudoangular Momentum in α-Quartz]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While the linear motion of phonons is widely understood as arising from the translational symmetry of crystal lattices, recent studies have revealed the intrinsic rotational motion of phonons in condensed matter with discrete rotational symmetry. These phonons, termed chiral phonons, carry angular momentum associated with the rotational motion of atomic masses, as well as pseudoangular momentum arising from the phase winding of their circular motion. Chiral phonons give rise to novel physical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Water-solid interactions on NaCl: Tracking adsorption to deliquescence with in situ scanning probe microscopy under a wide range of water vapor pressure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Water adsorption and phase transitions on NaCl surfaces before dissolution play a crucial role in understanding interfacial water-solid interactions. In this study, we employ variable-pressure scanning probe microscopy (SPM) to systematically investigate nanoscale morphological and tribological changes across a wide range of relative humidity (RH). At extremely low RH (<10-2%), water shows a strong affinity for Na+ ions, leading to increased friction, particularly at surface defects such as step...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fucoxanthin suppresses amyloid-β and pyroglutamate-3-Aβ accumulation by modulating the PI3K/Akt/GSK-3β signaling pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aberrant aggregation of amyloid-β (Aβ) peptides is a hallmark of Alzheimer's disease (AD), contributing to synaptic dysfunction and cognitive decline. Recently, pyroglutamate-modified Aβ (pE3-Aβ) has emerged as a key contributor to Aβ pathology, as it is a highly aggregation-prone variant that enhances amyloid seeding and accelerates plaque propagation. β-Secretase (BACE1) and glutaminyl cyclase (QC) are essential enzymes for generating Aβ and pE3-Aβ, respectively, and represent key therapeutic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concurrent variations of the unique course of the azygos vein, the kinked common carotid artery, and the branching pattern of the internal iliac arteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This case highlights that various rare vascular anomalies may coexist in a single individual; anatomist, surgeons, and other clinicians should be aware of this possibility during dissection and surgical procedures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding Surface-Bound Isomers: A QIT-ToF-SIMS Platform Integrating Tandem Mass Spectrometry and Laser Spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A quadrupole-ion-trap-integrated time-of-flight secondary ion mass spectrometry (QIT-ToF-SIMS) system was developed to enable detailed molecular surface analysis via tandem mass spectrometry combined with laser photodissociation spectroscopy. In this approach, secondary molecular ions were selectively isolated in the ion trap using the stored waveform inverse Fourier-transform technique and subsequently subjected to collision-induced dissociation or photoinduced dissociation. Using isomeric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification and characterization of a novel, low-temperature-active GH8 endo-β-1,4-glucanase exhibiting broad pH stability from Antarctic <em>Glacieibacterium</em> sp. PAMC 29367]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endo-β-1,4-glucanase plays an essential role in the breakdown of cellulosic substances that consist of D-glucose units linked by β-1,4-glycosidic bonds. In this work, the gene encoding a novel extracellular glycoside hydrolase (GH) family 8 endo-β-1,4-glucanase (GluS) from Glacieibacterium sp. PAMC 29367, an Antarctic lichen (Megaspora verrucosa)-associated bacterial species, was identified, cloned, and characterized. The GluS gene (1080-bp) was predicted to express a non-modular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High light intensity enhances cannabinoid biosynthesis through concerted gene expression in hemp (<em>Cannabis sativa</em>) flowers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings demonstrate that a light intensity of 600 μmol·m^(-2)·s^(-1) effectively enhances both biomass and cannabinoid accumulation at the flowering stage, providing valuable insights for controlled-environment hemp cultivation aimed at maximizing CBD yield.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Boric acid-mediated sol-gel construction of transparent, photoactive TiO<sub>2</sub> films]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Correction for 'Boric acid-mediated sol-gel construction of transparent, photoactive TiO(2) films' by Su Yeon Rhee et al., Chem. Commun., 2025, https://doi.org/10.1039/d5cc05088j.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practices and perceptions of 5-aminosalicylic acid use in Crohn's disease: a nationwide survey of physicians in Korea by KASID Guidelines Taskforce Team]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This survey reveals a substantial gap between clinical guidelines and current practice in Korea regarding 5-ASA use for CD. Many physicians continue to view 5-ASA as a relevant option, particularly for patients with low inflammatory burden. These discrepancies likely reflect practical factors such as clinical experience and drug characteristics, which should be carefully considered before excluding 5-ASA from CD management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Patient Satisfaction and Trust Through Electronic Patient Portals: Mediating Effects of Patient-Centered Communication and Self-Care Skills Among Chinese Deaf and Hard-Of-Hearing Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the impact of Electronic Patient Portals (EPPs) on patient satisfaction and trust among Deaf and Hard of Hearing (DHH) patients in China. Utilizing data from a sample of 317 DHH patients, the study employs regression analyses and mediation models to explore relationships among EPPs use, patient-centered communication (PCC), self-care skills, patient satisfaction, and trust in healthcare providers and institutions. The findings reveal that EPPs significantly enhance PCC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-Month Postoperative Tibial Sesamoid Position Predicts Recurrence After Minimally Invasive Hallux Valgus Correction: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Postoperative TSP on anteroposterior standing radiographs at 1 month after surgery was associated with HV recurrence after MITO surgery. Precise correction of TSP may be essential to reduce the likelihood of HV recurrence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial Expression of Concern: Prevention of multiple system atrophy using human bone marrow-derived mesenchymal stem cells by reducing polyamine and cholesterol-induced neural damages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of Ultranarrow Band Red Photoluminescence from Pure Organic Self-Assembled T2T Micro-Rods: A Route to High-Resolution Light Sources]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultranarrow emission linewidths and high spectral purity are essential for next-generation displays and advanced optoelectronic/photonic applications. A red photoluminescence (PL) peak with a full width at half-maximum (FWHM) of 3.2 nm at 625 nm is reported from pure organic π-conjugated 2,4,6-tris(biphenyl-3-yl)-1,3,5-triazine (T2T) self-assembled micro-rods (SAMRs). The sharp PL emission intensifies under prolonged exposure and increased laser power, indicating a photo-brightening (PB) effect....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between normal-weight central obesity and asymptomatic hyperuricemia in Korean adults: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In Korean adults aged over 20 years, normal-weight central obesity was significantly associated with asymptomatic hyperuricemia. Therefore, screening tests and proper management of asymptomatic hyperuricemia in normal-weight central obesity individuals are necessary.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experience With Janus Kinase Inhibitors in Acquired Perforating Dermatosis in Older Adults: A Case Series and Review of Literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acquired perforating dermatosis (APD) is a group of conditions characterized by transepidermal elimination and extrusion of dermal components. Patients often present with severe pruritus to the degree of disordering daily life and have comorbid diabetes mellitus (DM) or chronic kidney disease (CKD). However, owing to the limited number of cases, unmet clinical needs exist for effective treatment in the absence of large-scale clinical trials and established clinical guidelines. Therefore, this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimum Reporting Items for Clear Evaluation of Accuracy Reports of Large Language Models in Healthcare (MI-CLEAR-LLM): 2025 Updates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent systematic reviews have raised concerns about the quality of reporting in studies evaluating the accuracy of large language models (LLMs) in medical applications. Incomplete and inconsistent reporting hampers the ability of reviewers and readers to assess study methodology, interpret results, and evaluate reproducibility. To address this issue, the MInimum reporting items for CLear Evaluation of Accuracy Reports of Large Language Models in healthcare (MI-CLEAR-LLM) checklist was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonmass Lesions on Breast Ultrasound: Radiologic-Pathologic Correlation and a Practical Guide to Diagnostic Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Breast lesions that do not meet the criteria for a mass on ultrasound (US), analogous to asymmetry on mammography or nonmass enhancement on MRI, are frequently encountered during diagnostic or screening US. These lesions, referred to as nonmass lesions (NMLs), are discrete areas of altered echotexture compared to surrounding breast tissue, lacking the threedimensionality or conspicuity of a mass. Their subtle nature makes it difficult-particularly for less experienced US operators-to distinguish...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to "When AI Meets Coronary CT: Overcoming Challenges and Enhancing Accuracy in CAD-RADS Reporting"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Increased Chest CT Utilization on the Diagnosis of Pneumonia in Older Adults: A Population-Based Study of 930,654 Individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Chest CT acquisition among older Korean patients with pneumonia increased steadily between 2009 and 2018. The population-level pneumonia incidence also increased, mainly in pneumonia diagnosed with chest CT acquisition. Further research is needed to assess the potential impact of increased chest CT utilization on mortality and the risk of overdiagnosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of LJ-4378 and tirzepatide in mouse models of obesity and weight regain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We previously developed LJ-4378, a dual ligand for A(2A) and A(3) adenosine receptors, as a potential anti-obesity agent. In this study, we compared the anti-obesity effects of LJ-4378 with those of tirzepatide (TZP), a dual agonist of glucagon-like peptide-1 and glucose-dependent insulinotropic polypeptide receptors, and one of the most potent FDA-approved obesity therapeutics. Using a mouse model of diet-induced obesity, we assessed the effects of LJ-4378 and TZP on body weight loss, metabolic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective, Observational Study of the Efficacy, and Tolerability of a Same-Day, Low-Volume D-Sorbitol, Ascorbic Acid, and Sodium Picosulfate Regimen for Colonoscopy Bowel Preparation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This prospective, observational study demonstrated that a same-day, low-volume D-sorbitol, ascorbic acid, and sodium picosulfate bowel cleansing regimen showed high efficacy, excellent completion rates, and a favorable safety profile in outpatient colonoscopy practice. This could represent a convenient alternative to traditional split-dose preparations, potentially improving patient compliance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refining EI-MS library search results through atomic-level insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The inherent complexity of mass spectra and the lack of direct correlation between spectral and structural similarities retards structure elucidation and accurate peak annotation. Our methodology employs modified atomic environments from topological radii zero to represent collections of annotated spectral peaks. Rather than aiming for de novo structure prediction from spectra, our objective is to refine and re-rank candidate structures retrieved by existing library search methods using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Red cell distribution width and cerebral white matter hyperintensity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Red cell distribution width (RDW) is an indicator of red blood cell size heterogeneity and may reflect underlying chronic hypoxemia or inflammation. While RDW has been associated with the prognosis of various pulmonary and cardiovascular diseases, its relevance in cerebrovascular disease remains underexplored. In this study, we evaluated the association between RDW and cerebral small vessel disease (cSVD). We evaluated consecutive health check-up participants who underwent brain MRI between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reassessing chest compression sites in pediatric cardiopulmonary resuscitation without ventilatory support using echocardiographic assessment: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The recommended chest compression site during pediatric cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR) is based on studies that did not account for dynamic respiratory changes in cardiac position. Since cardiac position changes with respiratory phase, the optimal site during CPR without respiratory support, which physiologically corresponds to the end-expiration state, may differ. We assessed heart position at end-expiration using echocardiography. A prospective observational study was conducted in 18...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical performance of 3D-printed and milled resins for pediatric provisional restorations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given the growth-related challenges in pediatric and adolescent patients and the increasing adoption of digital workflows, durable yet adaptable materials are needed for provisional restorations. This study evaluated the mechanical performance of two 3D-printed resins, Graphy TC-80DP (GP) and NextDent C&B MFH (ND), and a milled nano-hybrid resin, Mazic Duro (MD). A multidimensional assessment was conducted, including fracture resistance, flexural strength, flexural modulus, viscoelasticity, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis, in vitro, and in silico studies of 4-chlorophenyl-sulfonyl Indole based thiosemicarbazones as competitive α-glucosidase inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The urgent need for effective and novel solutions to address the rising global epidemic of diabetes mellitus (DM) has become a priority for researchers. This chronic ailment, with its alarming prevalence and life-threatening complications (neuropathy, retinopathy and nephropathy), necessitates novel therapeutic strategies. Herein we have synthesized a novel series of N-substituted indole-based thiosemicarbazone derivatives 5(a-y) and explored their potential as α-glucosidase inhibitors. All the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimally overlapping technique of bioresorbable scaffolds in a porcine coronary artery model: proof-of-concept study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overlapping stent placement is a common approach for treating long coronary artery disease, but is associated with increased risks of restenosis and thrombosis. This preliminary study evaluated the efficacy and safety of a minimally overlapping technique using bioresorbable scaffolds (BRSs) compared with the conventional overlapping technique in a porcine coronary artery model. Eight coronary arteries were randomly assigned to two groups. In the overlapping group, two BRSs overlapped by 2.4 mm....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trans cinnamaldehyde enhances TRAIL induced apoptosis through ER stress mediated upregulation of DR5 in colorectal cancer cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trans-cinnamaldehyde (TCA), a natural compound isolated from the stem bark of Cinnamon cassia, has been recognized as a potential therapeutic agent for treating various diseases, including inflammatory conditions and diverse cancers. TNF-related apoptosis-inducing ligand (TRAIL) is known to induce apoptosis selectively in cancer cells while sparing normal cells. However, resistance to TRAIL-mediated apoptosis is a significant limitation in cancer therapy. This study aimed to investigate whether...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-sensitive ethanol detection using a chemiresistive SnO<sub>2</sub> thin-film gas sensor functionalized with RuO<sub>2</sub> nanosheets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents the design and fabrication of a ruthenium dioxide (RuO(2)) nanosheets-functionalized tin dioxide (SnO(2)) thin-film gas sensor integrated with a microheater in a suspended membrane structure. The RuO(2) nanosheets are synthesized via an intercalation-driven exfoliation process and subsequently deposited onto a sputtered SnO(2) thin film. Due to the catalytic properties and high surface-to-volume ratio of RuO(2) nanosheets, the functionalized sensor demonstrates a 337%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screen time and pubertal development: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Screen time is associated with pubertal onset in both boys and girls, although substantial heterogeneity and cross-sectional designs limit causal inference. Future longitudinal and experimental studies are needed to clarify underlying mechanisms and inform evidence-based guidelines for healthy pubertal development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of clinical features and pancreatic cancer risk between genetic mutations associated versus alcohol associated chronic pancreatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GCP shows distinct trajectories and an elevated early pancreatic cancer risk, particularly in SPINK1 gene mutation carriers, supporting genotype-stratified surveillance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Lung Volume Reduction and Symptomatic Radiation Pneumonitis in Lung Cancer Patients Undergoing Definitive Concurrent Chemoradiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ipsilateral lung volume reduction during RT may serve as an early predictor of symptomatic RP, independent of traditional dosimetric factors. Monitoring volume changes with re-simulation CT could enhance RP risk assessment and guide adaptive RT planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Initial Clinical Outcomes of Hypothermic Machine Perfusion in Deceased Donor Kidney Transplantation: A Pilot Comparative Feasibility Study from South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This pilot comparative study indicates that HMP is feasible for DDKT with prolonged CIT and yields comparable short-term outcomes to SCS. Dynamic perfusion parameters, including flow rate and renal resistance, may provide insights into early graft function, but validation in larger cohorts is required.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus on Management of Refractory Nontuberculous Mycobacterial Pulmonary Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study offers a structured approach to managing treatment failure in NTM-PD, addressing patient selection, treatment intensification, de-escalation, and supportive care while championing individualised strategies. Future research should concentrate on validating predictive factors for treatment response, refining therapeutic regimens, and investigating host-directed therapies to enhance patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethnicity, P2Y<sub>12</sub> Inhibitor Potency, and Bleeding: Revisiting the "East Asian Paradox"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Controlling the porous structure of alginate ferrogel for anticancer drug delivery under magnetic stimulation" [Carbohydrate Polymers 223 (2019) 115045]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Serum 25-Hydroxyvitamin D as a Risk Factor for Frailty in Community-Dwelling Older Men: A Korean Nationwide Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that low serum 25(OH)D concentrations are a potential risk factor for frailty, particularly in men. Further research is warranted to determine whether vitamin D supplementation in such high-risk older adults could help mitigate frailty.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Twig-Like Middle Cerebral Artery : Acquired Lesion Rather than Congenital Anomaly]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: T-MCAs may represent an acquired secondary anomaly rather than a congenital lesion, followed by steno-occlusion of the focal MCA with new arterial network formation. Both Moyamoya angiopathy and chronic atherosclerosis likely contributed to disease progression. Formation of a microaneurysm, dilatation of the lenticulostriate artery, and hemodynamic stress can lead to stroke.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Analysis of Retrograde Trans-Synaptic Retinal Degeneration Based on Lesion Topography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RTSD progression was pronounced in both the pRNFL and mGCIPL during the first 4 years, with greater severity observed in areas topographically linked to the brain lesion. Although RTSD developed regardless of lesion etiology, older age, male gender, severe VFD, intracerebral hemorrhage, and malignant tumors were associated with significantly faster progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Focused ultrasound-triggered doxorubicin liposomes reshape tumor microenvironment to boost checkpoint depletion in triple-negative breast cancer model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High Intensity Focused Ultrasound (HiFUS) combined with cavitation-responsive liposomes (IMP301) offers a therapeutic strategy to enhance immunotherapy efficacy in triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC). This study investigates how HIFUS, a non-invasive modality, remodels the tumor microenvironment (TME), transforming "suppressive" tumors into "responsive" ones and improving susceptibility to immune checkpoint blockade (ICB). We show that HIFUS increases vascular permeability and induces...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated in silico and in vitro assessment of estrogen and androgen receptor activity of 10 selected PFAS within an Integrated Approach to Testing and Assessment (IATA)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The potential of per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS) to disrupt endocrine systems continues to be a regulatory concern. However, effectively prioritizing these structurally diverse chemicals remains challenging due to inconsistencies in predictive and experimental data. In this study, we employed a multi-tiered evaluation strategy that combines in silico modeling, in vitro assays, and curated mechanistic data within the OECD's Integrated Approach to Testing and Assessment (IATA)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phenolated lignin nanoparticles with improved stability and biofunctionality: A comparative study of nanoprecipitation and solvent exchange fabrication techniques]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study lignin was chemically modified by phenolation to investigate its application for a comparative study of nanoprecipitation and solvent exchange assisted nanoparticle fabrication to evaluate their potential for biomedical applications. Phenolation successfully incorporated phenolic hydroxyl groups onto Kraft lignin (3.65 mmol/g) and Milled wood lignin (2.10 mmol/g) quantified via ^(31)P NMR and 2D-HSQCNMR. The plausible functional pathway was also studied to map the phenolic density...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spirometry-Defined Restriction Modifies the Association Between Forced Vital Capacity and Bronchiectasis Exacerbation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The presence of a spirometry-defined restrictive component was associated with higher annual rates for any AE and severe AE, which modified the FVC, not FEV1, effect on the risk for such events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective associations between psychosocial stress and the risk of type 2 diabetes in middle-aged adults: findings from the KoGES_CAVAS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Recent psychosocial stress was associated with an increased incidence of T2D, underscoring the importance of integrating psychosocial factors into diabetes prevention strategies, particularly for individuals with abdominal obesity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-Period-Cohort Analysis of dietary sodium, potassium, and sodium-to-potassium ratio in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Despite improvements, sodium intake remains excessive, and potassium insufficient, particularly in younger adults and recent cohorts. Public health interventions should prioritize reducing sodium and promoting potassium-rich foods to reduce cardiovascular risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic value of electrodiagnostic parameters for assessing initial severity in Bell's Palsy: A retrospective study of 3219 patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ENoG DI and MUAP interference patterns serve as reliable early electrophysiological indicators of facial paralysis severity, providing objective markers for patient stratification. These findings establish standardized electrodiagnostic criteria for severity assessment, enabling evidence-based early rehabilitation decisions in Bell's palsy management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patterns of social participation among people with developmental disabilities and associated factors in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the importance of considering the unique characteristics of each class in effectively promoting active social participation among individuals with DD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Cell-of-Origin and MYC/BCL2 Status on the Risk of Central Nervous System Relapse in Primary Breast Diffuse Large B-Cell Lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MYC/BCL2 DE and synchronous bilateral breast involvement may help identify patients at higher risk for CNS relapse. Further studies are warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real World Efficacy and Safety of First Line Chemo Immunotherapy in Extensive Stage Small Cell Lung Cancer and its association with molecular subtype]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this real-world Korean cohort, first-line chemo-immunotherapy achieved outcomes comparable to pivotal trials, supporting its role as standard care for ES-SCLC in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[cPLA2α-driven Cox-2/PGE2 axis promotes hypoxia-induced senescence in Jurkat T cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[T-cell dysfunction is a critical obstacle to effective anti-cancer immunotherapy. Despite the fact that hypoxia is a common feature of the tumor microenvironment, the mechanisms driving T-cell senescence under hypoxic conditions remain largely unexplored. This study investigated the impact of hypoxic conditions on CD4^(+) T-cell senescence using Jurkat T cell line. Under hypoxia, T cell exhaustion was not induced; however, senescence-associated β-galactosidase (SA-β-gal) activity and lipid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superomedial coverage with pectoralis muscle on completely wrapped, underfilled breast implant to achieve minimal rippling and dynamic tear-drop shaped appearance: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although prepectoral reconstruction has many benefits over subpectoral breast reconstruction, incidence of rippling can significantly reduce patient satisfaction. The authors devised a refined surgical technique for implant pocket dissection, aiming to reduce rippling by utilizing the muscle action and inherent thickness of the pectoralis major muscle. A total of 80 patients (92 breasts) who underwent prepectoral direct-to-implant (DTI) reconstruction between January 2019 and July 2023 by a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Techno-economic feasibility of high-efficiency enzymatic synthesis of puerarin myristate using low-toxicity solvent]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Puerarin is an isoflavone with the efficacy of flavonoids and medicinal effects but with low lipid solubility and stability that hinders its food-based application. Puerarin myristate (PM) was synthesized via enzymatic transesterification to improve the lipid solubility. Optimal PM synthesis conditions were determined. Then, techno-economic analysis (TEA) was performed for the first time to develop an efficient PM production process. Under optimal PM synthesis conditions, the reaction time was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasonication time dependent structuring of heat-treated legume proteins: interfacial adsorption and stabilization of faba bean and pea protein isolates in high internal phase Pickering emulsions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated ultrasonication time dependent restructuring of heat-treated legume proteins, focusing on how sequential heat and ultrasound (HU) treatments influence the interfacial adsorption and stabilization of faba bean protein isolates (FBPIs) and pea protein isolates (PPIs) in high internal phase Pickering emulsions (HIPPEs). Proteins were first modified by heat treatment (90 °C, 2 h) and subsequently subjected to ultrasonication (20 kHz, 120 W, 5-20 min). The resulting samples...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal data pooling from multiple waterbodies to improve machine-learning predictions of cyanobacterial blooms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate early warning of cyanobacterial blooms (CBs) is essential for protecting water resources and public health. However, most monitoring sites provide only small weekly datasets that limit machine-learning (ML) model generalization. Pooling data from multiple, similar waterbodies can increase sample size but also introduces heterogeneity that may reduce transferability. Here we evaluate a pragmatic pooling strategy based on cluster analysis of site-level CB patterns for 45 lakes and rivers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Balance Perception and Sensory Integration in Children with Non-Progressive Brain Injury: The Role of Visual Input and Foot Pressure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundPostural control in children with non-progressive brain injury (NPBI), such as cerebral palsy, is often impaired due to deficits in vestibular and somatosensory integration. While static balance has been studied, few have assessed how these children perceive anterior-posterior dynamic tilt and how this sensory dependance differs from children with typically developing (TD).ObjectiveThis study aimed to examine how visual input and foot pressure influence anterior-posterior dynamic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Diagnosis of Human Leptospirosis by Detection of Antibodies to Leptospira-Secreted Virulence-Modifying Protein Exotoxins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ambiguous clinical presentation of leptospirosis poses challenges for accurately assessing the global burden of this emerging disease. As a result, leptospirosis has not been recognized for inclusion in the WHO's neglected tropical diseases list. This underscores the urgent need for a diagnostic biomarker for early detection of illness and well-defined estimation of disease burden in urban and low-income settings. The recently discovered PF07598 gene family encoding virulence-modifying...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imaging Sensing of Cadmium-Induced Single Cancer Stem Cells in Tumor Spheroid Fabricated by 3D Bioprinting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the formation of cadmium-induced CSCs within individual HepG2 tumor spheroids, which are fabricated using 3D bioprinting of HepG2 cancer cell-laden hydrogel composed of alginate and gelatin. The quantification of cadmium-induced single CSCs in single spheroids was performed through multicolor single-cell 3D imaging of CSC biomarkers, without the need to isolate spheroids from the hydrogel. Single HepG2 CSCs exhibiting the aldehyde dehydrogenase 1 (ALDH1)^(+)/CD133^(+)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large Language Model Versus Manual Review for Clinical Data Curation in Breast Cancer: Retrospective Comparative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LLM-based curation of automatically extracted, deidentified clinical data demonstrated comparable effectiveness to manual physician review while reducing processing time by 95% and physician hours by 91%. This 2-step approach-automated data extraction followed by LLM curation-addresses both privacy concerns and efficiency needs. Despite limitations in integrating multiple clinical events, this methodology offers a scalable solution for clinical data extraction in oncology research....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of long working hours on metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease, with and without increased alcohol intake, in healthy workers: A 10-year cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Long working hours are increasingly recognized as a significant occupational hazard linked to various adverse health outcomes. This study aimed to assess how prolonged working hours relate to the subsequent development of metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) and metabolic and alcohol-associated liver disease (MetALD), based on a newly proposed classification system. We analyzed data from 117,354 Korean employees who underwent at least two abdominal ultrasound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of blood culture positivity at intensive care unit admission on mortality in infective endocarditis: Machine learning and deep learning-based causal inference models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Blood culture positivity at ICU admission is associated with a modest yet clinically significant increase in in-hospital mortality among IE patients. The application of advanced machine learning and causal inference models enhances risk stratification and may inform more targeted clinical interventions in this high-risk group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selective inhibition of long isoforms of phosphodiesterase 4D mitigates liver fibrosis in mouse models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic inflammation leads to tissue fibrosis which can disrupt the function of the parenchyma of the organ and ultimately lead to organ failure. The most prevalent form of this occurs in chronic hepatitis which leads to liver fibrosis and, ultimately, cirrhosis and hepatic failure. Although there is no specific treatment for fibrosis, the phosphodiesterase 4 (PDE4) competitive inhibitors have been shown to ameliorate fibrosis in rodent models. However, competitive inhibitors of PDE4 have shown...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pentatropis Capensis as a Novel Bioresource for Selenium Nanoparticle Synthesis: Insights into Biocompatibility, Cytotoxicity and in Vitro Toxicity Test on Zebrafish]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pentatropis capensis is traditionally used to treat several ailments, yet its potential as a bioresource for green nanotechnology remains unexplored. Selenium nanoparticles (Se NPs) synthesized via plant-based methods are gaining attention for their biomedical and environmental applications. In this study the synthesized Se NPs were characterized using DLS, TEM, SEM with EDAX, XRD, FTIR and UV-visible spectroscopy. UV analysis revealed a characteristic absorbance at 266 nm, SEM and TEM imaging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A review of removal of per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances using metal-organic framework-based nanoadsorbents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFASs) are a category of extremely persistent environmental pollutants. Metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) have appeared as promising adsorbents for PFAS removal due to their large surface area, tunable porosity, and versatile surface chemistry, which are among the numerous treatment technologies available. This review critically evaluates current developments in the design, fabrication, and application of MOF-based (nano)materials for the adsorption of PFAS in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GapSense: Similarity Estimation-Based Gap Filler with TGS-Reads for Genome Assemblies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advances in next-generation sequencing have led to an explosion in sequencing data, accelerating genome assembly research. However, draft genomes generated after scaffolding still contain unresolved gaps, often caused by repetitive regions and sequencing errors. These gaps may contain biologically meaningful sequences and thus require accurate resolution. However, existing gap-filling tools often exhibit limited reliability, especially when applied to large and complex eukaryotic genomes, due to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in ferroelectric materials, devices, and in-memory computing applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferroelectric memories have undergone a transformative evolution from conventional perovskite-based materials to modern fluorite-structured ferroelectrics, driven by the pursuit of scalable, low-power, and CMOS-compatible non-volatile memory solutions. The observation of ferroelectricity in nanoscale HfO(2)-based films has enabled integration with CMOS-compatible processes, providing advantages such as potential scalability, low power consumption, and non-volatility, while facilitating continued...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeepIMB: Imputation of non-biological zero counts in microbiome data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DeepIMB effectively addresses the challenges posed by non-biological zeros in microbiome data. By improving the quality of the data and the reliability of downstream analyses, DeepIMB represents a significant advancement in microbiome research methodologies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virucidal activity of Cannabis sativa L. (hemp) root and stem extracts against Japanese encephalitis virus: role of stigmasterol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Japanese encephalitis virus (JEV) poses a significant public health risk due to the lack of effective antiviral therapies. To identify novel antiviral agents, we evaluated the antiviral activity of ethanol extracts and organic solvent fractions derived from the roots and stems of hemp (Cannabis sativa L.). Noncytotoxic concentrations of the extracts and fractions were determined using in vitro cytotoxicity assays. At these concentrations, several fractions demonstrated potent virucidal activity,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Phase 3 Trial of Atacicept in Patients with IgA Nephropathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this prespecified interim analysis, treatment with atacicept resulted in a significantly greater reduction in proteinuria than placebo at week 36 in patients with IgA nephropathy. (Funded by Vera Therapeutics; ORIGIN 3 ClinicalTrials.gov number, NCT04716231.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Contact Area Between 3D-Printed Silicone Implant and Nasal Bone as a Predictive Factor for Implant Deviation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De Novo Aneurysm Formation After Internal Carotid Artery Sacrifice: Impact of Aneurysmal Versus Non-Aneurysmal Etiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: De novo aneurysm formation following ICA trapping appears to occur exclusively in patients with an underlying aneurysmal etiology, particularly at sites of hemodynamic stress such as the ACoA. Close imaging surveillance is recommended during the first two years post-trapping, especially in patients with robust collateral circulation or pre-existing aneurysms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical significance of serum IgE/IgG4 ratio in patients with IgG4-related disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although the serum IgE/IgG4 ratio did not correlate with baseline disease activity, it was independently associated with remission at 1 year. This finding suggests its role as a prognostic biomarker for remission in IgG4-RD, capturing immunologic features not reflected by absolute IgG4 or IgE levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multifunctional ferroelectric synaptic memristors based on HfAlO<sub><em>x</em></sub> with enhanced Pavlovian learning and physical reservoir computing systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the growing demand for energy-efficient, high-speed data processing systems, ferroelectric memristors based on HfAlO(x) (HAO) have emerged as promising candidates for neuromorphic computing. In this study, we fabricated a metal-ferroelectric-insulator-semiconductor structure with a W/HAO/ZrO(2)/n^(+) Si stack and investigated the influence of annealing duration at relatively low-temperature (500 °C) on ferroelectric and synaptic properties. Grazing incidence X-ray diffraction and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metagenome-assembled genomes reveal microbial signatures and metabolic pathways linked to coronary artery disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gut microbiota has emerged as a critical factor influencing cardiovascular disease (CVD) risk, particularly coronary artery disease (CAD) development. Using fecal metagenomic shotgun sequencing, we investigated gut microbiota signatures associated with CAD and provided strain-resolved insights through metagenome-assembled genome (MAG) reconstruction. We analyzed 14 patients with CAD and 28 propensity score-matched healthy controls. Differential abundance analysis identified 15 CAD-associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41196050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[pH-Regulated Ring-Opening/Closing Transformation in Polyoxometalates Enables High-Performance Nonlinear Optical Crystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inorganic polyoxometalate (POM) crystals are a promising class of materials with considerable potential in modern laser science and technology. However, the limited understanding of POM formation mechanisms and the unclear structure-property relationship between POMs and nonlinear optics (NLO) have hindered the rational design and controllable synthesis of high-performance inorganic POM-based NLO crystals. Herein, we report the successful synthesis of two novel polar heteropolymolybdates,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single versus Dual Antiplatelet therapy for Stroke prevention in Patients with First ever Embolic Stroke of Undetermined Source]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundThis study aims to evaluate the efficacy and safety of dual antiplatelet therapy (DAPT) versus single antiplatelet therapy (SAPT) for patients with a first-ever embolic stroke of undetermined source (ESUS).MethodsWe assembled a multicenter cohort and a propensity score-matched (PSM) subset to compare DAPT with SAPT. The primary outcome was a composite of recurrent ischemic stroke, myocardial infarction, or all-cause death, and the safety outcome was major bleeding. Follow-up extended...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vessel-Specific Myocardial Mass in Patients With Stable Coronary Artery Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study quantified the myocardial mass subtended by each major artery in the coronary circulation. Understanding the vessel-specific mass at risk has significant clinical implications for personalizing revascularization strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the Secretory Pathway: New Insights Into Protein Release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In eukaryotes, protein secretion plays essential roles in intercellular communications and extracellular niche-building. Protein secretion generally requires a signal sequence that targets cargos to the canonical secretory pathway consisting of the endoplasmic reticulum (ER), the Golgi apparatus, plasma membrane, and vesicles moving between these compartments. However, cytoplasmic proteins lacking signal sequences (e.g., IL1β, Acb1, FGF2) have been detected, and many have defined functions in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequential trench well based microfluidic platform to isolate bacteria from whole blood with large volume processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The separation of bacteria from infected blood is a crucial step for downstream bacterial detection and analysis. However, the extremely low bacterial concentration and high proportion of blood cells present significant challenges for effective separation. In this study, we present a microfluidic-based approach utilizing a sequential trench well structure that leverages the sedimentation-based separation process to effectively isolate bacteria from whole blood. Experimental results demonstrated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Free-Standing Functional Laser-Induced Graphene-PVA Laminates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Laser-induced graphene (LIG) merges the high conductivity of graphenic carbon with direct laser patterning, yet most LIG remains bound to its polymer substrate, limiting its use as thick, transferable electrodes. Thick free-standing LIG is highly sought for powering and warming flexible systems but remains elusive. Here, we present a solvent-free laminate approach that transforms substrate-bound LIG into thickness-tunable, free-standing films through laser-assisted exfoliation, stacking, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing an Efficient System for Hybrid Rice Seed Production Using Partial Male Sterility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient production of hybrid rice seeds requires male sterility systems to overcome the challenges of self-pollination. In this study, we identified male gametic transfer defect (GTrD)5 and GTrD9 as essential genes for the process of male gamete transmission in rice. Mutations in these genes cause partial male sterility by impairing pollen tube elongation, thereby reducing the fertilisation rate. Using CRISPR/Cas9 technology, we developed gtrd5flo5 and gtrd9flo5 double mutants that combined...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gender differences in the association between smoking and the risk of suicide in depressed patients: a longitudinal national cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Smoking is associated with increased suicide risk among individuals with depression, with notable gender differences in risk magnitude and modifying factors. These findings highlight the need for gender-specific suicide prevention strategies. Limitations include reliance on self-reported smoking data and lack of time-varying measures of exposure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lower LEDD and Polypharmacy Rates Beyond the Honeymoon Period in Patients With Parkinson's Disease Integrative Western-Korean Medicine Interventions: A CARE-Compliant Case Series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that integrative treatment may contribute to lowering LEDD and medication counts in patients with PD, which could potentially reduce hospitalization rates and the associated social costs. Further prospective studies comparing the integrative and nonintegrative treatment groups are needed to clarify these findings and evaluate the role of integrative treatment in the long-term management of PD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes among children with primary nephrogenic diabetes insipidus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with primary NDI exhibit a dynamic growth trajectory, delayed achievement of normal GFR with subsequent risk of chronic kidney disease, and frequent treatment-associated complications. These findings underscore the need for timely and individualized long-term management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding Fibromyalgia: Genetic Insights into Gut and Immune System Interactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights the role of gut microbiota and inflammatory proteins (cytokines/chemokines) in the pathogenesis of FM. Through Gene Ontology (GO) functional enrichment and Kyoto Encyclopedia of Genes and Genomes (KEGG) pathway analyses, the findings suggest their involvement in immune regulation, inflammatory responses, and viral pathways. These findings provide new insights into potential therapeutic targets for modulating gut health and immune responses, opening new avenues...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A reflection on 'Aggregation-induced emission enhancement of a <em>meso</em>-trifluoromethyl BODIPY <em>via</em> J-aggregation': from fundamental discovery to versatile sensing platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The BODIPY family of dyes enjoys great popularity for its advantageous luminsecence characteristics in solution. By contrast, most BODIPY dyes are quenched in the solid state. In rare instances, BODIPY derivatives have been found to undergo aggregation-induced emission (AIE) behavior, leading to unexpectedly red-shifted bands. In 2014, S. Choi et al. demonstrated that the 1,3,5,7-tetramethyl BODIPY derivative that bears a trifluoromethyl group at the meso position formed emissive J-aggregates,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41195073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can posttreatment blood inflammatory markers predict poor survival in gynecologic cancer?: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Peripheral blood inflammatory markers (PBIMs) are widely used for prognostication of several malignancies, including gynecologic cancers. However, most studies do not report when PBIMs have been sampled, and the ones that do usually use pretreatment levels. Considering their potential to reflect the host immune status, posttreatment PBIMs and their dynamic changes from pretreatment levels may also carry prognostic information. A systematic review and meta-analysis were conducted to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Liraglutide on Patients With Metabolic Dysfunction-Associated Steatotic Liver Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Liraglutide improved hepatic steatosis and metabolic parameters, not LS, in patients with MASLD, though its effect on LS was limited. These findings support the favorable influence of liraglutide on MASLD management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevated IL-6 levels in the intestinal mucosa of patients with gastrointestinal Behçet's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of the quality improvement program on Clostridioides difficile infection management: a quasi-experimental study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Quality improvement program enhanced the quality of CDI treatment in terms of prompt treatment and discontinuation of concomitant laxatives and associated antibiotics. (cris.nih.go.kr; KCT0005892).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elderly-onset inflammatory bowel disease in Asia: clinical characteristics and therapeutic strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The incidence and prevalence of elderly-onset inflammatory bowel disease (EO-IBD) are increasing worldwide. The rising incidence of EO-IBD in Asia is driven by rapid industrialization and an aging population. Older patients often have multiple comorbidities and polypharmacy, which make diagnosis and management of the disease more challenging. Additionally, Asian patients with EO-IBD exhibit unique clinical characteristics, including frequent ileal involvement. Differences in phenotype between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asian-Pacific perspectives on the management of very early-onset inflammatory bowel disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Children diagnosed with inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) before the age of 6 years are considered to have "very early-onset IBD (VEO-IBD)," which is challenging to diagnose and treat. Notably, many children with VEO-IBD have monogenic forms of the disease, meaning that early genetic testing is useful. However, because the prevalence of genetic variants causing VEO-IBD differs globally, the diagnosis and treatment of this disease should be tailored to each region. In the present review paper, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Janus kinase inhibitors in ulcerative colitis: is upadacitinib taking the lead?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gallstone burden and risk in Korean patients with ulcerative colitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validating clinical feasibility of MRCAT and deep learning-based synthetic CT images for cervical cancer patient]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MRCAT and DL-based synthetic CT images demonstrated clinical applicability, achieving plan quality similar to that of plans based on genuine planning CT images.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Klinefelter Syndrome Identified by Next-Generation Sequencing as a Risk Factor for Venous Thromboembolism: A Single-Institution Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal analysis of alcohol consumption pattern and menopause-specific quality of life in middle-aged women undergoing the menopausal transition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Light, moderate and heavy drinking appear to be associated with poorer scores on the menopause-specific quality of life questionnaire, with greater vulnerability in women with lower anti-Müllerian hormone levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multifunctional Edged-Satellite AuAg Nanoparticles-Based Integration Platform for Screening, Validation, and Elimination of Vibrio Bacteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multifunctional materials converge various physical and chemical properties, while often being hampered by complicated synthesis procedures and inconsistent performance. A straightforward strategy is presented for synthesizing robust multifunctional plasmonic nanoparticles (NPs), AuAgNPs with edged satellites (ES-AuAgNPs). The ES-AuAgNPs possess various characteristics of i) alloyed Ag/Au with a 7:3 ratio, ii) numerous satellited NPs with narrow nanogaps on face-to-face edges, and iii) a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41194434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum interference and occupation control in high harmonic generation from monolayer WS<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two-dimensional hexagonal materials such as transition metal dichalcogenides exhibit valley degrees of freedom, offering fascinating potential for valley-based quantum computing and optoelectronics. In nonlinear optics, the K and K' valleys provide excitation resonances that can be used for ultrafast control of excitons, Bloch oscillations, and Floquet physics. Under intense laser fields, however, the role of coherent carrier dynamics away from the K/K' valleys is largely unexplored. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying pathways to achieve diverse objectives of the National Essential Diagnostics List: developing an assessment framework based on field studies in Cambodia, Indonesia, Lao PDR, and the Philippines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The newly developed assessment framework can support high-level officials in initiating NEDL development and promoting its effective use. It can also guide health ministries in selecting NEDL leads and technical committee members and help identify intermediary outcomes for monitoring NEDL operationalization. Although empirical evidence on NEDL outcomes remains limited owing to its early global implementation stage, this study provides valuable insights to support the future...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of thermal perceptions, metabolic rate, clothing, and local skin temperature in people with cold constitution in air-conditioned office environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cold constitution refers to a phenomenon in which individuals have a higher sensitivity to cold and feel colder than others. This research aimed to examine the associations of morphological characteristics, personal factors, thermal perceptions, and local skin temperature (t(sk)) with cold constitution by conducting a field experiment. It also explored differences in these aspects between individuals with and without cold constitution, in a thermoneutral office environment during summer and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitomycin C-induced DNA double-strand breaks are enhanced by catalytical inactivation of DNA polymerase κ in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Polk plays a systemic role in mitigating MMC-induced DSBs, likely through both DNA replication-dependent and -independent mechanisms. Furthermore, Polk appears to protect against DSBs caused by endogenous mutagens in some organs such as the adrenal cortex, prostate, and retina.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41199376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood methylome signatures in children exposed to maternal type 1 diabetes are linked to protection against islet autoimmunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exposure to maternal type 1 diabetes (T1D) during pregnancy provides relative protection against T1D in the offspring. This protective effect may be driven by epigenetic mechanisms. Here we conducted an epigenome-wide blood analysis on 790 young children with and 962 children without a T1D-affected mother, and identified differential DNA methylation (q < 0.05) at multiple loci and regions. These included the Homeobox A gene cluster and 15 T1D susceptibility genes. The differential methylation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Cellular senescence in white matter microglia is induced during ageing in mice and exacerbates the neuroinflammatory phenotype]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multicenter retrospective study on the risk factors of stricture formation after moderate circumferential defect resection in esophageal endoscopic submucosal dissection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with a 50-75% circumferential mucosal defect after esophageal ESD, steroids were used in > 40% of the patients, with 5% of the patients developing postoperative stenosis. Larger circumferential mucosal defect and longer procedural duration were considered as the most relevant risk factors. Stricture prevention should be more aggressively considered in cases at high-risk for stenosis, even though the mucosal defect area was less than three-fourth of the circumference.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing translational research in metastatic cancer through an open science environment: the UPTIDER experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Translational research in metastatic cancer is limited by insufficient metastatic samples. Post-mortem tissue donation programs address this issue by facilitating comprehensive sample collection. Sustaining such programs requires an open science environment (OSE) to ensure multidisciplinary collaboration, research standards, and patient privacy. While often seen at publication, we demonstrate the benefit of developing upstream phases by presenting the OSE from our institutional post-mortem...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transformer-based multiclass segmentation pipeline for basic kidney histology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current applications of deep learning in renal pathology focused on anatomical structures with morphology, yet little research has focused on the performance of models, such as versatility, in regions with severe kidney damage. In this study, we explored the difference in modal/domain shift capabilities between CNN-based and Transformer-based models. Firstly, we adopted two splitting strategies-WSI-level and patch-level-to stimulate sampling on multiple modal data distribution (i.e., renal WSIs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a prognostic nomogram for survival in patients with brain metastases from colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brain metastases from colorectal cancer are rare but carry a dismal prognosis. This study aimed to develop and externally validate a prognostic model for individualized survival prediction in affected patients. The model was constructed using a training cohort of 112 patients diagnosed with brain metastases after initial colorectal cancer treatment at our institution between 1985 and 2017, and validated in an external cohort of 114 patients referred for brain metastasis treatment between 1987...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolation and characterization of bacteriophages for carbapenem resistant Enterobacter cloacae complex strains]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There has been an increased interest in phage therapy for the treatment of antimicrobial resistant bacterial infections due to the decreasing effectiveness of antibiotics. While phage therapy has been successful, it often requires time to isolate and characterize phages suitable for phage therapy. Here, we isolated and characterized three phages against carbapenem-resistant Enterobacter cloacae complex (ECC) strains to potentially be applied in phage therapy. ECC strains commonly cause sepsis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automatic detection of sister chromatid exchanges using machine learning models and image analysis algorithms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[After DNA replication, two chromatids with identical genetic information are formed in organisms; these are called sister chromatids. Sister chromatid exchange (SCE) is a recombination event between genetically equivalent sequences. Since no genetic changes occur before or after SCE, it does not have detrimental effects on cells. However, SCE is induced by treatments with DNA-damaging agents or by the knockout of genes encoding recombination suppressors, such as BLM. Therefore, SCE has been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutation of CMTR2 in Lung Adenocarcinoma Alters RNA Alternative Splicing and Reveals Therapeutic Vulnerabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA splicing dysregulation has emerged as a hallmark of cancer and a promising therapeutic target; however, its full landscape in human solid cancer remains poorly characterized. To address this, we perform alternative splicing analyses using RNA-sequencing data from 751 lung adenocarcinoma samples from our cohort integrated with 519 samples from The Cancer Genome Atlas. Visualization of splicing patterns using t-distributed stochastic neighbor embedding reveals substantial inter-tumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Acute and long-term effects of psilocybin on energy balance and feeding behavior in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioenergetics and lipid metabolism in Alzheimer's disease: From cell biology to systemic health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a complex neurodegenerative disorder characterized by progressive cognitive decline. Although amyloid-β and tau pathologies remain central to our understanding of AD, growing evidence suggests that disrupted lipid metabolism and impaired bioenergetics are closely linked to these hallmark features. Genetic, lipidomic and functional studies point to alterations in cholesterol, phospholipids and polyunsaturated fatty acids, which can influence mitochondrial function,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive analyses of oral health-related quality of life in head and neck cancer patients with maxillary prostheses after maxillectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Swallowing function, surgical reconstruction, and social activities were significantly associated with OHRQoL in patients with HNC with maxillary prostheses after maxillectomy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The potential hidden dangers in household products for infant's immune system: Consequences for childcare]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We suggest simple changes in everyday life aimed at reducing contact with these products in infants and young children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vascular and inflammatory diseases after COVID-19 infection and vaccination in children and young people in England: a retrospective, population-based cohort study using linked electronic health records]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The rarity of severe diseases following COVID-19 infection balanced against rare COVID-19 vaccination-related adverse effects is an important consideration for vaccination policies. We aimed to assess the short-term and long-term risks of vascular and inflammatory diseases following first COVID-19 diagnosis and vaccination in children and young people.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microphase separation in maltooligosaccharide-based block co-oligomers with dominant sugar volume fractions: Toward a comprehensive understanding of the phase behavior]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Block co-oligomers (BCOs) consisting of oligosaccharides and hydrophobic terpenoid blocks exhibit microphase-separated structures of various morphologies with sub-10 nm periodicity, thereby rendering them of interest for use in a range of nanotechnological applications. However, their microphase separation behaviors have yet to be fully elucidated across a broad range of sugar volume fractions, especially with regard to sugar-rich regimes. In this study, the microphase separation behaviors of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered coagulation factor VIII with enhanced secretion and coagulation potential for hemophilia A gene therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The major challenges of gene therapy for hemophilia A using adeno-associated virus (AAV) vectors are reducing vector doses and the long-term maintenance of stable factor VIII (FVIII). Here, we developed engineered human B-domain-deleted FVIIIs (FVIIISQs) with enhanced secretion and coagulation potential. Intracellular accumulation was markedly reduced in some engineered FVIIISQs, resulting in reduced unfolded protein responses. The administration of AAV vectors carrying engineered FVIIISQ to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41198051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Durations of Fever and Other Symptoms among COVID-19 Outpatients Administered Ensitrelvir During the 2023 Japanese XBB Epidemic Period]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ensitrelvir significantly shortened fever and symptom durations in mild to moderate COVID-19 outpatients. Patients with higher fever or more symptoms may benefit, even with repeated COVID-19 vaccination.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical exposure in childhood: A study on organophosphate flame retardants and plasticizers in a Flemish birth cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Humans are exposed daily to contaminants such as organophosphorus flame retardants (PFRs), legacy plasticizers (LPs), and alternative plasticizers (APs). To date, most biomonitoring studies in children have only focused on analysis of LP metabolites and a subset of PFRs and APs. This study investigated exposure to multiple PFRs, LPs and APs in the ENVIRONAGE birth cohort quantifying 13 PFR metabolites in 655 urine samples, while we measured 8 LP and 13 AP metabolites in urine of 328 children....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The exacerbating role of Ras guanyl-releasing protein 1 in idiopathic inflammatory myopathies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Idiopathic inflammatory myopathies (IIMs) are autoimmune disorders characterized by muscle injury mediated by both T cells and macrophages. Ras guanyl-releasing protein 1 (RasGRP1) is a guanine exchange factor for a small G protein Ras, expressed in immune cells. In this study, we investigated the role of RasGRP1 in IIMs. RasGRP1 was expressed in either CD8+, CD4+ or CD68+ cells in muscles from IIM patients as well as a murine model of myositis, C protein-induced myositis (CIM). RasGRP1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Skeletal Muscle Mass and Liver Fibrosis Synergistically Predict Prognosis in Colorectal Cancer: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Low TPV and high FIB-4 score are independent prognostic markers of poor long-term outcomes in CRC patients. A prognostic model integrating TPV and FIB-4 score provides improved risk stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Operational thresholds and microbial mechanisms in high-solid anaerobic membrane bioreactors treating swine wastewater: from process performance to metabolic pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated swine wastewater treatment using a high-solid anaerobic membrane bioreactor (HSAnMBR), focusing on microbial adaptive mechanisms and process stability under stepwise-increased organic loading rates (OLRs: 5-26 g COD/L/d). The HSAnMBR achieved high efficiency at OLRs ≤ 17 g COD/L/d, with COD removal > 96 % and optimal methane yield (0.28 L CH(4)/g COD(removed)). However, OLR elevation to 26 g COD/L/d induced volatile fatty acid (VFA) accumulation (5.57 g/L), causing acute...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical and biological characterization of glycidamide-adducted adenine in DNA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acrylamide, a food contaminant, is metabolically converted to glycidamide (GA), which reacts with nucleobases in DNA. Although several GA adducts with dG, dA, and dC are known, the mutagenic potency of each adduct remains unclear. Here we focused on N⁶-(2-carboxy-2-hydroxyethyl)-2'-deoxyadenosine (N⁶-GA-dA), which is produced by the Dimroth rearrangement of N1-(2-carboxy-2-hydroxyethyl)-2'-deoxyadenosine (N1-GA-dA). We separately prepared N1-GA-dA and N⁶-GA-dA and measured their Dimroth...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural basis for E3 ubiquitin ligase UHRF1 binding to nucleosome core particle and histone H3 ubiquitination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The maintenance of DNA methylation in differentiated cells is regulated by a ubiquitin signal generated by UHRF1 (ubiquitin-like with PHD and RING finger domain 1), which plays a pivotal role in recruitment of DNA methyltransferase DNMT1 to hemimethylated CpG sites. UHRF1 catalyzes multiple mono-ubiquitinations on histone H3 within nucleosomes. However, the structural mechanisms underlying the binding of UHRF1 to nucleosomes and the subsequent formation of the ubiquitin signal remain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication, physicochemical characterization and in vitro evaluation of pre-osteoblast cells on bacterial cellulose/hydroxyapatite reinforced with chitosan composite scaffold for bone tissue engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing scaffold with a balance between porosity and mechanical strength remains a key challenge in bone tissue engineering. This study investigates the suitability of in-situ fabricated bacterial cellulose (BC)/hydroxyapatite (HA) coated with chitosan (CS) at different concentrations (0.5, 1, 1.5 and 2 wt%) for bone tissue regeneration. The physicochemical characterizations confirmed uniform distribution and presence of the three components in the scaffolds. The scaffolds exhibited porosity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catalytic mechanism and differential alarmone regulation of a conserved stringent nucleosidase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Insights into bacterial metabolic adaptation during stress is crucial for understanding early mechanisms of antibiotic resistance. In the Gram-negative bacterium Escherichia coli, the universal stringent response produces the alarmones (p)ppGpp that target many cellular proteins. The cellular nucleosidase PpnN is regulated by (p)ppGpp and was shown to balance bacterial fitness and persistence during fluoroquinolone exposure. pppGpp and ppGpp both activate PpnN, but differentially regulate its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Universal newborn hearing screening in Kuwait: Outcomes and implications for national implementation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using long RNA fragment degradation ratio to estimate the time elapsed since bloodstain deposition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[When crimes that involve injuries or deaths are investigated, it is sometimes necessary to estimate the length of time that has elapsed since bloodstains were deposited at the crime site. A method based on the degree of bloodstains' RNA degradation is one of the most commonly used indicators, but the applications of general real-time polymerase chain reaction (PCR) techniques for this purpose are often limited by the techniques' inability to quantify long (>400 bp) DNA fragments, rendering them...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of biomarkers to predict renal function decline and its deceleration in patients with type 2 diabetes and diabetic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We identified four noninvasive biomarkers that independently correlated with the eGFR, among which urinary type IV collagen excretion and serum sTM levels were particularly useful in predicting eGFR decline.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor Re: Analytical and clinical validation of PATHWAY HER2 (4B5) assay for assessment of HER2-low/HER2-ultralow status and eligibility for trastuzumab deruxtecan in DESTINY-Breast06: Clinical validation of the VENTANA PATHWAY anti-HER2/neu (4B5) assay in HER2-low and HER2-ultralow breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-cultural network structures of social anxiety, body dysmorphic, and major depressive disorder symptoms in individualistic vs. collectivistic societies: A comparison between American, German, and Japanese populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Social anxiety disorder (SAD), body dysmorphic disorder (BDD), and major depressive disorder (MDD) are highly comorbid, which may be influenced by cultural variables associated with individualism vs. collectivism with particular emphasis on shame. This study investigated the network structures comprising symptoms of SAD, BDD, MDD, and shame across three countries typically associated with either a high tendency of collectivism (Japan), a high tendency of individualism (USA), or in between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Loss of Actrt1 in non-hematopoietic stroma suppresses pathological angiogenesis and tumor progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor progression and therapeutic resistance depend not only on tumor cells but also on the tumor vasculature, a central component of the tumor microenvironment (TME). Accordingly, normalization and remodeling of tumor vessels represent a promising therapeutic strategy, highlighting the urgent need for approaches that selectively and efficiently modulate this compartment. Actrt1 (ArpT1) is an actin-related protein implicated in ciliogenesis, but its roles in the TME are unknown. Here, we show...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Salivary oxytocin responses in mothers and full-term newborns in early skin-to-skin contact for the first 2 hours after birth: Effects of synthetic oxytocin administration and epidural analgesia in labor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Drug administration during labor may reduce maternal salivary oxytocin levels in the first 2 h after birth. Healthcare professionals should provide information on different approaches, such as a non-pharmacologic approach, for pain relief for primipara during labor.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systemic chemotherapy for patients with resectable or resected colorectal cancer liver metastases: An individual patient data meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Systemic chemotherapy improves PFS of patients with resectable or resected CRCLM. This effect is stronger for patients with synchronous metastases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of inhomogeneity on the Compton profiles of expanded fluid metals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[On the basis of thermal unrestricted Hartree-Fock theory of electron-ion lattice gas in the density-matrix formalism, Compton profiles of simple fluid metals are calculated at reduced densities and elevated temperatures. We thereby examine how spatial inhomogeneity of conduction electrons affects the Compton profiles, reciprocal form factors and electron kinetic energies. Comparison of numerical results with experimental data for rubidium suggests a crossover from nearly homogeneous to strongly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41197235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251107023734&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>