<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 19:21:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Membrane Tethering of Honeybee Antimicrobial Peptides in Drosophila Enhances Pathogen Defense at the Cost of Stress-Induced Host Vulnerability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial peptides (AMPs) represent a promising alternative to conventional antibiotics in combating multidrug-resistant pathogens, yet their clinical translation is hindered by proteolytic instability, cytotoxicity, and poor bioavailability. Herein, it is demonstrated that glycosylphosphatidylinositol-mediated membrane tethering of honeybee defensin1 (Def1) in Drosophila melanogasterenhances its antimicrobial efficacy by ≈ $$\approx$$ 100-fold compared to secreted or untethered forms,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between adherence to cancer prevention guidelines and cancer risk: a comprehensive systematic review and dose-response meta-analysis of cohort studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: No systematic review and meta-analysis has comprehensively assessed the association between adherence to major cancer prevention guidelines and risks of cancers in cohort studies. We aimed to evaluate the associations of adherence to the 2018 and the 2007 World Cancer Research Fund/American Institute for Cancer Research (WCRF/AICR) and the 2012 American Cancer Society (ACS) guidelines with risks of multiple cancer outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BINOL-3,3'-Dicarboxylic Acid: Resolution for the Key Intermediate of (S)-bepotastine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[(S)-Bepotastine is a highly selective histamine H1-receptor antagonist in the treatment of allergic rhinitis and other allergic diseases. We achieved a facile and convenient synthesis of (S)-bepotastine by resolving an early stage synthetic precursor. We devised a new class of resolving agent, BINOL-3,3'-dicarboxylic acid which could be considered as an axial version of tartaric acid. As the first example, we successfully resolved racemic piperidinyl ether by (S)-BINOL-3,3'-dicarboxylic acid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the service readiness of a Paraguay public healthcare center for the primary healthcare system using the WHO SARA tool]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that merely implementing health system-related policies, such as national health plans or service coverage mandates, is insufficient without targeted strategies addressing health workforce distribution, resource allocation, and health infrastructure development. The term 'inequality gaps' refers specifically to disparities in healthcare access, particularly in the distribution of healthcare workers and essential medical resources. This study provides novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robust Metal and Semiconductor Phase Transition Memristor Using Ag-Intercalated Transition Metal Dichalcogenide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal (1T/1T')-semiconductor (2H) phase transition memristors (PTMEMs) based on intercalated alkali metal ions (Li^(+)) in transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDs) exhibit excellent electrical properties, including heterosynaptic plasticity. However, the low stability of Li^(+) ions limits retention and on/off ratios of the PTMEMs. Here, a phase transition in MoTe(2) induced by intercalated Ag^(+) ions is demonstrated for the first time, enabling robust memristor operation. The migration of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-time rodent behavior classifier using color-based body segmentation (R2C2)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The heavy reliance of animal studies on human observers makes them prone to observer-specific biases. To mitigate such shortcomings, much research has been focused on computerizing the characterization of animal behavior. Such automation can lead to more reliable and cost-effective behavior quantifications. Yet, there remain challenges in developing end-to-end solutions that allow users to easily train custom behavioral classifiers with minimal data while maintaining low computational demands....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triglyceride-glucose index variability and risk of all-cause and cardiovascular mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triglyceride-glucose (TyG) index is a reliable marker of insulin resistance with predictive value for cardiovascular risk. While metabolic variability independently impacts cardiovascular outcomes and mortality, the clinical significance of TyG index variability remains unclear. We investigated whether higher TyG index variability increases the risk of mortality. This retrospective cohort study analyzed data from 3,094,062 individuals who participated in the National Health Screening Program...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obstructive Sleep Apnea and Cerebral Microbleeds in Middle-Aged and Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, moderate to severe OSA was independently associated with an increased risk of incident CMBs over an 8-year follow-up. These results add to the evidence for the importance of sleep apnea to brain health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a weighted Subjective Memory Complaints Questionnaire (SMCQ-R) for early symptomatic Alzheimer's disease detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundSubjective memory complaints are potential early indicators of Alzheimer's disease (AD), but their diagnostic utility is limited by high prevalence in cognitively normal older adults. The original Subjective Memory Complaints Questionnaire (SMCQ) shows suboptimal specificity and assigns equal weight to all items.ObjectiveTo develop and validate a revised SMCQ (SMCQ-R) with improved diagnostic accuracy through systematic item selection and empirical weighting.MethodsUsing a development...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Short-Term Surgical Outcomes for Thymectomy with Various Minimally Invasive Approaches: A Single-Center Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: All three minimally invasive approaches for thymectomy demonstrated comparable short-term outcomes, although robot-assisted thoracic surgery procedures had longer operative times. These findings suggest that lateral video-assisted thoracoscopic surgery, lateral robot-assisted thoracic surgery, and subxiphoid robot-assisted thoracic surgery are all safe and effective options, enabling surgeons to select the most appropriate technique based on individual patient characteristics and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From childhood trauma to complex PTSD: a network analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Network analysis enables the understanding of complex posttraumatic stress disorder (CPTSD) as interconnected symptoms, with Bayesian networks allowing causal inference. However, existing network studies have included populations with varied trauma types and durations, yielding mixed results, and have rarely incorporated trauma histories into the analyses, despite their etiological significance.Objective: This study examines the structural relationships and potential pathways between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reversible Chemistry for Cancer Therapy and Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reversible chemistry strategies in cancer treatment and diagnosis have attracted significant attention due to their unique ability to dynamically respond to both exogenous (e.g., light, ultrasound, and magnetic fields) and endogenous (e.g., pH, redox potential, and hypoxia-normoxia) stimuli, thereby modulating the functional characteristics of materials. Reversible cancer therapy offers distinct advantages over irreversible cancer therapy including sustainable cyclic function, shape-specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Ink Writing of Skin-Mountable Free-Form Thermoelectric Sensors Based on Ag<sub>2</sub>Te Composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flexible thermoelectric sensors convert temperature gradients into electrical energy, allowing rapid, real-time responses to subtle temperature changes without relying on external power sources or mechanical vibrations. These features allow seamless integration into wearable electronics and humanoid robotic systems, where mechanical flexibility, environmental stability, and customizable design are essential. In this study, a skin-mountable free-form thermoelectric sensor was fabricated through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breast Cancers Detected and Missed by AI-CAD: Results from the AI-STREAM Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose To evaluate the characteristics of breast cancers detected and missed by artificial intelligence-based computer-assisted diagnosis (AI-CAD) during screening mammography. Materials and Methods This retrospective secondary analysis was conducted using data from the Artificial Intelligence for Breast Cancer Screening in Mammography trial (ClinicalTrials.gov: NCT05024591), a prospective, multicenter cohort study performed from 2021 to 2022. AI-CAD results were categorized into nine subgroups...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biphasic MoO<sub>2</sub>/Mo<sub>2</sub>C-Passivated Graphite Anodes for Fast-Charging Lithium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fast charging of commercial lithium-ion batteries severely compromises long-term cycle durability, particularly in cells using high mass-loading thick electrodes. Such performance decay originates from interfacial kinetic limitations in the graphite anode as follows: (i) a sluggish Li^(+) desolvation at the electrolyte-graphite interface, (ii) a hindered Li^(+) diffusion across the solid electrolyte interphase (SEI), and (iii) a restricted Li^(+) insertion into the graphite, which collectively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunicate-Inspired Carboxymethyl Cellulose Hydrogel Filler for Treating Age-Associated Vocal Fold Atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For the treatment of dysphonia and aspiration induced by presbylaryngis, injection laryngoplasty is widely conducted. Here, the feasibility of carboxymethyl cellulose hydrogel modified with pyrogallol (CMC-PG) is checked for injection laryngoplasty. CMC-PG, owing to its low viscosity, is easily injectable in liquid form and can self-polymerize into a hydrogel without the need for oxidative cross-linking agents. Moreover, the CMC-PG hydrogel demonstrates improved stability, tissue adhesiveness,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum nanoplasmonic alchemy: transforming yttrium into an on-chip hydrogen sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a nanoplasmonic hydrogen sensor based on a gold-yttrium-platinum plasmonic waveguide, numerically investigated using rigorous coupled wave analysis (RCWA). Upon hydrogen absorption, the yttrium layer undergoes a reversible phase transition from metallic to semiconducting, which alters its dielectric permittivity and modulates the optical response of the device. These hydrogen-induced changes lead to a pronounced plasmon resonance red-shift (Δλ) and enhanced differential reflectance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and Validation of Dynamic Prediction Model for Thromboembolic and Bleeding Risk in Patients With Atrial Fibrillation Initiating Direct Oral Anticoagulants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These dynamic prediction models offer a novel approach for reassessing thromboembolic and major bleeding risks in patients with atrial fibrillation receiving DOACs, demonstrating superior performance compared with existing models. Enabling regular risk updates based on the patient's current status, these tools support personalized and dynamic risk assessments in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Combining Traditional East Asian and Conventional Western Medicine on Acute Stroke Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TM, when integrated into CM care, may be linked to less favorable functional outcomes after AIS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxygen-terminated Ti<sub>3</sub>C<sub>2</sub>T<sub><em>x</em></sub> MXene <em>via</em> electrophoretic functionalization for electrochemical nitrate reduction to ammonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electrochemical nitrate reduction reaction (eNO(3)RR) is a promising method for efficiently producing ammonia (NH(3)), which is a carbon-free fuel and hydrogen carrier. However, eNO(3)RR suffers from low NH(3) selectivity due to the sluggish protonation steps (*NH(2) → *NH(3)), widely regarded as the rate-determining step (RDS), competing with N(2) formation. Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXene (MX) has emerged as a potential electrocatalyst for eNO(3)RR due to its excellent NO(3)^(-) adsorption capability,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Charged Polyampholyte Interfaces: Synthesis, Properties, and Antifouling Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biocompatible hydroxyapatite (HA) is a biomaterial widely used in the regeneration and replacement of dental and bone tissue. On these HA surfaces, complex multicellular communities known as biofilms are established by pathogenic microorganisms, contributing to 75% of all bacterial infections and presenting a significant public health concern. Among the various charged polymers, zwitterionic polymers are commonly used for antifouling applications due to their ability to form a strong hydration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in reactive carbon capture <em>via</em> carbonate/bicarbonate electrolysis for efficient CO<sub>2</sub> utilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical reduction of carbon dioxide (CO(2)RR) offers a crucial pathway for converting CO(2) into value-added chemicals. Despite significant progress in catalyst and electrolyzer development, the practical application of the CO(2)RR remains hampered by challenges stemming from limited CO(2) conversion efficiency by carbonate (CO(3)^(2-)) and bicarbonate (HCO(3)^(-)) formation. Reactive carbon capture (RCC) integrates CO(2) capture and electrochemical conversion, directly utilizing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heteroepitaxial Strain Engineering and Interfacial Energy Transfer Boosting Optoelectronic Properties in C<sub>60</sub>/WS<sub>2</sub> van der Waals Heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Engineered van der Waals (vdW) heterostructures, combining molecular semiconductors and atomically flat nanomaterials, offer vast opportunities to tailor optoelectronic properties at heterointerfaces. Here, the heteroepitaxial assembly of C(60) molecules on monolayer tungsten disulfide (ML-WS(2)), where an anisotropic compression strain within the C(60) lattice at the heterointerface induces the formation of 1D polymeric C(60) strings and activates otherwise symmetry-forbidden S(1) → S(0)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frequency and Associated Factors of Interruptions During the Medication Administration Process Among Nurses in South Korea: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings highlight the importance of understanding the distinct characteristics of interruptions and developing targeted strategies based on their sources and contributing factors. Creating supportive environments and fostering an organisational culture that actively prevents unnecessary interruptions are essential for enhancing medication safety and workflow efficiency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PRDX5 Regulates Mitochondrial Function and Nuclear Spreading in Myogenesis and Acts With PRDX3 to Delay Muscle Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings reveal a previously unidentified role of PRDX5 in coordinating mitochondrial function and nuclear positioning during myogenesis and muscle regeneration. The combined deficiency of PRDX3 and PRDX5 accelerates muscle aging by exacerbating oxidative stress and mitochondrial dysfunction, suggesting that enhancing their activity may be a promising therapeutic strategy to prevent sarcopenia and age-related muscle degeneration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strain-Insensitive Heater on Wrinkled Surface Integrated with Carbon Nanotube Bundles for Wearable Thermal Therapy and Multimodal Tactile Displays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flexible or stretchable heaters can generate heat despite their deformation, making them suitable for various applications such as wearable devices and human-machine interfaces. This study presents the development and characterization of a highly stretchable heater integrating vertically aligned carbon nanotubes (VACNTs) on a wrinkled elastomer substrate designed to maintain consistent heating performance under mechanical strain. Through a synergistic design considering both material and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the healing rate with meniscal repair concomitant with anterior cruciate ligament reconstruction and isolated meniscal repair based on magnetic resonance imaging signal intensity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: IMSI is a simple and conventional parameter for the assessment of meniscal healing. The healing rate of meniscal repair concomitant with ACL reconstruction compared with isolated meniscal repair using IMSI was similar to that of MRI reading. Thus, concomitant ACL reconstruction significantly improves the healing process of meniscus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Quadriceps Muscle Fatigue With Return to Preinjury Sports Following Primary Anterior Cruciate Ligament Reconstruction Using Hamstring Autograft and Tibialis Anterior Allograft]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The work fatigue, SLHD, IKDC score, and KOOS Sport and Recreation subscale were better in patients who returned to preinjury sports levels than in those who did not. Work fatigue of the quadriceps muscle and SLHD were associated with return to preinjury sports levels, whereas work fatigue of the quadriceps muscle, SLHD, and IKDC score were associated with postoperative sports levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the robustness of slide-level AI predictions on out-of-focus whole slide images: A retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings empirically suggest that the typical levels of WSI blurriness encountered in clinical practice may not significantly compromise the robustness of slide-level AI classification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PDGFRα+ fibroblast ablation exacerbates pathologic features in house dust mite-induced allergenic asthma model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Asthma, a chronic inflammatory airway disease, remains a major global health concern. Fibroblasts, the cell type responsible for tissue repair and fibrosis, are therefore a potential therapeutic target for asthma-related lung disease. However, the role of fibroblasts in the onset and progression of asthma is poorly understood. Thus, we sought to determine the consequence of fibroblast loss on lung homeostasis and asthma development using a transgenic mouse model to ablate PDGFRα+ fibroblasts. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of colorectal cancer in kidney transplant recipients and patients with end-stage renal disease undergoing hemodialysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The risk of CRC after KT remained significantly lower than that of patients undergoing dialysis, even after landmark analysis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term clinical outcome and risk stratification across stages of cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic syndrome in a nationwide cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A higher CKM stage was associated with a progressive increase in the risk of all-cause mortality and major cardiovascular events. Clinicians may benefit from prioritizing the early identification of high-risk individuals and implementing targeted management strategies based on CKM staging to improve long-term adverse outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Prospective Multicenter Study on the Evaluation of Frequency of Idiopathic Intracranial Hypertension in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The frequency of IIH in headache clinics in Korea was low. Typical obesity profiles, clinical characteristics, and papilledema are less common in Korean patients with IIH. Although the SNNOOP10 list seems to be feasible, clinical suspicion alone may not be sufficient to screen for IIH, particularly in Asians.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sleep Disturbance Among Workers: Interaction and Mediation of Job Satisfaction and Social Support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We highlight the significant relationship between low social support at work and insomnia. Job satisfaction plays a crucial mediating role in this relationship.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Prepregnancy Maternal Fasting Glucose Levels on Pregnancy and Neonatal Morbidity in Women With Pregestational Diabetes Mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Elevated prepregnancy FPG levels were associated with higher frequencies of preterm birth, macrosomia, and LGA. Neonates born to women with diabetes-range FPG had higher rates of TTN, RDS, and neonatal hypoglycemia. Prospective longitudinal studies incorporating both prepregnancy and gestational glycemic status are needed to establish the causal relationship between glycemic control and pregnancy outcomes in women with diabetes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increasing Diabetes Incidence and Prevalence Among Koreans Aged Under 30 Years: Socioeconomic Disparities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The rising burden of diabetes among young Koreans, particularly among socioeconomically disadvantaged groups, underscores the need for targeted public health interventions and early detection programs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacteroides eggerthii Ameliorates MASLD through Host-Microbe Signaling and Highlights 2-Hydroxyisocaproate as a Potential Effector]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Bacteroides eggerthii ameliorates MASLD via gut-liver axis modulation, including bile acid metabolism and hepatic lipid signaling. These underscore its therapeutic potential and highlight HICA as a novel microbiome-derived metabolite with anti-steatotic activity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative Multi-Omics Profiling Identifies Infiltrative HCC as an Immunotherapy-Resistant Subtype with Distinct Molecular Features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Infiltrative HCC is a clinically aggressive and molecularly distinct subtype of advanced HCC. Morphological classification and type IV infiltrative signatures may guide risk stratification and therapeutic decision-making in advanced HCC treated with immunotherapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiation Exposure to Operators in Coronary Procedures Between Left Distal and Right Conventional Radial Access]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: During coronary procedures, no significant differences were observed in the operator radiation exposure at the left wrist, head, and chest between left DRA and right TRA groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CPT1B-Mediated Fatty Acid Oxidation Induces Pigmentation in Solar Lentigo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cellular senescence is associated with altered lipid metabolism, including increased cellular lipid uptake, upregulated lipid biosynthesis, and deregulated lipid breakdown. Previous studies have reported that carnitine palmitoyltransferase (CPT), the rate-limiting enzyme in fatty acid oxidation that catalyzes the conversion of acyl-CoA to acylcarnitine, is involved in various senescence-related diseases. Although solar lentigo (SL) is an age-related pigmentary disorder characterized by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulating Mixed Emotions: The Role of Emotion Goals on Experiential, Expressive, and Physiological Responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While mixed emotions are prevalent, the impact of intentional regulation on these states remains unclear. To investigate how individuals modulate these complex emotional states across experience, expression, and physiology, we propose a three-dimensional extension of the Evaluative Space Model (3D-ESM). We used this model to examine whether negative and positive emotion goals during cognitive reappraisal of emotionally ambivalent stimuli (disgusting-amusing) differentially influence negative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Contrast-Enhanced MRI in the Evaluation of Soft Tissue Tumors and Tumor-Like Lesions: Technical Principles and Clinical Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dynamic contrast-enhanced (DCE) MRI is an advanced imaging technique that involves intravenous administration of a contrast agent followed by serial imaging to characterize temporal enhancement patterns. This technique provides essential information on tissue vascularity, perfusion, and capillary permeability, which are essential for characterizing soft tissue lesions. DCE-MRI plays a valuable role in differentiating benign from malignant lesions, distinguishing neoplastic from non-neoplastic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CarpeDeam: a de novo metagenome assembler for heavily damaged ancient datasets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[De novo assembly of ancient metagenomic datasets is a challenging task. Ultra-short fragment size and characteristic postmortem damage patterns of sequenced ancient DNA molecules leave current tools ill-equipped for ideal assembly. We present CarpeDeam, a novel damage-aware de novo assembler designed specifically for ancient metagenomic samples. Utilizing maximum-likelihood frameworks that integrate sample-specific damage patterns, CarpeDeam demonstrates improved recovery of longer continuous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling the evolution of virtual reality in nursing education: a BERTopic-based analysis of research trends and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study employs BERTopic, an advanced natural language processing (NLP) technique, to systematically analyze the thematic evolution and research hotspots of virtual reality (VR) applications in nursing education from 2008 to 2025. Using a corpus of 683 peer-reviewed articles from Web of Science, we applied BERTopic's transformer-based embedding and hierarchical clustering pipeline to identify latent topics, quantify their temporal trends, and visualize inter-topic relationships through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Fine-mapping genomic loci refines bipolar disorder risk genes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective Study of Three-Dimensional Bi-directional Barbed Threads for Midface and Nasolabial Fold Rejuvenation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: 3D bi-directional PDO threads demonstrated safety and efficacy for midfacial rejuvenation, producing sustained wrinkle reduction and investigator-rated aesthetic improvement at 6 months. While a paired comparison with other thread types would have provided stronger evidence, ethical and technical limitations precluded direct contralateral-thread trials. These prospective data nonetheless contribute objective evidence to a field largely informed by retrospective or anecdotal reports.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Cryogenic Particle Delivery in Enhancing Skin Penetration and Absorption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cryogenic particle delivery significantly enhances skin penetration and absorption, particularly when combined with MTS, demonstrating a synergistic effect. Its ability to deliver compounds safely and effectively highlights its potential as a transformative tool for therapeutic and cosmetic transdermal applications. Future in vivo studies are warranted to validate these findings and optimise its clinical applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: ELMO2-related intraosseous vascular malformation: new cases with novel pathogenic variants, clinical follow-up and therapeutic approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating voluntary care seeking effects on COVID-19 outcomes and health system costs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In an endemic COVID-19 setting with reduced enforcement measures, intervention success increasingly depends on voluntary compliance behaviors shaped by risk perceptions and population immunity. We used a previously developed behavior adaptation model, calibrated to Omicron wave data (February 1-May 31, 2022) in South Korea, to compare health outcomes (cumulative incidence, treated cases) and costs (vaccination, testing, treatment) under two scenarios: only mandatory compliance versus a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinguishing acute and chronic TMD in adolescent patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective cross-sectional study aimed to elucidate the clinical and imaging characteristics of chronic temporomandibular disorder (TMD) compared to acute TMD in adolescents, and to identify factors associated with symptom chronicity. The study included 158 adolescent patients with TMD (103 females and 55 males; mean age, 15.08 ± 2.23 years), classified into acute TMD (symptom duration < 6 months) and chronic TMD (symptom duration ≥ 6 months) groups. We identified the adolescent patients...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-enhanced bilingual banking assistant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Financial literacy and access to banking services are still major challenges, especially in multilingual regions. Many people who do not speak English fluently face difficulties using traditional banking online systems. To help solve this problem, we developed a bilingual banking assistant that works in English, Hindi, and Hinglish (a mix of Hindi and English). To ensure user privacy without storing client conversations, the proposed assistant processes natural language banking queries and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital impression accuracy for bone-level and tissue-level implants using scan bodies of different heights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intraoral scanning has gained acceptance for its accuracy comparable to conventional implant impressions. This study compared digital impression accuracy based on implant placement level and scan body height. Two mandibular partial edentulous models missing the left second premolar and first molar, were used: one with a tissue level implant and the other with a bone level implant. Models were divided into four groups: Group TS-S (bone level, short scan bodies), Group TS-R (bone level, Regular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public values in public R&amp;D through natural language processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given South Korea's recent 16.6% reduction in research and development (R&D) budgets for 2023, there is an urgent need for more efficient and strategic R&D policy management. Previous studies evaluating R&D outputs have primarily relied on quantitative metrics or expert opinions, making it challenging to assess qualitative outcomes systematically. However, existing literature lacks data-driven, scalable approaches that go beyond counting outputs to systematically capture and interpret the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assembly of dynamic helical β-peptides with switchable handedness into multiple types of metal-peptide frameworks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-directed assemblies of helical peptides are emerging chiral biomimetic materials, yet dynamic helical peptides remain underexplored. Here we report the coordination-driven assembly of dynamic 12/10-helical β-pentapeptides into distinct metal-peptide frameworks (MPFs) with silver ions. Ligand 1, consisting of cis-2-aminocycloheptanecarboxylic acid with alternating chirality, exhibits solvent-dependent screw-sense preference: (P)-helix in protic and (M)-helix in aprotic solvents. The two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residual Metal Artifact Reduction in CT Images: An Unsupervised Residual and Contrastive Learning Approach for Preserving Metal Structures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We hope that this unsupervised learning model can contribute to good achievements in the MAR field while overcoming the limitations of data construction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Healthcare Photonic Nanomaterials and Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between coronary artery calcium and the progression of calcific aortic valve disease: a hospital population-based observational retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CAC was significantly associated with the progression of CAVD. Particularly, CAC≥400 was linked to progression toward significant AS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct NO<sub>2</sub> formation from N<sub>2</sub>-O<sub>2</sub> supercritical fluid plasma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate a novel approach for the direct formation of nitrogen dioxide (NO[Formula: see text]) in a supercritical nitrogen-oxygen mixture using laser-produced plasma. By tightly focusing a nanosecond laser pulse into the dense fluid, we generate a high electron density plasma that enables chemical reactions not accessible under ambient conditions. Optical emission and absorption spectroscopy confirm the in-situ formation of NO[Formula: see text], and parametric investigations reveal that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Metabolites of Fairy Chemicals in Tea and Coffee: Methylated AHX and AOH]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fairy chemicals (FCs), such as 2-azahypoxanthine (AHX), 2-aza-8-oxohypoxanthine (AOH), and imidazole-4-carboxamide, are molecules with diverse functions in plants. Methylation of plant hormones is recognized to affect the physiological functions of plants. We predicted that plants regulate the physiological activity of FCs through methylation and launched a project searching for methyl derivatives of FCs. We synthesized 7-methyl-AHX (1), 9-methyl-AHX (2), 7- methyl-AOH (3), 9-methyl-AOH (4), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preserving the native knee joint line obliquity in total knee arthroplasty benefits ankle movement during the five times sit-to-stand test]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that the ankle ROM is influenced following TKA during the 5xSTS task, suggesting that alignment strategies may have biomechanical effects extending beyond the knee joint. A deeper understanding of these effects could inform rehabilitation strategies and optimise surgical outcomes following TKA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Versatile Genome Editing Using Type I-E CRISPR-Cas3 in Rice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Type I-E CRISPR-Cas3 derived from Escherichia coli (Eco CRISPR-Cas3) can introduce large deletions in target sites and is available for mammalian genome editing. The use of Eco CRISPR-Cas3 in plants is challenging because 7 CRISPR-Cas3 components (6 Cas proteins and CRISPR RNA) must be expressed simultaneously in plant cells. To date, application has been limited to maize protoplasts, and no mutant plants have been produced. In this study, we developed a genome editing system in rice using Eco...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abnormal fetal genitalia: two- and three-dimensional ultrasound assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prenatal diagnosis of abnormal external genitalia may still be difficult even with 3D ultrasound. Postnatal cross-examination by pediatric experts should be mandatory when abnormal external genitalia are suspected prenatally.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Environmental sensitivity, supportive parenting, and the development of attachment and internalizing problems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Supportive parenting experiences link to secure attachment development, and secure attachment in turn links to children's emotional well-being. However, little is known whether child-factors, like their environmental sensitivity, moderate these associations for better or for worse. We used longitudinal data (three data waves spanning two years) from 614 children (Wave 1: M(age) = 10.28; SD(age) = 0.58; 44% boys). At all waves, attachment was operationalized as children's knowledge of the Secure...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Margin Status following Simple Excision of Head and Neck Basal Cell Carcinoma: A Population-Based, Cross-Sectional Study of 9,291 Excisions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A mainstay treatment of head and neck basal cell carcinoma (BCC) is excision with a fixed surgical margin. Large-scale evaluation of post-surgical margin status is necessary to improve outcomes. This cross-sectional study assessed margin outcomes following excision of head and neck BCCs across Danish healthcare settings, including risk factors for tumour-positive margins. Histopathology records on BCCs excised by all medical specialities between 1 January-31 December 2022 were retrieved from The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valve-in-valve transcatheter aortic valve implantation with balloon-expandable versus self-expandable valves in degenerated surgical bioprostheses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ViV-TAVI is a safe and effective treatment for patients presenting sBVD. Improved hemodynamic valve performance with SEV over BEV observed during early follow-up did not translate into long-term lower mortality rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isomeric effects of Al<sub>13</sub> Keggin clusters as catalyst support on oxidation reactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionic crystals were synthesized by combining a catalytically active polyoxometalate [Al(OH)(6)Mo(6)O(18)]^(3-) with Keggin-type [Al(13)O(4)(OH)(24)(H(2)O)(12)]^(7+) isomers (ε-Al(13) or δ-Al(13)) serving as catalyst supports. The influence of the Al(13) isomers on catalytic activity in sulfide oxidation was systematically investigated. The ionic crystal containing δ-Al(13) exhibited superior catalytic performance, which was attributed to stronger interactions with sulfide substrates, as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extended Plasmonic Nanostructures Templated by Tobacco Mosaic Virus Coat Protein]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Optical and magnetic metamaterials possess interesting properties that cannot be achieved with conventional materials. However, there is currently no synthetic method offering both scalability and nanometer spatial precision. Biotemplating is a promising technique that has the potential to organize nanoscale components with high precision while being scalable and low-cost. Here, we demonstrate a versatile template using hexahistidine-tagged tobacco mosaic virus coat protein. The protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of ascorbic acid as an intervention of metal toxicity in dogs in Kabwe district]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-essential metals and metalloids are known to induce oxidative stress in exposed organisms, often leading to cellular damage and systemic toxicity. While chelation therapy remains the primary treatment for metal toxicity, its application is limited by side effects. L-ascorbic acid (L-AA), a widely available antioxidant, has emerged as a promising nutritional intervention for mitigating metal-induced oxidative stress. Dogs, whose blood lead levels (BLLs) closely mirror those of humans, have...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychometric properties of the Japanese version of the Demoralization Scale-II (DS-II) in cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The DS-II-J is a valid and reliable tool for assessing demoralization in Japanese cancer patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative hepatic encephalopathy following laparoscopic repair of diaphragmatic hernia after radiofrequency ablation: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This case report describes a rare, late complication of radiofrequency ablation for hepatocellular carcinoma. A 77-year-old woman with a history of hepatocellular carcinoma presented with an incarcerated diaphragmatic hernia (DH), which was successfully repaired using emergency laparoscopic surgery. However, 2 months later, she developed hepatic encephalopathy due to severe fecal impaction. Imaging and endoscopy revealed significant colonic stenosis at the hernia repair site. The stenosis was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three-year insights from a proton therapy centre: Evolving strategies in ependymoma treatment planning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Tailored planning approaches, depending on location and relationship to the brainstem, are essential when treating ependymoma patients. A hybrid PT-XT approach, is feasible in well-selected patients, demonstrating acceptable target coverage, brainstem doses, and to date no occurrence of symptomatic brainstem injury.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical efficacy of casirivimab and imdevimab in preventing COVID-19 in the Omicron BA.5 subvariant epidemic: a retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CAS + IMD may be effective for post-exposure prophylaxis of COVID-19 during the Omicron BA.5 subvariant epidemic. However, prudent clinical use should consider the circulating variant profile. Further research is warranted to validate CAS + IMD's role in COVID-19 post-exposure prophylaxis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the utility and challenges for implementation of a risk prediction system: a usability study with hospital pharmacists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The paper-format prediction model was positively evaluated by frontline pharmacists, especially for its clear and straightforward nature. As anticipated, however, limitations such as manual data input and paper-based format were identified by some participants. Integration into electronic health records and broader clinical validation will be necessary to advance the clinical application of this prediction model and ensure real-world applicability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fosphenytoin may be effective in shortening the half-life of lamotrigine in case of overdose: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Fosphenytoin administration may be effective for treating lamotrigine overdose.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of coronavirus disease on the incidence rate of methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus among hospitalized patients with lung cancer: a nationwide retrospective cohort study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The incidence rate of MRSA among hospitalized patients with lung cancer decreased steadily after the COVID-19 pandemic. These findings suggest that routine hospital-wide infection control measures implemented during the pandemic may yield lasting benefits even in the absence of targeted interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-series datasets of meteorological variables and influenza incidence in Kawasaki City, Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: Although a wealth of studies has explored the impact of individual meteorological variables on influenza transmission, investigations of these effects within key subgroups-such as viral type, sex, and age-remain scarce. Moreover, long-term daily time-series influenza surveillance data are exceptionally limited. To address these shortcomings, we herein present a meticulously curated daily time-series dataset spanning approximately 11 years from Kawasaki City, Japan, to facilitate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute epiglottitis in an older patient: a case report and review of the literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Acute epiglottitis is a medical emergency with a rapid progression and severe consequences, thus requiring a high index of clinical suspicion in patients presenting with nonspecific symptoms. A multidisciplinary approach and immediate therapeutic measures are imperative to ensure the safety of the airway through basic and invasive procedures, in addition to strict postprocedural follow-up. This approach is fundamental to optimize health outcomes among these patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[White matter lesions associated with the reemergence of grasp reflexes in patients with idiopathic normal pressure hydrocephalus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The inhibition of grasp reflexes is achieved via a right-lateralized prefrontal cortex-basal ganglia-thalamocortical 'stopping' network.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Byte into sustainability: a scoping review of digital food environment attributes that shape consumers' sustainability perceptions, attitudes, intentions, and behaviours]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring lifestyle activities as possible protective factors for life satisfaction: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High engagement in lifestyle activities had a protective effect on life satisfaction. The differences in the relationship between each activity type and life satisfaction varied based on participants' characteristics. To maintain life satisfaction, it is necessary to understand the contribution of different activity types and the individual characteristics of the target population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyclonal immunoglobulin G deposits with distinctive appearance in the tubular basement membrane: a report of two cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Summary of present design of discrete choice experiments for patient preferences in lung cancer based on the ISPOR ESTIMATE checklist]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our scoping review using the ISPOR ESTIMATE checklists found that the consideration points remained the focus of Evaluation, Stochastic, and Trade-offs in DCE studies on patient preferences for lung cancer treatments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use it or lose it: a four-year follow-up assessing whether physical activity near one's capacity reduces the risk of functional decline among older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Engaging in physically demanding activities, irrespective of baseline physical capacity, may help slow functional decline in old age. Older adults should be encouraged to engage in physically demanding activities to enhance their functional capacity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pericardial effusion as a potential site of localized DNA virus reactivation following U-CB transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pericardial effusion (PCE) is a serious complication after allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplantation, but its etiology is not fully understood, particularly the role of viral reactivation. We investigated the presence of DNA viruses in pericardial fluid from nine umbilical cord blood transplant recipients who underwent pericardiocentesis. Multiplex PCR detected DNA viruses in seven patients (78%), with Epstein-Barr virus being most common. The clinical context of viral detection appeared to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resilience in neurodivergence: professional perspectives mapped to the World Health Organisations' International Classification of Functioning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Individuals with childhood-onset divergent neurological development, such as autism or Attention-Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD), may live a good life according to objectively or subjectively determined standards. Yet, most research has focused on deficits and risks for negative outcomes. This international study forms part of a larger project examining the factors contributing to well-being, mental health, and functioning outcomes in neurodivergent populations using the World Health...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Incidence of opioid-induced constipation in non-cancer patients using weak opioids for chronic pain in Japan: a cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A 0.5-V MI-OTA-based shadow universal filter with integrated passband gain compensation and low-pass control for low-frequency applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultra-low-power active filters have received increasing attention in recent years due to emerging applications such as bio-signal sensing and wearable electronic devices, where they are employed in the analog front-end to eliminate interference noise. This paper presents a novel voltage-mode shadow universal filter based on multiple-input operational transconductance amplifiers (MI-OTAs). The multiple-input functionality of the OTA is implemented using the multiple-input bulk-driven MOS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical utility of comprehensive genomic profiling versus Oncomine Dx target test in pathological stage II-III non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The next-generation sequencing (NGS)-based Oncomine Dx Target Test (ODxTT) is the standard tool for guiding postoperative adjuvant therapy in patients with non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) in Japan. To advance precision oncology, we evaluated the clinical utility of an in-house comprehensive genomic profiling (CGP) assay, Rapid-Neo, as a complementary approach to ODxTT in surgically resected NSCLC. Patients with pathological stage II-III NSCLC who underwent anatomical surgical resection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Exploring the association between adolescent psychotic-like experiences and components of social performance using a multi-level virtual reality paradigm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamics of one-dimensional spin models via complex-time evolution of tensor networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Studying the real-time dynamics of strongly correlated systems poses significant challenges, which have recently become more manageable thanks to advances in density matrix renormalization group (DMRG) and tensor network methods. A notable development in this area is the introduction of a complex-time evolution scheme for tensor network states, originally suggested for solving Anderson impurity model and designed to suppress the growth of entanglement under time evolution. In this study, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between aortic valve calcification and cardiovascular events in patients with chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The association between aortic valve calcification (AVC) and cardiovascular (CV) events across diverse populations including patients with chronic kidney disease (CKD) remains controversial. This study aimed to determine whether AVC is associated with CV events in patients with CKD. In this prospective study, 1,279 participants with CKD were enrolled. A Cox proportional hazard model was applied to determine the association between AVC and CV events. The participants were divided into the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyper-maturity and accelerated aging in the hippocampus of mouse models of neuropsychiatric disorders with anxiety-like behavior]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proper maturation of neuronal and glial cells in the hippocampus is essential for emotional regulation and cognitive function. While pseudo-immaturity, defined as arrested or reversed development, has been extensively implicated in various neuropsychiatric conditions, the opposite phenomenon, hyper-maturity, remains underexplored. Here, we present transcriptomic evidence of hippocampal hyper-maturity across 17 datasets from 16 mouse models with genetic, pharmacological, or other experimental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of risk factors for Takotsubo cardiomyopathy in older patients using large-scale medical reimbursement data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Takotsubo cardiomyopathy (TTS) is triggered by mental or physical stress and accompanied by symptoms such as acute myocardial infarction. In previous studies, although several cardiovascular risk factors have been reported, specific risk factors other than these remain unclear, particularly in older populations. In this study, we investigated associations between TTS and other diseases in Japanese high-risk older people. In this matched case-control study, age and sex were used as matching...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nardilysin in adipocyte regulates insulin sensitivity via HIF1α and PPARγ]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity is a critical global health issue and a major risk factor for type 2 diabetes mellitus (T2DM). However, molecular mechanism by which obesity leads to T2DM has not been fully elucidated. Here, we investigated the role of adipocyte nardilysin (NRDC) in insulin sensitivity using adipocyte-specific NRDC-knockout mice (Adipo-KO). Despite no difference in body weight, Adipo-KO demonstrated enhanced glucose tolerance and insulin sensitivity exclusively under high fat diet (HFD) conditions....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Instanton-like effect caused by qubit-boson interaction in light of quantum simulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The renormalized quantum Rabi model describing a qubit-boson interaction has the transition from SUSY to its spontaneous breaking under suitable conditions. It is caused by how the X-gate coupled to the Bose field works properly between the two symmetrical wells made by the bosons coupled to a qubit. According to Polyakov's idea, there is the possibility that an instanton tunneling the barrier between those symmetrical wells appears as the classical trajectory. In this paper, therefore, under a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Regulatory Mechanism of Water Permeation by the Selectivity Filter Arginine in Aquaporin Revealed by Solid-State NMR and Computational Analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The selectivity filter (SF) of aquaporins (AQPs) governs substrate specificity and permeation efficiency. Despite its functional importance, the mechanistic basis of SF-mediated water transport remains poorly understood, primarily due to the challenge of analyzing the local chemical environment surrounding the SF region. In this study, we employed an integrated approach combining functional measurements, magic-angle spinning solid-state nuclear magnetic resonance (MAS ssNMR) spectroscopy, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Senkyunolide I Alleviated Renal Fibrosis in UUO Mice by Regulating the Nrf2/xCT/GPX4 and NLRP3/Caspase-1/GSDMD Pathways to Inhibit Ferroptosis and Pyroptosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Senkyunolide I (SI), a natural phthalide compound extracted from the traditional Chinese medicine Ligusticum chuanxiong, exhibits significant potential in the treatment of fibrosis-related diseases. This study focuses on the forms of cell death as an entry point to investigate the impact of SI on renal fibrosis (RF) and related mechanisms in a unilateral ureteral obstruction (UUO) mouse model. We established a UUO mouse model for SI treatment and evaluated the alleviating effect of SI on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cyclic-di-GMP interferes with DNA-MucR-DNA bridging to derepress genes targeted by the xenogeneic silencer MucR]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The tradeoff between the benefits and costs of maintaining AT-rich accessory genes is vital in bacterial ecology and evolution. MucR is a conserved xenogeneic silencer for AT-rich accessory genes within α-proteobacteria, but its anti-silencing mechanisms remain unknown. By focusing on Sinorhizobium fredii, a facultative nitrogen-fixing microsymbiont of diverse legumes, this work reports that elevated c-di-GMP promotes the condition-dependent expression of various MucR1-targets, while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Hypothetical PM2.5 Intervention for the Risk of Hospitalization for Cardiovascular Diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study using data from the UK Biobank, the absolute risk reduction of hospitalization for stroke, myocardial infarction, heart failure, and arrhythmia due to hypothetical ambient PM2.5 interventions was quantified. The findings suggest the beneficial cardiovascular health impacts of further strengthening the current PM2.5 regulations in the United Kingdom.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incomplete Family History and Meeting Algorithmic Criteria for Genetic Evaluation of Hereditary Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cross-sectional study, the magnitude of the association between incomplete family history documentation and identification of patients eligible for hereditary cancer genetic evaluation depended on whether data were missing randomly or systematically. These findings suggest that health care organizations implementing CDS algorithms should assess their specific missing data patterns and consider tailored approaches to handling incomplete family history...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time to Total Hip Arthroplasty Among Patients in the US Military Health System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study of TRICARE enrollees, variation in THA receipt was identified across multilevel factors. These finding suggest that policy and programming decisions could benefit from including TRICARE-participating orthopedic surgeon locations, structural factors, and reimbursement models to optimize THA access.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Broadband optical modulation and control at millikelvin temperatures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A universal experimental challenge in studying radiation effects on cryogenic devices is precisely and accurately characterizing the position-dependent device response near the energy detection threshold. We have developed a compact cryogenic optical beam steering system that can be used to generate O (μs) pulses of small numbers of photons over the energy range of 1.3-3.4 eV at room temperature, and deliver those photons via fiber optic to any specified location on the surface of a detector...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Persisting or recurrent dermatological manifestations in Long-COVID: Data from a national cohort of 1741 patients from Italy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Climate, Heat, and the Limits of Medical Diagnostics: Lessons From "America's Hottest City"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WIC Online Shopping: Challenges and Opportunities for Vendors and Farmers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND IMPLICATIONS: To ensure WIC online shopping success, it is essential to address both the barriers and facilitators experienced by vendors, farmers, and farmers' markets. While this study collected various perspectives and experiences from merchants, future research may also focus attention on WIC participant perceptions of shopping online with these food retailers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Prognostic Value of Incidentally Detected Coronary Artery Calcium Using Artificial Intelligence Among Individuals With Immune-Mediated Inflammatory Diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among those with IMIDs, incidental CAC-AI was highly prevalent and significantly associated with both all-cause mortality and MACE. These findings suggest that CAC-AI may provide important prognostic information, allowing for improved risk stratification and treatment within an already high-risk and undertreated population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ADMGCN: Graph Convolutional Network for Alzheimer's Disease Diagnosis with a Meta-learning Paradigm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MOTIVATION: Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a neurodegenerative disorder characterized by memory loss and cognitive decline. While graph convolutional networks (GCNs) have emerged as popular tools for AD diagnosis due to their ability to handle structural information and fuse multi-modal features, deep learning approaches face significant challenges including the requirement for large datasets and sensitivity to unbalanced label distributions in AD research. To address these limitations and enhance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of Polypoidal choroidal vasculopathy and diabetic retinopathy: Practice patterns amongst vitreoretinal surgeons of India-A VRSI survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The current preferences in the management of PCV and DR among Indian vitreoretinal surgeons are reported here. The results of this survey will assist fellow practitioners in understanding contemporary real-world practices in relation to established literature and in developing appropriate guidelines.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selenium levels as a sex-specific predictor of migraine in the ELSA-Brasil study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundEmerging evidence suggests a link between migraine and selenium (Se). Se is related to systemic low-grade inflammation and thyroid function, which in their turn are also linked to migraine. Thus, we aimed to explore these relationships and hypothesized that higher Se levels would be related to decreased risk of migraine with an influence of systemic low-grade inflammation and thyroid function.MethodsIn a prospective analysis of the Brazilian Longitudinal Study of Adult Health...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Far-Red Spray-On Imaging Probes for FAP-Targeted Cancer Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluorescence-guided surgery (FGS) using fluorescent imaging probes is an emerging technology that enables tumor margin detection at potentially higher accuracy than is possible with traditional means. Most FGS imaging probes are administered systemically, many hours before a planned surgery, and must have cleared the bloodstream once surgery is initiated, so as not to contaminate the operative field. Topical administration of specially designed conjugates in the form of spray-on probes (SOP)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An ultra-simple construction strategy for uncommon 3,4-diaryl-modified maleimide luminophores and their unique aggregation-induced asymmetric effect (AIAE) on conformation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A special photo-activated ring-expansion reaction was applied to construct uncommon 3,4-diaryl-substituted maleimide (MAI) derivatives as novel luminescent materials for organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs). The three derivatives exhibit significant asymmetric substitution conformations in the aggregated state and different electroluminescence properties despite their symmetric chemical structures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in the discovery of ALKBH 1-8 inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The AlkB family is a class of Fe(II) and α-ketoglutarate-dependent dioxygenases mainly involved in the dealkylation of nucleobases of both DNA and RNA. The proteins belonging to this family share a common mechanism of action and participate in different pathways, from DNA repair to epigenetic regulation. Human cells have nine homologues, ALKBH1 - 8 and FTO.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic and Structural Analyses of Non-Heme Iron Enzyme TqaM for α-Tertiary Amino Acid Synthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[α-Tertiary amino acids (ATAAs) are versatile building blocks for the synthesis of biologically active compounds. Although synthetic and enzymatic approaches to ATAA synthesis have been developed, additional methods for ATAA production remain in high demand. Here, we report detailed mechanistic and structural analyses of TqaM, a non-heme iron-dependent oxygenase that catalyzes the key oxidative decarboxylation of a β-amino acid to generate 2-aminoisobutyric acid, a representative ATAA. In vitro...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanding the Photosensitive Area via Electrode-Geometry Design in Anisotropic Semimetal TaCoTe<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two-dimensional materials exhibit strong light-matter interactions, rendering them ideal candidates for photodetectors. The key issue for photodetection is the separation of photogenerated electron-hole pairs, which are usually confined at the interfacial junctions. This confinement limits the active area in photodetectors based on two-dimensional materials. In this work, we demonstrate that through the codesign of electrode configuration and device geometry, a significantly expanded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Irg1l regulates neuromast size via metabolic reprogramming to promote supporting cell proliferation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[One of the most basic principles in embryonic development is ensuring the proper size of tissues and organs to meet functional needs. So far, an endogenous metabolite regulating organ size has not been described. The current study highlights itaconate, the product of Irg1, in regulating zebrafish neuromast size. Single-cell transcriptomic sequencing analysis of enzymes catalyzing metabolic processes revealed that irg1l, a homolog of Irg1, is highly expressed in supporting cells of developing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heat-treatment-induced enhancement of activity and stability in Rh/Mo-doped PtNi octahedra for the oxygen reduction reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platinum-based bi- and trimetallic octahedral nanoparticles are among the most promising catalysts for the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) at the cathode of proton exchange membrane fuel cells (PEMFCs). While these catalysts already exhibit excellent activity, their performance and durability can be significantly enhanced through reductive heat treatment and controlled doping. In this study, we investigate the structural and electrochemical evolution of Ni-rich PtNi and Mo/Rh-doped PtNi...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Location and Identity of Photoreceptors Contributing to the Full-Field Stimulus Test (FST)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantification of visual function in severe forms of inherited retinal disease is challenging because of lack of stable gaze. Full-field stimulus test (FST) was developed two decades ago as an outcome measure to evaluate potential changes to the vision after gene augmentation therapy in RPE65-associated Leber congenital amaurosis. With greater use, there has been greater interest in better understanding photoreceptors dominating the perception of FST. Review of the literature and currently...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relation between post-migration stressors and trauma treatment outcomes: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: People seeking refuge and asylum must often endure diverse adversities before, during, and after migration, making them more susceptible to develop psychological problems. The effect of post-migration stressors on responsiveness to psychological treatment is unclear.Objectives: To: (1) evaluate the scope of the literature on the relation between post-migration stressors (e.g. struggles related to legal status in the context of resettlement) and outcomes of interventions targeting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of distal femur intraosseous access in adult trauma: an evaluation of needle length]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Distal femur IO access appears to be a feasible alternative for vascular access in young, non-obese adult patients. Our findings suggest that standard IO needle lengths are adequate for this site in this population, supporting its potential incorporation into emergency protocols. Further research is recommended to validate these results and inform standardized guidelines for distal femur IO placement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Detection of Covert Consciousness With Functional Near-Infrared Spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MRI-based Habitat Analysis for the Prediction of Progression-Free Survival in Primary Spinal Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background Prediction of prognosis in patients with primary spinal tumors is critical for treatment planning but a clinical challenge. Purpose To develop an MRI-based nested habitat radiomics model to predict progression-free survival (PFS) in patients with primary spinal tumors. Materials and Methods This dual-center retrospective study analyzed patients with resected primary spinal tumors. Patients from March 2010 to August 2019 were assigned to a training set; from September 2019 to October...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abduction and adduction malpositioned lateral radiographs cannot be used for proper assessment of the posterior tibial slope]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Abduction/adduction malalignment significantly alters mPTS measurements on lateral knee radiographs. A clinically relevant difference of ≥2° was observed in over half of patients, and 15.9% changed classification relative to the 12° surgical threshold. Lateral radiographs with a PDD ≥ 5 mm should not be used for surgical planning, and repeat imaging should be considered when mPTS values approach surgical decision thresholds.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Digital Drying an Effective Method for Infrared Spectroscopy of Gaseous Biofluid?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent years, gaseous biofluid analysis has gained popularity as a diagnostic approach due to the noninvasive collection of gaseous bioprobes. Among many biofluids, human exhaled breath stands out as a promising option, providing strong evidence of volatile biomarkers for various diseases. However, identifying these biomarkers is challenging due to the high concentration of water vapor in exhaled breath. Various experimental techniques, such as mass spectrometry, electronic nose, infrared...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Relationship Between HIV Preexposure Prophylaxis Use and Laboratory-Confirmed Bacterial Sexually Transmitted Infection Positivity Among a Diverse, Multi-City Cohort of Sexually Active Sexual and Gender Minorities in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The presence of chlamydia, gonorrhea, or syphilis infection is a significant risk factor for HIV acquisition and transmission and disproportionately impacts men who have sex with men (MSM) and transgender women. While HIV preexposure prophylaxis (PrEP) reduces HIV risk, its use may influence sexual behaviors, potentially increasing sexually transmitted infection (STI) exposure. Conversely, PrEP users are often more engaged in care, regularly screened and treated for STIs, and may access other...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prior osteosynthesis-unlike osteotomy-raises revision risk after total knee arthroplasty, predominantly via periprosthetic infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prior osteosynthesis increases revision risk after TKA-predominantly via infection-whereas prior osteotomy does not. These findings support extended perioperative infection workup, staged hardware removal when indicated and careful implant selection in patients with prior osteosynthesis; outcomes after osteotomy are comparable to primary osteoarthritis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Electronic Health Record-Integrated Clinical Pathway Improves Care of Sexual Assault Survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pathway usage led to improved medical and forensic care of sexual assault survivors. Implementation of Electronic Health Record-integrated clinical pathways requires active use of the pathway rather than indirect learning from the presence of the pathway.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age- and sex-specific reference values for the Banff Patella Instability Instrument (BPII 2.0) in the German population based on 1309 participants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides the first age- and sex-stratified reference BPII 2.0 values for the German population. Higher age, female sex, the presence of comorbidities and a higher BMI have a significant negative impact on reference values for the BPII 2.0.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac Effects of Dapagliflozin in People with Chronic Kidney Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In a heterogeneous population of patients with chronic kidney disease, dapagliflozin significantly reduced left ventricular mass index compared with placebo. These findings provide mechanistic insights into the early treatment benefits of SGLT2 inhibitors seen previously in chronic kidney disease. Further research is needed to replicate and further define these early treatment benefits. (Funded by the Danish Cardiovascular Academy and Novo Nordisk Foundation; ClinicalTrials.gov...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetics of Cholesterol and Coronary Disease Risk across Six Global Ancestries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings demonstrated a consistent association between LDL-C and CAD risk across diverse ancestry groups that are often poorly represented in clinical trials, although effect magnitudes varied. (Funded by the National Institutes of Health and others.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age and Treatment Intensification in Metastatic Hormone-Sensitive Prostate Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We observed an interaction between age and systemic TI on OS for men with mHSPC. Our data provide information on potential treatment strategies for men 70 years or older, especially in low-volume synchronous disease, where radiotherapy to the primary site is the standard of care. (Funded by the National Institutes of Health and others.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-Stakeholder Engagement for Patient-Centered Research on Sleep Apnea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AbstractIn 2016, many clinicians and investigators in the field of sleep apnea were surprised when a large multinational clinical trial of continuous positive airway pressure (CPAP) therapy failed to demonstrate a reduction in cardiovascular events in patients with sleep apnea and established cardiovascular disease. When a review of the trial data suggested that CPAP nonadherence among trial participants might explain the negative results, it became clear that new approaches were needed. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Sensitivity of Commercial Assays for Varicella Zoster Virus Seropositivity in Pediatric Patients with Inflammatory Bowel Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Pediatric IBD guidelines recommend assessing varicella-zoster virus (VZV) immunity prior to immune suppression. We evaluated the sensitivity of the commercial VZV assay relative to the more sensitive glycoprotein IgG ELISA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the enantioselective synthesis mechanism of ammonium cations in solution using deep learning potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Asymmetric synthesis is fundamental to modern organic chemistry. Predicting the stereoselectivity of catalytic reactions in solution remains a challenging problem, as it requires a comprehensive understanding of the underlying mechanistic, energetic, and kinetic factors. To address this challenge, we propose an active learning workflow that integrates iterative cycles of ab initio molecular dynamics (AIMD) and deep learning potential molecular dynamics (DLPMD) simulations. To demonstrate its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From the Laboratory to the Clinic: Differentiation, Disease Modeling and Transplantation of Cardiac Organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardiac organoids (hiPSC-COs), an emerging novel methodology, simulate human cardiac development and disease progression, providing a powerful in vitro model for cardiovascular research. This study systematically reviews the progress of translational research on cardiac organoids from laboratory to clinical applications. It focuses on two major construction strategies: first, the self-organizing differentiation based on embryoid bodies can reproduce multi-lineage cardiac structures and is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protective Role of the Sodium Taurocholate Cotransporting Polypeptide S267F Variant Against Hepatitis B Virus Infection and Cirrhosis in the Vietnamese Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The sodium taurocholate cotransporting polypeptide (NTCP) serves as both a hepatic bile acid transporter and an essential entry receptor for hepatitis B virus (HBV). The S267F (rs2296651) polymorphism in the NTCP gene has been associated with reduced HBV susceptibility in East Asian populations. However, its clinical relevance in the Vietnamese population remains underexplored. We investigated the association between the NTCP S267F variant and clinical outcomes in 743 Vietnamese individuals,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turbulent Transport Characteristics and Mechanistic Insights into Particle Suspensions with Distinct Photoresponses: A Comparative Investigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An accurate comprehension of the transport laws governing particle-laden fluids holds substantial significance for efficient energy transfer and conversion processes. Nevertheless, current researches exhibit an ambiguous understanding of the transport characteristics of particle suspensions with varying response ranges under photoirradiation, particularly at high shear rates, necessitating further clarification. Herein, in a horizontal continuous pipe, the evolution of flow resistance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generating MRI-Derived CSF Proxy-Markers to Predict and Visualize Alzheimer's Disease Progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preclinical detection of Alzheimer's disease (AD) is crucial to efficiently recruit clinical trial participants for examining AD-modifying drugs and ultimately yield clinical benefits for at-risk individuals. Cerebral amyloidosis precedes synaptic dysfunction and neurodegeneration markers, followed by the onset of AD-related cognitive impairment. To improve early AD-biomarker detection accuracy, patient data is, however, often collected via invasive procedures such as a lumbar puncture or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating Pain Assessment in Nicotine and Tobacco Research and Treatment to Improve Cessation Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lunar rhythms in sleep patterns of children with a family history of autism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unstable Recompensation: An Intermediate Subtype in Patients With HBV-Related Decompensated Cirrhosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Recompensation is not a uniform condition and should be further subclassified. Unstable recompensation is a distinct state with poorer survival than stable recompensation, yet better outcomes than ongoing decompensation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impaired embryogenesis following intracytoplasmic sperm injection with an Arrdc5-/- mouse model of oligoasthenoteratospermia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oligoasthenoteratospermia (OAT) describes male infertility due to a combination of low sperm count, reduced sperm motility, and abnormal sperm morphology. A common course of action to produce offspring from sperm of males with this condition is intracytoplasmic sperm injection (ICSI). Here we used the Arrdc5 knockout mouse model of OAT to examine the ramifications of bypassing natural barriers preventing fertilization by defective sperm via ICSI on the viability of embryos and health of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome assembly and annotation of a deep-diving pinniped, the northern elephant seal (Mirounga angustirostris)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The northern elephant seal (Mirounga angustirostris) is the largest pinniped species in the northern hemisphere. The species is classified as being of least conservation concern by the IUCN-a triumph of conservation efforts despite hunting pressure that nearly led to its extinction more than a century ago. The historical range of the northern elephant seal extended from Baja California to Alaska, but overexploitation caused a severe demographic collapse and genetic bottleneck, with only an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning enhanced MRI radiomics in predicting pathologic response of head and neck squamous carcinoma to neoadjuvant chemoimmunotherapy: a retrospective analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In conclusion, deep learning features from MRI images can augment traditional imaging analysis to uncover hidden predictive patterns reflecting responsiveness to NACI in HNSCC patients, and integration of different data types provides a more robust prediction strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preventing exotic pet beetle invasion with an improved lightweight and efficient pest detection model deployed on mobile devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: EPB-YOLO-PD offers an effective solution for real-time detection of exotic pet beetles at customs checkpoints. It enables rapid and accurate classification, effectively handling challenging scenarios such as incomplete morphological features and visually confusing backgrounds, and provides a replicable framework for intercepting other invasive species. © 2025 Society of Chemical Industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insight Into the Cellular Activities of Tranexamic Acid as an Option for Melasma Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Melasma and other hyperpigmentation disorders represent a significant challenge in dermatology. Tranexamic acid (TXA), traditionally known for its antifibrinolytic activity via inhibition of plasminogen activation, has recently emerged as a promising depigmenting agent. However, its cellular effects on skin cells involved in melanogenesis remain poorly understood. In this study, we investigated TXA's impact on melanocytes, keratinocytes, and inflammatory cells. TXA directly inhibited melanin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world prognosis of sporadic bilateral RCC: a propensity score-based comparison of synchronous and metachronous cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Synchronous BRCC was associated with poorer survival than the metachronous group. These findings may offer important insights for managing patients with BRCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metronidazole-Loaded Cyclodextrin Nanogels for Antibacterial Therapy and Microbiota Regulation in Periodontitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a methacrylamide β-cyclodextrin-based nanogel (MACD nGel) is developed to load the antimicrobial drug Metronidazole (MNZ) for topical delivery for the treatment of periodontitis. The developed MACD nGel is synthesized by free radical polymerization and successfully loaded with MNZ. The nGel/MNZ system is shown to be effective against the main causative organisms of periodontitis, Porphyromonas gingivalis (P. gingivalis) and Fusobacterium nucleatum (F. nucleatum), and shows...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomechanical Effects of Lateral Ankle Ligament Injury and Repair on the Midfoot and Hindfoot Joints]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This biomechanical study demonstrates that combined ATFL and CFL repair effectively restores near-normal stress distributions across midfoot and hindfoot joints, particularly optimizing load transfer in the subtalar and talonavicular joints. The findings integrate biomechanical evidence with clinical relevance, providing a foundation for refining ligament repair protocols in ankle instability treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic implications and correlates of plasma ADA2 activity and ADA2 variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We confirmed the utility of plasma ADA2 activity as a diagnostic assay and showed that the inflammatory phenotype of DADA2 occurred in cases with residual activity. In vitro findings illustrate potential interactions of ADA2 variants to synergistically disrupt protein function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic regulation of crude Sphallerocarpus gracilis polysaccharides and probiotics on intestinal flora and its immune-related metabolites in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings demonstrate the prebiotic capacity of CSGP to synergize with probiotics in regulating intestinal microecology and immunity, highlighting its potential application in functional fermented dairy products. © 2025 Society of Chemical Industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028152052&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>