<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:21:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Microbulbifer discodermiae</em> sp. nov. and <em>Microbulbifer jejuensis</em> sp. nov., isolated from marine sponges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two Gram-stain-negative, facultatively anaerobic, non-motile and rod-shaped bacterial strains, designated 2201CG32-9^(T) and 2304DJ12-6^(T), were isolated from marine sponges collected in the Republic of Korea. Both strains exhibited catalase and oxidase activities but tested negative for nitrate reduction and indole production. Strain 2201CG32-9^(T) showed optimal growth at 30 °C and pH 7.0-8.0 in the presence of 3% (w/v) NaCl, whereas strain 2304DJ12-6^(T) grew optimally at 25 °C, pH 8.0 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-stratified hypertension risk prediction: integrating genetic risk scores with clinical markers in Korean adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Age-specific integration of GRS with clinical markers such as BMI and ba-PWV significantly improves hypertension prediction, offering actionable thresholds for precision prevention across age groups. These models provide clinically actionable tools for precision prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoparticle-Stabilized Porous Composite Architectures for Ultrasound-Driven Triboelectric Energy Harvesters in Soft Implantable Electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wireless powering of implantable medical devices (IMDs) using triboelectric nanogenerators (TENGs) has gained attention as a sustainable and battery-free energy strategy. Ultrasound-driven TENGs (US-TENGs) offer favorable biocompatibility and deep tissue accessibility, but their practical application remains limited by unstable acoustic vibration, filler aggregation at low contents, and complex electrode integration. Here, we report a porous polyimide composite-based TENG (PPC-TENG) designed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defect-Mediated In Situ CNT Growth in Hollow Porous Carbon From ZIF-8/ZIF-67 Bilayers for Efficient and Stable ORR Catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rational design of carbon-based electrocatalysts with hierarchical porosity, graphitic domains, and optimized active sites is crucial for advancing the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR). Herein, a bilayer core-shell ZIF (PS@BCZ)-derived strategy is presented that enables the in situ growth of carbon nanotubes (CNTs) and uniform embedding of cobalt nanoparticles (Co NPs) within an N-doped hollow porous carbon matrix (CNT-Co/N-HPC). Sequential ZIF-8/ZIF-67 growth on polystyrene spheres, followed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing glycol-alkyl copolymerization to realize nonvolatile and biologically relevant synaptic behaviors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic electrochemical synaptic transistors (OESTs) are attracting growing attention for neuromorphic computing, yet their long-term stability remains constrained by uncontrolled ion dynamics. Previous studies have incorporated glycol side chains to facilitate ionic transport, but a systematic understanding of how copolymerization with hydrophobic alkyl units governs ion doping and retention is still lacking. Here, we establish a rational backbone-side chain copolymer design strategy that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Bioavailability of a Thionated IMiD Derivative Nanosuspension for Parkinson's Disease Targeting α-Synuclein]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This enhancement in bioavailability supports the formulation of NS as a promising strategy for CNS-targeted therapies, providing a strong rationale for further investigation into the efficacy of MTPOM-NS in the chronic treatment of PD, which will be the focus of future studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ORF3 Gene of Porcine Epidemic Diarrhea Virus Causes Nuclear and Morphological Distortions with Associated Cell Death]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is increasing research interest in the ORF3 accessory protein of PEDV as a critical element for viral virulence. Here, wild type ORF3 (ORF3(wt)) gene was constructed in pEGFP-C1 vector. Additionally, two truncation mutants, ORF3-N (1-98 amino acids [aa]) and ORF3-C (99-224 aa) were inserted in the same vector. Results of ORF3 expression revealed early cytoplasmic localization but 12 h after transfection, ORF3 accumulated around the nucleus, especially ORF3-N. This caused chromosome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiologic Characteristics of 1.4 Million Multiplex PCR Tests for 12 Urogenital and Sexually Transmitted Infection Pathogens in Korea (2021-2024)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sexually transmitted infections (STIs) remain a global health concern, but large-scale multiplex PCR surveillance data are limited. This study aimed to characterize sex- and age-specific distributions, temporal patterns, and co-infection dynamics of 12 urogenital and sexually transmitted infection (STI) pathogens in Korea. We retrospectively analyzed 1,399,431 multiplex PCR test records (902,713 females, 496,718 males) collected nationwide between 2021 and 2024. Positivity rates were stratified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amodiaquine Modulates Aggregation and Disassembly of Amyloid-β and Tau and Attenuates Neuroinflammatory Responses and Aβ Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder characterized by the accumulation of amyloid-β (Aβ) plaques and hyperphosphorylated tau tangles, which synergistically accelerate disease progression. Since Aβ plaques and tau tangles are key factors in the development of AD, dual-targeting of Aβ and tau aggregation represents a promising therapeutic strategy. Amodiaquine (AQ), a quinoline-based antimalarial, has recently attracted attention for its ability to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Lactobacillus</em>-Fermented <em>Centella asiatica</em> Extract Inhibits Airway Inflammation in Cigarette Smoke Extract/LPS-Induced Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Centella asiatica, a widely used medicinal herb in Oriental and increasingly Western medicine, is applied for wound healing, dermatological disorders, and gastrointestinal illness. We investigated the effects of fermented C. asiatica extract (FCAE), prepared with Lactobacillus, on airway inflammation in a murine model of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) induced by cigarette smoke extract (CSE) and lipopolysaccharide (LPS). CSE/LPS stimulation caused marked immune cell infiltration in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of the Carbonation Behavior of Cement Mortar Containing Interior Stone Sludge and Recycled Mask Fibers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the carbonation and mechanical behavior of cement mortar incorporating artificial interior stone (AIS) sludge and recycled mask fibers (RMFs). Sludge, derived from AIS waste, replaced 30 wt.% of fine aggregate, while RMF from polypropylene masks was added at 0-1 wt.% of cement. Specimens were cured under normal and carbonation conditions (10% CO(2), 25 °C, 60% RH) for 7 and 28 days. Carbonation curing improved compressive and flexural strengths by up to 28% and 88%,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of Low-Frequency Metasurface Microwave Absorption Filter with Composite Molding and Size Dependency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a lightweight metasurface microwave absorption filter (MMAF) designed for low-frequency stealth applications in the L-band. The metasurface is optimized using a genetic algorithm to achieve broadband absorption at subwavelength thickness. The fabricated MMAF consists of a glass fiber-reinforced plastic layer, a metasurface layer, and a dielectric layer with a size of 30 × 30 cm². It maintains a reflection coefficient below -10 dB in the frequency range of 1.01-1.78 GHz....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lumbar Interlaminar Ventral Epidural Injection Without Catheter at L5-S1 for Lumbosacral Radicular Pain: A Pilot Feasibility Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Lumbar interlaminar ventral epidural injection (LIVEI) offers a promising alternative to transforaminal epidural injection (TFEI) by enabling ventral epidural delivery while minimizing complication risks. While previous approaches often required catheter assistance, this pilot study evaluates the safety, technical feasibility, and early outcomes of a simplified LIVEI method at L5-S1 without catheter insertion. Materials and Methods: Twelve patients with lumbosacral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metastatic Patterns of Malignant Germ Cell Tumors Vary by Histologic Subtype and Primary Site]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Malignant germ cell tumors (GCTs) are rare but clinically significant neoplasms arising in gonadal and extragonadal sites. Malignant GCTs, divided into seminomatous and non-seminomatous subtypes, show diverse biological behavior. Although molecular studies have advanced understanding of their origins and genetic features, little is known about metastatic patterns due to their rarity and generally favorable outcomes. This study aimed to describe metastatic patterns of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Copy Number Alteration Profiling from Plasma cfDNA WES in Advanced NSCLC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circulating cell-free DNA (cfDNA) sequencing offers a minimally invasive approach for profiling tumor genomes, but detecting copy number alterations (CNAs) from cfDNA whole-exome sequencing (WES) remains technically challenging due to noise and guanine-cytosine (GC)-related bias. Building upon our previous study that characterized read count patterns in cfDNA WES data, we developed and evaluated an advanced pipeline for robust CNA detection in patients with advanced non-small cell lung cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Practice of Nursing Students in South Korea's Community Treatment Centers During COVID-19: A Descriptive Phenomenological Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study explored the lived experiences of nursing students in South Korea who participated in clinical practice at Community Treatment Centers (CTCs) during the COVID-19 pandemic. Methods: This study was designed as a qualitative study and applied Colaizzi's descriptive phenomenology. Semi-structured interviews were conducted with ten nursing students who practiced at CTCs for three to four weeks. Data were analyzed through Colaizzi's seven procedural steps to derive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Inhibition of Triple-Negative Breast Cancer by Acetylsalicylic Acid and Recombinant Human APE1/Ref-1 in a Mouse Xenograft Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC) is a highly aggressive subtype with limited therapeutic options due to the lack of estrogen, progesterone, and HER2 receptors. This study investigated the synergistic anticancer effects of recombinant human apurinic/apyrimidinic endonuclease 1/redox factor-1 (rhAPE1/Ref-1) and acetylsalicylic acid (ASA), a combination that has not been previously tested in vivo. Methods: We treated MDA-MB-231 TNBC cells with rhAPE1/Ref-1, ASA, or their combination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endothelial Dysfunction: From Pathophysiology to Novel Therapeutic Approaches 2.0]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endothelial dysfunction (ED) is a multifactorial pathological process characterized by the loss of the endothelial physiological function, which is essential for maintaining vascular homeostasis [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the Effectiveness of a Behavioral Activation-Based Digital App for Treatment of Depressive Symptoms: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Our research investigated how a smartphone application utilizing behavioral activation principles affects depression levels in young adult populations. A total of 67 participants aged 20-30 years with clinically significant depressive symptoms (CESD-11 ≥ 16) were divided into treatment (n = 31) and comparison conditions (n = 36) through randomization procedures. Participants in the experimental group engaged with a BA-based mobile application (Maummove) over an eight-week period, while those in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexible Bronchoscopic En Bloc Cryoextraction of Endobronchial Leiomyoma Using a 1.7-mm Cryoprobe: A Case Report with One-Year Follow-Up]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Clinical Significance: Endobronchial leiomyoma is a rare benign tumor of the respiratory tract, accounting for less than 2% of all benign pulmonary neoplasms. Most cases have been treated surgically or with endoscopic modalities such as laser or rigid bronchoscopy-assisted cryotherapy. Flexible bronchoscopic cryoextraction has been rarely reported, typically with 2.2-mm probes. Small-caliber cryoprobes (1.1- and 1.7-mm) have been validated for diagnostic transbronchial cryobiopsy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Multivariate Predictors of Headaches Attributed to Rhinosinusitis in Pediatric Patients: A Comparative Study with Migraine and Tension-Type Headache]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pediatric HRS shows distinct predictors-young age, acute severe headache, nasal and auditory symptoms, allergic history, and family history-despite overlap with migraine and TTH. Structured use of these predictors with otolaryngologic assessment may improve diagnostic accuracy, reduce misclassification, and avoid unnecessary neuroimaging or inappropriate therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Congenital Torticollis to Leigh Syndrome: A Case Report of Diagnostic Evolution in an Infant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leigh syndrome is a rare, progressive mitochondrial disorder of childhood. Early diagnosis is often challenging due to nonspecific clinical manifestations. We report a 1-month-old male infant initially referred for suspected congenital muscular torticollis who ultimately received a diagnosis of Leigh syndrome. Despite unremarkable perinatal history, he subsequently developed persistent feeding difficulties, recurrent vomiting, failure to thrive, and global developmental delay. Early neurological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superoxide Dismutase 3 Deficiency Disrupts the Regulation of Oxidative Stress Caused by Polystyrene Nanoplastics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanoplastics have been recognized as emerging pollutants posing potential risks to ecosystems and human health. They are now detected ubiquitously in the environment and even human tissues, where their small size allows for tissue accumulation and cellular penetration. Growing evidence links nanoplastics to oxidative stress, yet the specific contribution of extracellular accumulation to toxicity remains poorly understood. To address this, we used zebrafish, a transparent vertebrate model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DEG-by-Index Ratio Transformation Normalization with Blood RNA-Seq Enhances Early and Consistent Detection of Mouse Tumorigenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Variability in blood RNA-Seq data can obscure transcriptional changes that reflect tumor responses, and conventional normalization methods such as RLE/DESeq2 or TMM/edgeR often fail to capture these changes consistently. To address this challenge, we applied DiRT (DEG-by-index Ratio Transformation), a normalization and analysis strategy previously used in insect models, to 111 blood RNA-Seq datasets from mouse tumorigenesis models. DiRT achieved clearer separation between tumor and control...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The efficacy and safety of prasugrel in acute coronary syndrome: a propensity-matched Korean cohort study focused on age and weight of patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41299333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this Korean PS-matched ACS cohort, prasugrel, even at a reduced dose, was associated with superior effectiveness compared to clopidogrel without a significant increase in bleeding risk. These benefits were consistently observed in ELB patients. Our findings support the use of prasugrel in selected high-risk populations and offer guidance for clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41299333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Northern migration patterns and winter habitat use of hooded cranes (Grus monacha) in Suncheon Bay, South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41299280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Results suggest managing paddy fields and mudflats as a single ecological unit, protecting key stopover sites, and testing spatially dispersed supplementary feeding to buffer late-winter shortages. This study provides the fine-scale linkage between winter habitat use and migration in Hooded Cranes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41299280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Device-level nonlinearity and temporal memory in optoelectronic reservoir computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reservoir computing (RC) has emerged as a promising computational paradigm for processing temporally correlated and nonlinear data with low training cost. Among various physical implementations, optoelectronic devices provide a unique opportunity to directly interface light with nonlinear dynamical systems, enriching the reservoir state space through device-intrinsic responses. Light can encode information in wavelength, intensity, and pulse duration, and stimulate multiple nodes in parallel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease and adverse pregnancy outcomes: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MASLD, MetALD, and ALD were independently associated with increased risks of apos, with risk further amplified by a greater number of CMRFs. These findings underscore the importance of enhanced prenatal management for female with pre-existing SLD, particularly those with multiple CMRFs, to mitigate the risk of apos.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three-Way Decomposition for Applied Health Equity Research: A Practical Tutorial to Understand and Address Inequalities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mediation analysis is essential for understanding causal mechanisms and designing effective policy interventions. This paper explains a comprehensive framework for implementing VanderWeele's (2009) three-way decomposition using natural effect models (NEM), focusing on its application in health equity research. While three-way decomposition helps social epidemiologists understand how social exposures influence health outcomes through differential mediator effects, its implementation through NEM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of incidental low-dose radiation on abscopal responses after stereotactic body radiotherapy in patients with metastatic cancer: a retrospective real-world analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stepwise Ligand-Exchange Strategy for the High-Yield Synthesis of Water-Soluble, Metal-Doped MAg<sub>24</sub> Nanoclusters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Water-soluble gold nanoclusters (NCs) with diverse nuclearities and protecting ligands have been extensively investigated as luminescent probes for biosensing and bioimaging. In contrast, the development of water-soluble silver NCs has progressed far more slowly, primarily because synthetic routes for producing stable Ag NCs with a broad range of protecting ligands are lacking. Herein, we present an efficient, high-yield stepwise ligand-exchange strategy that addresses this challenge, enabling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Negative regulation of reassortant canine influenza virus replication and key site identification in porcine and ferret bronchial epithelial cell lines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The segmented nature and high mutability of the influenza virus RNA genome facilitate rapid mutation and reassortment, allowing the virus to breach host barriers and migrate between different species, potentially leading to unpredictable influenza outbreaks. With dogs emerging as new natural hosts for influenza virus, vigilant surveillance and scientific prevention strategies are imperative. Here, based on our previous isolation of 21 strains, which are reassortments of the canine influenza...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Kinetics and Dual-Interfacial Stability in High-Areal-Loading Electrodes for Lithium Metal Batteries via Crosstalk-Active Polymer-Functionalized Carbon Nanotubes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the rapid shift toward sustainable energy systems, battery technologies offering high energy densities and long cycle life are critical. Lithium metal batteries (LMBs) are central to achieving high energy storage required by global sustainability efforts, yet their practical deployment faces critical limitations, including dendritic lithium deposition and challenges associated with thick cathode structures. To simultaneously overcome these issues, this research develops a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2D Material-Based Memristor Arrays for Flexible and Thermally Stable Neuromorphic Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The practical implementation of 2D material-based memristors for various applications, such as neuromorphic computing and flexible electronics, faces several challenges in scalability and thermal durability. Here, a large-area, flexible, and thermally durable electrochemical metallization memristor array is demonstrated based on an engineered Al(2)O(3)/MoS(2)/graphene heterostructure. A thin Al(2)O(3) layer and graphene serve as dual barriers, effectively suppressing the unintentional metal ion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Water Retention Ability of the Dermis Following Polynucleotide Intradermal Injection Using a Water Distribution Model: Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DNA-based Bi-layered effervescent ejecting microneedle (BEE MN) for glucose-responsive insulin delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microneedle-based drug delivery systems have gained increasing attention as minimally invasive alternatives to conventional injections, particularly for chronic diseases like diabetes. However, their limited drug-loading capacity and passive diffusion-based release mechanisms pose challenges in achieving precise and efficient drug administration. In this study, we present a novel bi-layered effervescent ejecting microneedle (BEE MN) system inspired by the penetration and retention mechanisms of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Dual-Targeted Therapy with Fucoidan-Functionalized Thrombolytic Discoidal Microparticles for Pulmonary Thromboembolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed systems may offer an alternative to conventional systemic thrombolysis coupled with adjunctive pharmacological interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the antimicrobial properties of synthetic tetrahydro-2<em>H</em>-1,3,5-thiadiazine-2-thiones (THTTs) through <em>in vitro</em> and <em>in silico</em> antileishmanial and antibacterial studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infectious diseases represent a significant health concern due to their high rates of morbidity and mortality. Despite significant advances in the understanding of the pathogenic infection, existing therapies to control those infections are still unsatisfactory. Herein, a total of 18 alkyl/aryl/aralkylamines or amino acids attached 1,3,5-thiadiazine-2-thiones (4a-i, 5a-g, 6 and 7) were synthesized via one pot domino synthesis and assessed their in vitro leishmanicidal and bactericidal potential....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rushed health workforce reform in South Korea: a Kingdon's multiple streams framework analysis of the 2024 medical school quota expansion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Quota expansion alone is unlikely to resolve disparities. Sustainable reform requires transparent forecasting, targeted incentives, capacity for priority specialties/regions, and participatory governance with multi-stakeholder collaboration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comparative analysis of biologics market dynamics in 12 countries: (Bio)similar and sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The introduction of biosimilars was significantly associated with reductions in the prices and expenditures of biologics in high-income countries. This underscores the potential role of biosimilars in supporting the long-term sustainability of the healthcare system.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Herbal Combination of <em>Angelica gigas</em>, <em>Zingiber officinale</em>, and <em>Aconitum carmichaeli</em> Alleviates High Fat Diet-Induced Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease in Mice Through NRF2-Mediated Regulation of Adipogenesis and Non-Shivering Thermogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity is a complex metabolic disorder characterized by excessive fat accumulation and is closely associated with non-alcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD), a condition that increases the risk of metabolic complications such as insulin resistance, type 2 diabetes, and cardiovascular diseases. JI017 is a recently optimized multi-herbal formula composed of Angelica gigas, Zingiber officinale , and processed Aconitum carmichaeli. Clinical records of these three herbs indicate their potentially...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequencing BCMA- and GPRC5D-targeting immunotherapies in multiple myeloma: Practical guidance from the European Myeloma Network]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The treatment landscape of heavily pretreated relapsed/refractory MM has changed considerably in recent years with the introduction of novel BCMA- and GPRC5D-directed immunotherapies, including CAR T-cell therapy, bispecific antibodies (BsAbs), and antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs). Treatment selection and sequencing become increasingly complex with the broad range of therapeutic options. In this review, the European Myeloma Network provides recommendations on how to best incorporate these novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence for pediatric height prediction using large-scale longitudinal body composition data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our model produces accurate and personalized growth curves, incorporating explainable AI techniques for enhanced clinical understanding. This method advances pediatric growth assessment and provides robust clinical decision support. Despite limitations including the absence of handwrist radiography comparison and Korean population specificity, our approach demonstrates significant potential for early identification of growth disorders and optimization of growth outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Efficacy of Real-Time Artificial Intelligence-Assisted Colonoscopy in Colorectal Polyp Detection: A Prospective Multicenter Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Real-time CADe-assisted colonoscopy significantly increased PDR and ADR and proved to be a strong independent predictor of adenoma detection (cris.nih.go.kr, KCT0009664).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and Tolerability of Anti-Tumor Necrosis Factor Alpha Therapy in Refractory Intestinal Behçet's Disease: A Large Single-Center Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Anti-TNF-α therapy could be an effective and tolerable option for refractory intestinal BD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structured Integration of an Artificial Intelligence-Based System for the Optical Diagnosis of Colorectal Polyps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Integrating CADx with the 3-second rule significantly enhances the performance of endoscopists in the optical diagnosis of colorectal polyps, with the greatest benefit observed among novice endoscopists.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Bowel Cleansing with Mini S-Oral Sulfate Tablet versus the Conventional Oral Sulfate Tablet: A Prospective, Randomized, Investigator-Blinded, Multicenter, Noninferior, Phase 3 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared with conventional OST, the mini S-OST split dose showed excellent efficacy, comparable safety and tolerability, with less gastric injury (ClinicalTrial.gov identifier NCT06287606).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Field Evaluation of a Novel Combined Vaccine Against Porcine Circovirus Types 2a/d, Mycoplasma hyopneumoniae and Mycoplasma hyorhinis With an Emphasis on Growth Performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The combined vaccine demonstrated strong efficacy under field conditions, providing protection against subclinical PCV2 infection, enzootic pneumonia caused by M. hyopneumoniae, and polyserositis caused by M. hyorhinis. These findings support its potential as an effective intervention for improving both health and productivity in swine herds.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practice of Cytopathology in Korea: A 40-Year Evolution Through Standardization, Digital Transformation, and Global Partnership]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Over four decades, Korea has advanced from a limited cytology service to a global model of digital and AI-integrated cytopathology. Since the founding of the Korean Society for Cytopathology (KSC) in 1986, a nationwide framework has been established-encompassing standardized practices, systematic education for specialists and cytotechnologists, and nationwide cervical screening through the National Cancer Control Program. A mandatory Quality Assurance Program (QAP) launched in 2005 ensured...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National trends in the prevalence of hypertension and diabetes stratified by sleep duration in South Korea, 2009-2022: A nationwide cross-sectional study: Trends and association of sleep duration in hypertension and diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increase in sleep-related issues is associated with various health problems, particularly hypertension and diabetes. Therefore, this study aims to address these gaps in the literature by analyzing the relationship between sleep duration and the prevalence of hypertension and diabetes. This study analyzed the association between hypertension, diabetes, and sleep duration using the Korea Community Health Survey database from 2009 to 2022. The study used weighted linear regression models to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global epidemiology of vaccine-associated intussusception in children and adolescents, 1968 to 2024: An international pharmacovigilance study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rotavirus vaccine associated intussusception has been investigated to some extent, limited research exists on intussusception caused by all vaccines from a comprehensive, global perspective. Thus, this study aimed to investigate the global burden of vaccine-associated intussusception using a comprehensive pharmacovigilance database. This study was conducted using data from the global pharmacovigilance database from 1968 to 2024. Reports of intussusception were identified by MedDRA code and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global burden of TNF-α inhibitors associated demyelinating diseases: A global disproportionality analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite case reports linking tumor necrosis factor-alpha (TNF-α) inhibitors to demyelinating diseases, large-scale epidemiological evidence is limited. We aimed to investigate this signal detection using a global pharmacovigilance database. This study identified reports of TNF-α inhibitor-associated demyelinating disease utilizing a global pharmacovigilance database spanning from 1968 to 2024. Five TNF-α inhibitors (infliximab, adalimumab, etanercept, certolizumab pegol, and golimumab) were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Myokines Serve as Supporters of Muscle-Brain Connectivity in Obesity and Type 2 Diabetes? Potential of Exercise and Nutrition Interventions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This review outlines current evidence on myokine alterations observed in OB and T2DM and discusses how exercise- and nutrition-based approaches may modulate the muscle-brain axis to mitigate metabolic dysfunction and preserve cognitive health. Targeting beneficial myokine pathways through tailored lifestyle interventions represents a promising avenue to support both skeletal muscle and neurocognitive function in individuals with metabolic disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Association Between Menopausal Transition and Obstructive Sleep Apnea with Effect Modification by Salt Intake: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: As high salt intake may increase obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) risk through fluid retention and upper airway narrowing during sleep, we aimed to determine whether dietary salt intake modified the association between menopausal transition and the risk of OSA. Methods: Between 2014 and 2018, we conducted a longitudinal study of 2572 women aged 42-52 years at the Kangbuk Samsung Hospital Total Healthcare Center. The participants were followed up until the end of 2024. OSA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rutin as a Circadian Modulator Preserves Skeletal Muscle Mitochondrial Function and Reduces Oxidative Stress to Protect Against D-Galactose-Induced Aging In Vitro and In Vivo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Skeletal muscle aging is characterized by impaired myogenic differentiation, disrupted circadian rhythms, elevated oxidative stress, and mitochondrial dysfunction. Rutin, a natural flavonoid with antioxidant properties, has been suggested to mitigate aging processes; however, its effects on circadian regulation and muscle homeostasis remain unclear. Methods: In vitro, differentiated C2C12 myotubes were treated with D-galactose (D-gal, 20 g/L) with or without rutin (20 μM). In vivo,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Pregnancy Nutritional Adequacy and Subsequent Gestational Diabetes Risk by Body Mass Index: A Prospective Cohort Study of 2227 Korean Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study evaluated the association between nutrient intake adequacy during early pregnancy and gestational diabetes mellitus (GDM) risk through a prospective cohort study of Korean pregnant women. Methods: A total of 2227 singleton pregnant women were included in this study. Dietary assessment was conducted once during early pregnancy enrollment using the 24 h dietary recall method. The collected dietary data were analyzed using the CAN-Pro Korean food composition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health State Utility Associated with Parenteral Nutrition Requirement in Patients with Short Bowel Syndrome and Intestinal Failure in Korea: A Vignette-Based Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Short bowel syndrome (SBS) is the leading cause of intestinal failure (IF) that often requires long-term parenteral nutrition (PN). Extended PN results in severe complications and reduced quality of life (QoL). This study aimed to evaluate the QoL utility weights associated with PN duration using vignettes. Methods: We developed detailed scenarios and descriptions to represent eight hypothetical health states, reflecting variations in PN frequency in both pediatric and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of a VSV-Based Pseudovirus Platform for In Vitro and In Vivo Evaluation of Nipah Vaccine-Induced Neutralizing Responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Nipah virus (NiV) is a zoonotic pathogen characterized by high fatality rates and pandemic potential, whereby there is an urgent need for developing safe and effective vaccines. However, the evaluation of NiV vaccine-induced immunity is hindered by the requirement of Biosafety Level-4 (BSL-4) containment. In this study, we developed a recombinant vesicular stomatitis virus (rVSV)-based pseudovirus-expressing NiV fusion (F) and attachment (G) glycoproteins using a luciferase reporter gene for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Genomics of Two Newly Sequenced Rodent-Derived and One Previously Reported Tick-Derived <em>Borrelia garinii</em> Strains from South Korea Reveals Plasmid Variation and Virulence Gene Diversity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Borrelia garinii is a spirochete associated with Lyme borreliosis and is widely distributed across Eurasia. Although its genomic features have been well characterized in Europe, genomic data from East Asian isolates remain limited. Two B. garinii strains, HN13 and HN18, were isolated from a wild rodent (Apodemus agrarius) in South Korea and subjected to whole-genome sequencing and comparative genomic analysis. Their genomic features were compared with those of a tick-derived Korean strain 935...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Respiratory Microbiome of Carbapenem-Resistant <em>Acinetobacter baumannii</em> Ventilator-Associated Pneumonia: A Pilot Study from the Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ventilator-associated pneumonia (VAP) is one of the most common hospital-acquired infections. Several studies have explored the potential role of the lung microbiome as a biomarker for identifying and predicting the prognosis of VAP. However, research on the respiratory microbiome in individuals with VAP caused by carbapenem-resistant Acinetobacter baumannii (CRAB) remains limited. Therefore, we aimed to analyze the respiratory microbiome of patients with CRAB VAP. Respiratory specimens were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Empirical and Definitive Antibiotics on Pediatric Febrile Urinary Tract Infection Caused by ESBL-Producing Enterobacterales]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the clinical impact of empirical antibiotic susceptibility on urinary tract infection (UTI) caused by extended-spectrum β-lactamase-producing Enterobacterales (ESBL-PEs) is limited, the role of definitive antibiotics remains unclear. This study evaluated therapeutic outcomes and recurrence in children with febrile UTI caused by ESBL-PE, focusing on pathogen susceptibility to empirical and definitive antibiotics. Medical records of 376 UTI episodes caused by ESBL-PE in children aged <10...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FP-ZOO: Fast Patch-Based Zeroth Order Optimization for Black-Box Adversarial Attacks on Vision Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks have outperformed conventional methods in various fields such as image recognition, natural language processing, and speech recognition. In particular, vision models are widely applied to real-world domains including medical image analysis, autonomous driving, smart factories, and security surveillance. However, these models are vulnerable to adversarial attacks, which pose serious threats to safety and reliability. Among different attack types, this study focuses on evasion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Golf Swing Analysis Framework Based on Efficient Similarity Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With advances in computing power and deep learning, image-based pose estimation has become a viable tool for quantitative motion analysis. Compared to sensor-based systems, vision-based approaches are cost-effective, portable, and easy to deploy. However, when applied to golf swings, conventional similarity measures often fail to match expert perception, as they rely on static, frame-wise posture comparisons and require strict temporal alignment. We propose a Dynamic Motion Similarity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing Medical Training with Mixed Reality and Haptic Feedback Simulator for Acupuncture Needling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditional acupuncture training often lacks consistent, objective feedback, while current extended reality (XR) solutions rarely include quantitative assessment. This study developed and evaluated a feedback-enabled mixed reality (MR) acupuncture simulator to improve skill acquisition through depth-responsive guidance. The system, used on Microsoft HoloLens 2, combines a MetaHuman-based virtual patient with expert-designed acupoint geometries. It provides depth-dependent vibrotactile cues via a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-Agent Deep Reinforcement Learning for Collision-Free Posture Control of Multi-Manipulators in Shared Workspaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In multi-manipulator systems operating within shared workspaces, achieving collision-free posture control is challenging due to high degrees of freedom and complex inter-manipulator interactions. Traditional motion planning methods often struggle with scalability and computational efficiency in such settings, motivating the need for learning-based approaches. This paper presents a multi-agent deep reinforcement learning (MADRL) framework for real-time collision-free posture control of multiple...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Effects, Phytochemistry, Drug Interactions, and Safety Profile of <em>Foeniculum vulgare</em> Mill. (Fennel): A Comprehensive Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Cardiovascular diseases remain the leading cause of mortality worldwide. According to the World Heart Federation, more than 500 million people were living with cardiovascular diseases in 2021. In this context, the use of medicinal plants has become increasingly widespread in populations as a preventive strategy against cardiovascular disorders. Foeniculum vulgare Mill., commonly known as fennel, is an aromatic and medicinal plant recognized for its beneficial properties in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design, Synthesis, and Biological Evaluation of 5',7-Disubstituted 7-Deaza-adenosine Analogues as Irreversible Pan-FGFR Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Fibroblast growth factor receptors (FGFRs) are frequently dysregulated in diverse cancers and represent important therapeutic targets. Here, we report the design and synthesis of a novel nucleoside-based scaffold which enables irreversible pan-FGFR inhibition as a potential anticancer strategy. Methods: A series of nucleoside analogues was synthesized and assessed through structure-activity relationship studies. Structural analyses, including X-ray co-crystallography and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population Pharmacokinetics of Radotinib in Healthy Volunteers and Patients with Chronic Myeloid Leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Radotinib is a second-generation tyrosine kinase inhibitor (TKI) that has been used for treatment of chronic myeloid leukemia (CML). This study was performed for the first time to characterize the pharmacokinetics of radotinib, identify the factors contributing to pharmacokinetic variabilities and explore alternative dosing regimens. Methods: A total of 640 plasma concentration-time datapoints obtained from 47 participants were evaluated using nonlinear mixed-effects...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determination of Nitrosamine Drug Substance-Related Impurities Derived from Nortriptyline and Sertraline Using LC-MS/MS: A Comparative Evaluation of Chromatographic Separation and Pharmaceutical Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Nitrosamine drug substance-related impurities (NDSRIs) are a class of potent genotoxic impurities that pose a critical risk to patient safety, thereby necessitating the stringent control of pharmaceutical products. Nortriptyline (NORT) and sertraline (SERT) are two widely prescribed antidepressants that form highly potent NDSRIs, N-nitroso-nortriptyline (NNORT) and N-nitroso-sertraline (NSERT), respectively. Despite these risks, a substantial gap exists in terms of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening-Identified Oxazole-4-Carboxamide KB-2777 Exhibits In Vitro Anti-Coronavirus Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Direct-acting antivirals vary by lineage and face rapid resistance. We identified the oxazole-4-carboxamide lead KB-2777 and aimed to define its in vitro activity across α/β-coronaviruses, time-of-addition (TOA) profile, host-response signatures, and combinability with benchmark DAAs. Methods: We tested KB-2777 (≤25 μM) against HCoV-NL63 (LLC-MK2), HCoV-OC43 (Vero E6; MRC-5 for transcript profiling), and PEDV (Vero E6). We quantified extracellular viral RNA by RT-qPCR at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Nanosystems and Emerging Therapies: Innovations in Tuberculosis Treatment and Drug Resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis (TB) remains a significant worldwide health challenge due to the limitations of conventional treatments and the rising incidence of drug-resistant Mycobacterium tuberculosis strains. This review consolidates the advancements in nanotechnology-based therapeutics, inhalable formulations, CRISPR-Cas tools, host-directed therapies (HDTs), and nanoparticle-based vaccine development aimed at enhancing TB management. Novel nanocarriers such as liposomes, solid-lipid nanoparticles (SLNs),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoparticle-Mediated Nose-to-Brain Delivery for Ischemic Stroke Therapy: Preclinical Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ischemic stroke remains a major cause of mortality and long-term disability, yet current therapeutic strategies are largely limited to reperfusion approaches such as intravenous thrombolysis and thrombectomy, which are constrained by narrow treatment windows and the risk of complications. Moreover, the blood-brain barrier (BBB) severely restricts drug penetration into the injured brain, limiting the translation of promising neuroprotective agents into clinical success. Intranasal (IN) delivery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[8-Hydroxy-2-Anilino-1,4-Naphthoquinone Prevents Against Ferroptotic Neuronal Death and Kainate-Induced Epileptic Seizures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Ferroptosis, an iron-dependent form of regulated cell death characterized by excessive lipid peroxidation, has been implicated in various acute and chronic brain disorders, including epilepsy. Although 1,4-naphthoquinone derivatives have been reported to regulate ferroptosis, their mechanistic roles in the nervous system remain underexplored. Here, we investigated the protective effects of 8-hydroxy-2-anilino-1,4-naphthoquinone (8-HANQ) on ferroptotic neuronal death in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved Intestinal Permeation of Cyclosporin a by FCIGRL-Modified Tight Junction Modulator in Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: Cyclosporin A (CsA) is an immunosuppressive drug that is highly effective. CsA, similar to other drugs with limited oral bioavailability due to poor membrane permeability, requires the use of absorption enhancers in its formulations. Phe-Cys-Ile-Gly-Arg-Leu (FCIGRL-OH), a peptide fragment of Zonula occludens toxin (ZOT), has been studied for its potential to enhance drug absorption by regulating intercellular tight junctions. This study aimed to evaluate the effects of four novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding the Dual Defense: Mechanistic Insights into Antioxidant and Anti-Inflammatory Phytochemicals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic diseases such as diabetes, cardiovascular disease, neurodegeneration, and cancer share a common pathogenic thread: they are driven by excessive oxidative stress and unchecked inflammatory responses [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Pyrethroid Exposure Levels and Obesity/Cardiovascular Indicators in Korean Adults: Focused on the 2nd National Environmental Health Survey (2012-2014)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study evaluated associations between urinary 3-phenoxybenzoic acid (3-PBA), a metabolite of pyrethroids, and cardiometabolic indicators in a nationally representative sample of Korean adults using data from the 2nd Korean National Environmental Health Survey (KoNEHS 2012-2014). Methods: Urinary 3-PBA concentrations were creatinine-adjusted; participants with urinary creatinine < 0.3 or > 3.0 g/L were excluded. Associations with triglycerides, BMI, HDL cholesterol,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toxicokinetic Characterization of MDM Hydantoin via Stable Metabolite DMH: Population Modeling for Predicting Dermal Formaldehyde Formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MDM hydantoin (MDMH), a formaldehyde-releasing preservative widely used in cosmetics, poses potential health risks due to its conversion to formaldehyde and systemically absorbed metabolites. Current safety assessments lack quantitative exposure data due to rapid degradation of MDMH in biological matrices. In the present study, we developed a validated LC-MS/MS assay for simultaneous determination of MDMH and its stable metabolite DMH in rat plasma, and characterized their toxicokinetics using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biocompatibility and Safety of 3D Printing Resins for Orthodontic Aligners: A Critical Review of Current Evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orthodontic aligners 3D-printed in resin currently provide a viable alternative to thermoformed ones. However, concerns have been raised regarding their biocompatibility. This review addressed the available scientific evidence on the biological properties of marketed resins for 3D printing of orthodontic aligners, encompassing cytotoxicity, estrogenicity, biofilm formation, and oral soft tissues reactions. A comprehensive literature search of several databases was conducted and PRISMA guidelines...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of High-Temperature Stress on Fatty Acid Composition and Undecylprodiginine Biosynthesis in <em>Streptomyces coelicolor</em> M511]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Actinomycetes are a representative group of bacteria that inhabit soil; in particular, Streptomyces coelicolor M511 produces actinorhodin and undecylprodiginine. Among them, undecylprodiginine has antibiotic and immunosuppression activity and is a secondary metabolite with high potential applications in biotechnological and pharmaceutical fields. High temperature stress (37 °C) reduced the biosynthesis of undecylprodiginine and induced specific branched chain alkylprodiginine derivatives,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Paraburkholderia suaedae</em> sp. nov., a Potential Plant Growth-Promoting Bacterium Isolated from the Halophyte <em>Suaeda japonica</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel bacterial strain was isolated from the roots of Suaeda japonica, a halophytic plant inhabiting tidal zones. Phylogenetic, genomic, and phenotypic analyses identified the isolate as a novel species within the genus Paraburkholderia, for which the name Paraburkholderia suaedae sp. nov. is proposed. The strain exhibits multiple plant growth-promoting traits, including the production of 1-aminocyclopropane-1-carboxylic acid, indole-3-acetic acid, and siderophore, along with the ability to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Study on Shifts in Human Skin Microbiome During Antarctica Expeditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The human skin microbiome plays a crucial role in maintaining skin health by acting as a barrier against pathogens and modulating immune regulation. This case study investigates the skin microbiome of two healthy Korean male individuals in their 20s during Antarctic expeditions, focusing on microbial changes, reversion to pre-expedition states, and the influence of environmental and lifestyle factors. Notable microbial alterations were observed, including increases in Pseudomonadota and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gamma-Ray and Thermal Neutron Shielding of Fe-Based Bilayer Composites with a Boron-Enriched Matrix and Tungsten Surface Coatings: Lead Benchmarks Included]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the design and experimental evaluation of Fe-B-Si-based bilayer composites engineered for dual shielding against gamma rays and thermal neutrons. The materials integrate a boron-enriched amorphous Fe matrix with surface coatings of high-Z fillers-lead (Pb) and tungsten (W)-dispersed in an epoxy resin. W or Pb powders (20-40 µm) were dispersed in epoxy resin at a high filler loading (60-70 wt% metal, approximately several tens to one by weight). This ensured a dense and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacial Gap Prediction in Laser Welding of Pure Copper Overlap Joints Using Multiple Sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a novel approach was proposed for predicting the interfacial gap in copper overlap joints by using deep learning and multi-sensor fusion. In this method, an image sensor, a spectrometer, and optical sensors tomography (OCT) sensors were used to develop and validate deep learning models under various gap conditions. The results revealed that the variation in melt pool dimensions, changes in keyhole behavior, intensity variations at specific wavelengths, and keyhole depth derived...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Configuration Effects of Freestanding TiO<sub>2</sub> Nanotube Arrays on Power Conversion Efficiency in Dye-Sensitized Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dye-sensitized solar cells (DSSCs) are known for their excellent low-light performance, cost-effectiveness, and flexibility. The photoanode has a crucial role in enhancing the overall performance of DSSCs and can be modified with different nanostructures. This study explores the impact of photoanode structure on the power conversion efficiency (PCE) of DSSCs, where four configurations of freestanding TiO(2) nanotube arrays (f-TNAs), closed-up, closed-down, open-up, and open-down, were employed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning Methods for the Prediction of Intraoperative Hypotension with Biosignal Waveforms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Intraoperative hypotension (IOH) is of great importance in preventing diseases such as postoperative myocardial infarction, acute kidney injury, and mortality. This study aimed to develop and validate machine learning and deep learning models that predict IOH using both biosignals and personalized clinical information for each patient. Materials and Methods: In this retrospective observational study, we used the VitalDB open dataset, which included intraoperative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Visual Grade and Hounsfield Unit Predict Adequate Bone Strength for Cementless Total Knee Arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: The use of cementless total knee arthroplasty (TKA) is increasing, but established methods for assessing bone quality to prevent early failure remain undefined. Current preoperative assessments using central bone mineral density (BMD) do not accurately reflect peripheral bone quality, and intraoperative evaluation is subjective. This study aimed to establish objective assessment methods by analyzing the correlations between a novel visual grading system, CT Hounsfield...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Ultrasonographic Parameter for Diagnosing Carpal Tunnel Syndrome: The Median Nerve-to-Ulnar Artery Cross-Sectional Area Ratio]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Carpal Tunnel Syndrome (CTS) is the most common entrapment neuropathy. Ultrasonography is a widely used diagnostic method for CTS, and the median-to-ulnar nerve cross-sectional area ratio (MUR) is a well-known parameter. However, the ulnar nerve may be affected by various conditions of the median nerve; therefore, we considered finding further parameters. The aim of the study is to identify the correlation between the median nerve-to-ulnar artery cross-sectional area...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Clinical Outcomes of Ulcerative Colitis with Concurrent Endoscopic and Histologic Remission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Therapeutic goals for ulcerative colitis (UC) have expanded beyond symptom control to include mucosal and histological healing. However, the long-term prognostic value of achieving both targets remains uncertain, particularly in Asian populations. This study aimed to evaluate long-term outcomes and relapse predictors in patients with UC who achieved both endoscopic and histologic remission. Materials and Methods: This prospective observational study consecutively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Embolization with Quick-Soluble Gelatin Sponge Particles for Lower Gastrointestinal Bleeding: A Multicenter Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Transarterial embolization (TAE) serves as a valuable alternative for gastrointestinal bleeding when endoscopy fails or is inaccessible. Quick-soluble gelatin sponge particles (QS-GSPs) dissolve rapidly and may reduce ischemic complications compared to permanent embolic agents. This study evaluated the safety and effectiveness of TAE using QS-GSPs for acute lower gastrointestinal bleeding. Materials and Methods: This retrospective multicenter study analyzed patients...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indications of Clinical Application of L5 Laminar Hook for the Surgical Correction of Degenerative Sagittal Imbalance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: The selection of the optimal distal level of fusion in long-level fusion surgery remains controversial. Fusion ending at L5 preserves motion but increases the risk of L5-S1 disc degeneration. The L5 laminar hook has been introduced to enhance distal fixation, but its indications and clinical effects remain unclear. This study aimed to investigate the indication of the L5 laminar hook and its effect on adjacent segment degeneration when performing long-level fusion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Neurokinin-1 Receptor Antagonists on Experimental Postoperative Adhesion: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis with Trial Sequential Analysis of Preclinical Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Postoperative adhesions are a major surgical concern. Preclinical studies of neurokinin-1 receptor antagonists (NK-1RAs) have reported inconsistent findings. We conducted a systematic review and meta-analysis with trial sequential analysis (TSA) to evaluate whether NK-1RAs prevent postoperative adhesions. Materials and Methods: We searched MEDLINE (via PubMed), EMBASE (via Ovid), Web of Science, and Google Scholar for animal studies assessing NK-1RAs applied to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prolonged Corrected QT Interval Is Associated with Lower Incidence of Maternal Hypotension During Spinal Anesthesia in Cesarean Delivery: A Prospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Spinal anesthesia is a common anesthetic method for cesarean delivery. However, it is associated with spinal hypotension, which can negatively impact both the mother and the fetus. We hypothesized that parturients with preoperatively prolonged corrected QT interval (QTc) would have a lower incidence of developing spinal hypotension. Materials and Methods: This prospective observational study analyzed eighty-five parturients undergoing cesarean delivery. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physical Activity Levels in Kazakhstan: A Cross-Sectional Nationwide Study on Demographic, Socioeconomic, and Regional Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Physical inactivity contributes to high rates of cardiovascular disease, diabetes, and obesity in Kazakhstan, yet national data remain scarce. The primary objective of this study was to assess the level of physical activity among the adult population of Kazakhstan. The secondary objectives were to identify demographic, socioeconomic, and regional factors associated with physical activity, to determine risk groups, and to develop recommendations aimed at increasing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of Sarcopenic Obesity Screening Tools: A Cross-Sectional Analysis Based on ESPEN and EASO Criteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Sarcopenic obesity, characterized by sarcopenia and obesity, is associated with adverse outcomes. The recent consensus from the European Society for Clinical Nutrition and Metabolism (ESPEN) and the European Association for the Study of Obesity (EASO) proposed a diagnostic algorithm (screening, diagnosis, and staging) for sarcopenic obesity. However, the effectiveness of recommended screening tools for sarcopenic obesity remains unclear. This study aimed to assess the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lower Myeloperoxidase-ANCA Titres at Diagnosis Are Associated with End-Stage Kidney Disease Progression During Follow-Up in Rituximab-Treated Patients with Microscopic Polyangiitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: To investigate whether myeloperoxidase (MPO)-antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody (ANCA) titres at diagnosis are associated with the risk of end-stage kidney disease (ESKD) progression in patients with microscopic polyangiitis (MPA) treated with rituximab. Materials and Methods: This retrospective cohort study included 34 patients with MPA who received rituximab. Clinical data, including MPO-ANCA titres at diagnosis and ESKD progression during follow-up, were assessed....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Burden of Esophageal Cancer and Its Correlation with Dietary, Metabolic, and Behavioral Risk Factors in 204 Countries and Territories: Results from the Global Burden of Disease Study 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Esophageal cancer (EC) remains a major global public health challenge due to its aggressiveness and poor survival rates. Therefore, this study aims to summarize the incidence, mortality, prevalence, and global burden of EC based on sex, age, and geographical divisions and to investigate the correlation of some risk factors including the Sociodemographic Index (SDI) and important health indicators to identify high-risk populations. Materials and Methods: We extracted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking the Cu-Co Interplay: Electrodeposited Spinel Co<sub>2</sub>CuO<sub>4</sub> as a High-Performance Hydrogen Evolution Catalyst]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing cost-effective and durable electrocatalysts with high hydrogen evolution efficiency remains a critical challenge for sustainable energy conversion. Herein, spinel-type Co(2)CuO(4) and Co(3)O(4) nanosheet electrodes were fabricated directly on Ni foam via a simple electrodeposition route and evaluated for the alkaline hydrogen evolution reaction (HER) in 1.0 M KOH. Structural and surface analyses confirmed the formation of phase-pure, porous, and highly interconnected nanosheet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cryopreserved Tissue Biospecimens Offer Superior Quality for Whole-Genome Sequencing of Various Cancers Compared to Paired Formalin-Fixed Paraffin-Embedded Tissues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Whole-genome sequencing (WGS) is integral to precision oncology, yet most cancer biospecimens used for WGS are formalin-fixed paraffin-embedded (FFPE) due to their widespread availability in clinical practice. However, FFPE processing can degrade DNA quality. This study compares WGS outcomes from matched cryopreserved (CP) and FFPE tumor samples, hypothesizing that CP tissues yield superior sequencing quality and variant detection. Fifty matched pairs of CP and FFPE tumor samples spanning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Plankton to Primates: How VSP Sequence Diversity Shapes Voltage Sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Voltage-sensing phosphatases (VSPs) provide a conserved framework for dissecting the mechanics of voltage sensing and for engineering genetically encoded voltage indicators (GEVIs). To evaluate how natural sequence diversity shapes function, we compared VSP voltage-sensing domains (VSDs) from multiple species by replacing the phosphatase domain with a fluorescent protein to enable optical detection of VSD responses. Every construct that reached the plasma membrane produced a voltage-dependent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Therapeutic Strategy for Renal Cell Carcinoma: Niclosamide Enhances Sunitinib Efficacy via DNA Repair and Cell Cycle Pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tyrosine kinase inhibitors (TKIs), such as sunitinib and sorafenib, are standard treatments for renal cell carcinoma (RCC). However, most patients treated with these drugs eventually develop drug resistance and relapse; therefore, new treatment options for RCC are urgently required. Recent studies have focused on combination therapies targeting distinct molecular pathways that may produce synergistic effects and help overcome drug resistance in RCC. Niclosamide, an anthelmintic agent, is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Molecular Characteristics of <em>KRAS</em> Codon-Specific Mutations in Advanced Pancreatic Ductal Adenocarcinoma with Prognostic and Therapeutic Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[KRAS mutations occur in over 90% of pancreatic ductal adenocarcinomas (PDACs), most commonly at codon 12, but the clinical implications of codon-specific subtypes in advanced disease remain unclear. We retrospectively analyzed 269 patients with advanced PDAC who underwent next-generation sequencing between 2020 and 2024 at a single tertiary cancer center. Clinical features, co-mutations, treatment outcomes, and survival were evaluated. KRAS mutations were detected in 92% of patients, most...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of AMPK/NLRP3 Signaling Mitigates Radiation-Induced Lung Inflammation by a Synthetic Lipoxin A4 Analogue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiation-induced lung inflammation (RILI) is a major complication of thoracic radiotherapy, characterized by excessive inflammation and subsequent fibrosis that compromise pulmonary function and treatment outcomes. This study explores the pharmacological properties of a newly synthesized Lipoxin A4 analogue (CYNC-2) to mitigate RILI by modulating the AMP-activated protein kinase (AMPK)/NOD-like receptor family pyrin domain containing 3(NLRP3) inflammasome pathway. A murine RILI model was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Evaluation of Sagittal Alignment in Total Knee Arthroplasty: Robot Sensor Versus Surgeon's Eye and Influencing Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Postoperative sagittal imbalance, including hyperextension and flexion contracture after total knee arthroplasty (TKA), adversely affects long-term outcomes. Conventional techniques depend on surgeons' visual estimation, which may vary with patient anatomy. This study compared the accuracy of sagittal alignment assessment between a robot-assisted system and surgeons' visual evaluation and analyzed the influence of body mass index (BMI) and anatomic factors on concordance. Methods:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of OXTR, COMT, and GRIN2B Polymorphisms on Brain Development in Preterm Infants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Preterm infants are at risk for developmental delays due to immature brain development and increased sensitivity to environmental stress. Genetic factors, such as polymorphisms in *OXTR* rs2268490, *COMT* rs4818, and *GRIN2B*, may influence these vulnerabilities and affect neurodevelopment. Methods: We recruited 91 preterm infants (<35 weeks gestation) admitted to the NICU at Hanyang University Seoul Hospital between January 2020 and December 2022. Brain MRIs were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exoscopic Visualization for Transorbital Surgery: Preliminary Anatomical and Clinical Validation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The endoscopic transorbital approach (ETOA) is a minimally invasive surgical route that provides access to the lateral skull base through the superior eyelid. Originally developed as an endoscopic procedure, ETOA has recently been explored using alternative visualization tools such as the exoscope. This study evaluates the effectiveness of exoscopic visualization across the different steps of transorbital surgery. Methods: Eight formalin-fixed cadaveric specimens (16...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is the Most Effective Strategy for Acute Postoperative Pain in Total Knee Arthroplasty-Retrospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Effective early postoperative pain control is essential for optimal recovery following total knee arthroplasty (TKA). In addition to pharmacological pain management, the choice of anesthetic agents and surgical technique can significantly impact postoperative outcomes. Remimazolam and robotic-assisted TKA (RA-TKA) have recently gained attention due to their potential advantages. This study aims to evaluate the effects of remimazolam and RA-TKA on acute postoperative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of qEEG TAR and TBR During Eyes-Open and Eyes-Closed with Plasma Oligomeric Amyloid-β Levels in an Aging Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objective: Timely and successful treatments for Alzheimer's disease (AD) depend on early detection. The Multimer Detection System (MDS-OAβ) for quantifying plasma oligomeric amyloid-β (OAβ) has shown promise as a biomarker of amyloid disease. The theta-to-alpha ratio (TAR) and theta-to-beta ratio (TBR) are two examples of spectral power metrics that can be used in resting-state quantitative EEG (qEEG) to evaluate brain function non-invasively. This study used resting-state EEG (rEEG)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Case of Lumbar Spinal Epidural Abscess and Facet Joint Septic Arthritis Caused by <em>Haemophilus influenzae</em> in an Immunocompetent Host]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background:Haemophilus influenzae rarely causes spinal epidural abscess or septic arthritis of the facet joints. We report a case of lumbar spinal epidural abscess and facet joint septic arthritis caused by H. influenzae in an immunocompetent host. Methods: A 53-year-old female patient with lumbar spine disc herniation presented with lower back pain 5 days before admission. Results: The patient was diagnosed with an epidural abscess at the right posterolateral aspect of the lumbar spine at the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Molecular Spectrum of <em>DDX41</em> Variants in Korean Patients with Hematologic Malignancies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background:DDX41 is one of the most frequent adult-onset myeloid neoplasm predisposition gene, yet its biology remains incompletely defined. This study investigated the frequency, spectrum, and clinical characteristics of DDX41 variants in Korean patients with hematologic malignancies, including the patterns of co-occurring somatic variants. Methods: We retrospectively reviewed 716 patients with hematologic malignancies who underwent targeted next-generation sequencing. In patients with germline...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-Specific Risk Factors for Cancer in a Long-Term Korean Cohort of Patients with Ankylosing Spondylitis Treated with TNF Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Tumor necrosis factor (TNF) inhibitors are widely used in ankylosing spondylitis (AS), but data on cancer risk in this young population remain limited. We aimed to identify factors associated with cancer during TNF inhibitor therapy and evaluate age-specific risks in Asian patients with AS. Methods: We analyzed 810 AS patients who initiated TNF inhibitors between 2003 and 2023 at a Korean tertiary center. Cox regression assessed cancer predictors; when sparse data limited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analgesic Efficacy of Acetaminophen/Ibuprofen as an Adjuvant in Patient-Controlled Analgesia for Postoperative Pain After Oncoplastic Breast Surgery: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Although patients with breast cancer often undergo multiple oncologic procedures after primary tumor resection, an optimal postoperative analgesic strategy remains undefined. We evaluated the efficacy of acetaminophen/ibuprofen as an adjunct to opioid-based patient-controlled analgesia (PCA) following oncoplastic breast surgery. Methods: In this double-blind randomized controlled trial, 79 patients were assigned to receive either acetaminophen/ibuprofen or saline. A 100 mL...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Cross-Sectional Study of Word Recognition and Cognitive Function in Older Adults with Hearing Loss Using a Standardized Neuropsychological Battery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: Dementia and hearing loss are prevalent conditions among older adults. This study aimed to determine the association between hearing loss and cognitive status using data from the Catholic Medical Center Clinical Data Warehouse (CMC-CDW). Methods: A retrospective review was conducted using the CMC-CDW. A total of 801 participants, aged 60 years and older, underwent bilateral speech audiometry and cognitive assessments using the Korea Mini-Mental State Examination (K-MMSE) and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Numerical Investigation of Crack Suppression Strategies in Ultra-Thin Glass Substrates for Advanced Packaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mechanical reliability of glass substrates is a key challenge for their adoption in advanced semiconductor packaging. This study employs finite element analysis to systematically evaluate the risk of edge crack propagation in large glass panels during redistribution layer (RDL) fabrication. The influence of critical factors-including crack location, number of RDLs, glass material and thickness, dielectric ABF properties, Cu content, and edge clearance-was examined. Results revealed that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-Wideband Double-Pentagonal Fractal Antenna for C-, X-, Ku- and K-Band Wireless Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fractal antennas employ self-similar geometries to generate scaled multiple resonances within compact structures, thereby achieving broadband performance. However, many reported designs remain constrained by narrow impedance bandwidths or demonstrate only multiband characteristics. To address these limitations, we present a novel pentagonal fractal antenna with ultra-wideband performance suitable for C, X, Ku and K-band applications. The key innovation lies in a double-pentagonal fractal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soft-Error-Resilient Static Random Access Memory with Enhanced Write Ability for Radiation Environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As semiconductor technologies advance, SRAM cells deployed in space systems face heightened sensitivity to radiation-induced soft errors. In conventional 6T SRAM, when high-energy particles strike sensitive nodes, single-event upsets (SEUs) may occur, flipping stored bits. Furthermore, with aggressive scaling, charge sharing among adjacent devices can trigger single-event multi-node upsets (SEMNU). To address these reliability concerns, this study presents a radiation-hardened SRAM design,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Situ Raman Measurement of the Growth of SiCOH Thin Film Using Hexamethyl-Disiloxane (HMDSO) Mixture Source in Semiconductor Interconnection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This research focuses on the real-time monitoring of SiCOH thin films grown by chemical vapor deposition (CVD) using Raman spectroscopy. To ensure the reliability of CVD-deposited materials in semiconductor processes, the study analyzes the growth and properties of thin films in situ. With the increasing demand for low-dielectric constant (low-k) materials due to the miniaturization of semiconductor components, real-time monitoring becomes essential for controlling film thickness, quality, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Negative Paper Spray Ionization Mass Spectrometry for the Determination of Endocrine-Disrupting Chemicals with Application to Paraben Analysis in Cosmetics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Paper spray ionization mass spectrometry (PSI-MS) enables rapid analysis with minimal sample preparation, yet negative-ion mode performance has been limited by poor sensitivity and unstable signals, similar to conventional electrospray ionization. In this study, we optimized negative PSI tandem MS (MS/MS) for twelve endocrine-disrupting chemicals (EDCs) and related biomarkers-including bisphenols, phthalates, parabens, and substituted phenols-used as model analytes. A systematic solvent and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide Trends in Healthcare Utilization and Expenditures Among Patients with Cervical Dystonia in Korea: A 7-Year Analysis Using Health Insurance Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Cervical dystonia (CD) is the most common focal dystonia, but nationwide evidence on healthcare use is limited. This study assessed trends in utilization and expenditures in Korea. Methods: Using National Health Insurance Service claims (2017-2023), we identified CD patients (ICD-10 G24.3) and analyzed annual patients, visits, and expenditures by demographics, medical system, service type, and specialty. Results: A total of 6614 patients (33,896 claims) were included....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Essential Safety Sheet in University Hospital and Healthcare Laboratories: A Comprehensive Evaluation Study with Longitudinal Impact Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A concise, task-level safety sheet can enhance the speed of safety-critical information retrieval and contribute to lower incident rates in hospital laboratories. While escalation accuracy showed only a favorable trend after correction, overall results support ESS as low-cost, scalable interventions to strengthen laboratory safety performance. Future studies should test generalizability across more sites and tasks to assess longer-term sustainability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dignity in Care of Older Patients with Cancer in Korea: A Hybrid Model Concept Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study explores the concept of dignity in care for older patients with cancer in Korea using the hybrid model. Methods: A three-phase hybrid model approach was employed for concept analysis. In the theoretical phase, a literature review was conducted to determine the attributes and definition of dignity in care. In the fieldwork phase, the practicability of the defined concept was assessed through practical observations. In the final analysis phase, findings from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacovigilance Signal Detection of Drug-Induced Hospitalizations and Mortality: A 5-Year Nationwide Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study aimed to comprehensively characterize the prevalence and patterns of drug-induced hospitalizations and death and to identify predictors strongly associated with drug-induced death. Methods: This study analyzed 29,438 serious adverse event (SAE) reports submitted to the Korea Adverse Event Reporting System (KIDS KAERS DB) database between January 2019 and December 2023. Disproportionality analysis was conducted to detect drug-event associations, and multiple...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validity of Online Patient Medication Reviews and Ratings (PMRRs) for Treatment Satisfaction with Medication Therapy Among Older Adults with Antihypertensive Medications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/objective: Online platforms for sharing prescription drug experiences are becoming increasingly available, yet their validity as measures of patient satisfaction remains unclear. This study aimed to evaluate the potential of an online drug review system, WePharm, as a proxy for treatment satisfaction among older adults taking antihypertensive medications. Methods: A cross-sectional survey using a convenience sample was conducted from February to July 2018 among patients aged 50-80...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designing Personalization Cues for Museum Robots: Docent Observation and Controlled Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Social robots in public cultural venues, such as science museums, must engage diverse visitors through brief, one-off encounters where long-term user modeling is infeasible. This research examines immediately interpretable behavioral cues of a robot that can evoke a sense of personalization without storing or profiling individual users. First, a video-based observational study of expert and novice museum docents identified service strategies that enable socially adaptive communication. Building...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly Sensitive Si-Based Electrolyte-Gated Transistor Array for Multiplexed Detection of Arboviruses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiplexed detection of arboviruses using a 4 × 4 Si-based electrolyte-gated transistor (EGT) array functionalized with specific aptamers has been investigated. The Si-based EGTs were fabricated using conventional Si microfabrication processes. The EGTs showed excellent intrinsic electrical characteristics, including a low threshold voltage of 0.8 V, a sub-threshold swing of 75 mV/dec, and a gate leakage of <10 pA, ensuring uniform device performance with low device-to-device variation....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutrophil extracellular traps and peptidylarginine deiminase 4-mediated inflammasome activation link diabetes to cardiorenal injury and heart failure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Diabetes promotes neutrophil inflammasome activation and NETosis, driving cardiac and renal inflammation and fibrosis. Peptidylarginine deiminase 4 deficiency prevents heart failure and preserves kidney function in experimental diabetes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accuracy comparative study of automatic landmarking and diagnostic models on lateral cephalograms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this study, the comparison was indirect, with each model having its strengths: the automatic landmarking model offers precise measurements, while the automatic diagnostic model provides quicker results. The choice between them depends on clinical needs, and future work should explore hybrid models to combine the advantages of both.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Avoiding splenectomy in splenic sclerosing angiomatoid nodular transformation through endoscopic ultrasound-guided tissue acquisition: a 36-month follow-up case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 48-mm splenic mass was incidentally discovered in a 78-year-old man upon computed tomography. Follow-up imaging at 12 months revealed enlargement to 60 mm, prompting endoscopic ultrasound-guided tissue acquisition with a 22-gauge needle. Histopathological analysis confirmed that it was a sclerosing angiomatoid nodular transformation. The patient was asymptomatic and had no hematologic abnormalities; therefore, splenectomy was not performed. After biopsy, the lesion regressed from 60 mm to 46...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling molecular environment of allomorphic N-salicylidene-4-halo-aniline crystals through iterative QM/QM' structural optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONTEXT: Two allomorphic crystals, photochromic N-salicylidene-4-bromoaniline (α-SA4B) and non-photochromic N-salicylidene-4-chloroaniline (β-SA4C), were simulated using a hierarchical hybrid quantum mechanical (QM/QM') method. Despite the similar potential energy surface (PES) profiles observed in their isolated forms, distinct differences emerged in the cluster model simulations of α-SA4B and β-SA4C. This observation suggests that the molecular environment influenced the torsional energy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of liver transection depth on surgical difficulty in robotic versus laparoscopic limited liver resection (TAKUMI-5)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study investigated impact of LTD on surgical outcomes in patients who underwent limited RLR compared to those who underwent limited LLR. LTD may be a useful parameter for estimating surgical difficulty in limited RLR. Moreover, robotic surgery may be favorable for deeper and limited liver resections.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraoperative Language mapping in a Japanese-English-French trilingual patient with a left Temporal lobe glioma: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case represents the first report of intraoperative language mapping in a Japanese-English-French trilingual patient, demonstrating both overlapping and language-specific cortical regions. The findings underscore the importance of individualized and multimodal language mapping in multilingual patients, particularly when typologically distant languages such as Japanese are involved.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Factors Associated with Non-Adherence To Anti-retroviral Therapy among People Living with HIV]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-adherence to antiretroviral therapy (ART) remains a major barrier to achieving viral suppression and HIV epidemic control, particularly in sub-Saharan Africa. Despite significant ART coverage in Tanzania, a substantial proportion of people living with HIV (PLHIV) fail to achieve optimal adherence, leading to drug resistance, treatment failure, and increased morbidity. This study determined the prevalence and factors associated with ART non-adherence among PLHIV. A cross-sectional study was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Care Partners' Perceptions of Amyloid-Targeting Therapy and Treat‑to‑Clearance for Alzheimer's Disease in Japan: A Qualitative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results suggest that providing clear explanations and facilitating shared decision-making when introducing ATT, as well as introducing follow-up care and long-term evidence after stopping treatment, are needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Integrative diagnostic approach to salivary gland tumors: from clinical evaluation to molecularly targeted therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diblock Copolypeptide Amphiphiles-Mediated Assembly and Structural Modulation of Porphyrin Dimers in Aqueous Media]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the design and self-assembly of supramolecular nanohybrids composed of a lipophilic zinc porphyrin dimer (ZnP)(2) and diblock copolypeptide amphiphiles. The peptide amphiphiles were designed with hydrophilic segments containing aspartic acid (Asp) and lysine (Lys) residues that favor β-sheet formation and hydrophobic segments composed of leucine (Leu) residues that drive aggregation in aqueous media. This balance of hydrophobic and hydrophilic interactions promotes the spontaneous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Membrane-Penetrating Molecular Device Based on a Triplex Containing Acyclic L-Threoninol Nucleic Acid Functionalized with Cholesterol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Membrane-penetrating molecular devices are valuable biological tools. Herein, we describe membrane-targeting molecular devices based on the triplexes of poly T acyclic L-threoninol nucleic acid (L-aTNA) tethered site-specifically to cholesterol and poly A DNA. The L-aTNA was linked to cholesterol in two different orientations. The membrane-binding properties differed depending on the orientation at the cholesterol linkage. One triplex adhered to giant unilamellar vesicles and the other...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Synchrotron-based infrared microspectroscopy unveils the biomolecular response of healthy and tumour cell lines to neon minibeam radiation therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Correction for 'Synchrotron-based infrared microspectroscopy unveils the biomolecular response of healthy and tumour cell lines to neon minibeam radiation therapy' by R. González-Vegas et al., Analyst, 2025, 150, 342-352, https://doi.org/10.1039/D4AN01038H.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Osteogenic gene expression in the temporal region of the opossum embryos: an insight into the evolution of synapsid skull unique to mammalian lineage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The skull of amniotes is categorized into three conditions based on skeletal arrangement in the temporal region: anapsid, synapsid and diapsid. Mammals (class Mammalia), a descendent lineage of the clade Synapsida, possess the synapsid skull, which is characterized by a single lower temporal arch that ventrally borders the lower temporal fenestra. Although we previously suggested, based on the data from placental mammals, that the reduction in the expression domain of the upstream osteogenic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuropsychiatric manifestations in systemic lupus erythematosus and antiphospholipid syndrome: pathophysiology and current insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuropsychiatric manifestations in systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) and anti-phospholipid syndrome (APS) represent complex clinical challenges due to their diverse presentations and multifactorial pathogenesis. Neuropsychiatric SLE (NPSLE) affects approximately 30-40% of SLE patients, with symptoms ranging from cognitive dysfunction to severe conditions such as stroke, seizures, and psychosis. In APS, cerebrovascular events, including ischemic stroke and transient ischemic attacks, occur in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ligand assisted reprecipitation of formamidinium-guanidinium lead iodide 2D perovskite nanowires]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two-dimensional (2D) lead halide perovskites have emerged as a promising alternative to their three-dimensional counterparts, offering superior ambient stability and enhanced moisture resistance. Additionally, A-site multi-cation perovskites have gained attention for their ability to improve stability and enhance optoelectronic device performance. Despite these advantages, the synthesis of multi-cation 2D perovskites has traditionally been limited by complex and time-intensive methods, hindering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[InterRAI Implementation: Health System Considerations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article focuses on the implementation of interRAI instruments at a national health system level. It is based on a narrative review undertaken by the authors from several interRAI member countries. Implementation experiences from several countries and searches of PubMed and other databases, grey literature sources, policy reports, and the interRAI repository, identified practical insights and recommendations relevant for health system implementation. Key considerations are outlined. These...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Covalent/metal-organic framework membranes with tailored pore functionality for accurate ion separation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ion-selective membranes present a promising solution for efficient ion extraction, a critical need addressing both water resource cycling and critical metal supplies. Conventional polymer membranes often exhibit an intrinsic permeability-selectivity trade-off, stemming from their disordered and random pore architecture. This structural limitation further complicates the understanding of how diverse ion species are transported within their non-uniform sub-nanochannels. Covalent organic frameworks...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laparoscopic near-infrared hyperspectral imaging system for identifying living porcine nerves and unexposed arteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surgical resection remains a key curative option for cancer, with minimally invasive approaches increasingly adopted. To enhance intraoperative visualization, we developed a laparoscopic near-infrared hyperspectral imaging (NIR-HSI) system comprising a custom laparoscope, supercontinuum light source, and acousto-optic tunable filter. Ex vivo NIR-HSI of porcine arteries, mesentery, and nerves revealed distinct spectral signatures from 1000-1402 nm. Pixel-based classification via neural networks...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maintenance of a High Quality of Life of a Pancreatic Cancer Patient in a Multidisciplinary Care Center: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multidisciplinary care with nutritional support, palliative care, exercise, and social support at the care center may have reduced the patient's psychological stress and maintained her physical and psychological well-being and ultimately improved her QOL and survival. The multidisciplinary care center may be a candidate for a new model system of palliative and hospice care that did not only provide pain/symptom control and terminal care but also maintained a high QOL of the patient.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fogarty Catheter Placement for Subglottic H-Type Tracheoesophageal Fistula via a Supraglottic Airway: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surgery for tracheoesophageal fistula (TEF) often necessitates the insertion of a Fogarty catheter (FC) to assist the surgeon in identifying the fistula. However, when the TEF is located close to the glottis, bronchoscopic identification of the TEF and FC insertion can be particularly challenging. A 2-month-old female infant exhibited frequent apneic episodes during feeding from postnatal day 5. A subsequent contrast swallow study and bronchoscopy led to the diagnosis of H-type esophageal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute coronary syndrome due to papillary fibroelastoma detected by intravascular ultrasound imaging: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Papillary fibroelastomas (PFEs) are rare benign cardiac tumours that most commonly affect the left-sided heart valves, especially the aortic valve. Although frequently asymptomatic, PFEs can cause embolic events, arrhythmias, or coronary artery occlusion.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical outcomes of atrial cardiac tumors: a single-center 14-case series including right atrial and malignant tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary cardiac tumors are rare, with myxomas predominating and usually located in the left atrium. Right atrial tumors are less frequent but clinically significant because of the risks of embolism, hemodynamic compromise, and conduction disturbance. We reviewed 14 patients who underwent surgical resection of atrial tumors at our institution. The cohort included three right atrial and 11 left atrial tumors, with two malignant histologies. All right atrial tumors were resected en bloc with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Attitudes of medical professionals towards high-risk suicidal patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although we found differences in attitudes towards suicide between health professionals, there were also many commonalities. By holding workshops with a wide range of professionals, and deepening mutual understanding, it may be possible to implement seamless suicide prevention measures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An icosahedral Au<sub>13</sub> nanocluster with three adjacent chlorides on opposite poles catalyses hydroamination of phenylacetylene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel anionic gold nanocluster, [Au(13)(dppeF)(3)Cl(6)]^(-), bearing six chlorides, has been synthesized using a bulky diphosphine, dppeF (1,2-bis[bis(3,5-ditrifluoromethylphenyl)phosphino]ethane) as a protecting ligand. Single-crystal X-ray diffraction analysis revealed that this nanocluster has an icosahedral Au(13) core, which is protected by each of three Cl ligands on opposite poles and by three dppeF ligands in an equatorial plane. This nanocluster acted as a homogeneous catalyst for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxahelicene-Based Pd<sub>2</sub>L<sub>4</sub> Cages: Synthesis, Optical Properties, and Guest Encapsulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[7-Oxa[5]- and 9-oxa[7]helicene-based ligands L1 and L2 bearing two pyridyl coordination sites were synthesized, and their self-assembly with Pd(II) ions into a Pd(2)L(4) cages was demonstrated. The self-assembled cages retained high fluorescence quantum yields (Φ(F) = 0.50 for Pd(2)L1(4)), exhibited significant circular dichroism (CD)/circularly polarized luminescence (CPL) activity for Pd(2)L2(4), and displayed guest-encapsulating behavior owing to the inherent oxahelicene ligands. Structural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smartphone App-based Eating Behavior Monitoring and Feedback Intervention for Glucocorticoid-induced Appetite Increase in Patients With Systemic Lupus Erythematosus: Protocol for a Pilot Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This pilot trial will provide foundational data on the feasibility and efficacy of smartphone-based real-time feedback in managing GC-induced appetite increase in patients with SLE. These findings may contribute to the growing body of literature on app-based interventions for medication-related adverse effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251127142102&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>