<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:20:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gemcitabine and Cisplatin Plus Polymeric Micellar Paclitaxel and Survival in Advanced Biliary Tract Cancer: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this randomized clinical trial, gemcitabine and cisplatin combined with polymeric micellar paclitaxel did not improve survival compared with gemcitabine and cisplatin combined in patients with previously untreated advanced biliary tract cancer. This study provides further evidence regarding the limitations of intensified chemotherapy with the addition of taxanes in advanced biliary tract cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multilevel Nanoarray Spin-Orbit Torque Device for Process-in-Memory Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The advancement of data-driven technologies has increased energy and time consumption in data transfer between processors and memory units, limiting further improvement in device performance. This challenge can be addressed by introducing process-in-memory (PIM) architecture, which alleviates data transfer overhead through in-memory computation. In this work, we propose multilevel nanoarray spin-orbit torque (SOT) devices for PIM applications. In a Hall bar structure with multiple ferromagnetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in growth and nutritional status of Korean toddlers and preschoolers: a cross-sectional study using 2010-2021 Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: South Korea is making significant progress in supporting toddlers and preschoolers, as evidenced by consistent increases in the proportion of children with normal growth and decreases in the prevalence of malnutrition. Future research should focus on exploring dietary patterns and analyzing specific food groups that are essential for promoting optimal growth and nutritional status in children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of the transposon-associated TnpB system of CRISPR-Cas in bacteria: <em>Deinococcus</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deinococcus radiodurans is one of the most radioresistant organisms found on Earth to date, showing extreme resistance to damage factors such as UV, drought, and mutagens, and is of great interest to scientists around the world. It was determined that the TnpB protein from D. radiodurans ISDra2 functions as an RNA-guided endonuclease, serving as a functional ancestor for the widely used CRISPR-Cas endonucleases. The CRISPR-Cas system is an "acquired immune system" found in most Bacteria and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean medicine inpatient care: trends and influencing factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Korean medicine inpatient care (KMIC) use was more common among females, individuals with poor subjective health status, and individuals engaging in regular physical activity. Patients primarily used KMIC for the treatment of accidents and musculoskeletal disorders and generally reported high levels of satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and Prospects in Multifunctional Composite Fibrous Materials Utilizing Porous Organic Polymers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Porous organic polymers (POPs) offer exceptional surface area, tunable pore sizes, and versatile chemical functionality, making them attractive for a range of advanced applications. However, their conventional powdered form limits processability, structural integration, and practical deployment. Integrating POPs into fibrous matrices through electrospinning, a scalable and versatile technique for producing nonwoven fibers, helps overcome these limitations and enables the creation of new material...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Modular Protein-DNA Multimer Model to Explore How Valence and Monomer Affinity Shape Multivalent DNA Binding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multivalent interactions enhance binding strength through the cooperative effects of multiple weak interactions. While multivalency is known to improve sensitivity, increased valency can also enhance nonspecific interactions, potentially compromising selectivity. Insights into the relationship between valency, affinity, and detection performance are needed to optimize both sensitivity and selectivity in multivalent systems. Here, we developed modular protein-DNA multimers (valency 1-4) with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of applying computerized adaptive testing to the Clinical Medical Science Comprehensive Examination in Korea: a psychometric study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The medical self-assessment CAT, the first of its kind in Korea, was successfully implemented nationwide without significant problems. These results indicate strong potential for expanding the use of CAT in medical education assessments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quality of Life in Oropharyngeal Cancer: A Retrospective Analysis of Patient Characteristics and Treatment Modalities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sociodemographic factors, clinicopathological characteristics, and treatment modalities significantly impacted the post-treatment QoL of patients with OPSCC. Individualized treatment planning and comprehensive post-treatment care are crucial for optimizing QoL, particularly in patients at higher risk of poorer outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of whole-body vibration on cognitive function: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Whole-body vibration exercise (WBV) is a low-intensity intervention for improving cognitive function, particularly among individuals who are older or have physical limitations. However, quantitative evidence regarding its effectiveness is limited. This meta-analysis aimed to quantify the effects of WBV on cognitive function and explore major moderating variables and differences across cognitive domains. Sixteen randomized controlled trials (RCTs) were included, yielding 37 effect sizes (Hedges'...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cumulative Cardiovascular Health Score Through Young Adulthood and Cardiovascular and Kidney Outcomes in Midlife]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These findings suggest that a higher cumulative CVH score from 30 to 40 years of age was associated with markedly lower risks of CVD and kidney events in midlife, highlighting the importance of sustained primordial prevention efforts throughout early life.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stratifying lung adenocarcinoma risk with multi-ancestry polygenic risk scores in East Asian never-smokers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Multi-ancestry PRS approaches enhance LUAD risk stratification in East Asian never-smokers, with consistent external validation, suggesting future clinical utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide for cardiac computed tomography ventricular volumetry using three-dimensional threshold-based segmentation for congenital heart disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In addition to morphologic evaluation, cardiac computed tomography with a short scan time and a high spatial resolution may be performed to assess ventricular function in children with congenital heart disease, especially when cardiac magnetic resonance imaging is unavailable, inadequate, or contraindicated. Caution should be exercised over the computed tomography radiation dose because greater radiation doses are used to assess ventricular function than morphology. The three-dimensional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reductive Amination of Carboxylic Acids via Nickel(II) Catalysis: A Ligand-Tuned Strategy for C-N Bond Formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A nickel(II)-catalyzed reductive amination of carboxylic acids with amines is described, employing phenylsilane as the reductant. The reaction proceeds via an iminium ion/imine intermediate and does not require prior carboxylic acid activation. A comprehensive evaluation of ligands identified bulky trialkyl monophosphines as optimal, with tricyclohexylphosphine providing the highest yield. This ligand-controlled protocol provides direct access to diverse secondary and tertiary amines from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Emergency Medical Services Call-to-Hospital Arrival Time on Outcomes of Cardiac Arrest: A Nationwide Prospective Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Shorter EMS call-to-hospital arrival times were significantly associated with lower in-hospital mortality rates and better neurologic outcomes in patients with out-of-hospital cardiac arrest.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling Defect Motifs in Amorphous GeSe Using Machine Learning Interatomic Potentials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ovonic threshold switching (OTS) selectors are pivotal in nonvolatile memory devices due to their nonlinear electrical characteristics and polarity-dependent threshold voltages. However, the atomic-scale origins of the defect states responsible for these behaviors remain unclear. In this study, we systematically investigate defects in amorphous GeSe using molecular dynamics simulations accelerated by machine learning interatomic potentials (MLIPs). We first benchmark several MLIP architectures,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deciding Whether to Adopt Artificial Intelligence for Screening Mammography Interpretation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulating oxygen release <em>via</em> manipulated microspheres embedded in thermoresponsive hydrogels for enhanced stem cell survival under hypoxia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ensuring a stable oxygen supply for transplanted cells remains a major challenge in the clinical translation of tissue engineering and regenerative medicine. Hypoxic environments caused by insufficient vascularization are a key factor leading to cell death and graft failure. To address this issue, we developed an injectable, oxygen-generating thermoresponsive hydrogel system based on poly(organophosphazene) (PPZ). By modulating the gelatin and calcium peroxide (CaO(2)) content, we fabricated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative evaluation of ultrafiltration membranes for exosome isolation from A549 cell-conditioned medium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[(N = 199)Although numerous exosome isolation protocols are available, a practical need remains for a direct, quantitative comparison of commonly used centrifugal molecular weight cutoff (MWCO) filters under identical and standardized conditions. In this study we isolated exosomes with 10, 50 and 100 kDa Amicon filters using A549 conditioned medium and performed multimodal characterization. The Z-average sizes of the exosomes were 49.24 nm (10 kDa), 61.64 nm (50 kDa) and 90.83 nm (100 kDa)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Human Development Index Category on Prostate Cancer Characteristics in Asia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights significant differences in prostate cancer management across 12 Asian countries and areas, emphasizing the influence of HDI on diagnostic and treatment outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of microscopic dynamics and continuum theory for Poiseuille and diffusioosmotic flows in a microchannel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diffusioosmotic flows in a microchannel are investigated using microscopic coarse-grained particle-based simulations that incorporate molecular interactions between fluid particles and channel walls. The fluid-wall molecular interactions, coupled with concentration gradients, generate flows in the potential regions where the interactions are effective, thereby driving global flows in the bulk. Fluid velocities in narrow potential regions obtained from simulations are quantitatively compared with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Geometry-Guided Osteogenesis in Bone-on-a-Chip Systems Using Triply Periodic Minimal Surface Scaffolds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The interplay between scaffold geometry and mechanical cues is critical in regulating osteogenesis within engineered bone microenvironments. To better mimic native bone physiology and improve regeneration strategies, it is essential to integrate precise topological control with physiologically relevant flow. Here, a bone-on-a-chip (BoC) system coupled with triply periodic minimal surface (TPMS)-based 3D scaffolds is presented to investigate how geometric parameters-pore shape and solidity-govern...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Alignment of MXene Films Induced by Electrostatic Repulsion from TaS<sub>2</sub> Nanosheets for Multifunctional Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fabricating freestanding films with pristine MXene aims at meeting all-around high standards of modern electronics through boosting high electrical conductivity, thermal conductivity, and robust mechanical strength. However, voids and defects arising during fabrication often limit the performance and versatility. An effective electrostatic repulsion-induced alignment strategy is suggested here to overcome the major obstacles in the industrial application of MXene films. This approach combines...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Energy-Efficient Dual Formate Electrosynthesis via Coupled Formaldehyde Oxidation and CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction at Ultra-Low Cell Voltage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical formate (HCOO^(-)) production via CO(2) reduction reaction (CO(2)RR) holds great promise for carbon-neutral energy systems; however, its practical implementation is significantly hindered by the high energy demand of anodic oxygen evolution reaction (OER). Replacing OER with a more energetically and economically favorable alternative anodic reaction is therefore essential. In this study, we developed a highly efficient Cu-Ag catalyst for anodic formaldehyde oxidation reaction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Perceived Nutrition is Associated With Physical, Mental, and Oral Health in Older Korean Americans Living in Subsidized Senior Housing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PurposeNutrition plays an important role in overall health, yet little is known about how perceived nutritional status relates to health outcomes among older Korean Americans.DesignCross-sectional survey design.SettingSurveys were conducted at six subsidized senior housing facilities in Los Angeles between April and June 2023.SampleThe sample included 318 Korean American adults aged 65 and older.MeasuresParticipants rated their nutritional status, as well as physical, mental, and oral health on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Effect Analysis in an In-Sensor Computing System Enabled by Retention-Engineered Synaptic Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In-sensor computing systems demonstrate significant potential for reducing system complexity and enhancing computational efficiency. However, current methodologies predominantly focus on monitoring and processing instantaneous sensor data, neglecting the crucial temporal aspects of sensor inputs. This limitation is particularly significant in healthcare applications, where the human body often exhibits delayed responses to external stimuli. Herein, we developed a synapse-based in-sensor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Micro-scale control of oligodendrocyte morphology and myelination by the intellectual disability-linked protein acyltransferase ZDHHC9]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mutations in the X-linked ZDHHC9 gene cause cognitive deficits in humans, with a subset of patients suffering from epilepsy. X-linked intellectual disability (XLID) is often ascribed to neuronal deficits, but here we report that expression of human and mouse ZDHHC9 orthologs is far higher in myelinating oligodendrocytes (OLs) than in other CNS cell types. ZDHHC9 codes for a protein acyltransferase (PAT), and we found that ZDHHC9 is the most highly expressed PAT in OLs. Wild-type ZDHHC9 localizes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable perovskite light emitters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perovskite light-emitting diodes (PeLEDs) that use lead (Pb)-based perovskites are promising candidates for the next generation of lighting and display technologies. However, concerns about the toxicity of Pb have delayed their progress toward commercialisation. From this viewpoint, we compare Pb-based, low-Pb and Pb-free perovskite systems, with a focus on toxicity and environmental impact. By calculating the amount of lead in different perovskite systems, we find that Pb-based and low-Pb...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fraternal cooperation of hierarchical cancer parallels metazoan multicellularity and eusociality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metazoan multicellularity and eusociality - both outcomes of the fraternal major transitions - have numerous features in common such as uneven distribution of group-establishing potential. In addition to this framework, I argue herein that the group-forming principles of metazoan multicellularity and eusociality are analogous to hierarchical cancer in that the cancer stem cells generate other cancer cells deprived of tumorigenicity. As such, I introduce concepts of germinating reproducers and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the Letter Regarding "Incidence of Osteopenia or Osteoporosis in Asian Patients With Chronic Hepatitis B"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IGFBP2 Mediates Human iPSC-Cardiomyocyte Proliferation in a Cellular Contact-Dependent Manner]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings demonstrate that cell-cell contact inhibits hiPSC-CM proliferation through adherens junction formation, sarcomeric assembly, and reduced IGFBP2 secretion. Importantly, exogenous supplementation of IGFBP2 can overcome cell contact-mediated inhibition of hiPSC-CM proliferation and facilitate the growth of 3-dimensional cardiac tissue. These insights provide valuable implications for advancing cardiac tissue engineering and regenerative therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum: Effects of a multi-component program based on partially hydrolyzed guar gum (Sunfiber®) on glycemic control in South Korea: a single-arm, pre-post comparison pilot clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article on p. 40 in vol. 30.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthy eating intentions among adults in China: a cross-sectional study of northern and southern regions and city tiers based on the theory of planned behavior]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings underscore the complexity of regional variations influencing dietary intentions and indicate that tailored health promotion strategies should incorporate regional characteristics. Future research should explore underlying factors, including regional cultural influences, to better inform policies and interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of fully-immersive virtual reality for paretic arm recovery in stroke rehabilitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this case-control study, the findings suggest that incorporating fully immersive VR-based training in rehabilitation may enhance upper limb function recovery in patients with stroke in the subacute phase. Further randomized controlled studies are required to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the Safety, Pharmacokinetics, and Antitumor Activity of Tusamitamab Ravtansine in Patients With Nonsquamous NSCLC With High or Moderate Expression of Carcinoembryonic Antigen-Related Cell Adhesion Molecule 5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tusamitamab ravtansine demonstrated a favorable safety profile, objective responses, and antitumor activity in patients with high CEACAM5-expressing NSq NSCLC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcome expectations, self-efficacy, eating environment, and eating behaviors by the stages of change in adequate sodium intake among university students: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We observed differences in factors according to the stages of change in adequate sodium intake. For the pre-action stage, nutrition education can be planned to modify negative expectations of eating adequate sodium, foster self-efficacy, and practice general eating behaviors and behaviors to gradually reduce sodium intake. It is also necessary to alter the physical environment to reduce sodium intake. In the action stage, support and reinforcement are needed to continually practice...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wellness-enhancing effects of the canine growth hormone releasing hormone therapy mediated by plasmid and electroporation in healthy old dogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging leads to increased disease susceptibility and weakened immunity, a condition known as immunosenescence. The growth hormone-releasing hormone (GHRH)/growth hormone (GH)/insulin-like growth factor 1 (IGF-1) axis plays a key role in both somatic growth and immune modulation. This study evaluated the clinical and immunological effects of a canine GHRH-encoding plasmid delivered by electroporation in 30 healthy senior dogs (aged 10-16 years). Dogs received a single intramuscular injection and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and risk factors of hepatocellular carcinoma in patients with autoimmune hepatitis in Asia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The incidence of HCC in Asian patients with AIH was higher than that reported in a recent European study. The risk factors included cirrhosis and hepatic decompensation at diagnosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variation in depression's impact on dementia risk by age in adults aged ≥75 years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Late-life depression is linked to an increased dementia risk; however, whether this relationship varies with age remains unclear.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication and Preclinical Evaluation of Hyaluronic Acid/Aminoclay Nanocomposite Microneedles for Noninvasive Delivery of Semaglutide in Anti-Obesity Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that Sema-AC/HA10 is an effective transdermal delivery system for semaglutide.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutrition quotient for preschoolers and key impacting factors in Korea: a cross-sectional study on food literacy, social support, and the food environment of primary caregivers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study confirmed that caregivers' food literacy and social support significantly affected preschool children's nutritional status. This suggests a need for tailored nutritional education and dietary support policies, particularly for low-income and rural populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of a multi-component program based on partially hydrolyzed guar gum (Sunfiber<sup>®</sup>) on glycemic control in South Korea: a single-arm, pre-post comparison pilot clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among adults with elevated FPG levels, a multi-component intervention program that included PHGG (Sunfiber^(®)) supplementation, structured dietary management, and the use of health-monitoring devices showed significant benefits in improving glycemic control, overall nutritional status, and gut health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the charactersitics and types of single-person households based on food purchase frequencies in Korea: a cross-sectional study using the 2023 Consumer Behavior Survey for Foods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study underscores the need for targeted nutrition programs to address the unique needs of single-person households depending on their characteristics. Specifically, this study highlights the importance of targeted interventions for "convenience-seeking" and "passive food consumer" to promote dietary competency and encourage healthy dietary behavior.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining the multiple mediation effects of creative personality and self-esteem on the relationship between exercise and smartphone dependence in adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The widespread use of smartphones has raised growing concerns about smartphone dependence among adolescents. This study investigates how exercise participation reduces smartphone dependence by examining the mediating roles of creative personality and self-esteem. Specifically, we examined a multiple mediation model to test how these two psychological constructs function both individually and sequentially. Using secondary data from the fifth wave of the Korean Children and Youth Panel Survey...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing a rabbit sham model of cervical esophageal surgery for circumferential esophageal transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Esophageal surgery and postoperative treatment in rabbits require careful attention. We anticipate that this study will provide valuable and practical information for researchers conducting esophageal studies using rabbits.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acetylated Epigallocatechin Gallate and Ascorbyl Palmitate: Comparative Study on Antioxidant Activity and Retardation of Lipid Oxidation in Fish Mince and Shrimp Oil]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antioxidant activities of acetylated epigallocatechin gallate (A-EGCG) and ascorbyl palmitate (AP) were compared using different in vitro assays and food model systems. Both A-EGCG and AP exhibited DPPH and ABTS radical scavenging activities and reducing power. AP demonstrated greater scavenging efficacy toward both radicals than A-EGCG (p < 0.05), while A-EGCG exhibited greater metal chelating activity (p < 0.05). Antioxidant activity increased as the concentration upsurged from 0.5 to 10 mg/L....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aspirin Use and Risk of HCC and Gastrointestinal Bleeding in Patients With HBV-Related Cirrhosis: A Landmark Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with HBV-related cirrhosis, the aspirin-treated group showed a significantly lower risk of HCC than the untreated group, whereas the risk of GI bleeding was significantly higher in the aspirin-treated group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knowledge and Concerns About Smoking-Related Health Risks: A Cross-Sectional Analysis of the 2021 International Tobacco Control Japan and Korea Surveys]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This cross-sectional study examined: (i) knowledge of smoking-related health risks among adults who currently and formerly smoke; (ii) concerns about personal health damage from smoking among adults who currently smoke; (iii) sociodemographic predictors of knowledge; and (iv) associations between knowledge and concerns in Japan and the Republic of Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum: Evaluation of the efficacy of the lumbar sympathetic ganglion block and the use of perfusion index as a predictor of its technical success: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of standardized electroencephalography terminology education among early-career neurologists in Korea: a single-group pretest-posttest study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Education is imperative for standardizing EEG descriptions. As such, developing educational modules that emphasize minor items including prevalence, frequency, duration, and amplitude will broaden the recognition of EEG features, improving the quality of future research and patient care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationship between anxiety and problematic mobile phone use among Chinese college students: a moderated mediation model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study further elucidates the intrinsic psychological mechanism underlying the relationship between college students' anxiety and problematic mobile phone use, determining that FoMO-SM and physical exercise play a mediating role in this relationship. This finding provides a substantial reference point for developing targeted and timely intervention strategies to address problematic mobile phone use among college students.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Centiloid values from deep learning-based CT parcellation: a valid alternative to freesurfer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings indicate that the CT parcellation pipeline achieves a level of accuracy similar to FS in CL quantification, demonstrating its reliability as an MRI-free alternative. In PET/CT, CT and PET are acquired sequentially within the same session on a shared bed and headrest, which helps maintain consistent positioning and adequate spatial alignment, reducing registration errors and supporting more reliable and precise quantification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance imaging-guided radiotherapy for portal vein tumor thrombus in hepatocellular carcinoma: outcomes and prognostic factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The rtMRgRT demonstrated feasibility in treatment of PVTT with favorable overall response and local control. Response to RT and combined TACE within a month post-RT were favorable prognostic factors for OS. Given the predominant patterns of disease progression after RT, timely management of HCC outside RT field may be crucial for enhancing the survival of patients with PVTT undergoing RT. The early combination of TACE within a month post-RT may be beneficial in this regard. Further...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of geographic atrophy secondary to age-related macular degeneration in Korean patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustained PSA screening is associated with downstaging and improved survival in prostate cancer: a 12-year Korean cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of nurses' perceptions of systems thinking on patient safety competencies: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nurses in the study population demonstrated moderate levels of both systems thinking and PSCs. These findings underscore the critical role of systems thinking in enhancing nurses' PSCs. The results can serve as a foundational basis for the formulation of hospital policies aimed at bolstering nurses' PSCs, thereby contributing to improved patient safety within healthcare settings. Policies and interventions on promoting systems thinking among nursing staff must be created and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Retrosynthetic crosstalk between single-step reaction and multi-step planning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Associated Factors of Olfactory and Gustatory Loss in Patients With Nasal Septal Deviation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The presence of CB and a high blood eosinophil count are significant predictors of OL in patients with NSD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commercially Available Artificial Intelligence Solutions for Gynaecologic Cytology Screening and Their Integration Into Clinical Workflow]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Historically, gynaecologic cytology, particularly cervical screening through Pap smear tests, has been instrumental in early cancer detection, but not without its challenges. These include variability in interpretation and the labour-intensive nature of manual screening processes. The advent of artificial intelligence (AI) technologies, especially machine learning and deep learning, heralds a new era in cytology, offering enhanced accuracy, consistency, and efficiency. These advancements promise...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protein expression of sialolith with antrolith and tonsillolith examined by immunohistochemistry and immunoprecipitation based high performance liquid chromatography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultrastructural and proteomic analyses have been performed to elucidate the growth mechanism of sialoliths. However, the role of salivary/blood proteins, inflammatory signaling proteins, inflammatory cytokines, and antimicrobial proteins has not been elucidated. This study examined eight sialoliths, one antrolith, and one tonsillolith which underwent radiological, histological, immunohistochemical (IHC), and immunoprecipitation-based high-performance liquid chromatography (IP-HPLC) analyses. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A machine learning analysis for hybrid nanofluid flow between two co-axial cylinders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates steady, incompressible, heat transfer and axisymmetric flow in a hybrid nanofluid, magnetite and multi-walled carbon nanotubes dispersed in water, confined in the annular space between two coaxial cylinders (outer radius normalized to 1, inner radius one quarter of outer). The outer cylinder rotates while a constant radial magnetic field is applied, and the hybrid mixture's effective thermophysical properties are evaluated using a two-step Hamilton-Crosser mixing model....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adsorptive potential of hydrochar produced from avocado waste biomass for the sequestration of Alizarin red S dye from aquatic environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study successfully synthesized Hydrochar (HC) and Modified Hydrochar (MHC), two affordable and environmentally friendly adsorbents, utilizing an integration of chemical activation and hydrothermal carbonization. Subsequently, the artificially produced adsorbents were employed to eradicate the Alizarin Red S (ARS) dye from the aquatic environment. The physical and chemical nature of the HC and MHC adsorbents were assessed by various characterization approaches namely, FT-IR, SEM, XRD, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimode phonon-polaritons in lead-halide perovskites in the ultrastrong coupling regime]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phonons play a central role in fundamental solid-state phenomena, including superconductivity, Raman scattering, and symmetry-breaking phases. Harnessing phonons to control these effects and enable quantum technologies is therefore of great interest. However, most existing phonon control strategies rely on external driving fields or anharmonic interactions, limiting their applicability. Here, we realize multimode ultrastrong light-matter coupling and theoretically show the modulation of phonon...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India Policy Insights: Estimates of Population Health and Social Determinants Indicators Across Policy Units]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving global development targets will largely depend on improvements made by developing and populous countries like India. Given the huge population base and diversely wide landscape of India, stakeholders and policy-makers at smaller geographic levels must be equipped with data to understand their respective territories and the target sub-groups. This paper presents the output of India Policy Insights; a project aimed at offering a comprehensive dataset of 122 key indicators on population...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhibition of ICAM1 diminishes stemness and enhances antitumor immunity in glioblastoma via β-catenin/PD-L1 signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma (GBM) stem cells (GSCs) are pivotal in tumor initiation, recurrence, and therapeutic resistance, underscoring their critical role in the complex pathology of GBM. Despite their recognized importance, the mechanisms by which GSCs facilitate immune evasion, especially in emerging immunotherapies, remain incompletely understood. Here, we identify intercellular adhesion molecule 1 (ICAM1) as a key regulator of GSC stemness and tumorigenicity, promoting an immunosuppressive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of risk factors for bleeding after gastric endoscopic submucosal dissection with an emphasis on age and sex differences: A nationwide population-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identified risk factors for post-ESD bleeding and highlighted the role of age and sex in risk stratification and personalized treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Free Jejunal Graft Vaginoplasty in Gender Affirmation Surgery: A Novel Technique]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A two-staged free jejunal graft for neovagina construction is a safe and effective method of gender-affirming surgery for transfeminine individuals. This paper presents a novel approach of using a free jejunal graft to line the neovagina. The new technique comprises two stages of surgery to ensure hemostasis and minimize swelling of the neovaginal canal. No major complication was noted in the donor or the recipient site after follow-up of at least 6 months on 10 patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell foundation models: bringing artificial intelligence into cell biology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A foundation model, a large-scale deep learning model pretrained on vast datasets, has revolutionized data interpretation through self-supervised learning with capacity for various downstream tasks. Concurrently, single-cell genomics is in urgent need of unified frameworks capable of integrating and comprehensively analyzing the rapidly expanding data repositories. Inspired by advances in foundation models, researchers have extended these techniques to single-cell analysis, giving rise to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HSF1-DBC1 axis drives prostate cancer progression by activating a metastatic transcriptional program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heat shock factor 1 (HSF1) is a key stress-protective transcription factor that acts as a guardian of proteostasis. HSF1 also plays multifaceted roles in tumor-associated processes including proliferation and metastasis. HSF1 is frequently overexpressed and activated in a wide range of cancers, including prostate cancer, and hijacked by cancer cells to promote their survival in harsh tumor microenvironments and during metastasis. However, mechanisms underlying the persistent activation of HSF1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trained immunity induced by DAMPs and LAMPs in chronic inflammatory diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The immune system has traditionally been divided into innate and adaptive branches, with immunological memory considered a hallmark of adaptive immunity. However, recent studies reveal that innate immune cells can also exhibit memory-like properties, known as trained immunity. This phenomenon involves the long-term functional reprogramming of innate immune cells following exposure to exogenous or endogenous stimuli, mediated by epigenetic and metabolic changes. Trained immunity enhances...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growth hormone treatment in cerebral palsy: long-term impact on growth, outcomes, and complications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: GH treatment led to significant improvements in growth and metabolic-related parameters without adverse effects on gross motor function or musculoskeletal complications. These findings suggest that GH treatment may be a safe and effective treatment option for children with cerebral palsy, providing potential benefits without increasing the risk of orthopedic complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Method for ATAC Sequencing Data Analysis for Understanding Chromatin Biology in Legumes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Assay for Transposase Accessible Chromatin followed by sequencing (ATAC-seq) is one of the widely used methods to understand the chromatin accessibility and identification of various cis-regulatory elements like enhancers, promoters, insulators, etc. in the genome. Initially proposed in animal model systems, this method has now been adopted successfully for few plant species. There is a need for further improvement with respect to sample preparation and tool development that can help users...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large-Scale Identification of Transposon Insertion Polymorphisms in Leguminous Plants from Paired-End WGS Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transposable elements (TEs) are dynamic genomic sequences that significantly influence genome architecture and function. Their ability to move and replicate within the genome positions makes them key drivers of genetic diversity and evolution. Understanding the role of TEs in shaping phenotypes, especially in plants, has become increasingly important. This chapter provides a detailed guide to the bioinformatics approach for the identification of transposon insertion polymorphisms (TIPs) using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical factors associated with jawbone remineralization after nonsurgical treatment and imaging-based insights into its processes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Bone remineralization following jawbone destruction is influenced by patient-specific characteristics and treatment-related factors. Changes in CT values during bone remineralization and metabolic activity detected using PET/CT provide insights into the underlying processes of bone remineralization.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diabetes as a risk factor for heatstroke: insights from a nationwide Japanese health insurance database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change has intensified heat-related illnesses, particularly in Japan, where summer temperatures frequently exceed 35 °C, posing heightened risk to vulnerable populations. Previous studies have primarily assessed heatstroke risks during heatwaves rather than analyzing the ambient temperature at onset, and most have been limited by small sample sizes. This study examined heatstroke incidence across different ambient temperatures, regions, and sexes in individuals with and without diabetes....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the editor: Unmet needs and emotional well-being of family caregivers of adult patients with cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining abnormal flow-mediated slowing of brachial-radial pulse wave velocity, a noninvasive vasoreactivity test]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Abnormal FMS response was linked to cardiovascular risk factors such as ageing, hypertension and beta blocker use. The FMS response patterns may enable qualitative interpretation of FMS tests, though validation against hard clinical outcomes is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Odor-based individual authentication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In response to growing demands for secure and user-friendly individual authentication methods, biometric technologies have seen widespread adoption, offering advantages over traditional password- or card-based systems. While current biometric systems primarily rely on physical traits such as fingerprints and facial structures, these modalities remain susceptible to theft and duplication. Human odor, composed of complex volatile organic compound (VOC) profiles unique to each individual, is a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Renal TRPM3 Channels Regulate Blood Pressure via Tubuloglomerular Feedback and Plasma Volume Control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TRPM3 channels contribute to BP regulation by modulating kidney function. Blunted tubuloglomerular feedback in Trpm3-KO mice disrupts NaCl reabsorption, leading to hypovolemia and lower BP. Thus, renal TRPM3 channels may serve as promising targets for BP regulation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Behavioral economics, lifestyle, and health-related factors associated with participation in breast and cervical cancer screenings: A cross-sectional analysis of Japanese women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Interventions incorporating behavioral economics approaches, such as addressing risk perception and promoting health behaviors, may enhance Japanese women's cancer screening participation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tracking down the origin and subsequent spread of SARS-CoV-2 lineage B.1.619]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Since late 2020, the emergence of variants of concern (VOCs) of SARS-CoV-2 has been of concern to public health, researchers and policymakers. Mutations in the SARS-CoV-2 genome-for which clear evidence is available indicating a significant impact on transmissibility, severity and/or immunity-illustrate the importance of genomic surveillance and monitoring the evolution and geographic spread of novel lineages. Lineage B.1.619 was first detected in Switzerland in January 2021, in international...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of artificial intelligence spirometry diagnostic support software in primary care: a blinded diagnostic accuracy study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI software achieved high sensitivity and specificity in identifying COPD using spirometry and basic demographic data and may support accurate diagnosis of COPD in primary care. AI software performed less well for other chronic respiratory disease categories.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Micronutrient Deficiencies as Early Signs of Celiac Disease: Exemplified by Two Cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Celiac disease is an important yet often overlooked condition that, when left untreated, can lead to intestinal villous atrophy, resulting in malabsorption and nutritional deficiencies. The clinical presentation of celiac disease varies greatly and is not limited to gastrointestinal symptoms. The diverse clinical picture and nonspecific manifestations can lead to difficulties in the diagnostic process and a delay in diagnosis. In this article, we discuss two cases in which the diagnosis was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Z-scheme overall water splitting on photocatalyst sheet mediated by carbon nanotubes using oxysulfide photocatalyst responsive to long wavelengths]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Narrow-bandgap photocatalysts enable broad visible-light absorption and, theoretically, should provide high solar-to-hydrogen (STH) energy conversion efficiencies. However, the actual performance of such materials is highly dependent on the design and fabrication of the water-splitting system. In this study, photocatalyst sheets were constructed using Ga-doped La(5)Ti(2)Cu(0.9)Ag(0.1)O(7)S(5) (Ga-LTCA, with absorption at λ < 700 nm) as the hydrogen evolution photocatalyst together with BiVO(4)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isotropic proton conduction in an anisotropic crystal: the role of molecular rotational dynamics in imidazolium dihydrogen phosphate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the intrinsic anhydrous proton conductivity and conduction mechanisms of solid electrolytes is of fundamental academic importance for their application in next-generation, non-humidified fuel cells. In this study, we investigated the anhydrous proton conductivity of single crystals of imidazolium dihydrogen phosphate (1), a material in which rotational motion of both the acid and base components is expected to contribute to the conduction mechanism. By controlling the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of Non-<em>Saccharomyces</em> Yeasts for Developing Unique Flavor Profiles in Nonalcoholic Mulberry Fermented Beverage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents an innovative exploration of non-Saccharomyces yeast strains isolated from fragrant flowers for use in mulberry juice fermentation, aiming to develop nonalcohol fermented beverages with distinctive and complex aroma profiles. Seventy yeast isolates were screened for sugar utilization efficiency and ethanol production. Thirty-six strains that produced more than 20-fold less ethanol than Saccharomyces cerevisiae were selected for volatile compound analysis using headspace...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategy for reproductive and developmental toxicity (DART) studies for marketing applications in pharmaceutical development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Studies on reproductive toxicity are conducted to assess the effects of chemicals and pharmaceuticals on the reproductive function and fetal development. However, depending on the indication or modality, Fertility and Early Embryonic Development (FEED), Embryo-Fetal Development (EFD), and Pre/Postnatal Development (PPND) studies which evaluate all reproductive stages or EFD studies in a second species may not be necessary. Therefore, based on the Common Technical Document (CTD), PMDA review...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of transsphenoidal surgery in 34 small dogs with pituitary-dependent hypercortisolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION AND CLINICAL RELEVANCE: Transsphenoidal surgery is an effective treatment for PDH in dogs weighing < 15 kg, particularly when the pituitary gland is small.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local perceptions of foodscapes and their representation in visual and texts: A visual content analysis of photography in Japanese coastal area]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The term "foodscape" has recently gained prominence in academic discourse, fostering interdisciplinary research into the relationship between food and local environments. This study focuses on the material aspect of foodscapes and aims to clarify how local residents perceive them. We also analyze differences between visual and textual expressions. Targeting university students in the coastal area of Japan, Ishinomaki district, Miyagi Prefecture, the research employs visual materials...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of spin-crossover behaviour in Co(ii)-terpyridine complexes possessing π-conjugated substations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exploring new compounds that exhibit spin-state switching under external stimuli is crucial for advancing materials science. However, the feasibility of combining π-conjugated moieties with Co(ii)-terpy cation units via an ethynyl group has not yet been investigated. This approach represents a hybridization strategy wherein distinct functional moieties are incorporated into a single coordination metal complex to achieve multifunctionality. In this study, we synthesised a series of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conformational constraints in [Ni(P<sup>R</sup> <sub>2</sub>N<sup>R'</sup> <sub>2</sub>)<sub>2</sub>] complexes for tuning H<sub>2</sub> production and oxidation: a DFT-based ligand design study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[Ni(P^(R) (2)N^(R') (2))(2)] complexes catalyze H(2) production or oxidation depending on the nature of the two bidentate P(2)N(2) ligands. Ligand design plays a crucial role in determining the reaction direction and catalytic properties. In this study, density functional theory (DFT) calculations were performed to analyze the structural and energetic properties of Ni complexes with (R, R') = (H, H), (Me, Me), (Cy, Me), ( ^(t) Bu, Me), (CF(3), H), and (NH(2), H). Based on the structural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term scratching analysis of mice using machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pruritus is a bothersome symptom that can occur at any time and is caused by a variety of physical and mental disorders. There is an urgent need to elucidate the detailed pathophysiology using animal models. Using image analysis and machine learning, we analyzed the scratching behavior of BALB/c mouse under both light and dark conditions and objectively quantified persistency, strength, and amount of pruritus. A 24-h analysis in naive mice revealed that mice scratched themselves more frequently...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor from Sumi and Tominaga: "Tolvaptan versus fluid restriction in moderate-profound hyponatremia: An open-label randomized clinical trial"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41030047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategies for discontinuing vasopressin and norepinephrine during the recovery phase of shock: a single-center retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients recovering from shock who received both arginine vasopressin and norepinephrine, discontinuing arginine vasopressin first was not associated with a higher risk of hypotension.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The roles of tertiary lymphoid structures in orchestrating immune responses in peripheral organs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tertiary lymphoid structures (TLSs) are ectopic lymphoid aggregates that develop in non-lymphoid organs under pathological conditions of chronic inflammation, such as cancer, autoimmune diseases, chronic infections, organ transplantation, and age-related disorders. TLSs produce various cytokines and chemokines, and orchestrate local adaptive immune responses by serving as sites for antigen presentation. TLSs have attracted significant attention because of their multifaceted roles in various...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expert consensus statement on the evaluation, treatment, and transfer of cardiogenic shock using a Delphi method approach: a report of the Japan Critical Care Cardiology Committee (J4 CS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative efficacy of biologics for uncontrolled asthma patients with chronic rhinosinusitis or nasal polyps: a systematic review and network meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating malaria risk behaviours and their determinants among at-risk populations in a pre-elimination setting, Sisaket Province, Thailand-Cambodia border]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite overall moderate KAP levels, gaps in attitudes and risk behaviours persist. Targeted strategies, such as social and behaviour change communication, should focus on improving attitudes among individuals with low education levels and reducing risk behaviours among males and those with poor practices by promoting adherence to effective preventive measures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A survey on management of milk feeding, weaning and housing of conventional and organic dairy calves in Europe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Based on the respondents' evaluations the survey suggests that there are discrepancies between recommendations based on research and the current practices regarding milk allowance and feeding frequency, and weaning. Legislative or industry regulations on timing of separation from the dam, milk type, or weaning age are primarily implemented for organic production systems in a smaller proportion of countries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dose-response relationship between transfusion and the incidence of infection in critically ill patients: a systematic review and dose-response meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest a non-linear relationship between RBC transfusion volume and HAI risk in critically ill patients, highlighting the need for further research to inform individualized transfusion strategies. Clinical Trial Registration http://osf.io/a9cwd.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Classifying diarrhea in critically ill patients through various criteria: a cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Diarrhea prevalence varied from 9-39% across definitions. WHO and ESICM, both frequency‑based, differed from BSCS and weight‑based criteria. Given the difficulty of accurate frequency counting in ICU patients, consistency‑ or weight‑based definitions may offer a more practical alternative for both clinical practice and research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decisional conflicts of male patients undergoing Assisted Reproductive Technology: a qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: This study aimed to clarify the decisional conflicts of men undergoing Assisted Reproductive Technology (ART). We used a qualitative descriptive research design. The participants were 10 men who had received ART. Data were collected from June to August 2023 by conducting semistructured interviews using a guide. The inclusion criteria were male patients who have experienced various infertility treatments and are currently receiving ART and within 5 years of their infertility...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Granisetron for prevention of postoperative shivering in surgical patients: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41029227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of ERCC1 on the outcomes of chemotherapy in advanced biliary tract cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The phase III randomized trial, JCOG1113 has demonstrated the non-inferiority of gemcitabine and S-1 (GS) therapy to gemcitabine and cisplatin (GC) therapy for advanced biliary tract cancer (BTC). However, biomarkers for favorable therapy or to predict patient prognosis remain lacking. In this study, we evaluated five candidate biomarkers potentially involved in the efficacy of cisplatin or S-1 by immunostaining tumor specimens obtained from JCOG1113 participants. The participants were randomly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Outcome Measures for Gait and Spontaneous Locomotor Activity in Dystrophic Dogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital outcome measures utilizing digital devices and instruments are highly effective in capturing significant changes quantitatively in clinical trials of patients with Duchenne muscular dystrophy. A dystrophic model of beagle dogs, known as canine X-linked muscular dystrophy in Japan (CXMD(J)), shows the symptoms of muscle weakness and has been evaluated for motor function using these digital outcome measures to assess therapeutic efficacy and monitor disease progression circumstantially....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparation of Size-Defined PEG-Grafted Copolymers as a Polymeric Nanoruler for Size Optimization in Passive Targeting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Size-dependent (or passive) targeting strategies are a major approach for designing nanomedicines (or nanocarriers) that can systemically deliver drugs to lesion sites as well as solid tumors. However, the optimal size range for passive targeting to various noncancerous lesion sites is unclear. Recently, we fabricated poly(ethylene glycol) (PEG)-grafted copolymers (gPEGs) as a size-tunable "polymeric nanoruler" to clarify the optimal size for systemic inflamed/noninflamed muscle tissue...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lipidomic Sample Preparation to Detect Phosphatidylcholine Alterations in Skeletal Muscle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Altered phospholipid compositions in skeletal muscle occur in muscular dystrophy and other pathological conditions; however, origins and relationships to the disease course are unclear. Liquid chromatography-mass spectrometry (LC-MS) technologies allow the determination of phospholipid compositions and alteration patterns in disease states. Here, we describe a basic protocol to prepare methanolic extracts from skeletal muscle, which may be analyzed by lipidomic LC-MS in order to detect...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robotic para-aortic lymph node dissection via the left renal vein as the starting point]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preoperative chemotherapy combined with gastrectomy and radical surgery may be useful in patients with gastric cancer and metastasis-positive para-aortic lymph nodes. Although robotic surgery is considered useful in difficult cases because it provides highly magnified three-dimensional high-definition images of anatomical views and precise techniques, a meticulous approach for para-aortic lymph node dissection (PALND) is important. We typically perform PALND via the left renal vein at our...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-time inline-IR-analysis via linear-combination strategy and machineś learning for automated reaction optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Automation has revolutionized many fields by improving efficiency, accuracy, and reproducibility. However, in organic chemistry, automating key tasks such as reaction optimization and analysis remains a significant challenge. To accelerate advancements in organic chemistry research and development, we propose a fully automated system based on real-time inline analysis performed by Fourier-transform infrared spectroscopy and assisted by a neural network model. To rapidly collect data, a linear...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The safety and effectiveness of transcatheter renal arterial embolization with tris-acryl gelatin microspheres in hemodialysis patients with autosomal dominant polycystic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Renal TAE with tris-acryl gelatin microspheres is considered a safe and effective treatment for symptomatic enlarged PCKs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001151949&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning-Enhanced Surveillance for Surgical Site Infections in Patients Undergoing Colon Surgery: Model Development and Evaluation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ML models can augment traditional SSI surveillance by improving early identification of patients at high risk. The XGBoost model offered the best trade-off between discrimination and calibration, suggesting its utility in clinical workflows. Incorporating structured and unstructured electronic health record data enhances model accuracy and clinical relevance, supporting scalable and efficient infection control practices.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[According to Which Criteria Should the Undiagnosed Diseases Network's Value Be Assessed?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Undiagnosed Diseases Network (UDN) exists at an intersection of diagnostic research and clinical care and has 2 main goals: to advance diagnostic science and to facilitate accurate diagnoses in individual patient-participants with rare conditions or so-called "medical mysteries." The value of the UDN's translational research and clinical application model and of the results it produces derive from whether and to what extent the UDN achieves its 2 goals. This article considers criteria...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is the Nature and Scope of Physicians' Duties of Care to Patients Without a Diagnosis?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patients whose conditions are undiagnosed face stress and limited, delayed access to interventions that address their specific needs. This commentary on a case describes key ethical values that tend to conflict when clinicians try to care for patients with undiagnosed conditions and underscores the need for equitable, precise care plans when the sources and causes of patients' illness experiences are yet unknown.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Are Ethical Merits and Drawbacks of Viewing "Medical Mysteries" as Human Subject Research?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patient-subjects' participation in an Undiagnosed Diseases Network (UDN) protocol can afford access to innovative diagnostic techniques, especially in genomic medicine, which can shorten the time it takes to accurately diagnose a so-called "medical mystery." But UDN research processes can be complex and involve many variables, which can suggest to some patient-subjects that having enrolled in a UDN protocol was not worthwhile. This commentary on a case rife with diagnostic ambiguity offers a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measures of General Intelligence and Risk for Alcohol Use Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: IQ and cognitive performance have a significant but context-dependent association with AUD risk, highlighting the need for a better understanding of the interplay among genetic factors, cognitive traits, and sociocultural influences on AUD susceptibility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polygenic Susceptibility in Peripartum, Alcohol-Induced, and Cancer Therapy-Related Cardiomyopathies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study, individuals with PPCM, ACM, and CCM were enriched for monogenic DCM variants and a high DCM polygenic score, suggesting a shared genetic susceptibility influenced by distinct environmental precipitants. These findings support a shared genetic architecture between secondary cardiomyopathies and DCM, although additional work with larger numbers of individuals with cardiomyopathy is needed to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Reflex Reaction to Rational Action-Personalizing Surgical Antibiotic Prophylaxis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental Health Challenges of Muslim Populations Exposed to War and Discrimination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heart Rate Variability Biofeedback for Substance Use Disorder: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this randomized clinical trial, findings suggest second-generation HRVB can reduce negative affect, craving, and substance use among individuals in early recovery from SUD. HRVB appears to confer benefit in part by disrupting the association between craving and subsequent AOD use; these results support HRVB as a potentially efficacious treatment for SUD and warrant further investigation in phase 3 trials.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bariatric Surgery, Employment, and Productivity Outcomes: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Bariatric surgery demonstrates positive short-term impact on productivity and employment, but its long-term occupational benefits remain uncertain. Certain subgroups, such as females and older adults, may require tailored postsurgery support to sustain employment and productivity gains. These findings highlight the critical need for long-term strategies to sustain the occupational benefits postsurgery and to develop targeted interventions for at-risk populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Characteristics of Adults at Risk of Medicaid Disenrollment Due to HR 1 Work Requirements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Profiles in Nonverbal Learning Disability, Academic Skills, and Psychiatric Diagnoses in Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cross-sectional study of heterogeneity in NVLD, 3 profiles reflected NVLD and were differentially associated with psychiatric and academic outcomes. One profile (profile 4) showed no specific visual-spatial deficits and no associations between visual-spatial processing and functional domains, pointing to a need to consider a revision to the NVLD research criteria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Memantine to Treat Social Impairment in Youths With Autism Spectrum Disorder: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this trial, memantine was well tolerated and significantly improved social impairments in youths with ASD. Elevated pgACC glutamate levels were associated with a favorable treatment response, supporting their potential as a biomarker for assessing memantine efficacy in individuals with ASD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-Effectiveness of HPV Self-Testing Options for Cervical Cancer Screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this economic analysis of a randomized clinical trial, directly mailing HPV kits to individuals who were screening adherent and overdue for screening was economically dominant over other strategies. Program costs declined rapidly over 4 years. Results support directly mailing HPV kits to eligible individuals as an effective, efficient, and affordable outreach strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Dose Reduction or Discontinuation vs Maintenance Antipsychotics After First Psychotic Episode Remission: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This randomized clinical trial found that DRD posed risks of relapse and worse quality of life over the first year but yielded better researcher-rated functioning at the third and fourth year, with a similar trend for symptom severity; because antipsychotic medication doses were comparable in the 2 groups from 1 year onwards, this finding is not a direct result of lower medication but may reflect a learning experience to use antipsychotics to better handle psychotic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Risk of Mesh Infection Requiring Removal After Elective Ventral Hernia Repair]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These findings suggest that the risk of mesh removal is low overall, even for people who experience a wound complication. These findings support the broad use of mesh for people undergoing elective open ventral hernia repair.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hospital Market Competition, Morbidity, and Resource Utilization Following Elective Cancer Resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lenvatinib after progression on pemigatinib and futibatinib in FGFR2 fusion-positive biliary tract cancer with an acquired kinase point mutation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biliary tract cancers (BTC) represent a heterogeneous group of malignancies with a poor prognosis and rising incidence. Oncogenic FGFR2 fusions are one of several actionable molecular alterations. In this context, selective FGFR tyrosine kinase inhibitors have demonstrated promising and durable response rates and are now approved and included in clinical guidelines. However, secondary kinase mutations frequently arise over time, leading to resistance against these drugs. We present the case of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transitory Topochemical Tailoring of a van der Waals Superconductor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Topochemical intercalation is widely used to access metastable phases with novel electronic properties, but the reverse reaction (deintercalation) typically restores the original state, limiting practical use. Here, we present a topochemical approach that employs a sacrificial intercalant that thermally decomposes to irreversibly lock in the new electronic state. Using 2-aminobutane as the sacrificial intercalant, we convert the van der Waals (vdW) material 1T-TiSe(2) into a superconductor and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomic aging clocks and the risk of mortality among long-term cancer survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Proteomic aging clocks hold promise as a predictor of all-cause and cancer mortality in LTCS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A concise review of social validity assessments during functional analyses of challenging behavior]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This concise review summarizes the trends and outcomes of social validity assessments specifically related to functional analyses published between 2020 and 2024. Results indicate that very little data on the social validity of functional analyses have been published. However, data that have been published are generally positive. We conclude with discussion and recommendations for researchers and clinicians.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between depression and metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease: a cross-sectional analysis from the paracelsus 10,000 Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this large, population-based cross-sectional study, depressive symptoms were found to be associated with MASLD, independent of metabolic risk factors and antidepressant use. However, given the observational design and limited detail on antidepressant type, dose, indication, and adherence, the findings should be interpreted with caution and do not support causal conclusions. Nevertheless, findings suggest that mental health considerations may be relevant in MASLD screening and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic significance of age at diagnosis and preceding infection varies across age groups in childhood immune thrombocytopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intelligent extraction of CT image landmarks for improving cam-type femoroacetabular impingement assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results of this study are promising for future development of a CAD software application for screening CT scans that may aid physicians to assess FAI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Aptamer-Functionalized Fluorescent Silica Nanoparticles for Highly Sensitive Detection of Leukemia Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced lipid-based niosomes for enhanced transdermal delivery of olmesartan medoxomil via intracutaneous drug depot: a novel biomimicry approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Olmesartan medoxomil (OMN), a highly selective antihypertensive agent but, with problematic oral delivery due to its low solubility and limited bioavailability. Therefore, biomimetic lipid-based niosomes were adopted as a novel approach to enhance OMN solubility and boost its transdermal delivery (TD). Initially, conventional niosomes were prepared by thin film hydration method. Formulation parameters were adjusted to obtain entrapment efficiency (EE > 75%), particle size (PS < 300 nm), zeta...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research progress of exosomes used in the Alzheimer's disease treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a common form of dementia characterized by memory loss, cognitive and linguistic abilities declining and self-care capabilities diminishment. With the aging population globally, AD poses a significant threat to public health. Current treatments for AD aim to alleviate symptoms and slow down disease progression, but due to the limited understanding of underlying disease mechanisms, AD is still impossible to be cured yet. In recent years, there has been an exponential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting Future Performance in Powerlifting: A Machine Learning Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The developed machine learning model provides valid and accurate predictions of individual powerlifting performance, by accounting for various individual characteristics. The model can assist coaches and athletes in setting realistic training goals and monitoring progress. Moreover, normative data for each lift and total performance were provided, stratified by sex, age, weight category, and initial strength levels, offering valuable benchmarks for athletes and coaches.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glycoproteomics analysis of colorectal cancer reveals differential alterations of glycoproteins and glycans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colorectal cancer (CRC) remains a global health concern, with an urgent need for better early detection and targeted therapies. Our glycoproteomics analysis comparing CRC to paracancerous (PCA) tissue revealed significant alterations. Global proteomic analysis showed more unique proteins in CRC, with differential expression across CRC stages, especially in protein synthesis, translation, and degradation pathways. Despite overall proteomic differences, intact glycopeptide analysis showed high...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Prognostic value of dynamic minimal residual disease monitoring for adolescent and adult T-lymphoblastic leukemia/lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oroxylin A exerts antiproliferative effects through downregulation of E6 and E7 oncogenes in cervical cancer HeLa cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Numerous plant compounds have shown promising antitumor potential against cervical cancer. Plant-based compounds offer abundantly available, easy, and inexpensive methods of treatment over genome-editing technologies (immunotherapeutics). Many flavonoids directly abrogated HPV-E6/E7 activity with a concomitant apoptotic conclusion. Cervical cancer initiation and progression are entirely dependent on the oncogenes E6 and E7 (constitutively expressed) leading to tumorigenesis. Therefore, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of novel low-dose CT methods for quantifying bone marrow in the appendicular skeleton of patients with multiple myeloma: initial results from the [<sup>18</sup>F]FDG PET/CT sub-study of the Phase 3 GMMG-HD7 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Novel CT-based quantification approaches for assessing BM involvement in the appendicular skeleton correlate with key clinical and PET parameters in MM. As low-dose, standardized techniques, they show promise for inclusion in MM imaging protocols, potentially enhancing assessment of disease extent and treatment response.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-epitope vaccine construct against <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em>: insights from immunoinformatics and molecular dynamics simulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The persistent challenge posed by multi-drug resistant Staphylococcus aureus infections worldwide necessitates new solutions. We describe the creation of a multi-epitope vaccine aimed at offering cross-strain immunity. Antigens α-haemolysin (Hla) and staphylococcal enterotoxin B (SEB) were chosen considering their high immunodominance and sequence conservation levels. B-cell and T-cell epitopes were combined into a multi-epitope vaccine with the proper adjuvant and linker sequences included to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of organism aging on the development of anti-PD-(L)1 therapy-associated adverse events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immune checkpoint inhibitor (ICI)-mediated release of immune suppression involves the risk of (re)activating the immune responses to self-tissues, which are considered 'side effects' of this therapy, immune-related adverse events (irAEs). Although the incidence of certain types of irAEs appears to be considerably increased in older patients, the effect of chronological aging on irAE development and their causative immunological mechanism are unclear. This review summarizes the potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a decellularized liver matrix-based nanomedicine for metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The incidence of metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) has increased, primarily because of excessive nutritional intake and sedentary lifestyles. However, clinical trials investigating therapeutic agents for this condition have reported them to have limited efficacy. In this study, we developed a novel nanomedicine comprising tannic acid (TA) and a decellularized liver matrix-TD-Nm-to promote recovery from MASLD. TD-Nm was synthesized and characterized, and in vitro...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PTSD and Increased Incidence of Cardiovascular Disease: Independent Effects and Moderation of Risk by Comorbidities, Sex, and Age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PTSD and comorbidities independently predict hypertension and ASCVD, and sex, age, and comorbidities modify PTSD-hypertension relationships, thus suggesting that preventive interventions address both PTSD and comorbidities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The complete genome assembly of Astragalus membranaceus: enabling more accurate genetic research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This complete genome assembly of A. membranaceus represents a significant advancement in the genomic characterization of A. membranaceus, providing a robust resource that will bolster genetic research, breeding programs, and medicinal applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated vertical wheel bioreactor integrated with process analytics for T-cell manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This integrated bioreactor platform provides a proof-of-concept design for multiplexed PAT integration, process optimization and feedback-controlled intelligent automation to enable discovery, monitoring and control of critical quality attributes and critical process parameters for cell therapy manufacturing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41032004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does the New Clinical Obesity Definition Address the Obesity Paradox in Cardiovascular Health?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shift Work and the Risk of Kidney Stones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41031993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001151953&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>