<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 07:34:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data-driven machine learning models for predicting engineering properties in deep-sea sediments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Predicting the properties of deep-sea sediments offers critical insights into past oceanic conditions, including sediment composition, stratigraphy, and geochemical signals. However, accurate prediction is hindered by the high spatial variability of these sediments. This study presents a data-driven machine learning framework to predict five key sediment properties. Five prediction scenarios were developed with tailored preprocessing and hyperparameter tuning, and Shapley additive explanations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel method of quantifying retinal vascular tortuosity in retinopathy of prematurity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the diagnostic performance of a novel vessel tracing software that quantifies retinal vessel tortuosity in premature infants for assessing retinopathy of prematurity (ROP). Seventy-three retinal images of premature infants were subjectively classified as having "Normal" or "Abnormal" tortuosity based on arterial tortuosity of the posterior retina by seven clinicians. The software then semi-automatically traced the same arteries within circular regions of interest centered at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inactivation of CDK4/6, CDK2, and ERK in G1-phase triggers differentiation commitment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Terminal cell differentiation, a process vital for tissue development and regeneration where progenitor cells acquire specialized functions and permanently exit the cell cycle, remains poorly understood at the molecular level. Using live-cell imaging and adipogenesis as a model, we show that the initial stage involves a variable number of cell divisions, driven by redundant CDK4/6 or CDK2 activation. Afterwards, a delayed decrease in cyclin D1 and an increase in p27 levels reduce CDK4/6 and CDK2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MAML1 drives Notch and Hedgehog oncogenic pathways by inhibiting Itch activity in triple-negative breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC) is an aggressive and heterogeneous breast cancer subtype with poor patient outcomes. TNBC heterogeneity arises from multiple dysregulated pathways, including Notch and Hedgehog, which contribute to tumor initiation, progression, and drug resistance. Identifying common molecular regulators of TNBC aggressiveness is crucial for developing effective therapeutic strategies. Here, we demonstrate that the transcriptional coactivator MAML1 drives TNBC aggressiveness...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UFL1-mediated UFMylation antagonizes IFT88 ubiquitination and degradation to maintain ciliary homeostasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[UFMylation, a post-translational modification involving the covalent conjugation of ubiquitin-fold modifier 1 (UFM1) to target proteins, has been implicated in a wide spectrum of human diseases. However, the underlying molecular mechanisms are poorly understood. Herein, we demonstrate that UFM1-specific ligase 1 (UFL1), the sole ligase for UFMylation, is indispensable for ciliary homeostasis. Genetic ablation of UFL1 in mice results in severe defects in ciliary structure and function in multiple...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Lysogenic control of Bacillus subtilis morphology and fitness by Spbetavirus phi3T]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: On the replicability of diffusion weighted MRI-based brain-behavior models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microglia across evolution: from conserved origins to functional divergence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microglia, the resident immune cells of the central nervous system, exhibit conserved developmental origins and core molecular signatures across vertebrate species, highlighting their crucial importance in the central nervous system. While homeostatic microglia maintain similar functions during phylogeny-such as immune surveillance, debris clearance, and synaptic pruning-their morphology, gene expression, and responses to stimuli remarkably vary by species. These differences reflect evolutionary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating large scale genetic and clinical information to predict cases of heart failure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We demonstrate the additive power of integrating GWAS- and EHR-derived risk scores to predict HF cases prior to diagnosis. This standardizable and scalable risk predictor may enable physicians to provide earlier interventions to improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced heme production in industrial Saccharomyces cerevisiae through metabolic engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to develop an efficient Saccharomyces cerevisiae-based cell factory for heme production. The industrial strain S. cerevisiae KCCM 12638, a starter strain used in American whisky production, was selected for its naturally high heme concentration, and its medium composition was optimized. Next, CRISPR/Cas9-based genome editing was employed to enhance carbon flux through the heme biosynthetic pathway by overexpressing HEM2, HEM3, HEM12, and HEM13 genes, which encode key enzymes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simultaneous determination of 14 underivatized amino acids using ion-pairing chromatography and isotope dilution tandem mass spectrometry for a reference measurement procedure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We describe the simultaneous quantification of 14 underivatized amino acids (AAs) in various matrices using ion-pairing liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry (LC-MS/MS) combined with isotope dilution mass spectrometry (IDMS) as a newly developed reference measurement procedure. The underivatized AAs were successfully separated on a reversed-phase column using mixed ion-pairing reagents of trifluoroacetic acid and heptafluorobutyric acid within 6 min through optimized gradient elution....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of high-purity pyrethrins certified reference material]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Certified reference materials (CRMs) are essential for reliable pesticide residue analyses. For this study, we hypothesised that stable and high-purity pyrethrins CRM containing six target compounds could be developed through the chromatographic purification of pyrethrum and argon-purged packaging. The purities of total and individual pyrethrins were determined using mass balance and external calibration methods. The CRM properties were evaluated using an ISO-guided approach. The candidate CRM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of game-based VR simulation on nursing students' mastery of level D PPE: A quasi-experimental design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Incorporating game-based VR into nursing curricula significantly improved nursing students' procedural knowledge and problem-solving ability. This approach holds promise for enhancing learner preparedness and competence in infection control in high-risk clinical contexts, providing a scalable and accessible educational tool for contemporary nursing education.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roadmap towards personalized approaches and safety considerations in non-ionizing radiation: from dosimetry to therapeutic and diagnostic applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This roadmap provides a comprehensive and forward-looking perspective on the individualized application and safety of non-ionizing radiation (NIR) dosimetry in diagnostic and therapeutic medicine. Covering a wide range of frequencies, i.e., from low-frequency to terahertz, this document provides an overview of the current state of the art and anticipates future research needs in selected key topics of NIR-based medical applications. It also emphasizes the importance of personalized dosimetry,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A universal 2D-on-SiC platform for heterogeneous integration of epitaxial III-N membranes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonconventional epitaxial techniques, such as van der Waals epitaxy and remote epitaxy, have attracted substantial attention in the semiconductor research community for their capability to repeatedly produce high-quality freestanding films from a single mother wafer. Successful implementation of these techniques depends on creating a robust, uniform two-dimensional (2D) material surface. The conventional method for fabricating graphene on silicon carbide (SiC) is high-temperature graphitization....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive in silico analysis of Acinetobacter isolates from South Korea reveals genomic diversity, antimicrobial resistance, virulence factors, and evolutionary dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brentuximab vedotin combined with cisplatin, cytarabine, and dexamethasone treatment in transplant-eligible Korean patients with relapsed or refractory Hodgkin's lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite its encouraging early efficacy, the administration of BV-DHAP in Korean patients with RRHL requires careful monitoring due to toxicity concerns.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic substrate design for enhanced mechanical and optical stability in island-bridge stretchable displays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Island-bridge designs are regarded as promising platforms for stretchable displays, but their mechanical and optical reliability is limited by two distinct failure modes: interfacial delamination, driven by localized strain concentration due to mechanical mismatch, and the substrate sagging, resulting from insufficient elastic recovery after repeated stretching. In this study, an island-bridge stretchable display that incorporates a multi-covalently crosslinked polyurethane is presented, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Predictors of Malignancy in Main Duct-Involved IPMN: The Critical Role of MPD Diameter Changes in a Multicenter Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dynamic MPD monitoring is essential for assessing malignancy risk in patients with MPD-involved IPMN. An MPD growth rate of ≥ 2 mm/year was the strongest predictor of malignant transformation, underscoring the value of longitudinal surveillance over static MPD diameter thresholds. Patients with rapid MPD growth should be considered for early surgical intervention or intensified monitoring to improve clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of conserved residues essential for the ciliogenic functions of WDPCP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we report a genetically engineered mouse model expressing a mutant Wdpcp gene that harbors a deletion of two codons encoding D481 and W482 that correspond to N512 and W513 in human WDPCP. Homozygous mutant mice, designated as Wdpcp-Z11, exhibited severe developmental abnormalities, including neural tube defects, craniofacial malformation, anophthalmia and polydactyly. The mutant WDPCP protein was expressed but failed to dock to the apical surface of the cell. Cilia formation and Hh...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NDST3-Induced Epigenetic Reprogramming Reverses Neurodegeneration in Parkinson's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parkinson's disease (PD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder characterized by the loss of dopaminergic neurons (DN) in the substantia nigra and disruption of cellular maintenance. Here, we demonstrate that NDST3-mediated epigenetic reprogramming halts neuronal degeneration and restores motor function in an animal model of PD. Following NDST3 administration, the DN and its associated circuits in the substantia nigra and striatum showed marked revitalization, accompanied by a considerable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optically-Coupled X-Ray Computed Laminography System for High-Speed Inspection of Lithium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional X-ray computed tomography systems for microstructure inspection typically employ a geometrically magnified imaging setup, requiring a micro-focus X-ray source to mitigate image blurring caused by a finite focal spot size. However, due to its low output power, the micro-focus X-ray source results in prolonged image acquisition times. This study presents a novel optically-coupled X-ray computed laminography system for high-speed inspection. In the proposed system, a scintillator is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Policy Inaction Risks Breaching the 2°C Climate Target]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite repeated increases in national climate pledges since the Paris Agreement, a significant gap remains between collective ambition and the action required to meet its temperature goals. Integrating these pledges with global models, we show that full implementation would still lead to approximately 1.7°C of warming, missing the 1.5°C target. When considering ongoing policy inaction, a cumulative shortfall of 505 GtCO(2)e in anticipated mitigation is expected, and this warming increases by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the <em>Panax ginseng</em> Meyer soil metagenome to uncover antagonistic bacteria against ginseng root rot disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Bacillus velezensis ARRI17 is an effective biocontrol agent that promotes ginseng growth and enhances disease resistance. Its natural compatibility with traditional farming practices, especially its presence with rice straw compost, positions ARRI17 as a promising and sustainable alternative.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean red ginseng extract suppresses food allergy by remodeling the gut microbiota and restoring immune homeostasis in IL4ra<sup>F709</sup> mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: KRGE mitigates FA in IL4ra^(F709) mice by restoring gut microbiota balance and immune homeostasis, suggesting its potential as a microbiota-targeted intervention for FA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[pH-activated liquid microdroplet carrier for enhanced phycocyanin oral delivery and sustained bioactivity post-digestion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although C-phycocyanin (PC) possesses various therapeutic functions, it is highly unstable under gastrointestinal (GI) conditions involving digestive enzymes and pH variations, leading to rapid degradation and subsequent loss of bioactivity before absorption. A protective oral delivery system is therefore essential to enhance its bioavailability and delivery efficiency. In this study, a water-immiscible, pH-responsive microdroplet system was developed using fish gelatin (FG) and fucoidan (FC) as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of pexophagy by a novel TBK1-MARCHF7-PXMP4-NBR1 Axis in PEX1-depleted HeLa cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peroxisomes are essential for lipid metabolism and redox balance, with pexophagy playing a critical role in maintaining cellular homeostasis. However, the regulatory mechanisms of pexophagy remain unclear. Through functional screening, we identified MARCHF7 as a novel E3 ligase regulating pexophagy. MARCHF7 depletion impaired pexophagic flux under PEX1 knockdown conditions. MARCHF7 binds to PXMP4 and promotes its ubiquitination at lysine 20 in PEX1-deficient cells. Depletion of PXMP4 impairs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of photobiomodulation therapy for ophthalmic diseases: protocol for a systematic review and meta-analysis of disease-specific and shared physiological outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Photobiomodulation therapy (PBMT)-a noninvasive therapeutic strategy-employs low-level red or near-infrared light to regulate cellular bioenergetics, reduce oxidative stress, and modulate inflammation. It has demonstrated therapeutic potential for several ophthalmic diseases, including age-related macular degeneration, diabetic retinopathy, glaucoma, retinitis pigmentosa, and dry eye disease. However, the clinical evidence remains fragmented due to heterogeneity in study designs,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a health literacy-based hypertension self-management education program using sign language for Deaf individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The H-SMILE program is designed for Deaf individuals with hypertension and may be particularly beneficial for those with limited health literacy who use sign language. The program, validated by experts and evaluated in a pilot test showing high satisfaction scores and strong feasibility, appears to be a promising intervention with the potential to enhance health literacy, promote self-management behaviors, and improve health outcomes among Deaf individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imputation disparities driven by recent selection and their impact on disease risk estimation in East and Southeast Asian populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate genotype imputation is essential for large-scale genetic studies and precision medicine. While East Asian (EAS)-specific reference panels like ChinaMAP and CHN100k have been developed, most studies still rely on multi-ancestry panels like TOPMed due to the large sample size. However, their performance in underrepresented groups like Southeast Asians remains unclear. Using high-coverage whole-genome sequencing and SNP-array data from 8,316 Chinese and Thai individuals, we systematically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic effects of graphene oxide loading and particle size in ice-templated carboxymethyl cellulose-based aerogels on dye removal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainable carboxymethyl cellulose/graphene oxide (GO) aerogels were fabricated via epichlorohydrin cross-linking and ice-templating for effective methylene blue (MB) removal from aqueous solutions. The synergistic effects of GO loading (1, 3, and 5 wt%) and particle size (500, 10, and 1 nm) on the structural, mechanical, and adsorption properties of aerogels were systematically explored. The optimal dye adsorption capacity (555.6 mg/g) was obtained at 3 wt% GO loading, owing to enhanced π-π...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Independent associations of physical activity and depression with open-angle glaucoma in a population-based analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patients with open-angle glaucoma (OAG), a chronic visual impairment, are at elevated risk of developing depression. Physical activity (PA) has been associated with benefits for mental health, but evidence is limited regarding its impact on depression risk in individuals with OAG. This study aimed to assess the association between PA and incident depression in a nationwide cohort of patients newly diagnosed with OAG. We conducted a retrospective cohort study using customized data from the Korean...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare utilization and costs after cranial epilepsy surgery and vagus nerve stimulation in pediatric drug-resistant epilepsy: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pediatric drug-resistant epilepsy (DRE) affects 30-40% of children with epilepsy, resulting in medical costs significantly higher than those of controlled epilepsy. Cranial epilepsy surgery (CES) and vagus nerve stimulation (VNS) are key interventions; however, their long-term economic impact remains ambiguous. Using South Korea's National Health Insurance claims data (2007-2022), we examined healthcare utilization and costs among children with DRE treated with antiseizure medications (ASM)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sucrose supplementation mitigates heat stress-induced alterations in rumen metabolism and immunity in dairy cows]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rapid global warming is affecting the metabolic and immune responses of dairy cows, making heat stress a major challenge in the industry. This study aimed to develop nutritional strategies to mitigate these effects. Sucrose has been identified as a carbohydrate that not only provides immediate energy to the rumen. Specifically, we investigated whether sucrose supplementation could alleviate heat stress-induced changes in rumen metabolism and blood immune parameters. A total of 12 Holstein cows...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lab-in-a-cartridge for real-time detection of tuberculosis via precise measurement of urinary lipoarabinomannan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current methods for detecting Mycobacterium tuberculosis (M.tb) in centralized medical facilities are a bottleneck in TB surveillance, particularly in resource-constrained regions. In response, we present a groundbreaking portable bio-tool, the lab-in-a-cartridge (LIC) system, designed for on-site detection of lipoarabinomannan (LAM) in trace amounts within the urine. The innovative design combines pumpless liquid handling and magnetic force-based enrichment with horseradish peroxidase polymer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomechanical properties of 3D-printed resin composites compared with subtractive CAD/CAM materials and direct light-cured composites: Color stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: This study aimed to evaluate the color stability of four three-dimensionally-printed (3D) resin composites, and compare them with nine other commonly used subtractive computer-aided designing/computer-aided manufacturing (CAD/CAM) materials and resin composites for direct restoration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Safety of Carfilzomib in Patients with Multiple Myeloma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this large real-world PSM analysis, carfilzomib was not associated with an increased risk of individual CV outcomes compared with other PIs, but it was linked to a higher incidence of all-cause 3P-MACE, underscoring the need for careful CV monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing generative AI for quality of life assessment: Foundations for a new research agenda]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Camostat mesylate restores intestinal barrier integrity and attenuated protein loss in experimental protein-losing enteropathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein-losing enteropathy (PLE) is a serious complication following the Fontan operation for single-ventricle congenital heart disease, characterized by excessive gastrointestinal protein loss, intestinal lymphangiectasia, and impaired epithelial barrier function. Dysregulated protease activity has been implicated in the pathogenesis of intestinal barrier disruption, suggesting protease inhibition as a potential therapeutic strategy. Here, we established a dextran sulfate sodium (DSS)-induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of the 2023-2024 monovalent XBB.1.5 vaccine against SARS-CoV-2 infection in people aged over 65 years in South Korea: A population-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings support continued COVID-19 vaccination efforts, particularly in older adults. Regular vaccination remains essential to maintaining immunity and mitigating transmission, guiding future strategies against emerging SARS-CoV-2 variants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the effectiveness of automatic and manual plasma-treated hydrogen peroxide mist disinfection in various teaching hospital environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Automated PTHPM disinfection can be as effective as manual PTHPM disinfection in eliminating microbial contamination in teaching hospital environments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interplay of nitric oxide and indole-3-acetic acid signaling in regulating arsenate toxicity in tomato seedlings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The problem of arsenic contamination is widespread, posing serious risks to both human health and crop productivity. Therefore, eco-friendly strategies are urgently needed to reduce metal stress-related yield losses and minimize its impacts on human health. Although the roles of nitric oxide (NO) and indole-3-acetic acid (IAA) in combating abiotic stresses, including metal toxicity, have been reported, the mechanisms underlying their interaction remain unclear. This study investigates whether...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[χ-separation Insights into Whole-brain Characterization of Age-related Patterns of Susceptibility in Healthy Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantitative Susceptibility Mapping (QSM) enables noninvasive assessment of brain tissue composition, but conventional approaches provide only a composite measure that merges paramagnetic and diamagnetic contributions, limiting biological specificity. Recent advances in χ-separation overcome this limitation by separating χ-paramagnetic (χ-para) and χ-diamagnetic (χ-dia) components within a single voxel. This study aimed to comprehensively characterize age-related trajectories of paramagnetic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cortical oscillations predict auditory grouping in listeners with various hearing configurations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Auditory grouping relies on the ability to bind tones with coherent spectral features over time to form auditory objects. Sensorineural hearing loss (SNHL) degrades spectral resolution, and the extent of this degradation varies with the hearing configuration. However, it remains unclear how SNHL impacts auditory grouping and whether different hearing configurations affect this ability. This study investigated task performance and cortical activity during auditory object detection in four groups...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Accuracy of the SARC-CalF in Community-Dwelling Older Adults: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: The Sarcopenia and Calf Circumference (SARC-CalF) tool has been proposed to enhance the detection of sarcopenia. A comprehensive systematic review evaluating the diagnostic performance of the SARC-CalF could support its broader adoption as a valid screening instrument. Thus, this study aimed to assess the diagnostic accuracy of the SARC-CalF in detecting sarcopenia risk among older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A systematic evidence map of air pollution studies on various ocular diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eyes may be more susceptible to environmental chemicals, including air pollutants, than other organs because of the nature of their direct exposure to the external environment. Although the ocular effects of air pollution are increasingly recognized, studies that have systematically synthesized previous findings are limited. This study aimed to identify research gaps about the impact of air pollution on ocular diseases in epidemiological and animal experimental studies using a systematic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Density functional modelling of lead-free Sn-based AmSnX<sub>3</sub> (Am=Rb, Cs; X=Cl, Br, I) perovskites as sustainable materials for optoelectronics and solar cell applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This research uses density functional theory to examine the structural, electronic, optical, mechanical, thermodynamic, thermoelectric, magnetic, and photovoltaic properties of Sn-based AmSnX(3) (Am = Rb, Cs; X = Cl, Br, I) perovskites. The tolerance factor (0.71-1.04) and the negative cohesive energy confirm the materials' structural and thermodynamic stability. The electronic properties show semiconducting behavior, with energy band gaps of 0.42 eV for RbSnBr3 and 1.02 eV for CsSnCl(3). The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-low-dose computed tomography (CT) protocol for guiding cryoablation in treating a T1a renal cell carcinoma (RCC): radiation doses and treatment outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ultra-low-dose CT-guided cryoablation contributes to significant dose reduction without compromising oncologic outcomes of small RCCs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystal structure of Bacillus dafuensis Thoeris B1 protein in complex with NAD<sup></sup>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Type 1 Thoeris defense system is an NAD^(+)-based innate immune mechanism that protects bacterial populations against viral infection by triggering NAD^(+) depletion-induced cell death. Central to this system is the TIR domain-containing protein Ths B, which uses NAD^(+) to synthesize a cyclic ADPR (cADPR) signal upon sensing viral antigens. However, the structural basis of NAD^(+) binding by Ths B remains poorly understood. Here, we report the 1.54 Å resolution X-ray crystal structure of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inappropriate antibiotic prophylaxis before dental procedures in congenital heart disease: Insights from a nationwide Korean cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A high proportion of dental AP prescriptions for Korean patients with CHD are still inappropriate according to the 2007 AHA guideline, particularly among pediatric populations and in primary-care clinics. Targeted stewardship-focused on pediatric dentists and clinic settings-is imperative to curb unnecessary antibiotic exposure while preserving prophylaxis for truly high-risk patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-surgical treatment of adult skeletal class III patient with severe alveolar bone loss by sequential segmental displacement and third molar extraction: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Compromised periodontal conditions pose challenges in orthodontic treatment. In particular, maxillomandibular skeletal discrepancies may require large-scale tooth movement, making it essential to avoid round-tripping movements to minimize dental and periodontal side effects. This case report describes a 49-year-old male patient with skeletal Class III malocclusion and severe alveolar bone loss, particularly affecting the anterior teeth, who sought non-surgical treatment with aesthetic lingual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hot melt extrusion-enhanced Angelica gigas alleviates benign prostatic hyperplasia via AR/ERK signaling: A network pharmacology-based mechanistic study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Benign prostatic hyperplasia (BPH) is a prevalent age-related condition in men that leads to various urinary symptoms. Although current BPH treatments provide moderate effectiveness, they are often accompanied by undesirable side effects, highlighting the need for alternative therapeutic strategies. This study investigates the potential of Angelica gigas Nakai (AG), processed using hot melt extrusion (HME) to enhance its bioavailability and pharmacological activity, for the prevention of BPH. To...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural network disruption after optic neuritis in Myelin oligodendrocyte glycoprotein antibody associated disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study indicates that MOGAD-ON patients experience significant disruptions in WM networks, particularly in the left temporal and occipital lobes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Prognostic Value of the Clinical Frailty Scale in Critically Ill Older Adult Patients in the Emergency Department]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher CFS scores were significantly associated with increased 3-month mortality among critically ill older ED patients, highlighting the prognostic value of the CFS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting Older Adults' Characteristics Using SARs Through Conversational Interaction: A Mixed-Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined how older adults engage with socially assistive robots (SARs) using a mixed-methods approach that integrated survey data, behavioral logs, and conversational data. Among 191 participants aged 65 and older, 40.8% actively interacted with the Hyodol SAR. Discriminant analysis identified education level, life satisfaction, and early usage frequency as key predictors of engagement. K-means clustering revealed three distinct user profiles: Social Engagers, who prioritized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations Between Cigarette Smoking and Poor Sleep Among Adults With a Lifetime Cancer Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270207/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Smoking among adults with a lifetime cancer diagnosis is correlated with poor sleep, highlighting the need for targeted smoking cessation interventions to improve sleep health in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270207/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glucose-Powered Ultrasmall Chemotactic Nanorobots for Retinal Degeneration Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retinal degeneration poses a growing global health challenge with limited effective treatments. Current options, such as intravitreal injections of therapeutic drugs, are severely constrained by the vitreous humor barrier, a dense, gel-like matrix that limits drug diffusion to the retina. Micro/nanorobots with active propulsion have emerged as promising platforms for targeted drug delivery to overcome biological barriers. Here, we report the design of chemotactic nanorobots that can actively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationships between growth mindsets and math achievement across socioeconomic status in 74 countries: Evidence from PISA 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Growth mindsets have gained attention from education stakeholders due to their potential to enhance academic outcomes. However, some studies found that the relationship between mindsets and student achievement varied by socioeconomic status, while others found no association. As a result, it remains unclear whether growth mindsets are more beneficial for students from higher- or lower-socioeconomic backgrounds, or whether their benefits are consistent across all socioeconomic groups. This paper...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical impact of prophylactic antibiotics in kidney transplantation: A retrospective observational cohort study with historical comparison]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this study, we observed that a single dose of cefazolin as perioperative antibiotic prophylaxis may lead to higher rates of postoperative urinary tract infections, but it could potentially lower the incidence of acute rejection within six months.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling the Structure of Λ Hyperons with Polarized ΛΛ[over ¯] Pairs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With data collected in a dedicated energy scan from 2.3864 up to 3.0800 GeV, the BESIII Collaboration provides the first complete energy-dependent measurements of the Λ electromagnetic form factors in the timelike region. By combining double-tag and single-tag events from the e^{+}e^{-}→ΛΛ[over ¯]→pπ^{-}p[over ¯]π^{+} reaction, we achieve a complete decomposition of the spin structure of the reaction at five energy points, with high statistical and systematic precision. Our data reveal that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal transformation of mitochondrial metabolism during neurogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neural stem cells (NSCs) are valuable in the quest to conquer neurodegenerative diseases due to their capability to reconstruct the damaged neuronal networks. However, deep understanding of the intercellular signaling mechanism controlling the lineage and fate of the stem cells is required before potential clinical applications. Here, we applied nondestructive and label-free electrochemical methods for the longitudinal tracking of NSC respiratory metabolism. Sharp change in the oxygen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk stratification of low-dose cytarabine and venetoclax in patients with AML ineligible for intensive chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prognostic risk categorization aids treatment selection for patients with acute myeloid leukemia (AML). Although the European LeukemiaNet (ELN) classifications (2017, 2022) for AML have been used to stratify outcomes for patients receiving intensive chemotherapy, application to patients receiving less intensive therapy, like azacitidine plus venetoclax, has been less satisfactory. In response, a 4-gene classifier that stratifies older patients with AML unfit for intensive chemotherapy into those...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automation of electrothermal cell sheet manipulator for seamless tissue assembly and handling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The manipulation of fragile biological tissues such as engineered cell sheets remains a major challenge for regenerative medicine and tissue engineering. Manual handling with tools like tweezers often induces wrinkling or tearing, compromising tissue integrity. Here, we present an automated cell sheet manipulator that integrates a thermoresponsive microchanneled poly(N-isopropylacrylamide) (PNIPAAm) hydrogel with an embedded microheater, mounted on a programmable three-axis motorized stage. Upon...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differences in symptom experiences and coping strategies based on post-traumatic growth and depreciation in cancer patients undergoing chemotherapy: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study highlights the importance of tailored psychological assessment for cancer patients. Understanding the distinct symptom experiences and coping strategies of different PTG-PTD clusters can guide the development of individualized nursing interventions that enhance patient well-being and recovery. Findings offer practical guidance for effective psychosocial support and holistic cancer care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-based exploration of volatile flavor diversity from food yeast species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Yeast shares a longer than 10 000-year history with humans in food fermentation by producing various volatile flavor compounds that contribute to the final taste and aroma of foods. Yeast-associated volatile flavor compounds include esters, benzenoids, sulfur compounds, and phenolic derivatives, and these enhance the sensory complexity of fermented foods and beverages. Genome-scale technologies have advanced and transformed our understanding of the genetic and evolutionary drivers of volatile...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia as a major comorbidity in late-onset epilepsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epilepsy is more common in the elderly population, with a higher prevalence of epilepsy-related neurological diseases, such as stroke and traumatic brain injury. Although dementia is also known to be a potential cause of epilepsy in the elderly, estimating its accurate contribution is challenging because of its high prevalence in the general elderly population. To characterize the clinical features of patients with comorbid dementia, we compared the characteristics of these patients with those...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obesity phenotypes and atherogenic dyslipidemias]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Atherogenic dyslipidemias are a hallmark of high-risk obesity phenotypes and a major contributor to ASCVD within the CKM framework. Precision medicine approaches that incorporate obesity phenotyping, targeted treatment strategies and population-level interventions are needed to reduce the burden of dyslipidemias and their cardiovascular sequelae.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Two Synthetic Routes to a Benzofuran Intermediate for Fruquintinib]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two practical routes were developed for the synthesis of a key benzofuran intermediate used to prepare fruquintinib, both of which commence from readily available monoprotected resorcinol derivatives. The first route involves constructing a 2-methylbenzofuran-3-carboxylic acid core from 2-bromo-5-methoxyphenol and a 2-butynoic acid derivative using Michael addition chemistry, followed by intramolecular Heck cyclization. Final deprotection afforded the benzofuran intermediate in 45% overall yield...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxygen-free discontinuous dewetting in a degassed mold for anisotropic colloidal hydrogel microparticle synthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anisotropic colloidal hydrogel microparticles offer unique advantages owing to their shape-dependent interactions, and enhanced diffusion and reaction kinetics, which is favorable in solution-based processes. However, their fabrication remains difficult, mainly due to limitations of surface energy and oxygen inhibition. In this study, we present a versatile synthesis platform for anisotropic colloidal hydrogel microparticles using oxygen-free discontinuous dewetting in a degassed mold. By a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Noise Suppression in Organic Photodiodes: A Comprehensive Review of Mechanistic Insights and Design Principles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic photodiodes (OPDs) are emerging as leading candidates for next-generation image sensors owing to their tunable photophysical properties, which enable broadband detection from the visible to X-ray regimes and open new possibilities for intelligent systems such as fingerprint sensing, gesture recognition, and medical imaging. Across these applications, minimizing the dark current density (J(d)) is of paramount importance, as it sets the noise floor, while thermal and low-frequency noises...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Datopotamab deruxtecan versus docetaxel for non-small cell lung cancer: a plain language summary of the TROPION-Lung01 study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Disease Distribution Matters for PCI Outcomes: Lessons From PPG-Based Prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Net Water Uptake With Catastrophic Functional Outcome After Thrombectomy in Patients With Large Infarcts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Elevated ASPECTS10-NWU is strongly associated with catastrophic functional outcome in patients with large infarcts treated with endovascular thrombectomy. Integrating the ASPECTS10-NWU with clinical variables may provide patient-specific prognostication that may assist clinicians in decision-making for endovascular thrombectomy in large infarcts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six Unrecorded Species of Polyporales (Agaricomycetes, Basidiomycota) from Mudeungsan National Park in Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The order Polyporales is a diverse group of macrofungi, comprising approximately 2500 species worldwide. The majority of these species are wood-decaying saprotrophs that contribute to the carbon cycle by degrading lignin, cellulose, and hemicellulose. They also produce valuable enzymes with wide industrial applications. Despite their ecological and industrial importance, the diversity of Polyporales in Republic of Korea remains relatively understudied compared to the global scale. Mudeungsan, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptomic analysis of skin biopsies in Prurigo nodularis patients: with and without atopic dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results provide insight into the molecular mechanisms of PN, particularly in the context of atopic dermatitis, and highlight that immune dysregulation and impaired skin barrier function are key factors in pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Prospective Cohort Study on the Usage, Safety, and Efficacy of Delamanid in Patients With Pulmonary Multidrug-Resistant Tuberculosis in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Delamanid demonstrated favorable safety and efficacy profiles for MDR-TB treatment under programmatic conditions, providing valuable and up-to-date evidence supporting its promising role in MDR-TB management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive review of the effects of <em>Panax ginseng</em> and its constituents against inflammatory diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unresolved inflammation can progress into severe diseases that need safer and more effective therapeutic strategies. The adverse effects of conventional anti-inflammatory agents have evoked interest in natural products as alternatives. Panax ginseng is a traditional medical herb famous for its diverse pharmacological properties. This review comprehensively discusses the anti-inflammatory effects of P. ginseng and its constituents against inflammatory bowel disease, hepatitis, sepsis, gastritis,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetics and pharmacological activities of protopanaxatriol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protopanaxatriol (PPT) is an active metabolite derived from protopanaxatriol-type ginsenosides from Panax ginseng, displaying broad range of pharmacological activities against various diseases with higher efficacy. Since ginsenosides are known to be active components from ginseng, exploring biological activities and functions of the components could be important in terms of understanding ginseng's pharmacological roles. In this review, we aimed to report biological role of PPT by analyzing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of white ginseng on reducing stress and tension by enhancing default mode network connectivity: A randomized, double-blinded placebo-controlled clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings of this study suggest that PGC has the potential to mitigate stress and tension, potentially through the modulation of DMN functional connectivity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean red ginseng mitigates pulmonary injury and enhances antiviral immunity in a low-dose pseudo-type SARS-CoV-2 infection model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Korean red ginseng modulates immune responses and promotes long-term immunity against low-dose PSV infection. Our data also support the potential of Korean red ginseng as a complementary therapeutic strategy for COVID-19 and an enhancer of vaccine efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of the MIND Diet on the Cognitive Function of Older Adults: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Mediterranean-DASH Intervention for Neurodegenerative Delay (MIND) diet is a brain-focused dietary pattern designed to prevent cognitive decline in older adults. This systematic review, conducted in accordance with Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses guidelines, aimed to examine the association between the MIND diet and cognitive function in older adults. Relevant studies published between 2015 and 2024 were identified through comprehensive searches of PubMed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Impact of Nutritional Intervention on Pressure Injury Healing in a Paraplegic Patient: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pressure injuries are common complications in patients with limited mobility, particularly those who are bedridden. These wounds not only cause pain and reduce quality of life but also lead to prolonged hospitalization, increased risk of infection, and higher healthcare costs. Among the various contributing factors, malnutrition plays a crucial role by impairing collagen synthesis, weakening immune function, and delaying tissue repair. Adequate nutritional support-particularly sufficient protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Secular Trends in Dietary Patterns Among Korean Adolescents: Using Data From the 2007-2022 Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to identify major dietary patterns among Korean adolescents, examine their changes over the past 16 years, and evaluate differences by sex. Data were analyzed from 7,679 adolescents aged 12-18 years who participated in the 2007-2022 Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey and completed health, examination, and nutrition surveys. Dietary intake was assessed using a 24-hour recall, and cluster analysis was performed based on the energy contribution of 26 food...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unstable occult scaphoid fracture diagnosed by dynamic point-of-care ultrasound: a case report and review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case report highlights the pivotal role of dynamic musculoskeletal ultrasound as an adjunct in the diagnostic algorithm for acute wrist trauma. It demonstrates its ability not only to identify a radiographically occult scaphoid fracture but, more critically, to provide immediate functional information about mechanical stability. This information is paramount for guiding appropriate and timely management to mitigate the risk of long-term complications. We advocate for the broader...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing musical creativity through AI: a chain-mediation model of self-efficacy and emotional intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The rapid advancement of AI technology is fundamentally transforming traditional music creation and influencing music education. However, whether and how the use of AI genuinely enhances musical creativity remains a subject for further exploration. This study aims to investigate the impact of AI usage on the musical creativity of music majors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[of Asia: Provision of Patient-Centered Care in Oral Cavity Cancer: A Qualitative Study With Patients, Caregivers, and Healthcare Professionals in Five Asia-Pacific Regions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study examined LA-OCSCC care management in five Asia-Pacific countries/territories with varying healthcare systems and infrastructure. Given LA-OCSCC's aggressive nature and high burden from disease and treatment, patients and caregivers require support beyond medical interventions. A multi-stakeholder approach with clinical and community care is essential to ensure a comprehensive and sustainable approach to patient-centered care within the different health systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triple Amperometric Microsensor for Simultaneous Real-Time In Vivo Monitoring of NO, CO, and H<sub>2</sub>S During Epileptic Seizures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitric oxide (NO), carbon monoxide (CO), and hydrogen sulfide (H(2)S) are endogenous gaseous signaling molecules, playing crucial roles in a wide range of biological processes. This study presents the fabrication and evaluation of a triple amperometric microsensor capable of the simultaneous and selective detection of NO, CO, and H(2)S for in vivo applications. The sensor integrates three platinum working electrodes into a single device. Each electrode was independently modified with specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Ultrasound-guided Superficial Cervical Plexus Block on Early Postoperative Recovery in Patients Undergoing Microvascular Decompression: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Superficial CPB did not improve early postoperative QoR in patients undergoing MVD. However, it reduced the incidence of PONV during the early postoperative period, which could potentially enhance patient comfort and satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Influencing Cultural Intelligence Among Nurses in Western Pacific Countries: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings emphasize the need for healthcare institutions to implement structured educational programs to enhance nurses' cultural intelligence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: 2025 position statement on active outdoor play]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Readability and information quality of LLM-Generated HIV content: a methodological content evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41266988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41266988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between psychological disorders and migraine in young U.S. adults with gender-specific analysis and marital status considerations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41266965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights distinct gender-based psychological correlates of migraine and reveals the social context of marital status as a potential modifier. These findings underscore the need for sex-sensitive and psychosocially informed strategies in migraine assessment and intervention, aligning with biopsychosocial models of pain and the goals of integrated headache care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41266965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two-photon induced coherence without induced emission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[At the heart of recent advances in quantum imaging and spectroscopy with undetected photons is the quantum optical effect known as induced coherence without induced emission. This quantum interference effect has enabled access to challenging wavelength regimes for imaging and spectroscopic applications. However, the potential of undetected photon quantum metrology, particularly the enhanced phase sensitivity offered by Fock or N00N states, has not yet been realized, as prior work focused only on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic nutritional index in risk of mortality following fulminant myocarditis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fulminant myocarditis (FM) is an acute fatal inflammation disease, but its chronic phase is unclear. A Japanese nationwide registry evaluated the long-term mortality in FM patients using a prognostic nutritional index (PNI). The retrospective cohort study included patients with clinically suspected or histologically proven FM available for PNI. PNI was assessed on admission and at discharge. We divided patients into two groups based on PNI at discharge (PNI ≤ 40 or PNI > 40) and analyzed the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bifurcation-based wide-range vacuum pressure micro-sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41272070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lung tissue T cells are activated in chronic obstructive pulmonary disease with non-small cell lung cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) is characterized by chronic inflammation of the respiratory tract and is associated with an increased risk of lung cancer. Non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) patients with COPD have been shown to exhibit favorable responses to anti-PD-1/PD-L1 therapy. In the present study, we investigated T cell profiles and functions in the lung tissues of NSCLC patients with or without COPD to provide the rationale for immunotherapy of NSCLC patients with COPD....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amniotic membrane transplantation promotes retinal hole closure in a rabbit model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amniotic membrane transplantation (AMT) is an effective treatment for refractory macular hole closure, yet the underlying mechanism supporting that effectiveness remains unclear. Here, we investigated the role of retinal regeneration in this process using an in vivo rabbit retinal-hole (RH) model in which AMT was performed on one of the holes. Histological and immunofluorescence examinations with anti-glial fibrillary acidic protein and anti-glutemine synthetase antibodies were conducted to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Finerenone ameliorates diabetic kidney disease exacerbated by deletion of natriuretic peptide/guanylyl cyclase-A signaling and dietary high-protein load]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Excessive protein intake is one of the main accelerators for chronic kidney disease including diabetic kidney disease (DKD). DKD is known to be a leading cause of end-stage renal disease; however, detailed molecular mechanisms remain unclear. Natriuretic peptides (NPs)/guanylyl cyclase-A (GC-A) signaling has been reported to exert protective effects against aldosterone-induced kidney injury. To investigate the role of NPs/GC-A pathway against DKD progression, we administered streptozotocin to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between intraocular pressure and climate parameters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the association between climate parameters and intraocular pressure (IOP). We used two large, multicenter cross-sectional datasets: the Japan Ningen Dock Study (JNDS), with 1,477,066 participants (52.3 ± 10.8 years), and the Jikei dataset, with 10,361 participants (50.3 ± 11.0 years). In both, IOP was measured via noncontact tonometry. We obtained daily average air temperature, station-level air pressure, and relative humidity from the Japan Meteorological Agency. We used...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationship between green tea consumption and happiness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although it has been suggested that green tea or its components may reduce psychological stress, the relationship between green tea intake and well-being has not been investigated in large-scale studies. In addition, no previous studies have simultaneously reported the relationships between green tea intake, social capital, and happiness. This study aimed to demonstrate the association between tea consumption and well-being after adjusting for its relationship with social network size. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A CRISPR/Cas9-induced restoration of bioluminescence reporter system for single-cell gene expression analysis in plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bioluminescence monitoring techniques have greatly contributed to revealing a variety of biological regulatory systems in living organisms, including circadian clocks. In plant science, these techniques are applied to long-term quantitative analyses of gene expression behavior. Transient transfection with a luciferase reporter using the particle bombardment method has been used for bioluminescence observations at the single-cell level. This allows for capturing heterogeneity and temporal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning enabled rapid detection of live bacteria in the presence of food debris]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The contamination of food with pathogenic bacteria is a major public health concern, requiring rapid and accurate detection methods. Conventional approaches, such as culture-based or molecular assays, are time-consuming, labor-intensive, and often demand specialized expertise. Here, we developed a deep learning-based strategy for rapid detection and classification of live bacteria using simple white-light microscopic images of microcolonies, even in the presence of morphologically similar food...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determining molecular structure, coordination geometry, and molecular symmetry using a continuous symmetry operation measure software]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chemists have a strong language describing and defining idealized polyhedra P and symmetry point groups G, but no efficient measure to correlate these to real molecular structures Q. The Continuous Symmetry operation Measure changes this by providing automated symmetry determination and a yardstick for quantifying deviations from symmetry. Symmetry and structure have been ascribed through experience, but this approach is error-prone and provides no measure that can correlate molecular structure...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bedtime snacking and glycemic deterioration in young children with Type 1 diabetes on multiple daily injections: a randomized controlled crossover trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Bedtime snacking in young children with T1D impairs nocturnal glycemia and reduces TIR, without decreasing the frequency of hypoglycemia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three-dimensional simulation of wall impingement and graft bending in anatomical double-bundle ACL reconstruction using weight-bearing upright multi-detector CT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study indicated high graft-notch impingement rates and large GBA for traditional AMB in the standing position, highlighting potential biomechanical challenges associated with traditional double-bundle ACLR configurations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Starch functionality and its role in microstructure development and oil absorption dynamics during deep-frying: A review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep-frying is a globally popular cooking technique due to the desirable organoleptic properties foods attain during this process. However, minimizing oil content in the production of these foods remains a challenge. Modification of the food microstructure has emerged as a key strategy in reducing oil absorption, either by modulating the food pore network properties or surface characteristics. Starch, which both comprises the major macronutrient in numerous deep-fried foods (e.g.,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biosynthesis and Export of Membrane-Enveloped Selenium Nanoparticles by <em>Escherichia Coli</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacteria reduce toxic selenium oxyanions, such as selenite, to elemental selenium (Se⁰), forming selenium nanoparticles (SeNPs) either intracellularly or extracellularly. However, the mechanism through which extracellular SeNPs (Ex-SeNPs) are exported remains unclear. In this study, we characterized Ex-SeNPs biosynthesized by Escherichia coli during the aerobic reduction of selenite. The SeNPs appeared within 2 h of exposure, remained extracellular, and displayed a consistent spherical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating photon with proton dose-response data alters a pulmonary complication model-based patient selection in esophageal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Including PT dose-response data into thoracic NTCP models alters pulmonary complication model-based patient selection in EC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial zoning-driven enhancement of simultaneous nitrogen and phosphorus removal: performance evaluation and microbial-metabolic responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To enhance the sustainability of wastewater treatment and mitigate water eutrophication, we developed a coupled partial nitritation/anammox (PN/A) and hydroxyapatite (HAP)-induced crystallization system. Conventional chemical crystallization for phosphorus removal relies heavily on reagents, leading to high operating costs. By inducing HAP crystallization biologically, this PN/A-HAP system reduces external chemical demand and lowers operating costs. All experiments used a defined synthetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2025 Top JPharmSci Reviewers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outstanding Early Career Scientists for 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of novel lamellar nanoparticle formulation using arginine-β-branched hexyldecyl phosphate for dermal delivery of pyridoxine dicaprylate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to develop novel lamellar nanoparticles (NP) using arginine-β-branched hexyldecyl phosphate (AHP) for dermal delivery of pyridoxine dicaprylate (PDC). NPs were prepared via the film rehydration method, and the effects of the distilled water (DW) and citric buffer (CB) rehydration buffers on PDC accumulation in the skin were also investigated. Dynamic light scattering, transmission electron microscopy, and small-angle X-ray diffraction (XRD) analyses revealed that NPs were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41271037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An index for deviation distance among amino acid sequences of antibody complementarity determining regions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monoclonal antibodies are currently essential biological molecules for immunotherapy and diagnosis. The adaptability of an antibody to humans is crucial for ensuring safety and achieving high therapeutic efficacy as a medicinal drug. A considerable amount of effort has been devoted to predicting the human likeness of recombinant antibody molecules to assess their suitability for clinical use. Many previous studies have utilized a database of antibody sequences. However, a rapid assessment of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Lactiplantibacillus mudanjiangensis strain isolated from post-fermented tea on dermal health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The effects of Lactiplantibacillus mudanjiangensis IYO1739 and Lactiplantibacillus plantarum IYO1653, isolated from Japanese post-fermented tea, and their type strains on skin cells were evaluated. The normal human epidermal keratinocyte (NHEK) cells were treated with each strain, and after 2 h, the cells were washed and the number of adhered bacteria was measured. L. mudanjiangensis showed high adhesion, while L. plantarum strains showed little adhesion. After washing, the cells were cultured...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reactivity of the Hydrated Electron]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrated electrons are created in virtually every radiation environment and in many photochemical or electrochemical environments where liquid water is present, so their reaction products and reaction rate constants are naturally important in applications. Thanks to the strong optical absorbance of (e-)(aq), these rate constants are easy to measure, and a large database has been accumulated. It is not generally appreciated that no working theory of hydrated electron reaction rates presently...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stem cells in your YouTube feed: The complex landscape and unexpected mediators of online information]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This Forum article explores 4,481 YouTube videos about stem cells to map how medical knowledge is shaped online. By analyzing content and user metrics, the article identifies key mediators and influential creators, revealing a complex discourse dominated by celebrity influencers in the promotion and discussion of putative stem cell treatments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endothelial senescent-cell-specific clearance alleviates metabolic dysfunction in obese mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accumulation of senescent cells is a key contributor to multiple diseases across the lifespan, including metabolic dysfunction. We previously demonstrated that elimination of senescent cells using senolytic drugs alleviates obesity-induced metabolic dysfunction. However, the contribution of senescent endothelial cells to metabolic disorders remains elusive. Hence, we crossed mice that allow selective elimination of senescent cells (p16^(Ink4a)-LOX-ATTAC mice) with Tie2-Cre mice...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative towing experiment to evaluate efficiency between beam trawl and dredge for capturing seafloor litter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, bottom-tow experiments using beam trawl and toothed dredge were conducted simultaneously in the same region to collect seafloor litter. Litter from both gear types, and from different collection parts (cod-end and gear-entangled samples), was characterized and compared. The results showed that dredges captured substantially greater amount of seafloor litter than beam trawls. For cod-end catches, dredge was 38.5 ± 12.7 times more efficient than beam trawl in terms of litter count,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychological palliative care for patients with interstitial lung disease in Japan: A secondary analysis of a National Survey of Japanese Respiratory Physicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Most physicians lack adequate psychological support resources for ILD despite frequent psychological symptoms. Systematic development of support structures and insurance coverage are needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The European Society of Gynaecological Oncology position statement: promoting inclusive surgical ergonomics in gynecological oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ERGONOMIC EQUITY IS ESSENTIAL FOR SAFE, HIGH-QUALITY SURGERY: The European Society of Gynaecological Oncology (ESGO) recognizes that poorly designed instruments and operating room environments contribute to musculoskeletal injuries, fatigue, and burnout, disproportionately affecting female and smaller-stature surgeons. Ergonomic equity is central to ensuring surgical precision, team well-being, and optimal patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Environmental drivers and ecological responses of seaweed litter production and decomposition: A comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seaweed beds are essential components of coastal ecosystems, playing a pivotal role in global carbon cycling and marine nutrient dynamics. The production and decomposition of seaweed litter directly influence sediment nutrient supply, benthic community structure, and ecosystem stability. This review synthesizes current research on seaweed litter production, deposition, and decomposition, with a focus on natural drivers (e.g., temperature, light, seasonal variations, hydrodynamics, and biotic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neon ion radiotherapy: physics and biology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neon ion (20Ne) beam radiotherapy was one of the primary particle therapy candidates investigated during the clinical trials beginning in the 1970s at the Lawrence Berkely National Laboratory (LBNL), which shutdown in the early 1990's. Currently, therapeutic neon ion beams are available at only one clinical facility worldwide, the National Institutes for Quantum Science and Technology (QST) in Chiba, Japan. Recently, neon ion beams were commissioned at QST Hospital as part of the first clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sea swimming during pregnancy and matrescence: Embodiment, experiences and the environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is a knowledge gap around pregnant women's experiences of sea swimming both within the social research sphere and wider public health communications. Using creative methods, this cross-disciplinary research focuses upon the embodiment and experiences of 13 pregnant and 5 matrescent women who sea swam during winter in the UK. Findings document the women's perceived health and wellbeing benefits of cold water swimming through pregnancy including a protected space for mothers to create time...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proximity-induced chirality at the achiral conductive interface by electrical control of enantiopure ion adsorption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chirality manipulation of materials has attracted substantial interest in a wide variety of fields in science and technology. Chiral molecular adsorption is a distinct approach for inducing chirality in achiral systems such as organic-inorganic hybrid compounds and nanomaterials. With the proximity effect of adsorbed chiral molecules on inorganic systems in mind, we demonstrate the artificial introduction of chirality to an achiral molybdenum disulfide surface by controlling the adsorption of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stay or go? Exploring physician turnover in European Hospitals-Evidence from the METEOR survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[According to the World Health Organization (WHO), in 2022 there was a shortfall of approximately 1.2 million doctors, impacting healthcare system and patient care. Understanding turnover intentions is crucial for managing the healthcare workforce and ensuring continuous, and high-quality patient care. This study investigates the prevalence of physicians planning to leave their hospital or the profession, and risk factors such as job demand, resources, satisfaction, and burnout across four...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial and century-scale temporal variation of wild Coffea canephora leaf functional traits and water use efficiency in Congo Basin forests]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study underscores the value of herbarium-based multitrait approaches in reconstructing long-term plant responses and their relevance for understanding climate sensitivity in tropical understory species.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kokumi Substance Obtained from Vegetable Protein Hydrolysates through Salt-Free Processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The kokumi substance of enzymatic hydrolyzed vegetable protein (EHVP) was isolated and evaluated for its effects on sensory perception. Sensory evaluation revealed that the addition of EHVP to beef extract solution significantly enhanced flavors such as mouthfulness and astringency. EHVP was fractionated through ultrafiltration and chromatography, and kokumi-containing fraction was isolated via sensory evaluation. The kokumi substance in EHVP was a glycopeptide consisting of a tetrapeptide and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41270020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circular Dichroism in Resonant Inelastic X-Ray Scattering: Probing Altermagnetic Domains in MnTe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[X-ray magnetic circular dichroism provides a means to identify ferromagnetic, chiral, and altermagnetic orders via their time-reversal-symmetry (T) breaking. However, the symmetry properties that govern circular dichroism (CD) in resonant inelastic x-ray scattering (RIXS) remain poorly understood. We show that, due to the inherent irreversibility of the RIXS process, RIXS-CD does not require T breaking to be present, but reflects the change in unitary symmetries associated with magnetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pure Hydrodynamic Instabilities in Active Jets of Puller Microalgae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Active fluids can develop spontaneous flow instabilities and complex patterns. However, spatiotemporal control of active particles has remained challenging, despite its relevance in biological and applied contexts. Here, we harnessed phototaxis to steer millions of swimming "puller" Chlamydomonas reinhardtii algae to create active jets and control both pearling and buckling instabilities through the preferential orientation of the cells. Our experiments, supported by a full analytical model and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural and Functional Basis of G Protein-Coupled Receptor 35 Activation by Pyrroloquinoline Quinone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pyrroloquinoline quinone (PQQ), an o-quinone-type nutrient, has been shown to exert diverse beneficial effects on the biochemical and physiological processes of mammals. However, the molecular mechanisms underlying these effects remain incompletely understood. Here, through screening of metabolite-sensing G protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs)─which respond to metabolites produced by gut microbiota or derived from nutrients─we found that PQQ selectively activates G-protein-coupled receptor 35...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of spontaneous regression of primary hepatic diffuse large B-cell lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a rare case of spontaneous regression of primary hepatic diffuse large B-cell lymphoma (DLBCL) in an 89-year-old man. A 12 cm solitary hepatic mass was found in the anterior and medial segments. Contrast-enhanced CT showed a hypovascular solid tumor. Serologic markers including hepatitis B virus, hepatitis C virus, human immunodeficiency virus, alpha-fetoprotein, protein induced by vitamin K absence or antagonist-II, carbohydrate antigen 19-9, and carcinoembryonic antigen were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uterus transplants or surrogacy? Exploring the ethics of assisted gestation through incentivization and compensation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of Adult Stem Cell-Derived Organoid Cultures: General Principles from the Mouse Gut]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adult stem cell (ASC)-derived organoid cultures have become an important model system for studying mammalian epithelial tissues in health and disease, including autoimmune conditions. Somatic stem cells are isolated and embedded into basement membrane-like matrix to allow for the in vitro outgrowth of miniature versions of functional epithelium in the presence of supportive growth factor niche. Organoids derived from tissues affected by autoimmune diseases, such as the intestine in inflammatory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recognizing the importance of papers on sustainable radiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical outcomes of lung cancer associated with autoimmune disease-related interstitial pneumonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Lung cancer with AD-IP had a poor prognosis, as did lung cancer with IIP, and the frequency of postoperative AE of patients with AD-IP was as high as that in those with IIP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances of cell therapies for AML/MDS: exploring the therapeutic potential of innate immune cells in AML/MDS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immunotherapy has revolutionized cancer treatments, yet checkpoint inhibitors and CAR-T cells have shown limited efficacy in acute myeloid leukemia (AML) and myelodysplastic syndromes (MDS). This limited efficacy is primarily due to the absence of lineage-specific antigens and the presence of suppressive microenvironments. Innate immunity offers a promising alternative, as it acts independently of neoantigens. The key players such as macrophages, dendritic cells, and natural killer (NK) cells...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of host and gut microbiota-altering interventions on sarcopenia or its defining parameters: a systematic review and meta-analysis of nutrition-based intervention studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Specific diets and probiotics offer potential to improve sarcopenia parameters.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Spirometric Lung Age with Survival Outcomes in Elderly Patients Undergoing Radical Surgery for Gastric Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The discrepancy between lung and chronological age may serve as a useful predictor of long-term outcomes, particularly non-GC-related mortality, in elderly patients undergoing curative gastrectomy. This metric may support risk stratification and inform surgical strategies in this vulnerable population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical characteristics and management of dupilumab-associated ocular surface disease in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dupilumab-associated ocular surface disease (DAOSD) is one of the most common adverse events associated with dupilumab (an anti-interleukin-4-receptor-alpha monoclonal antibody) during the treatment of patients with atopic dermatitis (AD). However, it rarely occurs in patients with bronchial asthma or chronic rhinosinusitis with nasal polyps. Adequate understanding of DAOSD is important for proper diagnosis and appropriate ophthalmic intervention. The aim of this review was to summarize and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Involvement of best-corrected visual acuity in sarcopenia: findings from baseline analysis of the Kyotango longevity cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates a significant relationship between lower visual acuity and sarcopenia. These findings support maintaining visual acuity to prevent age-related decline of physical functions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proton Pump Inhibitors Attenuate the Effectiveness of Nivolumab Monotherapy in Patients with Advanced Gastric Cancer: A Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Concomitant use of PPI may reduce the effectiveness of nivolumab in patients with advanced gastric cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seasonal variation in bacterial community composition in the brackish meromictic Lake Suigetsu]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lake Suigetsu, a deep meromictic lake connected to Wakasa Bay, receives freshwater inflow and exchange surface water with intruding seawater. To investigate bacterial community dynamics and substrate transport, we conducted seasonal 16S rRNA gene sequencing across three stratified layers (mixolimnion, chemocline, and monimolimnion) and two size fractions (0.2-0.8 µm for free-living; 0.8-3.0 µm for particle-attached). Community composition differed by depth, fraction, and season. Winter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of orthodontic treatment on front teeth with prior history of dental injury: a 4-year follow up]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION AND CLINICAL RELEVANCE: Injured front teeth are more prone to pulpal complications and RR than those without trauma. Long courses of treatment should be avoided, especially in severe injuries. Incisor extraction led to significantly worse gingival esthetic outcomes, although this didn't influence patient satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Technical note: Quantitative and qualitative analysis of diatom testing in methomyl poisoning case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diatom testing is conducted in forensic medicine primarily to support the diagnosis of drowning. In our previous study, a large number of diatoms, potentially originating from methomyl, were detected in the lungs of a cat found dead under circumstances suggestive of methomyl poisoning, but not involving drowning or submersion. In the present study, we collected human and animal cases suspected of methomyl poisoning, where the bodies showed no evidence of drowning or submersion. Diatom tests were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Speeding up, not slowing down, decreases the metabolic energy needed to stabilize walking in the sagittal plane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is a metabolic cost associated with stabilizing walking, but it remains unclear to what extent stabilizing walking in the sagittal plane contributes to this cost. Furthermore, strategies for stabilizing walking in the sagittal plane vary with speed, but it is unclear whether this also leads to a speed-dependent metabolic cost of stabilizing walking. Here, we explored the metabolic cost of stabilizing walking in the sagittal plane across speeds and its relationship with control strategies....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting Report on the 1st GlyCosmos Symposium &amp; Jamboree -Community-Driven Expansion of Glycan-Binding Molecules Resources]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world outcomes of anthracycline and taxane-based perioperative breast cancer therapy using the Japanese electronic medical record database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RDI was high in all groups. Clinicians should be cautious when administering AC q3w therapy owing to the high likelihood of patients developing Grade 4 neutropenia. For TC, a slightly lower pegfilgrastim administration rate and >20% Grade 4 neutropenia suggest the need for appropriate pegfilgrastim use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Herbicidal Pyridazinone Cyclic Keto-Enol Compounds Inhibit Acetyl-CoA Carboxylase and Homogentisate Solanesyltransferase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Novel aryl cyclic keto-enol (aryl-CKE) derivatives containing a pyridazinone moiety (5-hydroxy-4-phenyl-3(2H)-pyridazinone) exhibit distinct herbicidal symptoms on grass and broadleaf weeds. Herbicide efficacy tests on target-site resistant blackgrass and enzyme inhibition assays revealed that the herbicidal activity in grassy weeds was primarily attributed to ACCase inhibition. The bleaching effect of the representative compounds on broadleaf plants was initially hypothesized to result from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Decade of Mitochondria-Targeting Drugs in Cancer Treatment: Case Review on Mitochondria-Targeting Curcumin or Mitocurcumin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondrial targeting is of particular interest to researchers, as it presents as a personalized medicine approach in cancer cell metabolism and survival. By specifically targeting mitochondria, targeted therapies can disrupt energy production, induce apoptosis, and overcome drug resistance in cancer cells, potentially improving therapeutic outcomes. This review discusses the advancements in mitochondrial drug delivery over the last decade. It explores the potential of mitochondrial targeting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystal Structure of a GDP-bound Bombyx mori RabX6]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rab GTPases are molecular switches that control intracellular vesicular transport by cycling between GDP- and GTP-bound states. Insects encode an insect-specific subset, RabX; Bombyx mori RabX6 (BmRabX6) has been implicated in testis development and neuropeptide secretion, but its structure and mechanism were unknown. Here we report the 3.1 Å crystal structure of BmRabX6 in complex with GDP and Mg2+ (PDB: 9VLB), the first structure of an insect-specific Rab GTPase. BmRabX6 adopts the canonical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251122023452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>