<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 07:38:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonlinear kinematic impacts on nanofluid flow across rough surface with numerical simulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The current study demonstrates the intricate thermo-solutal transportation features of a nanofluid experiencing non-linear kinematics as it flows across a rough porous stretched interface. Previous work has typically been limited to smooth geometries, narrow parameter ranges, and few physical intuitions. However, this paper extends the analysis to include surface roughness, porosity effect, nonlinear stretching and essential physical phenomena like effect of magnetic field, Brownian motion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting gestational diabetes before conception for personalized interpregnancy weight management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamics of checkpoint receptors in γδ T cell subsets are associated with clinical response during anti-PD-1 immunotherapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gamma delta (γδ) T cells are innate-like lymphocytes with potent anti-tumor properties. Herein, we show that immune checkpoint receptors (ICRs) display differential expression and regulation by the JAK-STAT pathway in Vδ1 and Vδ2 cells and identify constitutive (e.g. TIGIT, PD-1) and inducible (e.g. TIM-3, LAG-3, CTLA-4) ICRs. In melanoma, all γδ T cell subsets downregulated AP-1 transcription factors, but Vδ1 cells specifically expressed high levels of ICR, TOX and inhibitory killer Ig-like...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[m6A regulators-based gene expression pattern is associated with immune microenvironment characteristics in hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the relationship between N6-methyladenosine (m6A) modification-related genes and the immune microenvironment characteristics of hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC), and to evaluate the potential of targeting m6A regulators to sensitize HCC cells to immunotherapy. RNA sequencing data and clinicopathologic data of HCC patients were obtained from TCGA and ICGC database. Based on the expression levels of 23 m6A modification regulators, the HCC samples were divided into three m6A clusters by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of pediatric kidney re-transplantation: a single-center cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Children with end-stage renal disease (ESRD) frequently require more than one kidney transplantation (KT) during their lifetime due to limited graft longevity. Despite this clinical reality, few studies have evaluated long-term outcomes following repeat pediatric KT. We conducted a retrospective single-center study analyzing 120 KTs performed in 89 pediatric recipients between 1993 and 2024. Outcomes included graft function, postoperative complications, and long-term graft and patient survival....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Divalent anion-driven framework regulation in Zr-based halide solid electrolytes for all-solid-state batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Research into solid electrolytes for all-solid-state batteries has intensified due to demand for safer and higher-energy-density batteries. Halide solid electrolytes are valued for their high ionic conductivity, oxidative stability, and ductility. Among them, Li(2)ZrCl(6) is cost-effective but has a relatively lower Li⁺ ionic conductivity (0.4 mS cm^(-1) at 25 °C) compared to other halides, such as Li(3)InCl(6) (> 1 mS cm^(-1) at 25 °C). Here, we elucidate a fundamental mechanism of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of the salience network in adolescent impulsivity using memory tasks and neuroimaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results indicate that the connection between the salience network and the noradrenergic locus coeruleus may function as a consistent neural indicator of impulsivity. Our findings indicate that this method can discern reliable brain biomarkers for impulsivity and can guide interventions aimed at enhancing self-control during adolescence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated genomic-transcriptomic analysis of clavulanic acid production in differentially productive Streptomyces clavuligerus strains]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clavulanic acid (CA) is a specific metabolite that inhibits β-lactamases, which inactivate β-lactam antibiotics, therefore reinstating the activity of β-lactams against β-lactamase-producing pathogens, and surmounting β-lactam resistance. While extensive efforts have been made to optimize CA production through random mutagenesis, these approaches often introduce deleterious mutations, limiting further yield improvements. In this study, whole-genome sequencing, time-resolved transcriptomics, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fibrinogen alpha and beta chains as non-invasive predictors of hepatocellular carcinoma progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) poses a significant global health burden due to its high incidence and mortality rates. Early diagnosis is crucial for improving patient outcomes; however, current diagnostic methods, such as the measurement of α-fetoprotein (AFP) levels, have notable limitations. Our study aimed to explore non-invasive markers with superior diagnostic efficacy for HCC. Our findings revealed a significant downregulation of FGA, FGB, and FGG in HCC, with lower expression levels...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of state-of-charge and temperature on the cross-plane thermal conductivity of a Li-ion pouch cell]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A thorough understanding of the thermal transport characteristics of Li-ion batteries is critical for the development of accurate thermal models and the enhancement of thermal management strategies. In this study, the cross-plane thermal conductivity ( k ⊥ ) of a commercial 20 Ah Li-ion pouch cell was systematically measured across a broad range of state-of-charge (SOC) levels and temperatures (20.6 to 43.3 ∘ C) using a custom-designed guarded hot plate apparatus. The results indicate that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rotating compensator spectroscopic ellipsometry based on frequency division multiplexing with retardation calibration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spectroscopic ellipsometry (SE) is widely used to obtain valuable information about materials such as optical constants or film thickness in a non-destructive way. Various types of SE, each possessing distinct characteristics, have been studied for specific applications. Here, we theoretically and experimentally demonstrate Frequency Division Multiplexing Rotating Compensator Spectroscopic Ellipsometry (FDM-RCSE) by using the frequency division multiplexing (FDM) technique and a rotating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frequency multiplexing with dispersion-engineered elastic metasurfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Distinguishing the frequency components of elastic waves is essential for ensuring the stability of mechanical systems. Herein, a frequency-multiplexed elastic metasurface is introduced, utilizing a dispersion engineering. The proposed dispersion-engineered elastic metasurface multiplexes frequency-dependent phase profiles, enabling frequency-selective wavefront tailoring. The phase profiles of the meta-atoms, derived from Kirchhoff-Love plate theory, are controlled solely by the plate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abrupt structural transition in exotic molybdenum isotopes unveils an isospin-symmetric island of inversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Like electrons in atoms, protons and neutrons in nuclei occupy orbitals in a shell structure with energy gaps at magic numbers. Radioactive-beam experiments revealed the disappearance of magic numbers in some neutron-rich isotopes. In these nuclei, configurations involving particles excited across the shell gap gain correlation energy, becoming the ground state. Neutron-rich regions of the nuclear chart that exhibit this property are known as "Islands of Inversion". Here we present the lifetime...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iridium(III)-catalyzed remote B(9)-H alkylation of o-carboranes with nitrile template]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carboranes, unique three-dimensional analogs of benzene, have attracted considerable attention owing to their potential in medicine, catalysis, and materials science. Consequently, the introduction of functional groups into carborane clusters has emerged as an important research focus. While directing group-assisted ortho-B-H activation of o-carboranes is well established, meta-B-H functionalization remains rare. Here we show iridium(III)-catalyzed remote B(9)-H alkylation of o-carboranes using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stimulating EPA Biosynthesis in <em>Microchloropsis salina</em> through Cultivation with Selected Myxobacterial Culture Supernatants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microalgae have emerged as a promising and sustainable platform for the production of omega-3 polyunsaturated fatty acids, offering an alternative to fish-derived sources. Among these, Microchloropsis salina (formerly Nannochloropsis salina) is particularly attractive as a candidate due to its naturally high eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA) content. In this study, bacterial supernatants from various myxobacterial strains were evaluated for their ability to enhance microalgal growth and EPA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Governing Synthetic Biology: A Co-Evolutionary Framework for Sustainable Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Synthetic biology has rapidly evolved from laboratory-based research to a core technology driving biomanufacturing, industrial innovation, and the global bioeconomy. Technological advancements such as next-generation sequencing, DNA synthesis, novel genome editing, and biofoundry automation are accelerating the industrial expansion and application of synthetic biology. However, despite these breakthroughs, current regulatory frameworks and societal acceptance are not in pace with technological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of an RT-LAMP-CRISPR/Cas12a assay for rapid and specific detection of Bandavirus dabieense]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bandavirus dabieense, a single-stranded RNA virus, is the causative agent of severe fever with thrombocytopenia syndrome (SFTS), a disease associated with high fatality rates. Early and accurate diagnosis is essential for improving clinical outcomes, particularly given the limited therapeutic options and high mortality rates associated with SFTS. However, while highly sensitive, conventional diagnostic methods such as PCR and qRT-PCR require specialized laboratory facilities and trained...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Encapsulin protein MAV2054 enhances Mycobacterium avium virulence by promoting Cdc42-dependent epithelial cell invasion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mycobacterium avium complex (MAC) organisms are widespread environmental pathogens associated with chronic pulmonary infections. Although M. avium is known to invade epithelial cells, the molecular mechanisms underlying this process remain incompletely understood. In this study, we identified a novel role for MAVRS09815 (formerly MAV2054), a family 2A encapsulin nanocompartment shell protein, in mediating bacterial adhesion, epithelial cell invasion, and in vivo virulence. We engineered a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of clopidogrel-based antiplatelet therapy versus warfarin as a secondary prevention strategy for AntiPhospholipid Syndrome-related STROKE (APS-STROKE): Rationale and design of a prospective, randomized, open-label, blinded-endpoint trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study will provide valuable information on the optimal secondary prevention strategy for APS-related stroke.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Augmentation of Humoral and Cell-Mediated Immune Responses by Recombinant Rabies Virus Expressing Canine Fc]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rabies virus (RV) infection causes a fatal neurological disease affecting both animals, particularly canines, and humans. As a novel approach, canine Fc fusion protein into a recombinant RV may enhance both humoral and cellular-mediated immunity and is expected a promising strategy for vaccine development and therapeutic interventions. To enhance the immunogenicity of a traditional rabies vaccine, we generated a recombinant RV-expressing canine Fc fusion protein (RV-Fc) by cloning the RV-Fc...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between weekend catch-up sleep and white blood cell count among Korean adults: A population-based cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Extended WCS was associated with elevated systemic inflammation in specific subgroups. Maintaining regular and moderate sleep patterns may help mitigate low-grade inflammation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Omega-3 Supplement Use and Cognitive Function in Korean Older Adults: An 8-Year Longitudinal Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: O3FA supplement use was associated with better maintenance of cognitive function over eight years. These findings suggest a potential role of O3FA supplementation in supporting cognitive health during aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stacked mutations in multi-copy AHAS genes enhance sulfonylurea herbicide resistance in soybean]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Weeds are a major factor that negatively impact crop yields. Developing herbicide-resistant germlines is crucial for efficient weed control. Sulfonylurea- and pyrimidinyl benzoate-based herbicides inhibit the function of acetohydroxyacid synthase (AHAS), a key enzyme in the biosynthesis of branched-chain amino acids in plants. To create soybean plants resistant to these classes of herbicides, we performed base editing of AHAS genes in Glycine max. A guide RNA was designed to target the codon for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Microbulbifer discodermiae</em> sp. nov. and <em>Microbulbifer jejuensis</em> sp. nov., isolated from marine sponges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two Gram-stain-negative, facultatively anaerobic, non-motile and rod-shaped bacterial strains, designated 2201CG32-9^(T) and 2304DJ12-6^(T), were isolated from marine sponges collected in the Republic of Korea. Both strains exhibited catalase and oxidase activities but tested negative for nitrate reduction and indole production. Strain 2201CG32-9^(T) showed optimal growth at 30 °C and pH 7.0-8.0 in the presence of 3% (w/v) NaCl, whereas strain 2304DJ12-6^(T) grew optimally at 25 °C, pH 8.0 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-stratified hypertension risk prediction: integrating genetic risk scores with clinical markers in Korean adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Age-specific integration of GRS with clinical markers such as BMI and ba-PWV significantly improves hypertension prediction, offering actionable thresholds for precision prevention across age groups. These models provide clinically actionable tools for precision prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoparticle-Stabilized Porous Composite Architectures for Ultrasound-Driven Triboelectric Energy Harvesters in Soft Implantable Electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wireless powering of implantable medical devices (IMDs) using triboelectric nanogenerators (TENGs) has gained attention as a sustainable and battery-free energy strategy. Ultrasound-driven TENGs (US-TENGs) offer favorable biocompatibility and deep tissue accessibility, but their practical application remains limited by unstable acoustic vibration, filler aggregation at low contents, and complex electrode integration. Here, we report a porous polyimide composite-based TENG (PPC-TENG) designed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defect-Mediated In Situ CNT Growth in Hollow Porous Carbon From ZIF-8/ZIF-67 Bilayers for Efficient and Stable ORR Catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rational design of carbon-based electrocatalysts with hierarchical porosity, graphitic domains, and optimized active sites is crucial for advancing the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR). Herein, a bilayer core-shell ZIF (PS@BCZ)-derived strategy is presented that enables the in situ growth of carbon nanotubes (CNTs) and uniform embedding of cobalt nanoparticles (Co NPs) within an N-doped hollow porous carbon matrix (CNT-Co/N-HPC). Sequential ZIF-8/ZIF-67 growth on polystyrene spheres, followed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing glycol-alkyl copolymerization to realize nonvolatile and biologically relevant synaptic behaviors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic electrochemical synaptic transistors (OESTs) are attracting growing attention for neuromorphic computing, yet their long-term stability remains constrained by uncontrolled ion dynamics. Previous studies have incorporated glycol side chains to facilitate ionic transport, but a systematic understanding of how copolymerization with hydrophobic alkyl units governs ion doping and retention is still lacking. Here, we establish a rational backbone-side chain copolymer design strategy that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Bioavailability of a Thionated IMiD Derivative Nanosuspension for Parkinson's Disease Targeting α-Synuclein]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This enhancement in bioavailability supports the formulation of NS as a promising strategy for CNS-targeted therapies, providing a strong rationale for further investigation into the efficacy of MTPOM-NS in the chronic treatment of PD, which will be the focus of future studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ORF3 Gene of Porcine Epidemic Diarrhea Virus Causes Nuclear and Morphological Distortions with Associated Cell Death]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is increasing research interest in the ORF3 accessory protein of PEDV as a critical element for viral virulence. Here, wild type ORF3 (ORF3(wt)) gene was constructed in pEGFP-C1 vector. Additionally, two truncation mutants, ORF3-N (1-98 amino acids [aa]) and ORF3-C (99-224 aa) were inserted in the same vector. Results of ORF3 expression revealed early cytoplasmic localization but 12 h after transfection, ORF3 accumulated around the nucleus, especially ORF3-N. This caused chromosome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiologic Characteristics of 1.4 Million Multiplex PCR Tests for 12 Urogenital and Sexually Transmitted Infection Pathogens in Korea (2021-2024)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sexually transmitted infections (STIs) remain a global health concern, but large-scale multiplex PCR surveillance data are limited. This study aimed to characterize sex- and age-specific distributions, temporal patterns, and co-infection dynamics of 12 urogenital and sexually transmitted infection (STI) pathogens in Korea. We retrospectively analyzed 1,399,431 multiplex PCR test records (902,713 females, 496,718 males) collected nationwide between 2021 and 2024. Positivity rates were stratified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amodiaquine Modulates Aggregation and Disassembly of Amyloid-β and Tau and Attenuates Neuroinflammatory Responses and Aβ Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder characterized by the accumulation of amyloid-β (Aβ) plaques and hyperphosphorylated tau tangles, which synergistically accelerate disease progression. Since Aβ plaques and tau tangles are key factors in the development of AD, dual-targeting of Aβ and tau aggregation represents a promising therapeutic strategy. Amodiaquine (AQ), a quinoline-based antimalarial, has recently attracted attention for its ability to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Lactobacillus</em>-Fermented <em>Centella asiatica</em> Extract Inhibits Airway Inflammation in Cigarette Smoke Extract/LPS-Induced Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Centella asiatica, a widely used medicinal herb in Oriental and increasingly Western medicine, is applied for wound healing, dermatological disorders, and gastrointestinal illness. We investigated the effects of fermented C. asiatica extract (FCAE), prepared with Lactobacillus, on airway inflammation in a murine model of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) induced by cigarette smoke extract (CSE) and lipopolysaccharide (LPS). CSE/LPS stimulation caused marked immune cell infiltration in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of the Carbonation Behavior of Cement Mortar Containing Interior Stone Sludge and Recycled Mask Fibers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the carbonation and mechanical behavior of cement mortar incorporating artificial interior stone (AIS) sludge and recycled mask fibers (RMFs). Sludge, derived from AIS waste, replaced 30 wt.% of fine aggregate, while RMF from polypropylene masks was added at 0-1 wt.% of cement. Specimens were cured under normal and carbonation conditions (10% CO(2), 25 °C, 60% RH) for 7 and 28 days. Carbonation curing improved compressive and flexural strengths by up to 28% and 88%,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of Low-Frequency Metasurface Microwave Absorption Filter with Composite Molding and Size Dependency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a lightweight metasurface microwave absorption filter (MMAF) designed for low-frequency stealth applications in the L-band. The metasurface is optimized using a genetic algorithm to achieve broadband absorption at subwavelength thickness. The fabricated MMAF consists of a glass fiber-reinforced plastic layer, a metasurface layer, and a dielectric layer with a size of 30 × 30 cm². It maintains a reflection coefficient below -10 dB in the frequency range of 1.01-1.78 GHz....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lumbar Interlaminar Ventral Epidural Injection Without Catheter at L5-S1 for Lumbosacral Radicular Pain: A Pilot Feasibility Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Lumbar interlaminar ventral epidural injection (LIVEI) offers a promising alternative to transforaminal epidural injection (TFEI) by enabling ventral epidural delivery while minimizing complication risks. While previous approaches often required catheter assistance, this pilot study evaluates the safety, technical feasibility, and early outcomes of a simplified LIVEI method at L5-S1 without catheter insertion. Materials and Methods: Twelve patients with lumbosacral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metastatic Patterns of Malignant Germ Cell Tumors Vary by Histologic Subtype and Primary Site]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Malignant germ cell tumors (GCTs) are rare but clinically significant neoplasms arising in gonadal and extragonadal sites. Malignant GCTs, divided into seminomatous and non-seminomatous subtypes, show diverse biological behavior. Although molecular studies have advanced understanding of their origins and genetic features, little is known about metastatic patterns due to their rarity and generally favorable outcomes. This study aimed to describe metastatic patterns of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Copy Number Alteration Profiling from Plasma cfDNA WES in Advanced NSCLC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circulating cell-free DNA (cfDNA) sequencing offers a minimally invasive approach for profiling tumor genomes, but detecting copy number alterations (CNAs) from cfDNA whole-exome sequencing (WES) remains technically challenging due to noise and guanine-cytosine (GC)-related bias. Building upon our previous study that characterized read count patterns in cfDNA WES data, we developed and evaluated an advanced pipeline for robust CNA detection in patients with advanced non-small cell lung cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41303594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Practice of Nursing Students in South Korea's Community Treatment Centers During COVID-19: A Descriptive Phenomenological Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study explored the lived experiences of nursing students in South Korea who participated in clinical practice at Community Treatment Centers (CTCs) during the COVID-19 pandemic. Methods: This study was designed as a qualitative study and applied Colaizzi's descriptive phenomenology. Semi-structured interviews were conducted with ten nursing students who practiced at CTCs for three to four weeks. Data were analyzed through Colaizzi's seven procedural steps to derive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Inhibition of Triple-Negative Breast Cancer by Acetylsalicylic Acid and Recombinant Human APE1/Ref-1 in a Mouse Xenograft Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC) is a highly aggressive subtype with limited therapeutic options due to the lack of estrogen, progesterone, and HER2 receptors. This study investigated the synergistic anticancer effects of recombinant human apurinic/apyrimidinic endonuclease 1/redox factor-1 (rhAPE1/Ref-1) and acetylsalicylic acid (ASA), a combination that has not been previously tested in vivo. Methods: We treated MDA-MB-231 TNBC cells with rhAPE1/Ref-1, ASA, or their combination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endothelial Dysfunction: From Pathophysiology to Novel Therapeutic Approaches 2.0]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endothelial dysfunction (ED) is a multifactorial pathological process characterized by the loss of the endothelial physiological function, which is essential for maintaining vascular homeostasis [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the Effectiveness of a Behavioral Activation-Based Digital App for Treatment of Depressive Symptoms: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Our research investigated how a smartphone application utilizing behavioral activation principles affects depression levels in young adult populations. A total of 67 participants aged 20-30 years with clinically significant depressive symptoms (CESD-11 ≥ 16) were divided into treatment (n = 31) and comparison conditions (n = 36) through randomization procedures. Participants in the experimental group engaged with a BA-based mobile application (Maummove) over an eight-week period, while those in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41301298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexible Bronchoscopic En Bloc Cryoextraction of Endobronchial Leiomyoma Using a 1.7-mm Cryoprobe: A Case Report with One-Year Follow-Up]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Clinical Significance: Endobronchial leiomyoma is a rare benign tumor of the respiratory tract, accounting for less than 2% of all benign pulmonary neoplasms. Most cases have been treated surgically or with endoscopic modalities such as laser or rigid bronchoscopy-assisted cryotherapy. Flexible bronchoscopic cryoextraction has been rarely reported, typically with 2.2-mm probes. Small-caliber cryoprobes (1.1- and 1.7-mm) have been validated for diagnostic transbronchial cryobiopsy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Multivariate Predictors of Headaches Attributed to Rhinosinusitis in Pediatric Patients: A Comparative Study with Migraine and Tension-Type Headache]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pediatric HRS shows distinct predictors-young age, acute severe headache, nasal and auditory symptoms, allergic history, and family history-despite overlap with migraine and TTH. Structured use of these predictors with otolaryngologic assessment may improve diagnostic accuracy, reduce misclassification, and avoid unnecessary neuroimaging or inappropriate therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Congenital Torticollis to Leigh Syndrome: A Case Report of Diagnostic Evolution in an Infant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leigh syndrome is a rare, progressive mitochondrial disorder of childhood. Early diagnosis is often challenging due to nonspecific clinical manifestations. We report a 1-month-old male infant initially referred for suspected congenital muscular torticollis who ultimately received a diagnosis of Leigh syndrome. Despite unremarkable perinatal history, he subsequently developed persistent feeding difficulties, recurrent vomiting, failure to thrive, and global developmental delay. Early neurological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superoxide Dismutase 3 Deficiency Disrupts the Regulation of Oxidative Stress Caused by Polystyrene Nanoplastics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanoplastics have been recognized as emerging pollutants posing potential risks to ecosystems and human health. They are now detected ubiquitously in the environment and even human tissues, where their small size allows for tissue accumulation and cellular penetration. Growing evidence links nanoplastics to oxidative stress, yet the specific contribution of extracellular accumulation to toxicity remains poorly understood. To address this, we used zebrafish, a transparent vertebrate model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DEG-by-Index Ratio Transformation Normalization with Blood RNA-Seq Enhances Early and Consistent Detection of Mouse Tumorigenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Variability in blood RNA-Seq data can obscure transcriptional changes that reflect tumor responses, and conventional normalization methods such as RLE/DESeq2 or TMM/edgeR often fail to capture these changes consistently. To address this challenge, we applied DiRT (DEG-by-index Ratio Transformation), a normalization and analysis strategy previously used in insect models, to 111 blood RNA-Seq datasets from mouse tumorigenesis models. DiRT achieved clearer separation between tumor and control...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41300367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The efficacy and safety of prasugrel in acute coronary syndrome: a propensity-matched Korean cohort study focused on age and weight of patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41299333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this Korean PS-matched ACS cohort, prasugrel, even at a reduced dose, was associated with superior effectiveness compared to clopidogrel without a significant increase in bleeding risk. These benefits were consistently observed in ELB patients. Our findings support the use of prasugrel in selected high-risk populations and offer guidance for clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41299333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Northern migration patterns and winter habitat use of hooded cranes (Grus monacha) in Suncheon Bay, South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41299280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Results suggest managing paddy fields and mudflats as a single ecological unit, protecting key stopover sites, and testing spatially dispersed supplementary feeding to buffer late-winter shortages. This study provides the fine-scale linkage between winter habitat use and migration in Hooded Cranes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41299280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of spin-orbit coupling in spin-to-lattice energy conversion in ferrite nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report on the influence of spin-orbit coupling (SOC) in governing spin-to-lattice energy conversion in ferrite nanoparticles (MnFe(2)O(4), Fe(3)O(4), and NiFe(2)O(4)). Using infrared thermography, ferromagnetic resonance measurements, and numerical temperature-profile fitting based on an analytical thermal model, we successfully identify and clarify distinct energy conversion pathways. Specifically, we decompose the process into three sequential steps: field-to-spin energy transfer, spin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput in vitro screening and in silico analysis for Zika virus inhibitor identification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Zika Virus (ZIKV) is a mosquito-borne virus that can cause serious health problems, including birth defects and neurological complications. Unfortunately, there are no antivirals currently approved for its treatments. In this study, we tested a library of 348 chemical compounds to find potential candidates that could block ZIKV infection. Seven compounds showed strong antiviral activity in laboratory experiments. Among them, Cephalotaxine, Docusate Sodium, and Saikosaponin B2 were the most...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Ultrathin, Cyano-Functionalized Copolymeric Memristor by iCVD Process for Driving Convolutional Neural Networks of High-Resolution Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For on-chip learning, ideal weight storage elements should have scalability, data retention, symmetry and linear conductance modulation, and weight fine-tuning capabilities. In this study, memristors are fabricated by employing cyano-based ultrathin copolymer films (<10 nm) using 2-cyanoethyl acrylate (CEA) and di(ethylene glycol) divinyl ether (DEGDVE) as functional monomers via an initiated chemical vapor deposition (iCVD) process, optimized to serve as a high-performance device for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring neurokinin-1 receptor antagonism for depression with structurally differentiated inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The neurokinin-1 receptor (NK1R) has been investigated as a potential target for major depressive disorder owing to its role in stress regulation and neuroinflammation. However, clinical trials of NK1R antagonists have yielded inconsistent results, leaving it unclear whether these outcomes reflect limitations of NK1R as a therapeutic target or shortcomings inherent to the clinical candidates tested. The majority of previously developed NK1R antagonists contain a 3,5-bis-trifluoromethylphenyl...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal trajectories of social isolation and loneliness across the lifespan during the COVID-19 pandemic in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During the prolonged Coronavirus Disease 2019 pandemic persisting through to 2023, social isolation became a major public health concern. Its impacts varied across age groups, but empirical evidence on longitudinal trajectories of social isolation in South Korea remains limited. Thus, this study examined social isolation and loneliness trajectories in South Korea using longitudinal data from three waves (2021-2023) involving 2395 participants aged 15-79. Over that three-year period, social...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phishing threat mitigation in E-commerce using a quantum-enhanced hybrid AI framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phishing websites continue to pose a significant cybersecurity threat, exploiting URL structures to deceive users and bypass traditional detection systems. Most existing models rely solely on classical deep learning, which often incurs high computational overhead and lacks interpretability. In this context, this paper proposes a quantum-enhanced hybrid AI model that integrates a classical neural encoder with a parameterized quantum circuit, leveraging quantum entanglement and superposition for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feature centric based deep learning approach for music mood recognition with HuBERT transformer model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, music mood classification is explored using advanced deep learning and transformer-based models to accurately predict the emotional content of music. Music plays a crucial role in human life, influencing emotions, behaviors, and mental states. Accurately classifying the mood of music is essential for applications such as music recommendation systems, emotional intelligence in AI, and mental health monitoring. With the growing impact of Artificial Intelligence (AI) in emotion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-based framework for time-dependent reliability analysis of a cable-stayed bridge with corroded PSC box girders under gravity loads]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proper maintenance of civil infrastructure, such as cable-stayed bridges, is critical to ensuring safe and efficient logistics and transportation. Prestressed concrete (PSC) box girders in such bridges are particularly vulnerable to corrosion-induced strand deterioration. Existing methods often overlook system-level behavior or rely on computationally intensive simulations. This study proposes a deep learning-based framework to evaluate the time-dependent reliability of cable-stayed bridges with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robust low complexity multisurface super twisting sliding mode control for DFIG systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wind energy has emerged as a key contributor to global decarbonization, with megawatt-class doubly fed induction generators (DFIGs) playing a central role in modern wind turbine systems owing to their high efficiency and controllability. However, conventional sliding mode control (SMC) strategies, including the super-twisting SMC (STSMC), often exhibit limited adaptability and high chattering when exposed to rapidly changing environmental and grid disturbances. In this study, we developed a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social network, perceived satisfaction with neighborhoods and depressive symptoms among older adults in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) pandemic has significantly affected social networks and perceived satisfaction with neighborhoods, potentially affecting the mental health of older adults. This study investigated the changes in these factors and their association with depressive symptoms among Korean older adults before and during the COVID-19 pandemic. The prevalence of depressive symptoms slightly increased during the pandemic (4.7-4.9%). Social networks weakened, whereas perceived...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of longitudinal outcomes and novel cluster identification in epilepsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The longitudinal course of epilepsy remains largely unpredictable. This study aimed to predict final outcome and classify dynamic longitudinal trajectories using artificial intelligence. A total of 2586 patients who first visited our epilepsy specialists between 2008 and 2017 and with at least 3 years of follow-up, were retrospectively enrolled. Supervised and unsupervised learning algorithms were employed to identify clusters with distinct longitudinal courses and to examine epilepsy parameters...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-targeted adversarial noise for 3D point cloud classification model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel method for generating dual-target adversarial examples in point cloud data, specifically designed to cause different models to misclassify into distinct attacker-specified classes. Although deep-learning models have been used to recognize 3D point clouds, they remain vulnerable to adversarial attacks that exploit the data structure. Our approach addresses this problem by minimizing the loss function using feedback from multiple models, thus ensuring targeted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating diagnostic accuracy of large language models in neuroradiology cases using image inputs from JAMA neurology and JAMA clinical challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study assesses the diagnostic performance of six LLMs -GPT-4v, GPT-4o, Gemini 1.5 Pro, Gemini 1.5 Flash, Claude 3.0, and Claude 3.5-on complex neurology cases from JAMA Neurology and JAMA, focusing on their image interpretation abilities. We selected 56 radiology cases from JAMA Neurology and JAMA (from May 2015 to April 2024), rephrasing the text and reshuffling multiple-choice answer. Each LLM processed four input types: original quiz with images, rephrased text with images, rephrased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A three-dimensional bipolar microneedle electrode array with local ground integrated at each sidewall for enhanced focal electric stimulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The need for spatially-confined electrical stimulation is growing in biomedical applications, for example intracortical stimulation and retinal implant, for enhancement of stimulating resolution. Local grounding techniques have been widely explored to suppress undesired current spread. However, in conventional microneedle arrays like the Utah array, grounding is typically achieved by assigning neighboring electrodes as ground or employing grounding wall around stimulating electrode, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sulfophenylated centimeter-sized graphene membrane in a direct methanol fuel cell]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An ideal proton exchange membrane should only allow protons to pass and remain impermeable to fuels, as required in fuel cell applications. In methanol fuel cells, high proton conductivity enables high power density, whereas methanol crossover between the electrodes degrades the catalyst activity and lowers efficiency. In conventional polymer membranes, however, conductivity and selectivity are often antagonistic: long transport pathways are needed to achieve selectivity, but these introduce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upper abdominal pain in a patient with a history of laparoscopic adjustable gastric banding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bidirectional In-Cell Photodetectors for Adaptive Luminance Control in Stretchable Displays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stretchable displays are attracting attention as next-generation platforms for wearable and IoT applications owing to their form factor. However, their visibility under external light is often degraded due to light transmission through mechanically stretched regions. To address this issue, we propose an in-cell bidirectional photodetector (B-PD) that can be integrated into subpixels of a stretchable backplane. The B-PD detects front and rear light through intentionally misaligned gate electrodes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Assessment of Growth and Protein Content in Basidiomycetous Fungi for Mycoprotein Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rising demand for sustainable and health-conscious protein sources has driven interest in fungal-derived mycoprotein as an alternative to conventional meat products. While commercial mycoprotein production predominantly relies on Fusarium venenatum, concerns over mycotoxin potential and limited strain diversity indicate the need to explore safer and edible basidiomycetes. In this study, 28 species across four taxonomic orders within Basidiomycota were screened for their potential as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strain-Level Differences of <em>Bifidobacterium breve</em> in the Gut Microbiome between Infants with and without Atopic Dermatitis: Insights from Genome Analysis and Immune Assays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bifidobacterium breve is recognized as a probiotic with immune-enhancing properties. However, our previous studies revealed that this species is present at a higher relative abundance in the gut microbiome of infants with atopic dermatitis (AD). The potential functions of B. breve in the gut microbiome may vary at the strain level between infants with and without AD (non-AD). In this study, B. breve strains were isolated from the feces of infants with and without AD and analyzed whole genome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and Challenges in Mycobacterial Genetic Engineering: Techniques for Knockout, Knockdown and Overexpression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genetic engineering of mycobacteria is challenging due to their hydrophobic cell wall structure and slow growth rates. Despite these obstacles, significant progress has been made to develop genetic engineering tools to study gene function and pathogenesis in these organisms. This review comprehensively explores the current methodologies employed in the genetic modification of mycobacteria, focusing on gene knockout, knockdown, and overexpression systems. Techniques covered include homologous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of the Gut Microbiome and Metabolomes by Fermentation Using a Probiotic Complex in a Dysbiosis-Associated Fecal Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory bowel disease (IBD), affecting up to 0.5% of the global population, is frequently associated with gut microbiota dysbiosis and metabolic imbalances, which contribute to chronic constipation and abdominal discomfort. This study investigated the modulatory effects of an eight-strain probiotic complex comprising Lactobacillus, Bifidobacterium, and Streptococcus species on the gut microbiome and metabolome using an in vitro fecal fermentation model derived from a single IBD patient with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut Microbiota Modulation by <em>Lacticaseibacillus paracasei</em> EFEL6501 Ameliorates Muscle Atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Probiotics play a crucial role in promoting host health by modulating the composition of the gut microbiota through the production of their own bioactive metabolites. The aim of the study was to investigate the anti-atrophic effects of Lacticaseibacillus paracasei EFEL6501 (EFEL6501) in dexamethasone (DEX)-treated C2C12 myotubes and a mouse model. In vitro experiments demonstrated that specific bioactive metabolites present in the cell culture supernatant (CS) and lysate supernatant (LS) of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pea Sprout Extract Promotes Hair Follicle Regeneration via Anagen Phase Prolongation and Dual Modulation of Oxidative and Inflammatory Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hair loss is a prevalent condition that affects individuals across all ages and genders. Its causes are multifactorial, involving genetic predisposition, hormonal imbalances, aging, stress and air pollution factors. A previous randomized clinical trial, reveals that daily administration of 100mg of pea sprout extract (PSE) for 8 weeks significantly increased hair density in patients, however, the underlying mechanisms remained unclear. Therefore, this study aims to investigate the efficacy and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antivirulence Activity and Therapeutic Potential of Jumbo <em>Vibrio</em> Phage pVa-22 against <em>Vibrio alginolyticus</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vibrio alginolyticus is an emerging zoonotic pathogen responsible for severe aquaculture and human infections, and its increasing antimicrobial resistance calls for alternative control strategies. Here, we report the isolation and characterization of the jumbo phage pVa-22, a phiKZ-like phage that infects V. alginolyticus. Morphological analysis of the phage via transmission electron microscopy revealed a large icosahedral capsid and contractile tail consistent with jumbo vibriophages. pVa-22...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Limosilactobacillus fermentum</em> 2L Ameliorates Chronic Stress-Induced Neuroinflammation through Gut-Brain Axis Modulation in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic stress contributes to neuroinflammation and psychiatric disorders through gut-brain axis dysregulation. This study investigated the therapeutic potential of Limosilactobacillus fermentum 2L in ameliorating stress-induced neuroinflammation using an unpredictable chronic mild stress (UCMS) model. Five L. fermentum strains were screened for probiotic properties, with strain 2L selected based on superior acid and bile tolerance, cellular adhesion, and antioxidant activity. C57BL/6J mice...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-stratified comorbidity transitions and interconnected mapping of nine allergic diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Allergic diseases exhibit increasing prevalence and multimorbidity across all ages, with strong age-dependent interrelationships. These findings highlight the need for integrated life-course-oriented strategies for allergic disease surveillance and management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolated iron deficiency in off-pump coronary artery bypass grafting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolite-mediated mechanisms linking the urinary microbiome to bladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bladder cancer is the most common malignancy of the urinary tract and is a major health burden globally. Recent advances in microbiome research have revealed that the urinary tract harbors a resident microbial community, overturning the long-held belief in its sterility. Increasing evidence suggests that microbial dysbiosis and microbially derived metabolites contribute to bladder cancer carcinogenesis, progression, and therapeutic responses. Distinct microbial signatures have been observed in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lactiplantibacillus koreensis sp. nov. and Lactiplantibacillus kimchii sp. nov., isolated from kimchi, a traditional Korean fermented food]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two Gram-stain-positive, facultatively anaerobic, rod-shaped, and non-motile lactic acid bacterial strains, designated as strains CBA3605T and CBA3606T, were isolated from kimchi, a traditional Korean fermented food. Both strains were oxidase- and catalase-negative, non-spore-forming, non-hemolytic, and non-gas-producing. Optimal growth conditions for the two strains were observed at 30°C, pH 5.0, and 0% NaCl. The two genomes were composed of a circular chromosome and three plasmids and the DNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparable Cardiovascular, Functional, and Lipid Profile Outcomes of High Intensity Telerehabilitation Versus Face to Face Rehabilitation in Chronic Stroke: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High-intensity telerehabilitation yielded cardiovascular, gait, and lipid benefits comparable to face-to-face care. Both high-intensity modalities were superior to moderate-intensity training for VO₂max. Telerehabilitation with wearables is a safe, feasible option for intensive stroke rehabilitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The "A-B-C" classification reveals outcome trajectories in patients with hepatocellular carcinoma under atezolizumab/bevacizumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Atezolizumab-Bevacizumab-Cluster (A-B-C) classification for unresectable HCC identified subgroups with histology, hepatic decompensation and patterns of progression, and prognostic trajectories, informing hypothesis generation for trial design and patient selection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early termination of six-minute walk test in COPD as simple prognostic marker vs. BODE index]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Early termination during the 6MWT is a simple, practical marker of poor outcomes in COPD, offering prognostic value comparable to the BODE index and aiding risk stratification when full assessment is impractical.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sprayable proteinic adhesive microgel-based immunosuppressive therapeutic coating for effective xenograft transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tissue transplantation is an essential therapeutic approach for restoring function in patients with tissue damage caused by aging or accidents. However, immune rejection remains a significant challenge because the host immune system recognizes transplanted xenografts as foreign, triggering systemic inflammatory responses and graft failures. Although conventional oral or intravenous immunosuppressive therapies can mitigate immune rejection, they are often associated with severe systemic side...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Lucerne Toolbox 3: digital health and artificial intelligence to optimise the patient journey in early breast cancer-a multidisciplinary consensus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Lucerne Toolbox 3 initiative addresses the pressing need for evidence-based integration of digital health and artificial intelligence (AI) technologies in early breast cancer care. The multidisciplinary consortium identified and prioritised 15 crucial medical knowledge gaps across the patient journey, from diagnosis to treatment and survivorship, using a modified Delphi consensus process with 112 unique members from 27 countries and 16 medical societies, trial groups, and patient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A prognostic classification system for extent of resection in IDH-mutant grade 2 glioma: an international, multicentre, retrospective cohort study with external validation by the RANO resect group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The efficacy of resection in IDH-mutant grade 2 gliomas remain controversial since terminology for the extent of resection has been inconsistently applied across studies. We aimed to establish a standardised classification for the extent of resection and assess the association between supramaximal resection and survival across molecular subtypes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and prognostic utility of laryngeal adductor reflex monitoring in anterior cervical spine surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Intraoperative LAR monitoring was feasible and demonstrated strong predictive value for RLN dysfunction during ACDF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Vivo tracing and systemic organ biodistribution of dermally exposed nano polystyrene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the skin barrier assumed to be intact and functionally competent effectively limits the transdermal penetration of exogenous substances, the potential for nanoplastics to penetrate this barrier and translocate systemically remains a critical toxicological concern. In this study, we employed radiolabelled ^(125)I-nano-sized polystyrene (^(125)I-nPS) to trace dermal penetration and to observe systemic biodistribution using a chronic dermal exposure model. Transcriptomic analyses revealed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of PAR2 antagonists through fragment molecular orbital-based hotspot analysis and allosteric sodium site dynamics simulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protease-activated receptor 2 (PAR2) is a G protein-coupled receptor (GPCR) implicated in inflammatory diseases and cancer, representing a validated therapeutic target. In our previous study, we combined molecular dynamics (MD) and fragment molecular orbital (FMO) analyses to rationalize binding mode differences between PAR2 agonists and antagonists. Here, we advanced this framework into a practical ligand discovery platform that integrates FMO-based hotspot mapping, pharmacophore modeling,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Life course determinants and adverse health-related outcomes of pre-frailty trajectories among older adults: Using the Korean Longitudinal Study of Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to identify pre-frailty trajectories among older adults, specifically examining the life course determinants of these trajectories and their associations with adverse health-related outcomes. Longitudinal analyses were conducted with a representative sample of 1955 older adults aged ≥65 years. Pre-frailty was measured by the 37-item Frailty Index. Participants were divided into three groups of pre-frailty trajectories: persistent pre-frailty (62.9 %), slowly increasing frailty...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparative high-performance liquid chromatography purification and structural characterization of xylobiose isomers synthesized by β-xylosidase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This research focused on synthesizing xylobiose isomers via β-xylosidase reaction and developing a preparative high-performance liquid chromatography (HPLC) separation method for their purification. The reverse reaction of β-xylosidase was conducted using 6.68 M xylose substrate at 50 °C for 24 h, resulting in 18.5 % (w/w) total xylobiose yield. Three distinct product peaks were identified and purified using preparative HPLC. Each xylobiose isomer was refined to >95 % purity through two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Prediction of Major Adverse Cardiovascular Events Within One Year After Percutaneous Coronary Intervention in Patients With Acute Coronary Syndrome: Machine Learning-Based Time-to-Event Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The proposed time-to-event ML model effectively captured dynamic risk patterns after PCI and identified key predictors with time-varying effects. These findings may support individualized postdischarge management and early intervention strategies to prevent MACE in high-risk patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature-Responsive, Injectable Poly(organophosphazene)-Based Hydrogel Adhesive for One-Step Hemostasis and Wound Closure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Their minimally invasive application and adaptability to irregular wounds make injectable hydrogel adhesives attractive for hemostasis and wound closure in surgical and emergency settings. However, current systems suffer from low mechanical strength, weak adhesion, and complex procedures. Here, we propose ADP-PPZ, a single-component, thermoresponsive hydrogel adhesive based on poly(organophosphazene) functionalized with succinimidyl carbonate (SC) groups. ADP-PPZ is readily injectable in its sol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41308117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Device-level nonlinearity and temporal memory in optoelectronic reservoir computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reservoir computing (RC) has emerged as a promising computational paradigm for processing temporally correlated and nonlinear data with low training cost. Among various physical implementations, optoelectronic devices provide a unique opportunity to directly interface light with nonlinear dynamical systems, enriching the reservoir state space through device-intrinsic responses. Light can encode information in wavelength, intensity, and pulse duration, and stimulate multiple nodes in parallel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease and adverse pregnancy outcomes: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MASLD, MetALD, and ALD were independently associated with increased risks of apos, with risk further amplified by a greater number of CMRFs. These findings underscore the importance of enhanced prenatal management for female with pre-existing SLD, particularly those with multiple CMRFs, to mitigate the risk of apos.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three-Way Decomposition for Applied Health Equity Research: A Practical Tutorial to Understand and Address Inequalities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mediation analysis is essential for understanding causal mechanisms and designing effective policy interventions. This paper explains a comprehensive framework for implementing VanderWeele's (2009) three-way decomposition using natural effect models (NEM), focusing on its application in health equity research. While three-way decomposition helps social epidemiologists understand how social exposures influence health outcomes through differential mediator effects, its implementation through NEM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of incidental low-dose radiation on abscopal responses after stereotactic body radiotherapy in patients with metastatic cancer: a retrospective real-world analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stepwise Ligand-Exchange Strategy for the High-Yield Synthesis of Water-Soluble, Metal-Doped MAg<sub>24</sub> Nanoclusters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Water-soluble gold nanoclusters (NCs) with diverse nuclearities and protecting ligands have been extensively investigated as luminescent probes for biosensing and bioimaging. In contrast, the development of water-soluble silver NCs has progressed far more slowly, primarily because synthetic routes for producing stable Ag NCs with a broad range of protecting ligands are lacking. Herein, we present an efficient, high-yield stepwise ligand-exchange strategy that addresses this challenge, enabling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Negative regulation of reassortant canine influenza virus replication and key site identification in porcine and ferret bronchial epithelial cell lines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The segmented nature and high mutability of the influenza virus RNA genome facilitate rapid mutation and reassortment, allowing the virus to breach host barriers and migrate between different species, potentially leading to unpredictable influenza outbreaks. With dogs emerging as new natural hosts for influenza virus, vigilant surveillance and scientific prevention strategies are imperative. Here, based on our previous isolation of 21 strains, which are reassortments of the canine influenza...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Kinetics and Dual-Interfacial Stability in High-Areal-Loading Electrodes for Lithium Metal Batteries via Crosstalk-Active Polymer-Functionalized Carbon Nanotubes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the rapid shift toward sustainable energy systems, battery technologies offering high energy densities and long cycle life are critical. Lithium metal batteries (LMBs) are central to achieving high energy storage required by global sustainability efforts, yet their practical deployment faces critical limitations, including dendritic lithium deposition and challenges associated with thick cathode structures. To simultaneously overcome these issues, this research develops a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2D Material-Based Memristor Arrays for Flexible and Thermally Stable Neuromorphic Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The practical implementation of 2D material-based memristors for various applications, such as neuromorphic computing and flexible electronics, faces several challenges in scalability and thermal durability. Here, a large-area, flexible, and thermally durable electrochemical metallization memristor array is demonstrated based on an engineered Al(2)O(3)/MoS(2)/graphene heterostructure. A thin Al(2)O(3) layer and graphene serve as dual barriers, effectively suppressing the unintentional metal ion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Water Retention Ability of the Dermis Following Polynucleotide Intradermal Injection Using a Water Distribution Model: Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DNA-based Bi-layered effervescent ejecting microneedle (BEE MN) for glucose-responsive insulin delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microneedle-based drug delivery systems have gained increasing attention as minimally invasive alternatives to conventional injections, particularly for chronic diseases like diabetes. However, their limited drug-loading capacity and passive diffusion-based release mechanisms pose challenges in achieving precise and efficient drug administration. In this study, we present a novel bi-layered effervescent ejecting microneedle (BEE MN) system inspired by the penetration and retention mechanisms of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41307103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Dual-Targeted Therapy with Fucoidan-Functionalized Thrombolytic Discoidal Microparticles for Pulmonary Thromboembolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed systems may offer an alternative to conventional systemic thrombolysis coupled with adjunctive pharmacological interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the antimicrobial properties of synthetic tetrahydro-2<em>H</em>-1,3,5-thiadiazine-2-thiones (THTTs) through <em>in vitro</em> and <em>in silico</em> antileishmanial and antibacterial studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infectious diseases represent a significant health concern due to their high rates of morbidity and mortality. Despite significant advances in the understanding of the pathogenic infection, existing therapies to control those infections are still unsatisfactory. Herein, a total of 18 alkyl/aryl/aralkylamines or amino acids attached 1,3,5-thiadiazine-2-thiones (4a-i, 5a-g, 6 and 7) were synthesized via one pot domino synthesis and assessed their in vitro leishmanicidal and bactericidal potential....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rushed health workforce reform in South Korea: a Kingdon's multiple streams framework analysis of the 2024 medical school quota expansion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Quota expansion alone is unlikely to resolve disparities. Sustainable reform requires transparent forecasting, targeted incentives, capacity for priority specialties/regions, and participatory governance with multi-stakeholder collaboration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comparative analysis of biologics market dynamics in 12 countries: (Bio)similar and sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The introduction of biosimilars was significantly associated with reductions in the prices and expenditures of biologics in high-income countries. This underscores the potential role of biosimilars in supporting the long-term sustainability of the healthcare system.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Herbal Combination of <em>Angelica gigas</em>, <em>Zingiber officinale</em>, and <em>Aconitum carmichaeli</em> Alleviates High Fat Diet-Induced Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease in Mice Through NRF2-Mediated Regulation of Adipogenesis and Non-Shivering Thermogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity is a complex metabolic disorder characterized by excessive fat accumulation and is closely associated with non-alcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD), a condition that increases the risk of metabolic complications such as insulin resistance, type 2 diabetes, and cardiovascular diseases. JI017 is a recently optimized multi-herbal formula composed of Angelica gigas, Zingiber officinale , and processed Aconitum carmichaeli. Clinical records of these three herbs indicate their potentially...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequencing BCMA- and GPRC5D-targeting immunotherapies in multiple myeloma: Practical guidance from the European Myeloma Network]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The treatment landscape of heavily pretreated relapsed/refractory MM has changed considerably in recent years with the introduction of novel BCMA- and GPRC5D-directed immunotherapies, including CAR T-cell therapy, bispecific antibodies (BsAbs), and antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs). Treatment selection and sequencing become increasingly complex with the broad range of therapeutic options. In this review, the European Myeloma Network provides recommendations on how to best incorporate these novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence for pediatric height prediction using large-scale longitudinal body composition data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our model produces accurate and personalized growth curves, incorporating explainable AI techniques for enhanced clinical understanding. This method advances pediatric growth assessment and provides robust clinical decision support. Despite limitations including the absence of handwrist radiography comparison and Korean population specificity, our approach demonstrates significant potential for early identification of growth disorders and optimization of growth outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Efficacy of Real-Time Artificial Intelligence-Assisted Colonoscopy in Colorectal Polyp Detection: A Prospective Multicenter Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Real-time CADe-assisted colonoscopy significantly increased PDR and ADR and proved to be a strong independent predictor of adenoma detection (cris.nih.go.kr, KCT0009664).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and Tolerability of Anti-Tumor Necrosis Factor Alpha Therapy in Refractory Intestinal Behçet's Disease: A Large Single-Center Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Anti-TNF-α therapy could be an effective and tolerable option for refractory intestinal BD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structured Integration of an Artificial Intelligence-Based System for the Optical Diagnosis of Colorectal Polyps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Integrating CADx with the 3-second rule significantly enhances the performance of endoscopists in the optical diagnosis of colorectal polyps, with the greatest benefit observed among novice endoscopists.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Bowel Cleansing with Mini S-Oral Sulfate Tablet versus the Conventional Oral Sulfate Tablet: A Prospective, Randomized, Investigator-Blinded, Multicenter, Noninferior, Phase 3 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared with conventional OST, the mini S-OST split dose showed excellent efficacy, comparable safety and tolerability, with less gastric injury (ClinicalTrial.gov identifier NCT06287606).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Field Evaluation of a Novel Combined Vaccine Against Porcine Circovirus Types 2a/d, Mycoplasma hyopneumoniae and Mycoplasma hyorhinis With an Emphasis on Growth Performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The combined vaccine demonstrated strong efficacy under field conditions, providing protection against subclinical PCV2 infection, enzootic pneumonia caused by M. hyopneumoniae, and polyserositis caused by M. hyorhinis. These findings support its potential as an effective intervention for improving both health and productivity in swine herds.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41306062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practice of Cytopathology in Korea: A 40-Year Evolution Through Standardization, Digital Transformation, and Global Partnership]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Over four decades, Korea has advanced from a limited cytology service to a global model of digital and AI-integrated cytopathology. Since the founding of the Korean Society for Cytopathology (KSC) in 1986, a nationwide framework has been established-encompassing standardized practices, systematic education for specialists and cytotechnologists, and nationwide cervical screening through the National Cancer Control Program. A mandatory Quality Assurance Program (QAP) launched in 2005 ensured...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National trends in the prevalence of hypertension and diabetes stratified by sleep duration in South Korea, 2009-2022: A nationwide cross-sectional study: Trends and association of sleep duration in hypertension and diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increase in sleep-related issues is associated with various health problems, particularly hypertension and diabetes. Therefore, this study aims to address these gaps in the literature by analyzing the relationship between sleep duration and the prevalence of hypertension and diabetes. This study analyzed the association between hypertension, diabetes, and sleep duration using the Korea Community Health Survey database from 2009 to 2022. The study used weighted linear regression models to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global epidemiology of vaccine-associated intussusception in children and adolescents, 1968 to 2024: An international pharmacovigilance study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rotavirus vaccine associated intussusception has been investigated to some extent, limited research exists on intussusception caused by all vaccines from a comprehensive, global perspective. Thus, this study aimed to investigate the global burden of vaccine-associated intussusception using a comprehensive pharmacovigilance database. This study was conducted using data from the global pharmacovigilance database from 1968 to 2024. Reports of intussusception were identified by MedDRA code and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global burden of TNF-α inhibitors associated demyelinating diseases: A global disproportionality analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite case reports linking tumor necrosis factor-alpha (TNF-α) inhibitors to demyelinating diseases, large-scale epidemiological evidence is limited. We aimed to investigate this signal detection using a global pharmacovigilance database. This study identified reports of TNF-α inhibitor-associated demyelinating disease utilizing a global pharmacovigilance database spanning from 1968 to 2024. Five TNF-α inhibitors (infliximab, adalimumab, etanercept, certolizumab pegol, and golimumab) were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Myokines Serve as Supporters of Muscle-Brain Connectivity in Obesity and Type 2 Diabetes? Potential of Exercise and Nutrition Interventions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This review outlines current evidence on myokine alterations observed in OB and T2DM and discusses how exercise- and nutrition-based approaches may modulate the muscle-brain axis to mitigate metabolic dysfunction and preserve cognitive health. Targeting beneficial myokine pathways through tailored lifestyle interventions represents a promising avenue to support both skeletal muscle and neurocognitive function in individuals with metabolic disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Association Between Menopausal Transition and Obstructive Sleep Apnea with Effect Modification by Salt Intake: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: As high salt intake may increase obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) risk through fluid retention and upper airway narrowing during sleep, we aimed to determine whether dietary salt intake modified the association between menopausal transition and the risk of OSA. Methods: Between 2014 and 2018, we conducted a longitudinal study of 2572 women aged 42-52 years at the Kangbuk Samsung Hospital Total Healthcare Center. The participants were followed up until the end of 2024. OSA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rutin as a Circadian Modulator Preserves Skeletal Muscle Mitochondrial Function and Reduces Oxidative Stress to Protect Against D-Galactose-Induced Aging In Vitro and In Vivo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Skeletal muscle aging is characterized by impaired myogenic differentiation, disrupted circadian rhythms, elevated oxidative stress, and mitochondrial dysfunction. Rutin, a natural flavonoid with antioxidant properties, has been suggested to mitigate aging processes; however, its effects on circadian regulation and muscle homeostasis remain unclear. Methods: In vitro, differentiated C2C12 myotubes were treated with D-galactose (D-gal, 20 g/L) with or without rutin (20 μM). In vivo,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Pregnancy Nutritional Adequacy and Subsequent Gestational Diabetes Risk by Body Mass Index: A Prospective Cohort Study of 2227 Korean Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study evaluated the association between nutrient intake adequacy during early pregnancy and gestational diabetes mellitus (GDM) risk through a prospective cohort study of Korean pregnant women. Methods: A total of 2227 singleton pregnant women were included in this study. Dietary assessment was conducted once during early pregnancy enrollment using the 24 h dietary recall method. The collected dietary data were analyzed using the CAN-Pro Korean food composition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health State Utility Associated with Parenteral Nutrition Requirement in Patients with Short Bowel Syndrome and Intestinal Failure in Korea: A Vignette-Based Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Short bowel syndrome (SBS) is the leading cause of intestinal failure (IF) that often requires long-term parenteral nutrition (PN). Extended PN results in severe complications and reduced quality of life (QoL). This study aimed to evaluate the QoL utility weights associated with PN duration using vignettes. Methods: We developed detailed scenarios and descriptions to represent eight hypothetical health states, reflecting variations in PN frequency in both pediatric and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of a VSV-Based Pseudovirus Platform for In Vitro and In Vivo Evaluation of Nipah Vaccine-Induced Neutralizing Responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Nipah virus (NiV) is a zoonotic pathogen characterized by high fatality rates and pandemic potential, whereby there is an urgent need for developing safe and effective vaccines. However, the evaluation of NiV vaccine-induced immunity is hindered by the requirement of Biosafety Level-4 (BSL-4) containment. In this study, we developed a recombinant vesicular stomatitis virus (rVSV)-based pseudovirus-expressing NiV fusion (F) and attachment (G) glycoproteins using a luciferase reporter gene for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Genomics of Two Newly Sequenced Rodent-Derived and One Previously Reported Tick-Derived <em>Borrelia garinii</em> Strains from South Korea Reveals Plasmid Variation and Virulence Gene Diversity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Borrelia garinii is a spirochete associated with Lyme borreliosis and is widely distributed across Eurasia. Although its genomic features have been well characterized in Europe, genomic data from East Asian isolates remain limited. Two B. garinii strains, HN13 and HN18, were isolated from a wild rodent (Apodemus agrarius) in South Korea and subjected to whole-genome sequencing and comparative genomic analysis. Their genomic features were compared with those of a tick-derived Korean strain 935...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Respiratory Microbiome of Carbapenem-Resistant <em>Acinetobacter baumannii</em> Ventilator-Associated Pneumonia: A Pilot Study from the Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ventilator-associated pneumonia (VAP) is one of the most common hospital-acquired infections. Several studies have explored the potential role of the lung microbiome as a biomarker for identifying and predicting the prognosis of VAP. However, research on the respiratory microbiome in individuals with VAP caused by carbapenem-resistant Acinetobacter baumannii (CRAB) remains limited. Therefore, we aimed to analyze the respiratory microbiome of patients with CRAB VAP. Respiratory specimens were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Empirical and Definitive Antibiotics on Pediatric Febrile Urinary Tract Infection Caused by ESBL-Producing Enterobacterales]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the clinical impact of empirical antibiotic susceptibility on urinary tract infection (UTI) caused by extended-spectrum β-lactamase-producing Enterobacterales (ESBL-PEs) is limited, the role of definitive antibiotics remains unclear. This study evaluated therapeutic outcomes and recurrence in children with febrile UTI caused by ESBL-PE, focusing on pathogen susceptibility to empirical and definitive antibiotics. Medical records of 376 UTI episodes caused by ESBL-PE in children aged <10...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FP-ZOO: Fast Patch-Based Zeroth Order Optimization for Black-Box Adversarial Attacks on Vision Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks have outperformed conventional methods in various fields such as image recognition, natural language processing, and speech recognition. In particular, vision models are widely applied to real-world domains including medical image analysis, autonomous driving, smart factories, and security surveillance. However, these models are vulnerable to adversarial attacks, which pose serious threats to safety and reliability. Among different attack types, this study focuses on evasion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Golf Swing Analysis Framework Based on Efficient Similarity Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With advances in computing power and deep learning, image-based pose estimation has become a viable tool for quantitative motion analysis. Compared to sensor-based systems, vision-based approaches are cost-effective, portable, and easy to deploy. However, when applied to golf swings, conventional similarity measures often fail to match expert perception, as they rely on static, frame-wise posture comparisons and require strict temporal alignment. We propose a Dynamic Motion Similarity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing Medical Training with Mixed Reality and Haptic Feedback Simulator for Acupuncture Needling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditional acupuncture training often lacks consistent, objective feedback, while current extended reality (XR) solutions rarely include quantitative assessment. This study developed and evaluated a feedback-enabled mixed reality (MR) acupuncture simulator to improve skill acquisition through depth-responsive guidance. The system, used on Microsoft HoloLens 2, combines a MetaHuman-based virtual patient with expert-designed acupoint geometries. It provides depth-dependent vibrotactile cues via a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-Agent Deep Reinforcement Learning for Collision-Free Posture Control of Multi-Manipulators in Shared Workspaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In multi-manipulator systems operating within shared workspaces, achieving collision-free posture control is challenging due to high degrees of freedom and complex inter-manipulator interactions. Traditional motion planning methods often struggle with scalability and computational efficiency in such settings, motivating the need for learning-based approaches. This paper presents a multi-agent deep reinforcement learning (MADRL) framework for real-time collision-free posture control of multiple...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Effects, Phytochemistry, Drug Interactions, and Safety Profile of <em>Foeniculum vulgare</em> Mill. (Fennel): A Comprehensive Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Cardiovascular diseases remain the leading cause of mortality worldwide. According to the World Heart Federation, more than 500 million people were living with cardiovascular diseases in 2021. In this context, the use of medicinal plants has become increasingly widespread in populations as a preventive strategy against cardiovascular disorders. Foeniculum vulgare Mill., commonly known as fennel, is an aromatic and medicinal plant recognized for its beneficial properties in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design, Synthesis, and Biological Evaluation of 5',7-Disubstituted 7-Deaza-adenosine Analogues as Irreversible Pan-FGFR Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Fibroblast growth factor receptors (FGFRs) are frequently dysregulated in diverse cancers and represent important therapeutic targets. Here, we report the design and synthesis of a novel nucleoside-based scaffold which enables irreversible pan-FGFR inhibition as a potential anticancer strategy. Methods: A series of nucleoside analogues was synthesized and assessed through structure-activity relationship studies. Structural analyses, including X-ray co-crystallography and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population Pharmacokinetics of Radotinib in Healthy Volunteers and Patients with Chronic Myeloid Leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Radotinib is a second-generation tyrosine kinase inhibitor (TKI) that has been used for treatment of chronic myeloid leukemia (CML). This study was performed for the first time to characterize the pharmacokinetics of radotinib, identify the factors contributing to pharmacokinetic variabilities and explore alternative dosing regimens. Methods: A total of 640 plasma concentration-time datapoints obtained from 47 participants were evaluated using nonlinear mixed-effects...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determination of Nitrosamine Drug Substance-Related Impurities Derived from Nortriptyline and Sertraline Using LC-MS/MS: A Comparative Evaluation of Chromatographic Separation and Pharmaceutical Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Nitrosamine drug substance-related impurities (NDSRIs) are a class of potent genotoxic impurities that pose a critical risk to patient safety, thereby necessitating the stringent control of pharmaceutical products. Nortriptyline (NORT) and sertraline (SERT) are two widely prescribed antidepressants that form highly potent NDSRIs, N-nitroso-nortriptyline (NNORT) and N-nitroso-sertraline (NSERT), respectively. Despite these risks, a substantial gap exists in terms of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening-Identified Oxazole-4-Carboxamide KB-2777 Exhibits In Vitro Anti-Coronavirus Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Direct-acting antivirals vary by lineage and face rapid resistance. We identified the oxazole-4-carboxamide lead KB-2777 and aimed to define its in vitro activity across α/β-coronaviruses, time-of-addition (TOA) profile, host-response signatures, and combinability with benchmark DAAs. Methods: We tested KB-2777 (≤25 μM) against HCoV-NL63 (LLC-MK2), HCoV-OC43 (Vero E6; MRC-5 for transcript profiling), and PEDV (Vero E6). We quantified extracellular viral RNA by RT-qPCR at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Nanosystems and Emerging Therapies: Innovations in Tuberculosis Treatment and Drug Resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis (TB) remains a significant worldwide health challenge due to the limitations of conventional treatments and the rising incidence of drug-resistant Mycobacterium tuberculosis strains. This review consolidates the advancements in nanotechnology-based therapeutics, inhalable formulations, CRISPR-Cas tools, host-directed therapies (HDTs), and nanoparticle-based vaccine development aimed at enhancing TB management. Novel nanocarriers such as liposomes, solid-lipid nanoparticles (SLNs),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoparticle-Mediated Nose-to-Brain Delivery for Ischemic Stroke Therapy: Preclinical Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ischemic stroke remains a major cause of mortality and long-term disability, yet current therapeutic strategies are largely limited to reperfusion approaches such as intravenous thrombolysis and thrombectomy, which are constrained by narrow treatment windows and the risk of complications. Moreover, the blood-brain barrier (BBB) severely restricts drug penetration into the injured brain, limiting the translation of promising neuroprotective agents into clinical success. Intranasal (IN) delivery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[8-Hydroxy-2-Anilino-1,4-Naphthoquinone Prevents Against Ferroptotic Neuronal Death and Kainate-Induced Epileptic Seizures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Ferroptosis, an iron-dependent form of regulated cell death characterized by excessive lipid peroxidation, has been implicated in various acute and chronic brain disorders, including epilepsy. Although 1,4-naphthoquinone derivatives have been reported to regulate ferroptosis, their mechanistic roles in the nervous system remain underexplored. Here, we investigated the protective effects of 8-hydroxy-2-anilino-1,4-naphthoquinone (8-HANQ) on ferroptotic neuronal death in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41304754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of ionization potential depression for generation of strongly coupled plasmas in high-pressure supercritical fluids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The photosphere, one of the Sun's inner layers, and white dwarfs exist as plasmas with high electron density and relatively low temperature, satisfying the strongly coupled condition that the Coulomb coupling parameter exceeds unity. While strongly coupled plasmas are prevalent throughout space, it is difficult to produce and sustain such states in the laboratory with a sufficiently long lifetime for investigation of basic transport processes. To surmount these obstacles, we have developed a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Generative Model-Driven Design of Microbial Synthetic Promoters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A synthetic promoter is an artificially designed DNA sequence based on naturally occurring promoter elements, enabling more precise control of gene expression than natural promoters. Design of synthetic promoters with tunable expression levels is key to precise genetic regulation in microbes, supporting metabolic engineering, natural product biosynthesis, and diverse biotechnological applications. Recent advances in deep learning have made it possible to generate functional synthetic promoters...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41309366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designing Personalization Cues for Museum Robots: Docent Observation and Controlled Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Social robots in public cultural venues, such as science museums, must engage diverse visitors through brief, one-off encounters where long-term user modeling is infeasible. This research examines immediately interpretable behavioral cues of a robot that can evoke a sense of personalization without storing or profiling individual users. First, a video-based observational study of expert and novice museum docents identified service strategies that enable socially adaptive communication. Building...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41305301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly Sensitive Si-Based Electrolyte-Gated Transistor Array for Multiplexed Detection of Arboviruses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiplexed detection of arboviruses using a 4 × 4 Si-based electrolyte-gated transistor (EGT) array functionalized with specific aptamers has been investigated. The Si-based EGTs were fabricated using conventional Si microfabrication processes. The EGTs showed excellent intrinsic electrical characteristics, including a low threshold voltage of 0.8 V, a sub-threshold swing of 75 mV/dec, and a gate leakage of <10 pA, ensuring uniform device performance with low device-to-device variation....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41302797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional and clinical significance of the RNA m<sup>6</sup>A methyltransferase complex in breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The RNA modification N⁶-methyladenosine (m⁶A) plays a key role in RNA processing. It is catalysed by the RNA methyltransferase complex (MTC) which includes METTL3, METTL14 and CBLL1. Recently, a METTL3 inhibitor demonstrated promising preclinical results in several cancer types, yet the therapeutic potential of targeting m⁶A in breast cancer (BCa) remains poorly understood. Utilising a large BCa cohort, we identified that increased METTL14 and CBLL1 expression was associated with a more...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examination of How Mall Visits Moderate the Impact of Adverse Weather on Daily Step Counts: A Multilevel Analysis Using Nationwide Data from a Smartphone Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change has led to an increase in extreme weather events. Adverse weather conditions limit outdoor activities, reduce step counts, and negatively affect health. Malls offer a possible alternative for walking in such weather; however, their step-loss mitigating role remains unexplored. We analyzed data from 18,666 individuals aged ≥ 18 years (mean ± standard deviation: 48.0 ± 12.6; women: 71.5%), tracking daily step counts over a year using a smartphone application. Step count data were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning-Guided Multimodal Synchrotron Analysis Workflow for Fuel Cell Electrocatalyst Discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Synchrotron radiation provides exceptional sensitivity and resolution, enabling the acquisition of highly precise information critical for advancing fuel cell technology. When combined with machine learning-based, data-driven approaches, it offers powerful insights into reaction pathways and is poised to significantly accelerate the discovery of next-generation fuel cell catalysts. However, the singular characterization and complex feature space of synchrotron radiation data, necessitates a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Historical and current spatiotemporal patterns of wild and vaccine-derived poliovirus spread]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Outbreaks of vaccine-derived poliovirus type 2 (cVDPV2) have become a major threat to polio eradication. However, variations in spatiotemporal spread have not been quantified. Here we analysed cVDPV2 cases and wild poliovirus type 1 sequences to uncover spatiotemporal patterns and drivers of poliovirus spread. Between 1 May 2016 and 29 September 2023, 3,120 cVDPV2 poliomyelitis cases were reported across 75 outbreaks in 39 countries. Outbreaks had a median observed circulation of 202 (range...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between oral management and complications after hematopoietic stem cell transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Pre-HSCT oral management by dentists may not reduce the duration of severe oral mucositis or all-cause mortality, but may reduce post-transplant infections. Further studies are warranted to clarify the components of oral management that most effectively affect oral mucositis and mortality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of membrane protein activity by cyclopropane fatty acids in Escherichia coli lipid environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Membrane proteins are crucial in cellular processes like signal and energy transduction and are influenced by the properties of the surrounding lipid bilayer. Fatty acids, key components of phospholipids, adjust membrane properties in response to environmental changes; however, their direct effect on membrane protein activity is poorly understood. Cyclopropane fatty acids (CFAs) are produced by a cyclopropane fatty acid synthase (Cfa) by adding a methylene group to unsaturated fatty acids. CFAs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[dFlpTag, a RMCE-based tool for simultaneous endogenous protein tagging and cell labeling in Drosophila]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conditional protein tagging is a potent technique for elucidating protein expression patterns. The existing MiMIC and CRIMIC insertion collections in Drosophila genome offer a foundation for rapidly generating conditional protein tagging strains. In this study, we introduce dFlpTag, a new tool designed to create both constitutive and conditional protein tagging strains from MiMic or CRIMIC insertions. Moreover, dFlpTag enables co-labeling of the source cells of the protein of interest in a cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KDIGO 2025 ADPKD guideline through pediatric eyes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128023815&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>