<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 07:37:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Directly reprogrammed NK cells driven by BCL11B depletion enhance targeted immunotherapy against pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study presents a synergistic immunotherapy platform that integrates NK reprogramming, CAR engineering, and tumor sensitization. The combinatorial approach significantly enhances antitumor efficacy in PDAC and offers a promising strategy for overcoming immune resistance in solid tumors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamics of the DNA Viral Community in Korean Coastal Waters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in metaviromics have revealed vast viral diversity across aquatic environments, yet coastal marine viromes remain underexplored compared to their open-ocean counterparts. In this study, we analyzed 49 surface water samples from 16 coastal sites around Korea, generating 265 gigabases of metagenomic sequence data. Following quality control, 754 DNA viral contigs of ≥10 kb (medium quality or higher) were recovered, with bacteriophages comprising 95% and nucleocytoplasmic large DNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-pot production of colored bacterial cellulose]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Due to health and pollution concerns, sustainable textile production is receiving increasing attention. Bacterial cellulose (BC) offers an environmentally friendly alternative to petroleum-based fabrics. However, the use of petroleum-based synthetic colorants and toxic reagents in dyeing processes impedes the fully sustainable production of colored BC. To address this issue, we developed a one-pot production system for colored BC biosynthesis, aiming to simplify and streamline the manufacturing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Cryptographic Transistor with Stochastic Carrier Trapping and Detrapping for a True Random Number Generator]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A cryptographic transistor called a cryptosistor, based on CMOS technology, is demonstrated as a true random number generator (tRNG). It exploits stochastic carrier trapping and detrapping at a deliberately destabilized interface between the gate oxide and silicon channel. Three entropy sources contribute to randomness: impact ionization-generated carriers, jittered out-diffusion carriers, and carriers affected by trapping/detrapping. To enhance carrier variation, a low-quality tetraethyl...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhibition of nuclear ROCK2 by a novel thiourea derivative induces potent antitumor effects through PTEN/FOXO1 pathway restoration in prostate cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aberrant activation of the PI3K/Akt signaling pathway and frequent silencing of the tumor suppressor PTEN are central drivers of prostate cancer progression and therapeutic resistance. Addressing this dual dysregulation, we identified compound 25, a novel thiourea derivative, as a potent and selective anticancer agent. Among structurally related analogs, 25 exhibited the strongest antiproliferative activity in prostate cancer cells, while showing minimal cytotoxicity toward normal colon and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Portable duplex digital PCR for on-site detection of IDH mutations in gliomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate identification of critical genetic markers in brain tumors, such as isocitrate dehydrogenase (IDH) mutations, is vital for predicting overall survival, which can reach 11.4 years for IDH-mutant gliomas compared to 14.6 months for IDH-wildtype glioblastoma (GBM). However, existing diagnostic methods, including immunohistochemistry and next-generation sequencing, are time-consuming and difficult to implement in post-surgical contexts. Here, we present a proof-of-concept for a portable,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Microbial production of propionic acid through a novel β-alanine route" [Metabol. Eng. (2026) 219-231 93]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tracing threats across the land-marine transition areas: Decoding heavy metal sources and risks in soil-water-sediment systems of northern and eastern coastal China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heavy metal(loid)s (HMs) in coastal environments exhibit complex cross-media transport and ecological risks under the combined influence of natural and anthropogenic processes. This study conducted a comprehensive tri-media (soil, water, and sediment) assessment in a typical coastal area of northern and eastern China. The study integrated geochemical baselines (GeoBs), source apportionment, partitioning behavior, and ecological risk prediction. GeoBs of cadmium (Cd) and lead (Pb) in both soil...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrodynamic flutter and free-surface breakup of a retracting elastic sheet]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We study the hydrodynamic flutter and wrinkling of a retracting elastic sheet and the resulting interfacial flow phenomena. A simple experimental model is constructed in which the elastic sheet is initially stretched and floats on a free surface. When the sheet retracts rapidly from the initially stretched state, the imbalance of the shear stresses exerted on the sheet causes the tip to flutter. Because of this tip flutter, the free surface becomes unstable, breaking up into separated liquid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Electromagnetic Interference Shielding Performance in Multilayered Thermotropic Polyarylate Composites Reinforced with Carbon Nanotubes, Carbonyl Iron Particles, and Carbon Fibers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of lightweight, thermally stable, and high-performance electromagnetic interference (EMI) shielding materials is critical for next-generation electronic applications. In this work, thermotropic polyarylate (TP)-based composites reinforced with 3 wt % carbon nanotube (TCNT3), 5 wt % carbon fibers (TCF5), and 80 wt % carbonyl iron particles (TCIP80) are fabricated via melt compounding, hot-pressing, and multilayer stacking. Microstructural analyses reveal well-dispersed fillers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Dynamics-Based Optimization of Glyme Electrolytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the demand for high-energy-density lithium-ion batteries has increased, lithium metal batteries have emerged as promising alternative. Glyme-based electrolytes are attractive candidates for lithium metal systems due to their high ionic conductivity and improved electrochemical stability compared to conventional carbonate-based electrolytes. In this study, we employed atomistic molecular dynamics simulations to optimize glyme electrolytes with the goal of enhancing the ionic conductivity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic Surgery for Obese Type 2 Diabetes: Korean Multicenter Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: After adjusting for baseline differences, no statistically significant difference in T2DM remission was observed between SG and RYGB at 1 and 2 years in Korean patients with BMI ≥ 30 kg/m². These findings should be interpreted with caution given the modest sample size and limited follow-up. Prospective studies are needed to validate these findings and support clinical decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pan-cancer single-cell RNA sequencing analysis refines multi-origin monocyte and macrophage lineages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor-associated macrophages (TAMs) play crucial and important role in cancer dynamics by affecting homeostasis, immunosuppression, and angiogenesis within the tumor microenvironment. Using single-cell transcriptomics, we constructed a comprehensive atlas of myeloid cell populations across healthy and pan-cancer tissues that revealed heterogeneity. Our analysis suggested that TAMs may arise from two distinct origins: C1QC+ TAMs, which likely are derived from resident tissue macrophages, SPP1+...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bevacizumab plus erlotinib in advanced solid cancers with Krebs cycle gene mutations: A multicenter phase II study (BRISK; KCSG AL22-16)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Bevacizumab plus erlotinib demonstrated promising efficacy in tumors with Krebs cycle gene mutations, warranting further investigation beyond FH-deficient RCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MALDI mass spectrometry analysis of <em>N</em>-glycans through DMTMM-mediated benzylamidation and Girard's reagent P labeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glycosylation is one of the major post-translational modifications of proteins and plays important roles in diverse biological processes, including cell signaling and recognition. Matrix-assisted laser desorption/ionization mass spectrometry (MALDI-MS) has been widely used to analyze glycans formed through glycosylation because it generates mainly singly charged ions and offers relatively high ionization efficiency for glycans. In this study, we present a method for MALDI-MS-based N-glycan...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncovering elusive ultrafast charge transfer-driven structural changes in 4,4'-bis(9-carbazol-9-yl)-1,1'-biphenyl, a paradigmatic molecular triad]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic semiconductors have attracted significant attention for their potential in flexible, lightweight, and tunable optoelectronic applications. Among them, 4,4'-bis(9-carbazol-9-yl)-1,1'-biphenyl (CBP) is one of the most widely employed host materials. However, despite its extensive applications, its intrinsic excited-state dynamics and subsequent structural evolution remain underexplored. In this study, we combined femtosecond transient absorption (fs-TA) spectroscopy and nonadiabatic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>In Silico</em> Target Discovery of Kaempferol: Therapeutic Effect of Kaempferol on Atopic Dermatitis through Regulation of Aryl Hydrocarbon Receptor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aryl hydrocarbon receptor (AhR) is known to bind several exogenous ligands such as natural plant flavonoids, synthetic polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons, and dioxin-like compounds, but its association with kaempferol (KF) is unknown. Therefore, in this study, AhR was explored as an atopic dermatitis (AD)-regulating target of KF for AD regulation using in silico prediction, and pharmacological prediction and various AD-induced models confirmed that KF exhibited pharmacological activity through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A CMOS Voltage Reference with PTAT Current Using DIBL Compensation for Low Line Sensitivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a low-power CMOS voltage reference with low supply sensitivity, designed and verified in a 180 nm standard CMOS technology. A DIBL-based line-sensitivity (LS) compensation path is incorporated into the conventional PTAT generation circuit to simultaneously provide a reference voltage and a bias current with improved LS. The proposed circuit achieves LS values of 0.01%/V for the voltage reference and 0.07%/V for the bias current reference over a supply voltage range of 1.4 V...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transmit-Receive Module Diagnostic of Active Phased Array Antenna Using Side-Lobe Blanking Channel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article presents a diagnostic method for transmit-receive modules (TRMs) in an airborne active phased array antenna (APAA). Given the spatial constraints of airborne radar systems, the diagnostic functionality was implemented using the peripheral probe method. To minimize the space, cost, and time required for modifications to the existing APAA, the side-lobe blanking (SLB) channel was employed as the probe. To prevent TRM saturation and to determine the fault detection threshold, an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SH003 as a Redox-Immune Modulating Phytomedicine: A Ferroptosis Induction, Exosomal Crosstalk, and Translational Oncology Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Redox dysregulation, ferroptosis evasion, and immune suppression are major barriers in cancer therapy. SH003, a multi-herbal formulation standardized under GMP conditions and evaluated in early-phase clinical studies (NCT03081819; KCT0004770), demonstrated a favorable safety profile supporting its translational potential. Preclinical studies reveal that SH003 disrupts mitochondrial homeostasis, triggers endoplasmic reticulum stress apoptosis, and sensitizes resistant tumors to ferroptosis via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Evidence on the Use of Traditional Korean Medicine in Managing Intervertebral Disc Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Korean medicine healthcare (KMHC), a form of traditional medicine including acupuncture and herbal medicine, is widely utilized by patients with intervertebral disc disease (IVDD). With the increasing use of real-world evidence (RWE) in the medical field, this study aims to derive RWE on KMHC utilization and its associated factors in patients with IVDD. Methods: Data from 495 individuals who received outpatient healthcare for IVDD regardless of the purpose such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ligand-Assisted Purification of Mixed-Halide Perovskite Nanocrystals with Near-Unity PLQY for High-Color-Purity Display Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cesium halide perovskite nanocrystals (PNCs) have emerged as promising materials for application in high-color-purity displays due to their exceptional optoelectronic properties, which include narrow emission linewidths, tunable bandgaps, and high photoluminescence quantum yields (PLQYs). However, preserving these characteristics during purification remains a major challenge as surface ligand detachment during the washing process can lead to increased defect states, reduced quantum efficiency,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expert Perspectives on Enhancing Analytical Methods for Multi-Ingredient Dietary Supplements (MIDS): A Qualitative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing demand for multi-ingredient dietary supplements (MIDS), driven by diverse consumer health needs, has introduced analytical challenges in product testing and quality control. These challenges stem from complex ingredient interactions, formulation variability, and the diverse physicochemical properties of the individual components. To examine these issues and explore practical solutions, this study employed semi-structured focus group interviews with 33 industry professionals and 10...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative Analysis of Gene Networks Associated with Adipose and Muscle Traits in Hanwoo Steers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to characterize tissue-specific expression patterns in Hanwoo steers by identifying co-expression modules, functional pathways, and hub genes related to fat and muscle traits using Weighted Gene Co-expression Network analysis (WGCNA). RNA-Seq data were generated from three muscle tissues (longissimus muscle, tenderloin, and rump) and two fat tissues (back fat and abdominal fat) collected from six 30-month-old Hanwoo steers. Quality control of raw sequencing reads was performed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of Expression Quantitative Trait Loci (eQTL) for Adipose-Specific Regulatory Mechanisms in Hanwoo (Korean Cattle)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the genetic regulatory mechanisms of fat accumulation is crucial for improving beef quality. Hanwoo (Korean native cattle) is renowned for its high intramuscular fat (marbling), yet the genetic regulation of adipose gene expression remains insufficiently understood. In this study, we performed expression quantitative trait loci (eQTL) analysis using RNA-Seq data and genotype data from backfat tissue of 75 Hanwoo steers to identify regulatory variants associated with adipose...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effects of Vibration Therapy on Activities of Daily Living After Stroke: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Activities of daily living (ADL) are critical for independence after stroke, yet many survivors remain functionally limited. Vibration therapy (VT), including whole-body and focal modalities, has been proposed as an adjunct to enhance recovery, but effects on ADL remain unclear. This study aimed to evaluate the overall effectiveness of VT on ADL and to identify moderating factors. Methods: A systematic review and meta-analysis were conducted following PRISMA 2020...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing Obstructive Sleep Apnea Management: Recent Trends from Conventional to Innovative Therapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) is a common disorder characterized by recurrent upper airway collapse during sleep, leading to intermittent hypoxemia and sleep fragmentation. Untreated OSA is associated with increased risks of cardiovascular, metabolic, and neurocognitive comorbidities, as well as considerable socioeconomic burden. Positive airway pressure (PAP) remains the gold standard therapy; however, limited long-term adherence underscores the need for alternative, patient-centered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Cariogenic Organic Acid Concentrations According to Combined Use of Sucrose and Sugar Alcohols]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: This study involves a quantitative analysis of organic acids (lactate, acetate, propionate, formate, butylate, pyruvate, and valeric acid) concentrations after applying sucrose and sugar alcohols such as xylitol and erythritol in the oral cavity. Methods: Saliva samples were obtained from five volunteers before and up to 60 min after oral washing with sucrose and sugar alcohol (xylitol and erythritol). Concentrations of seven organic acids (lactate, acetate, propionate, formate,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long Noncoding RNA Lnc-MTPAP-1 Overexpressed by Particulate Matter Suppresses Apoptosis in Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lung cancer remains one of the most common and lethal malignancies worldwide, with poor prognosis largely due to late-stage diagnosis and resistance to therapy. Emerging evidence indicates that long non-coding RNAs (lncRNAs) play critical roles in cancer development, metastasis, and treatment resistance. Particulate matter (PM), a major environmental pollutant and recognized Group 1 carcinogen, has been linked to lung cancer through mechanisms that may involve dysregulation of lncRNA expression....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Technologies for Monoclonal Antibody Discovery and Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monoclonal antibodies (mAbs) represent one of the most successful classes of biopharmaceuticals, with more than 100 approved for treating oncological, immunological, and infectious diseases. Antibody discovery and development have been driven by diverse methodologies. Classical strategies such as mouse hybridoma technology, phage display, transgenic mouse models, and single B cell isolation have enabled the generation of high-affinity therapeutic antibodies. Beyond binding affinity, recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exosomal microRNA Panels for Detecting Early-Stage Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Early diagnosis of lung cancer requires lung nodule biopsies, which can lead to severe complications. This study aimed to identify optimized panels of exosomal microRNAs (miRNAs) for non-invasive diagnosis of early-stage non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC). Materials and Methods: This study comprised four phases: discovery, validation, optimization, and confirmation. In the discovery phase, next-generation sequencing profiled 2656 exosomal miRNAs in serum samples (n = 76) from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seaweed Foliar Biostimulants Improve Growth and Phytochemicals of Thai Basil (<em>Ocimum basilicum</em> L.) in a Plant Factory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to identify the optimal concentration of seaweed extract (SE) for enhancing growth, photosynthetic traits, antioxidant activity, and bioactive compound accumulation in Thai basil (Ocimum basilicum L.) plants cultivated in a fully controlled plant factory. Basil plants were foliar-sprayed twice weekly with five SE concentrations (0.5, 1.0, 1.5, 2.0, and 2.5 mL·L^(-1)), while untreated plants served as controls. After 28 days of transplanting, plant growth parameters,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing multi-task in vivo toxicity prediction via integrated knowledge transfer of chemical knowledge and in vitro toxicity information]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of potential drug toxicity is a crucial step in early drug development. in vivo toxicity assessment represents a key challenge that must be addressed before advancing to clinical trials. However, traditional in vivo experiments primarily rely on animal models, raising concerns regarding cost, time efficiency, and ethical considerations. To address these challenges, various computational approaches have been developed to support in vivo toxicity evaluations, though these methods...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KLC3 regulates axonemal glutamylation via RAB11/FIP5 in polycystic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[KLC3 was identified as a novel ciliary gene in a previous study that caused cyst formation due to abnormal ciliary defects in cyst-lining cells of polycystic kidney disease (PKD) models. RAB11FIP5 is a regulator of tubulin post-translational modification (PTM) in primary cilia and is located on basal bodies. Here, we determined the relationship between KLC3 and RAB11FIP5 mediated tubulin PTM, which may be involved in cyst progression in patients with PKD. KLC3 co-localizes and interacts with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Association Between Cohabitation With Dementia Patients and Family Mental Health: Age-Stratified Findings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dementia is a global health issue and its effects on family caregivers are substantial. This study investigated the relationship between cohabitation with patients and the mental health of families in South Korea. On the basis of the nationwide data, 24,874 individuals with dementia within their families were included in the analysis. Multivariate logistic models were used to compare the 3 mental health issues (stress, depression, and suicidal ideation) between the cohabiting and noncohabiting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive factors for dementia among older adults in South Korea: an interpretable machine learning analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Age and education were the strongest predictors of cognitive function, while modifiable factors-including oral health, depression, social engagement, and IADL performance-played significant roles across subgroups. This interpretable machine learning approach revealed nuanced patterns of predictor importance across cognitive status, age, and sex, underscoring the value of targeted interventions to reduce dementia risk in aging populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cancer risks of hematopoietic/lymphatic and urinary system in pharmaceutical plant workers: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: From this systematic review and meta-analysis, the authors concluded that potential hazardous occupational exposures of workers in pharmaceutical plants could pose an increased risk of hematopoietic/lymphatic system and urinary system cancer. Future studies should be conducted with a more thorough dose-response relationship distinction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative Outcomes of Single-Port Robot-Assisted Versus Conventional Nipple-Sparing Mastectomy with Immediate Reconstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The SP RA-NSM procedure is a safer and more favorable surgical approach that could serve as a significant alternative to CNSM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanically resilient 3D lattices with soft-hard bicontinuous nanostructures via phase-separated interpenetrating composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving simultaneously high strength and toughness in lightweight architected materials remains a fundamental challenge because of the inherent tradeoff between these properties. Herein, we propose a novel strategy for fabricating robust 3D lattice structures by integrating photopolymerization-induced phase separation with the formation of an interpenetrating phase composite (IPC). This approach enables the creation of bicontinuous nanostructures composed of a soft acrylate phase and a hard...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient nanophotonic devices optimization using deep neural network trained with physics-based transfer learning methodology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose a neural network (NN)-based surrogate modeling framework for photonic device optimization, especially in domains with imbalanced feature importance and high data generation costs. Our framework, which comprises physics-based transfer learning (PBTL)-enhanced surrogate modeling and scalarized multi-objective genetic algorithms (GAs), offers a generalizable solution for photonic design automation with minimal data resources. To validate the framework, we optimize quantum cascade laser...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraoperative hypotension after remimazolam or propofol induction with sevoflurane maintenance in angiotensin II receptor blockers-treated patients: a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Robot-assisted laparoscopic prostatectomy (RALP) is associated with hemodynamic shifts; patients on angiotensin receptor blockers (ARBs) are especially susceptible to intraoperative hypotension. We investigated whether induction with remimazolam reduces the intraoperative hypotension incidence and severity compared with propofol in this population. Herein, 112 hypertensive patients undergoing RALP who continued ARB therapy received remimazolam (0.2 mg/kg) or propofol (1-1.5 mg/kg) for anesthetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia in older adults with schizophrenia: a 12-year analysis of prevalence, incidence, and treatment patterns in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Older adults with schizophrenia face a significantly elevated risk of dementia. However, recent trends remain unclear within South Korea's rapidly aging schizophrenia population. This study aimed to quantify the burden of dementia in older schizophrenia patients by examining prevalence, incidence, dementia subtypes, pharmacologic treatment, and healthcare utilization. Using nationwide Health Insurance Review and Assessment (HIRA) data from 2010 to 2021, we identified 220,378 individuals aged ≥50...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinicoradiologic differences between orbital schwannoma and cavernous venous malformation: a retrospective comparative case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To compare the clinical and radiological characteristics, and surgical outcomes of orbital schwannoma and cavernous venous malformation (CVM). We retrospectively compared 13 and 26 patients with biopsy-proven orbital schwannoma and CVM, respectively, analyzing clinical features, magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) and computed tomography (CT) features (including dynamic contrast enhancement [DCE] imaging, apparent diffusion coefficient [ADC] and CT attenuation), surgery type, and outcomes. In both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Appendicitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The appendix is a small, worm-like diverticulum of the caecum, potentially having a role in regulating intestinal microbiota and immunology. Inflammation of the appendix, acute appendicitis, is one of the most common reasons for acute abdominal pain in children and adults and surgical emergency visits worldwide. The pathophysiology of appendicitis is still poorly understood. During the past decade, evidence has overturned the long-lasting dogma that all appendicitis cases have a clinical course...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Lactococcus lactis and Bifidobacterium longum attenuate Clostridioides difficile- or Clostridium symbiosum-induced colitis and depression/anxiety-like behavior in male mice" [Microb Infect 27(7) (2025) 105560]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathologist-Artificial Intelligence (AI) Concordance in HER2 Interpretation for Advanced Biliary Tract Cancer: Intra-observer, Inter-observer, and Human-AI Variability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biliary tract cancer (BTC) is a rare, aggressive malignancy with a poor prognosis. HER2 is overexpressed in a subset of BTC patients, and recent advances in HER2-targeted agents are expanding therapeutic options. However, accurately assessing HER2 expression is challenging in BTC, especially at low levels. This study compared HER2 interpretations in advanced BTC by pathologists using light microscopy (LM) and digital pathology (DP) and evaluated the potential of artificial intelligence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endovascular vs. Open Surgical Approach in Patients with Acute Limb Ischaemia: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Endovascular and open revascularisation yielded comparable early outcomes. Endovascular treatment offered modest improvements in long-term survival, shorter hospital stays, and fewer infections, but with an increased risk of intracranial haemorrhage. Given the heterogeneity and limited number of randomised trials, further high-quality evidence is needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychiatric and psychosocial determinants of suicidality: Findings from a national mental health survey in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MDD, nicotine dependence, social isolation, and self-harm were identified as the strongest factors distinguishing suicidal ideation from suicide attempts, although the cross-sectional design limits causal inference.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-term β-lactam antibiotic exposure promotes peptidoglycan translocation to the brain and impairs functional connectivity and social recognition in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Broad-spectrum β-lactam antibiotics, such as ampicillin, disrupt the commensal gut microbiota and reduce its diversity. However, their potential short-term impact on the translocation of bacterial peptidoglycan (PGN) fragments to the brain and subsequent effects on brain function remain unexplored. In this study, we investigate the effects of a clinically relevant dose of ampicillin on PGN translocation into the brain, gene expression, brain functional connectivity, and social behavior in young...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Safety and Efficacy of Remimazolam versus Propofol for ERCP with the patient Under Deep Sedation: A Multi-center Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Remimazolam is a safe and effective alternative to propofol for sedation during ERCP, demonstrating comparable sedation efficacy, higher patient satisfaction, reduced injection site pain, and fewer moderate-to-severe cardiopulmonary adverse events. Remimazolam thus has strong clinical utility, particularly in patients at a higher risk of sedation-related complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Special Report: Recommendations on Screening for Hydroxychloroquine Retinopathy (2026 Revision)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The American Academy of Ophthalmology Recommendations on Screening for Hydroxychloroquine (HCQ) Retinopathy are now a decade old. This revision provides an update, based on current knowledge. Major points and changes are: NATURE OF TOXICITY: The retina typically remains clinically normal for many years on HCQ, but there is an unpredictable point at which signs of toxicity may develop.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intestinal barrier alterations in mice following fecal microbiota transplant from children of IBD-affected mothers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Fecal microbiomes of children of mothers with IBD exhibit characteristics that reduce epithelial tight junction barrier genes and tolerogenic tryptophan metabolism. Microbiome-induced gut barrier disruptions may contribute to an enhanced IBD predisposition in infants of mothers with IBD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced microplastic removal using a mini-hydrocyclone with microbubbles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microplastics (MPs) are prevalent in aquatic environments and pose a serious risk to human health through the adsorption of toxic substances and entry into the food chain. Therefore, the development of effective removal strategies is essential. Mini-hydrocyclones (MHCs) offer a promising solution for MP separation owing to their high throughput, rapid processing, and low maintenance. However, their performance diminishes when interacting with MPs with densities similar to that of water. To...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Referral care utilization and financial burden of comorbidities among individuals with pulmonary tuberculosis: A two-part model analysis of Indonesia's national health insurance data, 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study reports that individuals with pulmonary tuberculosis who also have noncommunicable diseases face a much heavier financial burden within Indonesia's National Health Insurance program. Strengthening primary care and integrating tuberculosis and noncommunicable disease management should be implemented to reduce costs and improve health outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Survival benefit of resectability determined by multiple surgeons in BCLC-C Stage: A single-center cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Determining resectability at the BCLC-C stage and performing resection may improve survival.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Process for Quality Management of Electronic Medical Records-Based Data: Case Study Using Real Colorectal Cancer Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In sum, we developed a rules-based QMP to address errors and impute missing values in Korea Clinical Data Use Network for Research Excellence data, enhancing data quality. The applicability of the process to real-world datasets highlights its potential for broader use in clinical studies and cancer research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Assessment of Fine Motor Control and Vocalization in Parkinson Disease Through a Smartphone App: Cross-Sectional Study of Time-Severity Interaction Effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates that a smartphone-based assessment, conducted over just a few minutes, can detect subtle temporal changes in fine motor and vocal control. The app successfully captured the earlier onset of dysrhythmia in individuals with PD and, importantly, identified significant time-severity interaction effects in vocal performance. This suggests that such digital tools can provide sensitive, dynamic insights into symptom progression, potentially enabling more precise...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vitamin B supplementation enhances the efficacy of non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs in patients with painful foot and ankle conditions: A multicenter, prospective, randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Combining vitamin B complex with anti-inflammatory drugs effectively reduces pain and improves function in patients with chronic foot disorders. This combination therapy offers a promising strategy for improving pain control and functional outcomes in orthopaedic outpatient settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic role of effective radiation dose to immune cells in esophageal cancer treated with definitive chemoradiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A higher EDIC is an independent predictor of poor survival in patients with esophageal squamous cell carcinoma undergoing CCRT. Reducing radiation exposure to the immune system through optimized radiation planning and lymphocyte-sparing techniques may improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Freud Gradiva and the Aesthetic Unconscious: Lessons for the Plastic Surgeon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wilhelm Jensen Gradiva (1903) and Freud 1907 interpretation reveal how repression, delusion, and recollection shape the psychic transformation of desire. This triadic process offers valuable insight into the hidden emotional dynamics that often underlie aesthetic motivation in plastic-surgery patients, where the pursuit of beauty may reflect unresolved inner conflict. A hermeneutic-conceptual analysis was conducted on Freud Delusion and Dream in Jensen's Gradiva, complemented by reflective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Form, Tissue, and Prāṇa of Sculptor and Plastic Surgeon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of fibrosis, clinical events and mortality in MASLD: Data from the Global-MASLD study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this large global biopsy-based MASLD cohort, advanced fibrosis was highly prevalent and strongly linked to T2D. Both histologic fibrosis and NITs were independent predictors of mortality and clinical outcomes, underscoring the prognostic value of fibrosis assessment with non-invasive tests.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultraprocessed Food Consumption and Risk of Early-Onset Colorectal Cancer Precursors Among Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, higher UPF intake was associated with increased risk of early-onset colorectal conventional adenomas. These data highlight the important role of UPFs in early-onset colorectal tumorigenesis and support improving dietary quality as a strategy to mitigate the increasing burden of EOCRC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disparities in the Diagnosis and Treatment of Breast Cancer Among People With Disabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study of women with breast cancer, those with disabilities experienced significant disparities in stage at diagnosis, treatment access, and survival outcomes compared with those without disabilities. These findings highlight the critical need for targeted interventions to address disability-related barriers and ensure equitable health care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated With Patient Safety Activities of Clinical Nurses: A Cross-Sectional Secondary Data Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings provide a basis for educational programs to improve nursing skills and highlight the need to build an open and collaborative organizational culture.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes after coronary angiography in individuals with elevated lipoprotein(a)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Elevated Lp(a) levels are associated with increased burden of coronary atherosclerosis and significant residual risk for adverse outcomes following ICA, highlighting a need for targeted risk-reduction strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of transjugular and transfemoral approaches for leadless pacemaker implantation in Asian patients: an exploratory study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The transjugular approach for leadless pacemaker implantation demonstrated comparable procedural efficacy and pacing performance, with significantly lower rates of both puncture site bleeding and overall complications, as well as shorter hospitalization. These findings support its use as a safe and effective alternative access route, particularly in Asian patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic concordance and added value of doppler ultrasound and extended histopathologic features in primary Sjögren disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SGUS and MSGB demonstrate only fair diagnostic concordance and reflect complementary aspects of glandular involvement. Doppler ultrasound and extended histologic features provide limited incremental value. Key Points • In suspected primary SjD, SGUS and MSGB demonstrate modest agreement (κ = 0.334), with a 32.8% discordance rate. • MSGB with focus score ≥ 1 demonstrated the highest diagnostic accuracy, while extended histologic features (fibrosis, atrophy, LEL) did not provide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Description of Albimonas marina sp. nov., isolated from sea sand on the Yellow Sea Coast]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A Gram-stain-negative, anaerobic, short rod-shaped bacterium, designated as CAU 1670^(T), was isolated from a sea sand sample collected from Masiran Beach, Republic of Korea. Optimal growth conditions for the bacterium were identified as growth media containing 0-3% (w/v) NaCl at 30 °C and pH 5.5. Strain CAU 1670^(T) exhibited high 16S rRNA gene sequence similarity with Albimonas pacifica CGMCC 1.11030^(T) (97.8% similarity) and Albimonas donghaensis DSM 17,890^(T) (94.8% similarity). The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early response rates with adjunctive cenobamate in uncontrolled focal seizures: Prospective analysis of a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled study in a multinational Asian population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: To examine early responses to cenobamate therapy using prospective data from a dose-response study in Asian patients with focal seizures (YKP3089C035, C035) that employed a titration regimen starting at 12.5 mg/day.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Orbital Rim Removal in Endoscopic Transorbital Approaches: Unveiling Indications and Technical Nuances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study establishes ORR as a pivotal advancement in ETOA, demonstrating its capacity to significantly enhance surgical outcomes, particularly in specific tumor scenarios. The anatomic study convincingly demonstrated the inclusion of ORR significantly expanded the surgical exposure during the ETOA. The combination of clinical insights and the feasibility of anatomic study demonstrates ORR as a valuable tool, augmenting outcomes and expanding the surgical armamentarium for complex...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trimerization-Enhanced NIR-II/Photoacoustic Nanoprobes for Precision Osteosarcoma Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of photoacoustic imaging (PAI) and near-infrared II (NIR-II) fluorescence imaging holds transformative potential for cancer diagnostics but faces challenges in developing high-performance dual-modal contrast agents. We report tH7@CT8, an organic nanoprobe engineered through fluorophore trimerization to address the photothermal conversion efficiency limitations of small-molecule agents. Trimerization of the [1,2,5]thiadiazolo[3,4-g]quinoxaline fluorophore derivative H7 induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell-derived vesicles extruded from adipose mesenchymal stem cells attenuate intestinal inflammation and augment epithelial regeneration in a colitis model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adipose-derived stem cell (ADSC) cell-derived vesicles (CDVs) have been developed to overcome the limitations of ADSCs and ADSC extracellular vesicles (EVs). This study aims to analyze the characteristics and therapeutic effects of ADSC CDVs compared to ADSCs and ADSC EVs through ex vivo organoid and in vivo colitis experiments. ADSC CDVs were generated from ADSCs through serial extrusions using polycarbonate membrane filters. The characteristics and regenerative efficacy of ADSC CDVs were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-resolved nonlinear microspectroscopy with Gaussian beams: Spatial coherence dynamics in quantum materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a theoretical framework for time-resolved nonlinear microspectroscopy using structured light to probe spatial coherence transfer in condensed-matter systems. Unlike traditional photon echo (PE) spectroscopy, our method employs Laguerre-Gaussian (LG) modes to encode and track quantum coherence migration spatially. By expanding the diffusion propagator in LG modes, we reveal radial mode mixing and conservation of orbital angular momentum during coherence migration. Analytical formulas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Entropy and Human Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Entropy, a measure of disorder and randomness, is an essential feature of thermodynamics, chemistry, and information theory, but there has been little study of entropy in human aging. Entropy arises from random molecular interactions or other forms of damage and will manifest at all levels of human biology. It should also progress in concert across many systems and increase the risk of numerous aging-related conditions. Illustrating these principles, research by Hong in this issue of Aging Cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Assessment of Fine-Tuned Open-Source LLMs in Cardiology: From Progress Notes to Discharge Summary]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The generation of accurate discharge summaries from clinical progress notes represents a critical challenge in healthcare documentation, particularly in specialized domains like cardiology where limited annotated data and complex medical terminology pose significant barriers to automation. To address this challenge and improve clinical workflow efficiency, we developed a comprehensive approach combining synthetic data generation with fine-tuned large language models (LLMs), specifically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between erectile dysfunction and relative fat mass in adult men in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that RFM is associated with ED among adult men in the United States, with significant mediation effects via hypertension and cholesterol levels. Prospective longitudinal studies are warranted to further elucidate the role of RFM in ED development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allyl nonanoate as a novel bile-derived biomarker in metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Bile metabolomic profiling in MASLD revealed distinct clustering patterns, with several fibrosis-associated metabolites demonstrating a stepwise increase with hepatic fibrosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comparative study on stevioside- and rubusoside-assisted micellar solubilization of clofazimine for physicochemical and <em>in vitro</em> release properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study compares the micellization and encapsulation abilities of stevioside (STE) and rubusoside (RUB) for enhancing the solubility, stability, and bioavailability of clofazimine (CFZ), a poorly water-soluble antibiotic. CFZ-loaded micelles were prepared and characterized by FT-IR, XRD, DSC, SEM, and NMR. RUB showed a lower critical micelle concentration and significantly improved CFZ solubility (up to 2.06 mg/mL) compared to STE. CFZ-RUB complexes offered greater protection against UV and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of resection margin status on survival in gastric cancer: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: R1 resection significantly impairs survival across all stages of gastric cancer, with the extent and depth of microscopic involvement influencing prognosis. When R1 status is discovered postoperatively, subsequent resection should be considered to improve survival outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-based fatigue classification using heart rate variability and cortisol: A multimodal approach to wearable health monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that a fatigue prediction model based on cortisol and HRV can maintain significant predictive power with a reduced number of variables. These findings suggest the potential for practical implementation in wearable devices, enabling accurate fatigue monitoring while minimizing sensor count and computational burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of preoperative percutaneous transthoracic needle biopsy on pleural recurrence in clinically early-stage non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preoperative PTNB was statistically correlated with an increased pleural recurrence in clinical stage I NSCLC, even among patients without conventional high-risk pathological features. Careful consideration is warranted when deciding on PTNB for early-stage disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of OM-85 (Broncho-Vaxom) for prevention of acute exacerbations in patients with chronic airway diseases or chronic bronchitis: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that OM-85 therapy provides some benefits in improving exacerbation outcomes compared with placebo in patients with COPD or chronic bronchitis. Additional research is required to verify these findings due to the small number of trials and between-study heterogeneity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current lung cancer screening: a call for comprehensive reassessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive analysis of antihypertensive medications and their impact on lung cancer incidence and all-cause mortality: a population-based study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CCB use may increase the risk of lung cancer incidence and all-cause mortality compared with ARB use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of sarcopenia on early surgical outcomes in elderly patients following lung cancer surgery: a prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first large prospective study to evaluate sarcopenia according to international guidelines for lung cancer surgery. In this prospective study applying AWGS criteria, sarcopenia was not associated with increased early postoperative complications in elderly patients undergoing lung cancer surgery. However, sarcopenia was linked to poorer mental health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of pleural metastasis in non-small cell carcinomas undergoing intraoperative frozen section examination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pleural nodularity in operative field strongly indicated pleural metastasis in NSCLC. Additionally, ADC and SqCC exhibited distinct microscopic characteristics, with sclerotic fibrosis frequently accompanying pleural metastasis in ADC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structured training and early outcomes in major pulmonary resections by a junior thoracic surgeon: a retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A structured, stepwise approach-including assistantship, gradual case complexity, and cognitive preparation-enabled safe and efficient early-career outcomes in major pulmonary resections. These findings highlight the value of combined technical training and institutional perioperative support in facilitating the transition to independent surgical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bronchodilator response as an independent predictor of severity in bronchiectasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In bronchiectasis, BDR is associated with poorer lung function, more frequent exacerbation, and increased disease severity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of how sarcopenia affects functional outcomes in acute ischaemic stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenia, a common geriatric condition characterized by the loss of skeletal muscle mass and function, can negatively affect functional outcomes in acute ischaemic stroke; however, the underlying mechanisms remain unclear. We hypothesized that sarcopenia affects post-stroke outcomes, mediated through its impact on dysphagia, early neurological deterioration, or post-stroke recovery, particularly in patients with motor deficits. To explore this hypothesis, we included 600 consecutive elderly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasonographic Measurement After Multilayer Stimulation for Body Fat Reduction and Muscle Strengthening: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Combined electrical muscle stimulation, radiofrequency, and vacuum therapy produced significant reductions in abdominal fat and waist size, increased muscle thickness, and improved perceived contour with favorable tolerability. These findings support this multimodal, noninvasive approach as a promising option for abdominal shaping.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pertuzumab enhances the antitumor activity of T-DXd in HER2-positive gastric cancer cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For HER2-positive advanced gastric cancer (GC), a recent major therapeutic advancement is the development of trastuzumab deruxtecan (T-DXd), a HER2-directed antibody-drug conjugate. In this disease, simultaneously targeting HER2 and HER3 pathways has the potential to be a promising therapeutic strategy. However, the therapeutic approach of combining T-DXd with pertuzumab, which disrupts HER2-HER3 heterodimerization, has not yet been explored in GC, making this study a pioneering effort. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LiDAR-Based Long-Term Mapping in Snow-Covered Environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autonomous driving systems encounter various uncertainties in real-world environments, many of which are difficult to represent in maps. Among them, accumulated snow poses a unique challenge since its shape and volume gradually change over time. If accumulated snow is included in a map, it leads to two main problems. First, during long-term driving, discrepancies between the actual and mapped environments, caused by melting snow, can significantly degrade localization performance. Second, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Defect Identification in Automotive Brake Calipers Using PCA-Optimized Feature Extraction and Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to develop a non-contact automated impact-acoustic measurement system (AIAMS) for real-time detection of manufacturing defects in automotive brake calipers, a key component of the Electric Parking Brake (EPB) system. Calipers hold brake pads in contact with discs, and defects caused by repeated loads and friction can lead to reduced braking performance and abnormal vibration and noise. To address this issue, an automated impact hammer and a microphone-based measurement system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRTSC: Channel-Wise Recalibration and Texture-Structural Consistency Constraint for Anomaly Detection in Medical Chest Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised medical image anomaly detection, which does not need any labels, holds a pivotal role in early disease detection for advancing human intelligent health, and it is among the prominent research endeavors in the realm of biomedical image analysis. Existing deep model-based methods mainly focus on feature selection and interaction, ignoring the relative position and shape uncertainty of the anomalies themselves, which play an important guiding role in disease diagnosis, hampering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Learning-Enabled Diagnosis of Abdominal Aortic Aneurysm Using Pulse Volume Recording Waveforms: An In Silico Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the feasibility of diagnosing abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) via deep learning (DL)-enabled analysis of non-invasive arterial pulse waveform signals. We generated arterial blood pressure (BP) and pulse volume recording (PVR) waveform signals across a diverse synthetic patient cohort using a systemic arterial circulation model coupled with a viscoelastic model relating arterial BP to PVR while simulating a range of AAA severity levels. We confirmed the plausibility of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydroelectricity Generation from Fiber-Oriented Waste Paper via Capillary-Driven Charge Separation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydroelectricity energy harvesting has emerged as a promising, eco-friendly alternative for addressing the growing demand for sustainable energy solutions. In this study, we present a hydroelectricity energy harvester fabricated from shredded waste printing paper (WPP), offering a novel waste-to-energy conversion strategy that requires neither material purification nor complex processing. The device leverages the randomly entangled fiber network of WPP to facilitate capillary-driven moisture...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sensor-Efficient Estimation of Roll Misalignment via Side-to-Side Tension Differences in Roll-to-Roll Polymer Film Processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Roll misalignment in roll-to-roll (R2R) processes is a critical cause of lateral displacement and tension imbalance, leading to dimensional instability and surface defects in polymer films. Conventional analyses based on beam or camber models often require complex calibration and additional sensing, which can limit their applicability in real-time production environments. This study introduces a diagnostic approach that estimates web misalignment directly from side-to-side tension differences...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hardness and Surface Roughness of 3D-Printed ASA Components Subjected to Acetone Vapor Treatment and Different Production Variables: A Multi-Estimation Work via Machine Learning and Deep Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper analyzes the combined effects of acetone vapor treatment and 3D printing process parameters (layer thickness and infill rate) on the hardness and surface roughness of acrylonitrile styrene acrylate (ASA) components by using different machine learning and deep learning strategies for the first time in the technical literature. Considering the high-performance materials and aesthetic requirements of manufacturers, post-processing operations are highly critical for 3D-printed samples....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Review of Plasma-Synthesized/Modified Polymer and Metal Nanoparticles for Biomedical Applications Using Cold Atmospheric Pressure Plasma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review presents recent advancements in cold atmospheric pressure (AP) plasma (CAP) processes for the synthesis and surface treatment of polymer films and metal nanoparticles (NPs) in biomedical applications. We discuss the properties and applications of atmospheric pressure plasma (APP) processes, including dielectric barrier discharge (DBD) and plasma jet methods, highlighting their effectiveness in controlling surface characteristics such as wettability and functionalization.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Rosa canina</em> Extract Attenuates Muscle Atrophy in L6 Myotubes and Immobilized Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Skeletal muscle is essential not only for structural integrity but also metabolic homeostasis. Muscle atrophy, the loss of muscle mass and function, is closely linked to chronic and metabolic disorders and is driven by chronic inflammation, oxidative stress, impaired myogenesis, and disrupted protein homeostasis. The present study aimed to evaluate the protective effects and underlying mechanisms of Rosa canina extract (RCE), a polyphenol-rich plant known for its antioxidant and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mediterranean Diet Adherence and One-Year Metabolic Changes in Patients with Papillary Thyroid Cancer: An Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The Mediterranean diet (MD) has been associated with favorable metabolic outcomes in the general population. However, evidence of these associations among thyroid cancer survivors remains limited. This study examined whether higher MD adherence at diagnosis is associated with longitudinal changes in insulin resistance and lipid profiles in patients with papillary thyroid cancer (PTC). Methods: We analyzed 345 Korean patients aged ≥20 years with histologically confirmed PTC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current Utilization and Research Status of the Herbal Medicine Guibi-Tang and Its Variants for Cognitive Impairment: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Guibi-tang (GBT) and its variant Kami-guibi-tang (KGBT) are traditional East Asian multi-herb formulas prescribed for memory loss, insomnia, and fatigue. Preclinical data suggest multimodal neuroprotective actions, including cholinergic signaling modulation and activation of the cAMP response element-binding protein (CREB)/extracellular signal-regulated kinase (ERK) pathway; however, clinical evidence for cognitive disorders remains scattered. This scoping review aimed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Dietary Vitamin D Levels on Markers Related to Amyloidogenesis and Neuroinflammation in db/db Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that vitamin D may exert neuroprotective effects on the hippocampus and PFC in diabetic mice by mitigating neuronal damage and suppressing amyloidogenic and inflammatory gene expression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monoterpenoids from the Roots of <em>Liquidambar formosana</em> (Formosan Sweet Gum) Exhibit Senomorphic Activity Against Cellular Senescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results suggest that cinnamic acid-conjugated monoterpenoids may serve as interesting lead structures for the development of agents targeting the p16^(INK4A) pathway for the treatment of aging-associated diseases. Further studies will be required to clarify the mechanisms of action of this compound and to evaluate its in vivo efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-Obesity Effects of Acid-Processed <em>Citrus reticulata</em> Blanco Peel Extract Enriched in Highly Bioactive Polymethoxyflavones: Inhibition of 3T3-L1 Adipocyte Differentiation and Therapeutic Efficacy in <em>ob</em>/<em>ob</em> Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Chronic diseases linked to obesity represent a major global health challenge. Although pharmaceutical treatments show efficacy, their use is often limited by side effects. Methods: This study investigated the anti-obesity effects of acid-processed Citrus reticulata Blanco peels extract (CRBE) prepared through reflux extraction with 50% ethanol, followed by acid treatment using 3 M hydrogen chloride and neutralization. Results: Following acid treatment, the composition of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Multi-Omics Analysis Uncovers Immune-Metabolic Interplay in Hepatocellular Carcinoma Tumor Microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is one of the most common malignant liver tumors worldwide and is associated with a high mortality rate. Methods: In this study, we performed an integrated multi-omics analysis to characterize the immune and metabolic features of the tumor microenvironment (TME) in HCC. Tumor samples from 60 HCC patients were stratified into two groups based on immune activity score, and differentially expressed genes as well as differentially methylated regions were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Threshold-Based Overlap of Breast Cancer High-Risk Classification Using Family History, Polygenic Risk Scores, and Traditional Risk Models in 180,398 Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Breast cancer polygenic risk scores (PRS) and traditional risk models (e.g., the Gail model [Gail]) are known to contribute largely independent information, but it is unclear how the overlap varies by ancestry, age, disease type (invasive breast cancer, DCIS), and risk threshold. Methods: In a retrospective case-control study, we evaluated risk prediction performance in 180,398 women (161,849 of European ancestry; 18,549 of Asian ancestry). Odds ratios (ORs) from logistic regression...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing Cytoreductive Nephrectomy with Tumor Thrombectomy Between Open, Laparoscopic, and Robotic Approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: For surgical candidates with metastatic renal cell carcinoma with a tumor thrombus (mRCC-TT), surgery is cytoreductive nephrectomy with tumor thrombectomy (CN-TT). This is carried out through an open (OCN-TT), laparoscopic (LCN-TT), or robotic (RCN-TT) approach. The purpose of this study was to compare survival outcomes to CN-TT by operative approach. Methods: This was a retrospective analysis of all patients with a diagnosis of mRCC-TT, who underwent CN-TT from a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Impact of Postoperative Systemic Immune-Inflammation Index Changes in Epithelial Ovarian Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative SII monitoring, easily obtainable from routine blood tests, may help identify high-risk patients who could benefit from intensified surveillance or adjuvant treatment. Prospective multicenter studies are warranted to validate these findings and explore whether perioperative modulation of systemic inflammation can improve outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Esophageal and Gastric Cancer by Histologic Subtype in Steatotic Liver Disease: A UK Biobank Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Upper GI cancer risk in SLD patients is significantly modified by alcohol consumption, with combined metabolic dysfunction and alcohol exposure conferring the highest risks for esophageal adenocarcinoma and intestinal-type gastric cancer. Clinically, these findings suggest that SLD patients with any level of alcohol consumption require heightened cancer surveillance. Even minimal alcohol intake substantially increases cancer risk in metabolically compromised individuals, supporting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Federated Learning in Public Health: A Systematic Review of Decentralized, Equitable, and Secure Disease Prevention Approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Public health needs collaborative, privacy-preserving analytics, but centralized AI is constrained by data sharing and governance. Federated learning (FL) enables training without moving sensitive data. This review assessed how FL is used for disease prevention in population and public health, and mapped benefits, challenges, and policy implications. Methods: Following PRISMA 2020, we searched PubMed, Scopus, Web of Science, IEEE Xplore, and Google Scholar for peer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidental Findings on Abdominopelvic CT in Young Korean Soldiers: Prevalence, Clinical Relevance, and Healthcare System Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: This retrospective case series examines incidental findings (IFs) detected on abdominopelvic CT (APCT) among young Korean soldiers presenting with acute abdominal pain. APCT is a frontline test for acute abdominal pain but frequently reveals incidental findings (IFs) unrelated to the presenting complaint. While many IFs are benign, some require structured follow-up. In military settings with constrained access and frequent personnel transfers, IFs pose challenges for health-system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Chewing Difficulty and Number of Remaining Teeth with Anxiety (GAD-7) Among Korean Adults: Evidence from the 2023 KNHANES]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Oral health is increasingly recognized as a determinant of overall well-being, but its role in mental health remains underexplored. Chewing difficulty and tooth loss can impair nutrition, social interaction, and quality of life, thereby contributing to psychological distress. Objectives: This study examined the association between oral health indicators and anxiety among Korean adults. Methods: Data were obtained from 4746 adults aged ≥19 years who participated in the 2023 Korea...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nurse-Led Microsurgical Free Flap Monitoring: A Scoping Review and Evidence-Based Framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Postoperative free flap monitoring, traditionally performed by surgical residents, has shifted toward nurse-led models due to global workforce constraints. While this practice is widespread, its implementation is fragmented, creating a "standardization gap" between successful outcomes and reproducible protocols. This scoping review aimed to comprehensively map all available evidence on nurse involvement in free flap monitoring and synthesize the findings into an evidence-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Superconductivity near the Pressure-Tuned Quantum Critical Point of Charge-Density-Wave Order in Cu<sub>1-δ</sub>Te (δ = 0.016)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We have investigated the evolution of CDW states and structural phases in a Cu-deficient Cu(1-δ)Te (δ = 0.016) by employing high-pressure experiments and first-principles calculations. Raman scattering results reveal that the vulcanite structure at ambient pressure starts to change into the Cu-deficient rickardite (r-CuTe) structure from 6.7 GPa, which then becomes fully stabilized above 8.3 GPa. Resistivity data show that T(CDW1) (≈333 K) is systematically suppressed under high pressure,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Supported Polyhedral-like Co<sub>3</sub>S<sub>4</sub> Nanostructures Enabling Efficient High Current Hydrogen Evolution Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The advancement of overall water-splitting technologies relies on the development of earth-abundant electrocatalysts that efficiently produce H(2) as a chemical fuel while offering high catalytic efficiency, structural robustness, and low-cost synthesis. Therefore, we aim to develop a cost-effective and durable non-noble electrocatalyst for overall water splitting. A straightforward hydrothermal approach was employed to fabricate freestanding polyhedral Co(3)O(4) on a microporous Ni foam...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental Study on the Role of Bond Elasticity and Wafer Toughness in Back Grinding of Single-Crystal Wafers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Grinding semiconductor wafers with high hardness, such as SiC, remains a significant challenge due to the need to maximize material removal rates while minimizing subsurface damage. In the back-grinding process, two key parameters-the elastic modulus (Eb) of the grinding wheel bond and the fracture toughness (K(IC)) of the wafer-play a critical role in governing the behavior of diamond and the extent of wafer damage. This study systematically investigated the effect of Eb and K(IC) on diamond...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Branched Hyaluronic Acid for Reduced Viscosity and Enhanced Moisturization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite its remarkable moisturizing properties, the inherently high viscosity of high-molecular-weight hyaluronic acid (HA) restricts its practical application in skincare products, cosmetic formulations, and skin-contact medical devices. To overcome this limitation, we propose the incorporation of branched structures into HA to create a branched HA hybrid (bHH) by chemically coupling low-molecular-weight HA (200 kDa) with high-molecular-weight HA (700-2500 kDa). The introduction of branched...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vegetables and Glycemic Index: Exploring Their Correlation and Health Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Comparative evaluation revealed that DF exerts a buffering effect on glycemic response (GR) and supports the use of fiber ratios as a more stable and intrinsic parameter for predicting GI than standard estimation methods. Traditional approaches that rely on net carbohydrates may overlook important factors affecting glycemic impact, particularly the buffering effects of dietary fiber. This study advocates for the incorporation of carbohydrate-to-fiber ratios into GI estimation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Analysis and Risk Assessment of Polycyclic Aromatic Hydrocarbons Using Gas Chromatography-Mass Spectrometry from Herbs and Spices Distributed in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, four polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons (4PAHs: benz[a]anthracene, chrysene, benzo[b]fluoranthene, and benzo[a]pyrene (BaP)) were quantified in 110 herb and spice products marketed in South Korea. A validated gas chromatography-mass spectrometry (GC-MS) method achieved high sensitivity with limits of detection (LOD) ranging from 0.08 to 0.18 µg/kg and limits of quantification (LOQ) ranging from 0.24 to 0.55 µg/kg, with recoveries consistent with the Association of Official...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolation of Biofilm-Forming Bacteria from Food Processing Equipment Surfaces and the Biofilm-Degrading Activity of <em>Bacillus licheniformis</em> YJE5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Food processing environments are prone to microbial contamination, where biofilm formation by persistent bacteria reduces hygiene and food safety. In this study, 27 biofilm-forming bacterial strains were isolated from processing equipment surfaces, with the dominant strains identified as B. cereus LE3, B. cereus YJBR3, and P. cibi F25. An environmental isolate, B. licheniformis YJE5, exhibited no hemolytic activity and demonstrated strong enzymatic potential. Intracellular substances (ICS)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Total Eosinophil Counts, Serum Allergen-Specific IgE and Related Cytokines in Dogs with Atopic Dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canine atopic dermatitis (AD) is a chronic allergic skin disease in which various immunological markers have been investigated. While peripheral eosinophil counts, serum allergen-specific immunoglobulin E (IgE), and cytokines have each been evaluated in allergic disorders, their simultaneous assessment in dogs with AD has rarely been reported in Korea. This study aimed to evaluate the diagnostic and clinical utility of these parameters in affected dogs. A total of 93 dogs were included between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Adaptation of Wintering Water Birds to Man-Made Weirs in Relation to the Freeze-Thaw Process in Tancheon Stream, Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The roles of man-made weirs in flood control during the summer monsoon are well-known, but the function of habitats for wintering water birds has not been explored. This study examined the effects of man-made weirs on the wintering distribution of water birds in Tancheon Stream, Korea, with a focus on the impact of the freeze-thaw process. Data collected from January to February 2003 included thawed water surface ratios, water depths, sandbar areas, and bird distribution under different weather...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Calling Phenology of Two Frog Species in South Korean Rice Paddies Using Automated Call Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amphibian breeding phenology provides key insights into species' sensitivity to climatic and anthropogenic drivers. We used passive acoustic monitoring (PAM) with automated call detection to examine the calling activity of Dryophytes japonicus and Pelophylax nigromaculatus in South Korean rice paddies across five breeding seasons (2018-2022). Both species exhibited distinct seasonal patterns: D. japonicus showed a synchronous and concentrated calling peak in mid-June (GAM deviance explained =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glymphatic Dysfunction in Neuro-Pulmonary Complications Following Subarachnoid Hemorrhage: A New Perspective on Brain-Lung Axis Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH), often resulting from aneurysmal rupture, remains a life-threatening cerebrovascular disorder with high morbidity and mortality. While previous research has focused primarily on cerebral damage and neurological outcomes, growing evidence suggests that SAH also causes systemic complications, including pulmonary dysfunction. The underlying mechanisms linking SAH to lung injury, however, are not fully understood. The glymphatic system, a perivascular network that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of the iodate sorption mechanism by CoAl LDH through experiments and ab initio molecular dynamics simulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radioiodine released during the nuclear‑fuel cycle constitutes a persistent radiological hazard. In this study, the IO(3)^(-) uptake mechanism of CoAl LDH was resolved by combining pH‑controlled sorption experiments, synchrotron XAFS, and DFT-based AIMD simulations. At pH close to 6, approximately 90 % of IO(3)^(-) was removed, and the equilibrium distribution coefficient reached about 1.7 × 10⁴ mL g^(-1). EXAFS analysis indicated an average iodine-oxygen bond length of 1.81 Å and a coordination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Robust 2.5D Stereo Multi-Object Tracking with Lightweight Stereo Matching Algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multi-object tracking faces persistent challenges from occlusions and truncations in monocular vision systems. While stereo vision provides depth information, existing approaches require computationally expensive dense matching or 3D reconstruction. This paper presents a real-time 2.5D stereo multi-object tracking framework combining lightweight stereo matching with resilient tracker management. The stereo matching module employs Direct Linear Transform-based triangulation using only bounding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A plain language summary of the SAPPHIRE clinical trial of apitegromab in children and young adults with spinal muscular atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Body talk and the internalization of the ideal body image: examination based on the tripartite influence model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Negative fat talk and positive body talk did not moderate the effect of exposure to thin-ideal images on the internalization of the thin ideal. In contrast, exposure to thin-ideal images emerged as a significant factor in promoting the internalization of the thin ideal. Among women, negative muscle talk promoted the internalization of athletes' bodies. These findings may advance future research in eating disorder pathology and media psychology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cholesterol uptake capacity of HDL in culture medium of fresh primary human hepatocytes: an in vitro system for screening anti-atherosclerosis drugs focused on HDL functions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Removing excess cholesterol from atherosclerotic plaques is a crucial function of high-density lipoprotein (HDL). Compared to HDL cholesterol, cholesterol efflux capacity (CEC) is a better indicator of cardiovascular disease risk. However, this approach has several practical disadvantages, such as CEC assay requires cultured cells and takes several days to perform. Recently, we developed a simpler cell-free assay to assess the cholesterol uptake capacity (CUC), a new HDL functionality...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inulin-induced improvements on bowel habit and gut microbiota in adults with functional constipation: findings of a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Daily intake of 12 g inulin improves functional constipation by increasing stool frequency, positively affecting abdominal symptoms and well-being, and modulating the gut microbiota towards higher relative abundances of butyrate-producing genera.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermotolerance and post-fire growth in Rhizina undulata is associated with the expansion of heat stress-related protein families]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HSP20s are known to protect cells against heat stress, GSTs are involved in the detoxification of reactive oxygen species, and ACDs play a role in the metabolism of recalcitrant compounds present in post-fire environments. The expansion of these families thus suggests that they may play an important role in protecting and stimulating R. undulata ascospores during and after fire-induced heat shock, activating the fungus, and enabling it to colonise the root systems of conifers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of frailty on the adjustability of grasping force in community-dwelling older adults: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating circular economy in food waste management: insights from Thailand's shopping mall and community]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study introduces circular food waste management strategies that promote collaboration between large enterprises and community-based sectors. Thermal dehydration and anaerobic digestion were implemented as treatment technologies in a shopping mall and a local community, respectively. Thermally treated food waste from the shopping mall showed an average moisture content of 1.86% with 49.3% carbohydrates, 21.0% protein, 12.9% fat, 7.0% fiber, 8.7% ash, and a carbon-to-nitrogen (C/N) ratio of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expert Consensus-Based Criteria for Identifying Lumbar Facet Joint Pain in Primary Care: Development Using Factor Analysis and a Modified Delphi Method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Consensus-based diagnostic criteria for lumbar facet joint pain were developed, which offer a noninvasive, clinically practical approach to diagnosis, promoting early recognition and appropriate referral by general practitioners.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Daily physical activity and quality of life in patients with left ventricular assist devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The relationship between the physical activity status of patients with left ventricular assist devices (LVAD) and their quality of life (QOL) remains unclear. The aim of this study was to determine the association between physical activity status and QOL and to identify the factors influencing walking activity time in LVAD patients. Thirty outpatients with LVAD were included. Physical activity was measured using a triaxial accelerometer. QOL was assessed using the Kansas City Cardiomyopathy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interaction between gastric cancer organoids and peritoneal mesothelial cells suppresses the growth of gastric cancer organoids and induces drug resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The prognosis of gastric cancer with peritoneal dissemination is poor because of its resistance to chemotherapy. To investigate the mechanism of drug resistance in peritoneal metastasis, cancer organoids were established from the ascites of a patient with peritoneal metastases of gastric cancer. The histological characteristics of the tumors were preserved in the organoids. A co-culture system was established by overlaying human-derived mesothelial cells on gastric cancer organoids embedded in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JAXLEY: differentiable simulation enables large-scale training of detailed biophysical models of neural dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biophysical neuron models provide insights into cellular mechanisms underlying neural computations. A central challenge has been to identify parameters of detailed biophysical models such that they match physiological measurements or perform computational tasks. Here we describe a framework for simulating biophysical models in neuroscience-JAXLEY-which addresses this challenge. By making use of automatic differentiation and GPU acceleration, JAXLEY enables optimizing large-scale biophysical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of process parameters on surface roughness of laser powder bed fusion NiTi]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the influence of process parameters on the surface roughness of NiTi samples fabricated using laser powder bed fusion. The investigation uses a comprehensive full factorial design of experiments across wide ranges of scanning speed and laser power. The goal is to establish a direct correlation between surface finishings and manufacturing parameters. The coefficients obtained from the analytical fittings provide valuable insights into how roughness changes with processing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors for avascular necrosis of the femoral head in closed reduction following traction for developmental dysplasia of the hip]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Avascular necrosis (AVN) is a serious complication associated with the treatment of developmental dysplasia of the hip (DDH). In this study, we analyzed 241 affected hips from 232 patients who underwent closed reduction following traction (CR/TR) between 1995 and 2021 to identify risk factors for AVN and establish clinical strategies to reduce its incidence. All patients received four weeks of traction (horizontal, vertical, and gradual abduction) followed by closed reduction. The severity of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of anatomical adaptation in cemented femoral stems on mechanical properties and alignment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polished tapered femoral stems are widely used in total hip arthroplasty (THA) for their excellent long-term outcomes. However, anatomical mismatches in Asian populations increase the risk of periprosthetic femoral fractures and malalignment. This study evaluated the mechanical properties and radiographic alignment of the VLIAN stem-a cemented, polished, double-tapered stem with a rounded shoulder design developed for Asian femoral anatomy-compared to the Exeter stem. Mechanical testing assessed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutual inhibition between EPFL2 and auxin extends the intervals of periodic leaf morphogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rules behind the spatial arrangement of repetitive modules are key principles of multicellular morphogenesis. In plant shoots, PIN-FORMED 1 (PIN1)-mediated polar auxin transport instructs periodic formation of auxin maxima, which develop into lateral organs or leaf serrations. However, it remains unknown how the intervals of regularly arising auxin maxima are controlled. Here we show that a cysteine rich peptide EPIDERMAL PATTERNING FACTOR-LIKE 2 (EPFL2) dose-dependently determines the intervals...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased postoperative complication risk in elderly hip fracture patients with cerebrovascular disorders: A propensity score-matched nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cerebrovascular disorders are associated with increased postoperative infectious and cognitive complications in elderly hip fracture patients. These findings underscore the importance of incorporating cerebrovascular history into perioperative risk assessment and optimizing multidisciplinary care strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circumferential parallel ligation for debulking of very large neurofibromas in patients with neurofibromatosis type 1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CPL is safe and effective for debulking large neurofibromas in patients with NF1, offering reliable hemostasis without requiring costly surgical devices.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current definition of remission in eosinophilic granulomatosis with polyangiitis (EGPA) and future perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eosinophilic granulomatosis with polyangiitis (EGPA) is a rare systemic vasculitis for which achieving remission is the primary therapeutic goal. Historically, remission in EGPA was defined by the absence of active vasculitis, typically a Birmingham Vasculitis Activity Score (BVAS) of 0. However, this definition is insufficient as it overlooks the significant morbidity associated with long-term glucocorticoid (GC) therapy. Recent evidence highlights that even low-dose GCs carry substantial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breeding bafilomycin A1-resistant sake yeast to improve fermentative capacity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sake yeast exhibits remarkable fermentative capacity in mash environments, even under various stress conditions. Although breeding techniques aimed at improving the flavor of sake by modifying aroma compounds and organic acid composition have been employed, these approaches often result in reduced fermentative capacity. Furthermore, existing breeding methods aimed at enhancing fermentative capacity often result in increased acidity in the final product. In this study, we aimed to improve sake...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practice test of the German S3 guideline "Thyroid Nodules in Adults in General Practice": Evaluating feasibility, comprehensibility, and acceptance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The practice test showed the level of guideline comprehensibility and acceptance in general practice, highlighting areas of improvement. These include clearer communication with patients, interprofessional alignment and modification of materials according to patient requirements.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value and Reproducibility of Simplified Noninvasive Pulmonary Artery Pressure-Flow Relationships in Exercise Echocardiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Simple, 1-point mPAP/CO ratios measured during exercise offer prognostic performance comparable with slope-based methods, with greater reproducibility. This finding supports its adoption as a practical and robust approach for evaluating exercise pulmonary hypertension.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41233027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refugee stigma and its toll on mental health: development and validation of the refugee stigma scale (RSS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides robust evidence for the RSS as a scale assessing different dimensions of stigma related to refugee status. The RSS can provide valuable insight into the complex web of refugee status stigma and mental and physical health difficulties.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41232947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251114023752&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>