<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:35:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De novo transcriptome assembly and gene expression analysis of Cnidium officinale under high-temperature conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that proper clustering of genes based on expression levels and fold changes in two different experimental conditions, along with pathway mapping, may provide a comprehensive understanding of CO's response to heat stress. These insights could contribute to future research on heat tolerance and crop improvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploration of the genetic diversity of Avena Fatua L. (wild oat) through genotyping-by-sequencing and SDS-PAGE]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides data on the genetic diversity of A. fatua, a wild relative of cultivated oats, aimed at expanding the genetic pool of oats for future breeding programs. These findings are expected to be a foundational resource for oat breeding and genetic improvement efforts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiple freezing-melting pathways of high-density ice through ice XXI phase at room temperature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Various metastable ice phases and their complicated transition pathways have been found by pressurization at low temperatures at which slow kinetics and high metastability are easily achieved. By contrast, such diversity is less expected at room or elevated temperatures. Here, using a combination of a dynamic diamond anvil cell and X-ray free electron laser techniques, we demonstrate that supercompressed water transforms into ice VI through multiple freezing-melting pathways at room temperature,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digitally fabricated 3D slippery architectures for multifunctional liquid manipulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The primary challenge in creating controllable liquid-based materials lies in managing the structural complexities and multiscale interfaces that govern solid, liquid, and gas phase interactions. Current fabrication methods for liquid-infused surfaces lack topological flexibility, limiting them to planar and simple-patterned structures. Conversely, digitally fabricating slippery architectural materials marks a significant shift towards scalable microprinting of complex, topologically slippery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Rosuvastatin/Amlodipine FDC in Patients With Hypertension and Dyslipidemia: A Multicenter, Prospective, Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this large real-world study, Ros/Aml demonstrated a favorable safety profile and was effective in reducing MACCE risk, blood pressure, and lipid levels over 12 months. These findings in patients with hypertension and dyslipidemia support its use as a viable strategy for integrated cardiovascular risk management in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community Health Perspectives on Middle-aged Adults Living Alone: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This scoping review synthesizes evidence on the physical health, mental well-being, health behaviors, and overall quality of life of middle-aged adults living alone, highlighting its significance from a community health perspective. Recognizing the rapid growth of this demographic, this review evaluates the current research landscape, identifies critical gaps, and explores opportunities for targeted interventions. Following the JBI Scoping Review Guidelines, comprehensive searches were conducted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cross-sectional study on national cancer screening participation among people with physical disabilities: focus on health screening experience and perceptions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: To increase cancer screening participation among individuals with physical disabilities, it is crucial to not only reduce barriers to cancer screening but also enhance perceptions of its importance and benefits.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of sugammadex on the incidence of postoperative nausea and vomiting in patients undergoing laparoscopic abdominal surgery: a randomized controlled study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sugammadex did not significantly reduce the overall incidence of PONV within 48 h after surgery. However, a significant reduction in PONV was observed on postoperative day 1, suggesting a potential benefit in early postoperative period. In clinical settings where multimodal prophylaxis is routinely applied, the additional antiemetic benefit of sugammadex may be limited. Further studies are warranted to identify patient subgroups that may derive greater benefit from sugammadex in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NiH-Catalyzed Homobenzylic Hydroalkylation of Aryl Alkenes Using Sulfoxonium Ylides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present here the first example of NiH-catalyzed homobenzylic hydroalkylation of aryl alkenes mediated by a nickel carbene radical, achieving the elusive β-selectivity with excellent regiocontrol. Mechanistic investigations suggest that this transformation is enabled by the preferential engagement of NiH with bench-stable sulfoxonium ylides, whose unique chelation properties promote carbene activation prior to alkene insertion. The resulting nickel carbene radical is proposed to undergo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pushbutton-activated microfluidic cell-free biosensor for multiplexed pathogen detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we have developed a novel cell-free biosensor based on a multiplexed pushbutton-activated microfluidic device (mPAMD) that enables simultaneous detection of multiple 16S rRNAs of pathogens in a single device. The multi-step target-responsive cell-free protein synthesis process was seamlessly integrated into a single microfluidic device with an intuitive finger-pumping mechanism, allowing simultaneous mixing, aliquoting, and detection of 16S rRNAs through the production of reporter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of 10 principles of radiation protection in oral and maxillofacial radiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The finalized principles constitute a structured, evidence-based guideline aligned with international standards while addressing specific challenges unique to oral and maxillofacial radiology. They offer practical strategies to enhance patient safety and standardize radiographic decision-making. Further research should investigate their clinical implementation and recommend periodic updates to reflect evolving technologies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of GPT-4 for planning acupuncture treatment: comparison with human clinician performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GPT-4 made reasonable acupoint suggestions, with notable overlap observed with the prescriptions of doctors. This shows its promise for supporting medical decisions, education, and personalized medicine for patients undergoing acupuncture treatment. Future studies and validation are necessary to ensure the reliability and efficacy of applying GPT-4 in real-world settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic evaluation of different graded Holstein Friesian × Local (HF × L) crossbred breeding bulls of Bangladesh]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides insightful information on the genetic evaluation of different graded bulls that could be the basis for the proven crossbred breeding bulls' selection process at CCBDF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A naturally occurring promoter variation of <em>BrGSL-OHa</em> contributes to the conversion of gluconapin to progoitrin in <em>Brassica rapa</em> L. leaves]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glucosinolates (GSLs) are sulfur-rich secondary metabolites that play important roles in human health, plant defenses against pathogens and insects, and flavor. The genetic architecture of GSL biosynthesis in Brassica rapa L. remains poorly understood despite several mapping and gene prediction studies. This study conducted a conventional quantitative trait locus (QTL) analysis to identify putative genes regulating GSL biosynthesis in B. rapa in two field trials. Four consensus QTL clusters were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoscale Dynamics of Buried Charge Trap in Oxide-Nitride-Oxide Stacks Investigated Using Kelvin Probe Force Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding charge trapping and diffusion behavior is crucial for optimizing nonvolatile memory (NVM) devices, which commercially involve a silicon oxide-silicon nitride-silicon oxide (ONO) stack structure. However, studies on charge traps in ONO stack structures using Kelvin probe force microscopy (KPFM) have been limited. Here, we examine trapped charge dynamics in ONO devices using KPFM, especially trapped electrons and holes in the buried silicon nitride layer and on the exposed silicon...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital PCR Methods for Discovering Molecular Markers for Hanwoo Cattle Breed Genotyping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital PCR (dPCR) is the third generation of PCR for the absolute quantification of nucleic acids in the reaction without a standard curve by partitioning reactions. In recent years, various dPCR platforms have been developed and used in a variety of research and diagnostic applications. dPCR technology has significant potential as a tool for detecting species identification markers in large samples through accurate quantification of absolute copy numbers. In this chapter, we describe the dPCR...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A web-based mouse-tracking task for early perceptual language processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The study of language processing requires data from a wide range of languages but also data that are free from demand characteristics and meta-linguistic strategies. While eye-tracking has been successfully used to address the later issue, pragmatically, eye-tracking is often difficult to achieve with less well-studied languages. Therefore, the current paper presents a web-based mouse-tracking task that generates data that seem to reflect early perceptual processes similar to eye-tracking but...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A high-power spatial, single-cell view of pericytes in esophageal cancer metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural phylogenetics unravels the evolutionary diversification of communication systems in gram-positive bacteria and their viruses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in artificial-intelligence-based protein structure modeling have yielded remarkable progress in predicting protein structures. Because structures are constrained by their biological function, their geometry tends to evolve more slowly than the underlying amino acids sequences. This feature of structures could in principle be used to reconstruct phylogenetic trees over longer evolutionary timescales than sequence-based approaches; however, until now, a reliable structure-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of the machine learning and deep learning models with SHAP strategy for predicting groundwater levels in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this research, the groundwater levels (GWLs) were predicted by employing machine learning (i.e., stochastic gradient boosting (SGB), random forest (RF), generalized regression neural networks (GRNN), and group of method data handling (GMDH)) and deep learning (i.e., deep echo state network (Deep ESN) and long short-term memory (LSTM)) based on three predictive scenarios, Jeju Island, South Korea. In scenario 01, GWLs in Bongseong well was calculated utilizing rainfall, air temperature,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The chloroplast-targeted long noncoding RNA CHLORELLA mediates chloroplast functional transition across leaf ageing via anterograde signalling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The transition from chloroplast biogenesis to degeneration during leaf senescence is critical for plants' fitness, as it facilitates the relocation of nutrients to reproductive organs^(1-3). However, it remains largely unknown how the timing of this transition is regulated by the coordination between chloroplasts and the nucleus^(4,5). Here we describe the regulatory mechanism underlying this transition in Arabidopsis thaliana. CHLOROPLAST-RELATED LONG NONCODING RNA (CHLORELLA) is highly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human gut bacteria produce structurally related monoglycolipids with contrasting immune functions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gut symbiont Bacteroides fragilis can produce α-galactosylceramides (BfaGCs), sphingolipids with immunomodulatory functions that regulate colonic natural killer T (NKT) cells. However, their synthesis pathway and whether other human gut bacteria can produce them are unclear. Here, using genetic and metabolomic approaches, we mapped the sphingolipid biosynthesis pathway of B. fragilis and determined that α-galactosyltransferase (agcT) is essential and sufficient for colonic NKT cell regulation in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Normal and nonnormal polynomial regression mixture modeling for differential congruence effects: A simulation and tutorial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polynomial regression with response surface analysis (PRRSA) has been widely adopted in congruence research when the relation of congruence to an outcome is examined. However, PRRSA assumes that the congruence effects are homogeneous across all individuals. Polynomial regression mixture analysis (PRMix) allows for heterogeneity in the effect of congruence on an outcome across individuals and identifies latent classes of differential congruence effects. In this study, through Monte Carlo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated AI based identification of autism spectrum disorder from home videos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autism spectrum disorder (ASD) is a prevalent childhood-onset neurodevelopmental condition. Early diagnosis remains challenging by the time, cost, and expertise required for traditional assessments, creating barriers to timely identification. We developed an AI-based screening system leveraging home-recorded videos to improve early ASD detection. Three task-based video protocols under 1 min each-name-response, imitation, and ball-playing-were developed, and home videos following these protocols...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laplacian filter attention with style transfer GAN for brain tumor MRI imputation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Training deep neural networks with multi-domain data generally gives more robustness and accuracy than training with single domain data, leading to the development of many deep learning-based algorithms using multi-domain data. However, if part of the input data is unavailable due to missing or corrupted data, a significant bias can occur, a problem that may be relatively more critical in medical applications where patients may be negatively affected. In this study, we propose the Laplacian...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A highly miniaturized circularly polarized self-duplexing implantable antenna with enhanced performance for wireless capsule endoscopy applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiband implantable antennas are crucial components of biomedical implantable devices (BIDs), enabling the establishment of wireless communication links with external base stations. These types of antennas perform various functions such as data transmission, wireless power transfer, and control signaling. However, this scenario requires an external multiplexer in the BIDs to separate various frequency bands, imposing size constraints on the BIDs. This work proposes a self-duplexing circularly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Whole genome sequencing in adolescent idiopathic scoliosis cohort implicates multiple biological pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adolescent idiopathic scoliosis (AIS) is a complex genetic disorder. This study used whole-genome sequencing (WGS) to investigate the genetic basis of AIS in 119 patients from 103 families. Our WGS analysis identified known pathogenic or protein-truncating variants in 15 probands, and other strong or moderate candidate variants in 69 additional patients. We found both coding and non-coding mutations, including structural variants. Candidate genes included known AIS genes (e.g., COL11A2, FBN1)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Twelve-year nationwide cohort study identifying risk factors for conversion from mild cognitive impairment to Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mild cognitive impairment (MCI) is a pre-dementia phase preceding dementia of the Alzheimer's type (DAT). Despite numerous studies exploring the risk factors for the conversion from MCI to DAT, the results have been heterogeneous. This study aimed to investigate the incidence of the conversion from MCI to DAT and the risk factors contributing to DAT conversion in Korean patients with MCI. A 12-year nationwide retrospective study was conducted. We enrolled patients with MCI aged ≥ 40 years...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of molecular signature of long-term psychiatric sequelae in COVID-19 through proteome profiling of dried blood spots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuropsychiatric sequelae represent a significant aspect of post-acute sequelae of SARS-CoV-2 (PASC, or long COVID), posing considerable public health challenges. This study identified molecular signatures associated with PASC in individuals with psychiatric morbidities via dried blood spot proteomic analysis. We evaluated 51 COVID-19 survivors ≥ 60 days post-infection, categorizing them into three groups: those with new-onset psychiatric disorders (n = 16, psychiatric PASC), those with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strain-associated nanoscale fluctuating lithium transport within single-crystalline LiNi<sub>1/3</sub>Mn<sub>1/3</sub>Co<sub>1/3</sub>O<sub>2</sub> cathode particles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solid-state lithium diffusion dynamics are critical for the rate capability and longevity of Li-ion batteries. Conventionally, nanoscale lithium diffusion within individual battery particles has been simplified as being primarily driven by concentration gradients, despite the associated processes inducing local lattice expansion, contraction, and strain fields. Using operando scanning transmission soft X-ray microscopy with high spatial resolution and chemical sensitivity to track nanoscale...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pre-lithiation empowers the future of lithium-ion batteries: strategies, applications, and outlook]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immediate versus delayed coronary angiography in patients with non-ST segment elevation acute coronary syndrome complicated with acute decompensated heart failure: The EARLY-HF randomized clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Immediate CAG within 2 h of randomization did not demonstrate a clinical benefit over delayed CAG in this trial. However, the premature termination limits the ability to draw definitive conclusions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between smartphone screen time and fast food intake among adolescents: a cross-sectional survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The association between prolonged smartphone screen time and frequent fast food intake in adolescents suggests the need for targeted interventions addressing digital media use to promote healthier eating behaviors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extending the Lens: Long-Term Impact of COVID-19 on COPD Management and Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lung Cancer Risk in Preserved Ratio Impaired Spirometry and Airway Obstruction: A UK Biobank Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Preserved ratio impaired spirometry (PRISm) has emerged as a distinct pulmonary pattern with potential clinical significance, but its association with lung cancer risk remains unclear.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and immunogenicity of a homologous booster dose of a SARS-CoV-2 recombinant protein nanoparticle vaccine (GBP510) adjuvanted with AS03: 12 months follow-up result of an open-label, non-randomised extension of a phase 1/2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A homologous GBP510/AS03 booster was well tolerated and induced robust, durable neutralising antibody responses against SARS-CoV-2, including Omicron variant.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus position statements for the standardized application of histological grading and staging systems in MASH clinical trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The IMPG statements provide for the first time guidelines to promote consensus among liver pathologists for the histopathological evaluation and scoring of liver biopsies for MASH clinical trials. Furthermore, they may be used to inform supervised machine learning algorithms for quantitative MASLD histology assessments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Approach to Optimized Ultrasound Stimulation for Enhanced Astaxanthin Synthesis in Haematococcus pluvialis: the Cultivation Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astaxanthin, a ketocarotenoid, is a potent antioxidant, and the microalga Haematococcus pluvialis is one of the major natural producers of astaxanthin. In this study, a strategy utilizing ultrasound throughout the cultivation process was introduced to induce astaxanthin biosynthesis in H. pluvialis. The effects of various ultrasound intensities, treatment durations, and frequencies on both cell viability and astaxanthin induction were characterized and optimized. The optimized approach was then...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[68GA-FAPI PET/CT IN DIAGNOSIS OF THE BREAST CANCER DEPENDING ON THE MOLECULAR SUBTYPES AND EXPRESSION STATUS OF HUMAN EPIDERMAL GROWTH FACTOR RECEPTOR 2 (HER2/NEU)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates the diagnostic potential of 68Ga-FAPI PET/CT in women with newly diagnosed breast cancer (BC), with an emphasis on molecular subtypes and HER2/neu expression status. A total of 34 patients (median age: 55.5 years; range: 26-80) with histologically confirmed invasive BC underwent 68Ga-FAPI PET/CT prior to initiating treatment. Tumors were classified according to immunohistochemical markers (ER, PR, HER2/neu, Ki-67) into Luminal A, Luminal B (HER2-negative and HER2-positive),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding fibrotic encapsulation in plastic surgery implants: From biological mechanisms to precision interventions frontiers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitigating fibrotic encapsulation around implants is critical to ensuring the long-term success of implant-based procedures in plastic surgery. Fibrous capsule formation is a pathological foreign body reaction (FBR) that not only causes capsular contracture and implant failure but also creates a permissive microenvironment for bacterial colonization, thereby increasing the risk of infection. These adverse outcomes may ultimately necessitate implant removal or replacement, significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of resected-to-original middle hepatic vein length proportion on posthepatectomy liver failure after right-sided hepatectomy for perihilar cholangiocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although not statistically conclusive, MHV resection may increase the risk of PHLF or 90-day mortality in right-sided hepatectomy for PHCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bimetallic CoFe Borides: A New Pathway for the Transformation of Amorphous Borates to Metallic Borides for the Determination of Paracetamol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of transition metals as electrode materials that can exhibit good conductivity and fast electron transfer ability through electroactive sites is highly desirable because high sensitivity and selectivity can be achieved. When compared to other nonmetals, boron (B) possesses a lower electronegativity (χB-2.04) than carbon (χC-2.55), nitrogen (χN-3.04), and oxygen (χO-3.44) and thus forms a covalent linkage with electron-rich transition metals (Co or Fe) to form monometallic or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Germinal center-mediated broadening of B cell responses to SARS-CoV-2 booster immunization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Germinal centers (GCs) are key sites for antibody diversification and affinity maturation. SARS-CoV-2 messenger RNA (mRNA) vaccines elicit robust GC B cell responses in humans, but how these responses influence the breadth of immunity against viral variants remains unclear. We analyzed GC B cell responses in nine healthy adults after mRNA booster immunization. We show that 77.8% of the B cell clones in the GC expressed representative monoclonal antibodies (mAbs) recognizing the spike protein,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Attention to quantum complexity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The imminent era of error-corrected quantum computing demands robust methods to characterize quantum state complexity from limited, noisy measurements. We introduce the Quantum Attention Network (QuAN), a classical artificial intelligence (AI) framework leveraging attention mechanisms tailored for learning quantum complexity. Inspired by large language models, QuAN treats measurement snapshots as tokens while respecting permutation invariance. Combined with our parameter-efficient miniset...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of bed height on laryngoscopy force and operator ergonomics during simulated endotracheal intubation: A randomized controlled study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Bed height at xyphoid level reduced laryngoscopy force while improving laryngeal view and ergonomic comfort compared to ASIS level. Adjusting the bed height before endotracheal intubation can improve the operating environment, which in turn may contribute to safety of both patient and operator.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of JUC Spray Dressing in the Treatment of Methicillin-Resistant Staphylococcus Aureus Infections: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of Facial Synkinesis Severity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in FDA Data Integrity Enforcement Before and After the COVID-19 Pandemic: An Analysis of 1766 Warning Letters (2016-2023)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The observed patterns are consistent with a regulatory emphasis on risk-based DI oversight, particularly under remote or hybrid inspection models. For manufacturers-especially in PIC/S member countries where hybrid documentation persists-these findings underscore the practical importance of strengthening electronic quality systems. By offering a standardized ALCOA/ALCOA + -based rubric aligned with international guidance, this study provides a replicable framework for future DI...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal Strategy for Thromboprophylaxis in Fontan Circulation: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis with a Focus on Ethnic Differences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fontan circulation alters cardiovascular hemodynamics to maintain circulation using a single ventricle, which may consequently increase the risk of thromboembolism. This highlights the need for effective thromboprophylaxis strategies. This study assessed optimal thromboprophylaxis regimens for patients with Fontan circulation through a comprehensive meta-analysis of literature focused on personalized, ethnicity-based approaches. PubMed, Embase, and Cochrane Library databases were searched to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regiodivergent Addition of Allylic Acetals in Ruthenium-Catalyzed C-H/N-H Annulation Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Distinct reaction modes of π-allylruthenium complexes, derived from allylic acetals, in the urazole-directed C-H/N-H annulation are described. By controlling the reaction conditions, electrophilic addition of π-allylruthenium complexes at the α- and γ-positions was selectively achieved, resulting in the formation of dihydrocinnolines and benzodiazepines, respectively. A series of control experiments for plausible reaction mechanism were performed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PRRSV GP2a blocks the RLR signaling pathway by targeting RIG-I]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The strategy of viruses targeting RIG-I to disrupt the interferon (IFN) system represents an effective mechanism for evading innate immune responses. In this study, we observed that porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome virus (PRRSV) GP2a inhibited IFN production by targeting RIG-I. Further studies revealed that GP2a blocks the RIG-I-like receptor signaling pathway through two mechanisms: (i) GP2a induces K48-linked ubiquitination of RIG-I by promoting the interaction between RIG-I and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Triple Antiplatelet (Aspirin, Clopidogrel, and Cilostazol) and Modified Dual Antiplatelet (Aspirin and Low-Dose Prasugrel) Therapy in Patients With High On-Treatment Platelet Reactivity Undergoing Stent-Assisted Coil Embolization for an Unruptured Intracranial Aneurysm: A Prospective Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among patients with HTPR who underwent stent-assisted coil embolization for an unruptured intracranial aneurysm, there was no significant difference between the TAT and MDAT groups regarding the risk of all bleeding events and thromboembolic events during the 90 days of follow-up.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lymphadenopathy is an independent prognostic factor for patients with Waldenström macroglobulinaemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of vitiligo in clinical practice: a cross-sectional survey among experts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study shows similarities but also remarkable differences in assessed outcomes compared to the CDS for clinical trials. These results serve as a preparatory step toward developing a COS for clinical practice with the involvement of expert and non-expert dermatologists and patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Quinoxaline Units in Random Terpolymers on Enhancing Indoor Organic Photovoltaics: Lowering HOMO Level and Improving Miscibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth in demand for the Internet of Things (IoT) has increased the need for power sources capable of harvesting energy from indoor light sources. Indoor organic photovoltaics (IOPVs) have emerged as promising candidates due to their ability to effectively harness indoor light. However, efficient polymer donors tailored for indoor conditions remain rare, as most high-performance photoactive materials have been developed primarily for outdoor environments. Here, a series of PM6-derived...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, POSTECH, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal conditioning intensity: favorable outcome of a 3-day busulfan based regimen in younger acute myeloid leukemia patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Myeloablative conditioning is standard for younger acute myeloid leukemia (AML) patients undergoing allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplantation (HCT), but optimal busulfan dosing remains unclear. We retrospectively analyzed 686 AML patients aged <55 years who received busulfan-based conditioning (2, 3, or 4 days) for first HCT at Asan Medical Center between 2000 and 2020. A 3-day course of busulfan (Bu3) showed significantly better overall survival (OS, p < 0.001) and lower non-relapse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anisotropic Au nanobypyramids with molybdenum disulfide for plasmon-enhanced electrocatalysis, biosensing and energy production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The strategic integration of anisotropic plasmonic nanostructures with two-dimensional (2D) semiconductors presents an emerging route for designing multifunctional hybrid systems with advanced photoelectrochemical (PEC) capabilities. In this work, we report the synthesis of a core-shell nanohybrid, Au nanobipyramid@MoS(2) (AuNBP@MoS(2)), wherein gold nanobipyramids are uniformly encapsulated by few-layer MoS(2) nanosheets. This architecture promotes direct plasmon-semiconductor coupling under...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Small area geographic variation in girl and boy child marriage in India: a district-level longitudinal analysis, 2016 and 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We provide new insight into recent progress and setbacks in eliminating child marriage across India. We found considerable district-level heterogeneity and clustering of poorly performing districts, coupled with increasing local inequality, especially within the worst-performing districts. Intervention and policy may be more effective if informed by local inequality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Localized histopathological effects of high-salt intake on the aorta and kidney in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings indicate that a high-salt diet induces localized histopathological changes in specific regions of the aorta and kidneys. This study provides foundational data for understanding the pathological mechanisms of high-salt intake and offers insight into potential prevention strategies for salt-induced aorta and renal injury.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of decomposition of biodegradable mulching films under variable soil microbial conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Biodegradable mulching films (BDMs) are sustainable alternatives to polyethylene, but their degradation efficiency is strongly influenced by soil microbial composition. This study investigated the effects of Bacillus subtilis and Clostridium perfringens, two soil bacteria with distinct metabolic traits, on the decomposition of BDMs with different structures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How social engagement shapes depressive symptoms in later life: uncovering gendered and asymmetric effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Social engagement is widely recognized as a protective factor for mental health in later life, yet most studies treat it as a static condition and overlook potential asymmetries in the effects of becoming socially engaged and disengaged. This study examines (1) whether the mental health effects of entering and exiting social engagement are asymmetric, (2) whether these effects differ by the type of engagement (informal vs formal), and (3) whether gender moderates these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endothelial Dysfunction in Atherosclerosis: Experimental Models and Therapeutics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atherosclerosis is a cardiovascular disease that involves complex and multifactorial processes that are instigated from endothelial dysfunctions. In this review, we address endothelial dysfunction in atherosclerosis and the mechanisms, where they are characterized by structural and functional alterations in endothelial cells (ECs), as caused by inflammation, oxidative stress, or disturbed shear stress. In particular interest, we provide a comprehensive overview of the experimental models (in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ApneaWhisper: Transformer-Based Audio Segmentation for Fine-Grained Non-Invasive Sleep Apnea Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The model's fine-grained temporal resolution enables precise apnea event localization, duration estimation, and subtype classification. While ApneaWhisper performs robustly for OSA, challenges remain in distinguishing central (CSA) and mixed (MSA) sleep apnea, due to subtle or ambiguous acoustic patterns. The frame-level segmentation also facilitates accurate apnea-hypopnea index (AHI) estimation, which could reduce dependence on full PSG studies in certain clinical and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Durvalumab With or Without Tremelimumab in Combination With Chemoradiotherapy in Patients With Limited-Stage SCLC: Results from the Phase 1 CLOVER Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Durvalumab in combination with cCRT, with or without tremelimumab, was tolerable and active in patients with LS-SCLC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fertility-sparing treatments for patients with endometrial cancer: A comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endometrial cancer (EC) in young women is relatively likely to be early-stage, low-grade, and without risk factors. Fertility-sparing treatment with progestin is a potential primary approach for certain patients. However, several factors should be considered according to available guidelines. The potential indication for fertility-sparing treatment in patients with EC, as recommended by various societies of gynecologic oncology, includes young women with grade 1 endometrioid adenocarcinoma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spiral enteroscopy versus single-balloon enteroscopy for the evaluation and treatment of small bowel disorders: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Spiral and single-balloon enteroscopies demonstrated similar diagnostic and therapeutic yields and safety. Spiral enteroscopy achieved a greater insertion depth, and motorized systems improved the efficiency in terms of procedure times.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wavelength-Orthogonal Photoinitiated Polymerization-Induced Microphase Separation for Stepwise Ionogel Curing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionogels typically face a trade-off between stiffness and ionic conductivity, with phase separation being a potential solution. However, postmodification techniques to enhance stiffness after phase separation remain underexplored. To address this, we developed a stepwise ionogel curing strategy using wavelength-orthogonal photoinitiated polymerization-induced microphase separation (PIMS) to improve stiffness while preserving ionic conductivity. In the first curing step, blue light-initiated PIMS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative Pharmacoinformatic and Experimental Validation of Indonesian Red Algae as Novel Functional Food for Anti-Gastric Cancer Agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric cancer remains a major global health burden with limited therapeutic options due to resistance and toxicity of current treatments. Marine red algae-Gracilaria edulis, Eucheuma denticulatum, and Kappaphycus striatus-are underexplored sources of bioactive compounds that may offer multi-targeted, low-toxicity agents for gastric cancer therapy. This study integrated phytochemical profiling, structure-activity relationship (SAR) analysis, network pharmacology, molecular docking, molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cationic Point Defect Fluoride to Improve Reaction Kinetics in (All) Solid-State Li Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nickel-rich cathode materials (NCM) have emerged as promising candidates for lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) and all-solid-state batteries (ASSBs) due to their high reversible capacity (>200 mAh g^(-1)). However, surface side reactions with liquid and solid electrolytes during cycling increase interfacial resistance and accelerate capacity fading, thereby hindering the practical implementation of NCM cathodes. To achieve high-energy LIBs and ASSBs, it is essential to control the interfacial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Nationwide Survey by the Korean Society of Ophthalmic Plastic and Reconstructive Surgery (KSOPRS) on the Management of Thyroid Eye Disease in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Korean oculoplastic surgeons generally follow international TED guidelines, favoring IV GC and conventional therapies over biologics due to access and cost barriers. As biologics like teprotumumab become more accessible, region-specific guidelines integrating global evidence and local healthcare constraints will be critical for optimized patient care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ten-Year Trends of Intravitreal injection in Korea Using the Health Insurance Review and Assessment Service Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The patients receiving IVI and the total number of IVI have been steadily increasing, particularly in primary healthcare settings. Overall, medical expenses continue to rise. The findings of this study provide valuable evidence for the efficient allocation of medical resources in the future.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized Anesthesia Strategies for Cochlear Implantation: Insights on Local Anesthesia From a Single-institution Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CI under LA is a viable and safe alternative for selected high-risk patients. Implementation of tailored anesthesia protocols, particularly for individuals with mitochondrial disorders or cognitive vulnerability, facilitates optimized patient outcomes. These findings support a personalized approach to anesthesia selection in auditory rehabilitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered virus-like particle-assembled Vegfa-targeting Cas9 ribonucleoprotein treatment alleviates neovascularization in wet age-related macular degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: eVLPs exhibit the potential as a safe and efficient delivery platform for Cas9 ribonucleoproteins, achieving precise Vegfa downregulation and significant reduction in choroidal neovascularization in a mouse model of wet age-related macular degeneration. With transient delivery of gene editing enzymes, high editing efficiency, and minimal risk of genomic integration, eVLPs present a promising alternative to conventional delivery systems for advancing genome editing therapies in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of cellular and mitochondrial dysfunction by TRPV4 during early stages of Vincristine-induced neurotoxicity in cultured neuronal model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251011033455&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intracellular and mitochondrial Ca^(2+) play pivotal role in chemotherapeutics-induced toxicity. Here, we show that TRPV4, a thermosensitive ion channel implicated in pain, modulates mitochondrial Ca^(2+), ROS and temperature during chemotherapeutic stress. TRPV4 is present in the mitochondria and it regulates mitochondrial Ca^(2+), ATP, ROS and temperature. In this work, using specific probes and F11 cell (DRG-neuron-derived line) stably-expressing TRPV4 as a model system, we measured live cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251011033455&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Probing buccal-customized epigenetic clocks to investigate socioeconomic and health disparities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epigenetic clocks are emerging as promising tools for examining social and health disparities. These measures are typically developed using blood DNA methylation (DNAm) data. Cheek swabs, being less invasive than blood collection, can be used to assay buccal DNAm. This study examines how buccal-originated epigenetic clocks relate to socioeconomic status (SES) and health, and compares these associations to those of blood-originated clocks applied to buccal DNAm in the German SOEP cohort (N =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: A systematic algorithm using 16S ribosomal RNA for accurate diagnosis of pneumonia pathogens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNF213 c.14429G &gt; A (p.Arg4810Lys) is associated with non-arteritic retinal artery occlusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retinal artery occlusion (RAO) results in severe visual impairment and may indicate cerebral infarction and extracranial carotid artery stenosis at onset. RAO-related genetic factors remain understudied. We investigated the association between RAO and RNF213 p.Arg4810Lys (c.14429G > A), a genetic variant recently identified as a susceptibility factor for moyamoya disease, a risk factor for stroke. Patients diagnosed with non-arteritic (NA)-RAO at our department between May 2020 and April 2021...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase-specific learning curves in robot-assisted rectal surgery: implications for surgical training]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The learning period during RRS was shorter for the abdominal manipulation than for the pelvic manipulation, considering the absence of the consolidation phase. Education and training that consider these points may be useful for the more efficient learning of RRS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Normality of sagittal spinal alignment parameters reveals evolutionary signals in healthy adults across five countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The evolution of upright bipedalism required coordinated modifications in spinal curvature, pelvic orientation, and lower limb structure. However, it remains unclear whether sagittal alignment traits in modern humans have reached evolutionary stabilization or continue to exhibit developmental variability across populations. We hypothesize that certain sagittal alignment traits have undergone canalization-an evolutionary process that buffers against phenotypic variation-resulting in normal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of ultrasound-guided versus fluoroscopy-guided venous puncture techniques for pacemaker implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound-guided pacemaker puncture allows for visualization of vascular anatomy in real time, potentially reducing complications; however, detailed comparative studies with the traditional fluoroscopy-guided technique are lacking, particularly those incorporating objective imaging endpoints such as postoperative computed tomography (CT). In this study, we aimed to compare the procedural time and complications associated with fluoroscopy- and ultrasound-guided axillary and subclavian vein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rituximab-induced long-term remission in childhood-onset, uncomplicated, frequently relapsing or steroid-dependent nephrotic syndrome: a randomized, placebo-controlled trial and a follow-up study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rituximab maintains remission of complicated frequently relapsing or steroid-dependent nephrotic syndrome (FRNS/SDNS) by depleting peripheral B cells, but most patients eventually experience relapses after B cell recovery. We performed a multicenter, double-blind, randomized, placebo-controlled trial to assess rituximab's efficacy and safety for childhood-onset uncomplicated FRNS/SDNS (without prior treatment with glucocorticoid-sparing immunosuppressive agents) with a follow-up study to assess...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bilateral ocular motility impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing pharmacists' knowledge and practices involving dietary supplement omega-3 fatty acids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our survey demonstrated a substantial variability among pharmacists in their recommendations and counseling practices regarding OM3FA-DS. Despite concerns about the quality of DS products and a lack of guideline support for their use, 60% of pharmacists recommend OM3FA-DS. Respondents overwhelmingly expressed a need for improved information and education about DS in general, and OM3FA-DS in particular.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic accuracy of preoperative magnetic resonance arthrography for detecting midsubstance capsular tears: Irregular outline sign]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The IO sign on magnetic resonance arthrography is a reliable indicator with high sensitivity and specificity for diagnosing midsubstance capsular tear. The accurate preoperative diagnosis of a midsubstance capsular tear can assist in planning appropriate surgical interventions, especially for shoulder surgeons with less experience. Further studies are needed to confirm these findings in larger populations and with standardized imaging equipment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiology and prognosis of malignant peripheral nerve sheath tumor (MPNST) in Japan: A population-based analysis using the national cancer registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first study to analyze the national epidemiology and prognosis of MPNST in a socio-economically homogeneous, single ethnic group. MPNST primarily affected the skin and soft tissues, with a higher incidence in the AYA group. Surgery was associated with better outcomes, whereas chemotherapy and radiotherapy implied poorer prognosis owing to selection bias for unresectable cases. The NCR provides a valuable model for research on rare diseases in homogeneous populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Image Quality Variation with Gantry Rotation Time and Reconstruction Algorithm in Ultra-high-resolution CT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While DLR delivers superior image quality at gantry rotation times of 0.5-0.75s, it exhibits a loss of resolution and altered noise texture at 1.0 s. This degradation is likely attributable to the algorithm's limitations when processing data distributions that were underrepresented in its training set. Therefore, to optimize diagnostic performance, scan parameters must be carefully tailored to the specific reconstruction algorithm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of [<sup>177</sup>Lu]Lu-PSMA-617 in Patients with Metastatic Clear-cell Renal Cell Carcinoma: The Multicentre, Single-arm, Phase 2 RENALUT Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVE: Angiogenesis-targeting tyrosine kinase inhibitors (TKIs) and immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) are standard treatments for metastatic clear-cell renal cell carcinoma (ccRCC). However, therapeutic options remain limited after progression on these agents. Prostate-specific membrane antigen (PSMA) is highly expressed on the surface of endothelial cells in ccRCC, making radioligand therapy with [^(177)Lu]Lu-PSMA-617 a promising approach.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Additional arm-hand boost therapy (AHA-BOOST) in an inpatient rehabilitation setting during the subacute phase after stroke: protocol for a randomised controlled trial including a clinical, process and health economic evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: A considerable number of patients present with an upper limb impairment after stroke, which has a significant impact on daily life activities and quality of life. Currently, based on a Cochrane review, there is no high-quality evidence for any of the upper limb interventions used in routine practice. Therefore, the Jessa Hospital developed an additional arm-hand boost programme (AHA-BOOST), a novel, stratified intervention that integrates neurophysiological knowledge with an early...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Newly Onset Dyspnea During Pregnancy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of selective decontamination of the digestive tract in esophageal surgery: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Esophagectomy is a complex surgery with high mortality and morbidity caused by postoperative infectious complications such as pneumonia and anastomotic leakage. Selective decontamination of the digestive tract (SDD) with non-absorbable antimicrobial agents may lower the density of pathogenic organisms in the oropharynx and esophagus, thereby providing a perioperative prophylactic strategy. While SDD has shown benefits in intensive care units and lower gastrointestinal surgery, its efficacy and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IL-11 acts as a vaccine adjuvant in Nile tilapia (Oreochromis niloticus) against Streptococcus agalactiae, enhancing both cellular and humoral immune responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nile tilapia (Oreochromis niloticus) has become one of the most economically valuable fish species in global aquaculture. Recently, the industry has been increasingly affected by bacterial infections, particularly Streptococcus agalactiae, which has become a dominant pathogen causing severe disease outbreaks and economic losses. Interleukin (IL)-11 is a versatile cytokine involved in immune modulation, but its adjuvant potential has been rarely studied in fish. In this study, recombinant Nile...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enthesis-related progenitors recruited from the subacromial bursa contribute to rotator cuff healing in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: During the RC repair process, Scx^(+) and Scx^(+)/Sox9^(+) enthesis-related progenitors may be associated with endogenous PDGFRα^(+) and CD34^(+) mesenchymal stem/progenitors in the SAB near the tendon-bone repair site. SAB preservation positively impacts early histological and mechanical maturation after RC tendon-bone repair.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic response of partial nitritation-anammox systems to salinity stress with additional carbon input for stable nitrogen removal performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the response and adaptation mechanisms of the partial nitritation-anammox (PNA) process under salinity stress, with additional carbon input introduced to evaluate its influence on nitrogen removal pathways and microbial community dynamics. Building on a baseline experiment with an influent salinity of 8 g/L, different levels of carbon were added to examine effects on community structure, extracellular polymeric substance (EPS) composition, and overall nitrogen conversion....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptions of care providers on the implementation of an antenatal psychosocial clinical decision support system: the Born in Belgium Professionals platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Implementation strategies that emphasise training, interoperability, and alignment with existing workflows are essential to optimise adoption of antenatal psychosocial decision-support systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developmental relationships between visual cognitive skills and hiragana reading in Japanese children aged 4-8 years: insights from mirror letter reading task]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the development of visual cognitive abilities related to hiragana reading, focusing on how spatial relational processing influences letter, word, and pseudo-word recognition. Children aged 4-8 years participated in visual cognitive tasks, including figure-ground separation, left-right recognition, and spatial relationship processing. Their reading performance was also assessed for normal and mirrored hiragana letters, words, and pseudo-words. The experiment was conducted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing isoprimeverose-producing enzyme in genetically engineered Aspergillus oryzae through impeller shape and pH control for the large-scale fermentation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aspergillus oryzae is a filamentous fungus that serves as a source of polysaccharide-degrading enzymes. We constructed two self-cloning forms of A. oryzae that specifically express isoprimeverose oligoxyloglucanase (IpeA) and endoglucanase. These enzymes are essential for the enzymatic release of the rare sugar isoprimeverose (α-D-xylopyranosyl-(1→6)-D-glucopyranose) from tamarind xyloglucan. Of the two, IpeA is a key enzyme that is currently unavailable commercially. The primary objective of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Communication difficulties and strategies in migrant mental healthcare: A European survey of health and social care professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings highlight the urgent need for better communication strategies and awareness of the benefits and drawbacks of different strategies to enhance mental health service accessibility for migrants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Geriatric assessment in daily oncology practice for nurses and allied health professionals: An updated overview from SIOG Nursing, Allied Health and Scientists Interest Group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Professional societies such as the International Society of Geriatric Oncology (SIOG) and the American Society of Clinical Oncology (ASCO) recommend geriatric screening and assessment for all older adults being considered for cancer treatment, to optimize cancer treatment selection and develop a supportive care plan to optimize outcomes such as reducing their risk of treatment toxicity, hospitalisations, and improvements in function and quality of life. In many centres, nurses and allied health...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social-spatial residence patterns and adolescent mental health: Investigating the influences of residential segregation, neighborhood social cohesion, and race on persistent, distressing psychotic-like experiences in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prior work suggests that living among people who share similar identities may be protective against psychosis, but the meaning of this association in the context of racialized residential segregation is not well understood. We investigated the effects of evenness and exposure residential segregation on persistent, distressing psychotic-like experiences (PLEs) in Black and White adolescents living in urban neighborhoods with high and low social cohesion in the United States. Data from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of novel gene fusions in high-grade serous ovarian carcinoma: implications for tumorigenesis and targeted therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identified candidate driver fusion genes and suggested new therapeutic targets for HGSOCs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Macrophage CCL18 Promotes Lung Inflammation in Checkpoint Inhibitor Pneumonitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Checkpoint inhibitor pneumonitis (CIP) is a highly morbid complication of immune checkpoint immunotherapy, characterized by acute lung injury leading, in severe cases, to hypoxic respiratory failure and death. CIP incidence in lung cancer is high (10-15%). Yet, the pathophysiology of CIP is poorly understood. To investigate the mechanisms underlying alveolar inflammation in patients with CIP, human bronchoalveolar fluid (BALF) samples from control and CIP patients were analyzed using flow...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perspectives of nursing doctoral students on the impact of doctoral education on their professional and career development: A qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Doctoral education fosters growth and leadership among nurses, but structural and organizational barriers reduce its impact. It is imperative to enhance academic-practice integration, strengthen mentorship, and develop clinically focused doctoral pathways to optimize the benefits for nurses' professional development, patient care quality, and the healthcare system.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sensitivity analysis of dose-response model parameters for the bladder in prostate cancer radiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Parameter selection significantly influences high-risk subregion identification in DRMs, emphasizing the need for standardized parameter reporting for meaningful external comparisons.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Positive correlation between cognition and inflammation in the cerebral cortex of patients with mesial temporal lobe epilepsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cognitive impairments are commonly observed in individuals with mesial temporal lobe epilepsy (mTLE), yet the underlying mechanisms remain poorly elucidated. This study investigates the potential relationship between neuroinflammation as determined using radioligand binding to markers of neuroinflammation and cognitive dysfunction in this patient population. Quantitative autoradiography was performed using the radioligands [^(123)I]CLINDE (for 18 kDa translocator protein (TSPO)) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Parental Intentions to Use Digital Tools to Enhance Parent-Child Sexual Communication in Europe: Cross-Sectional Questionnaire Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the critical role of perceived usefulness, specifically relevance to parenting needs and the perceived quality of technology, in shaping parental intentions to use digital parent-child sexual communication tools. Developers of educational digital technologies should therefore prioritize high-quality design features to inspire usage. Future research should evaluate real-world digital tools to assess actual usage, long-term engagement, and their effectiveness...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cu-Catalyzed SF<sub>4</sub>-Alkynylation of Quinolones, Chromones and Cyclohexenones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the Cu-catalyzed SF(4)-alkynylation of quinolones, chromones, and cyclohexenones using pyridyl SF(4)-alkynes under Lewis acid assisted conditions, affording diverse SF(4)-linked heterocycles in good to high yields. The method leverages the electron-deficient, enone-like character of SF(4)-alkynes while maintaining broad functional group tolerance. Notably, the SF(4) unit remains stable under oxidative and acidic conditions, enabling efficient ring-reconstruction from six- to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ambident Reactivity of (Selenocarbamoyl)Phosphines: Transformation into a Crystalline (Phosphino)(Seleno)Iminium Salt and Transition-Metal Complexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although various types of selenoamides have already been developed, examples of derivatives bearing a third heteroatom that acts as a second reactive center have remained limited so far. Recently, we reported the synthesis, structure, and fundamental reactivity of (selenocarbamoyl)phosphines, which exhibit ambident reactivity at two principal sites, i.e., the phosphorus and selenium atoms, in reactions with electrophiles. Herein, we report the synthesis of the first crystalline...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Focused thermal energy at atomic microwave antenna sites for ecocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Green transformation demands efficient protocols to convert renewable energy into usable forms. Microwave (MW)-driven catalytic systems offer a promising electrification strategy for chemical processes by enabling targeted, energy-efficient reactions. Unlike conventional heating, MW irradiation can localize energy at catalytic active sites. A major breakthrough is the selective MW heating of isolated metal ions or nanoparticles. This study presents a general catalyst design strategy to control...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VAB-8/KIF26, LIN-17/Frizzled, and EFN-4/Ephrin, control distinct stages of posterior neuroblast migration downstream of the MAB-5/Hox transcription factor in Caenorhabditis elegans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hox transcription factors are involved in neuronal and neural crest development and differentiation, including migration, but the genetic programs employed by Hox genes to regulate terminal differentiation remain to be defined. In C. elegans, the Antennapedia-like Hox factor MAB-5 is both necessary and sufficient to induce posterior migration of the Q lineage neuroblasts and neurons downstream of canonical Wnt signaling. Q lineage fluorescence-activated cell sorting and RNA seq in mab-5...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Updates on the Endothelial Glycocalyx in Heart Failure with Preserved Ejection Fraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The endothelial glycocalyx (GCX) is a specialized form of extracellular matrix with a dynamic synthesis and degradation balance. It plays a pivotal role in regulating cell signaling, sensing the extracellular environment, and maintaining vascular permeability. In the setting of heart failure (HF), particularly in HF with preserved ejection fraction (HFpEF), systemic endothelial GCX degradation may represent an early pathophysiological mechanism. Indeed, HFpEF results from comorbidities-related...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data-efficient protein mutational effect prediction with weak supervision by molecular simulation and protein language models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning-based protein mutational effect prediction is widely used in protein engineering and pathogenicity prediction, but training data scarcity remains a major challenge due to high costs of experimental measurements. A previous study proposed data augmentation using computational estimates by molecular simulation. However, this approach has been limited to predicting mutational effects on thermostability. Here, we present a new data augmentation method that combines molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bottlenecks in advancing and applying multiomic data integration-common data resources as rate-limiting drivers-the high-impact use case of atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite striking successes in identifying novel biomarkers for improved patient stratification and predicting disease progression, numerous challenges remain in the effective integration and exploitation of multiomic data in biomedical applications beyond cancer, for which most bioinformatics strategies are developed and validated. That focus on cancer severely limits the effective development and advancement of algorithms in machine learning and artificial intelligence that do not suffer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioassay-guided isolation of antibacterial compounds from the leaf extract of Terminalia Arjuna against the Vibrio species in shrimp]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071530/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present research was intended to identify the bioactive molecules from the ethanolic extract of T. arjuna leaf against a diverse array of Vibrio species by means of a bioassay-guided fractionation. The antibacterial efficacy of compounds was assessed by the microdilution technique, while the brine shrimp mortality assay was employed to determine their toxicity. Following an initial screening, the ethanol extract underwent silica gel chromatography, succeeded by reversed phase HPLC, to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071530/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linking Order of RAX and OTX2 Following CRX in Polycistronic Vectors Can Partially Determine Efficacy of Direct Conversion to Photoreceptor-like Cells In Vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of image quality in pediatric portable chest radiographs using AI-based noise reduction and edge enhancement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI-based noise reduction significantly improves image quality by reducing noise. Although edge enhancement does not further suppress noise, it improves the visibility of delicate anatomical structures. This combined approach may enhance diagnostic confidence in neonatal chest radiography, particularly under low-dose conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MRI findings of granulomatous prostatitis induced by intravesical Bacillus Calmette-Guérin treatment for bladder cancer: a comparison with prostate cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Some PCa exhibit similar imaging findings to GP, but T1 hyperintensity and a diffuse morphology are characteristic features of GP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Online adaptive radiation therapy for muscle-invasive bladder cancer: short-course and high-precision definitive treatment for elderly or medically fragile patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CBCT-based online ART was considered a feasible therapeutic option for elderly or medically fragile patients with MIBC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The trajectory of cancer-related fatigue throughout lung cancer treatment and its association with physical activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with lung cancer experience significant increases in CRF throughout treatment, particularly those receiving (neo-)adjuvant treatment and surgery. PA levels during treatment were very low and tended to be related to lower fatigue increases. These findings highlight the importance of measuring CRF and the potential for exploring PA interventions to manage CRF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of the gut microbiota in the pharmacological effects of traditional Kampo medicine and natural products]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The human gastrointestinal tract harbors over a thousand coexisting bacterial species that together constitute a highly complex intestinal microbiome. Dysbiosis of this microbial ecosystem has been implicated in the pathogenesis of disorders such as ulcerative colitis and obesity and has driven the development of microbiota-targeted prevention and treatment strategies. Traditional Kampo medicines are used with the aim of restoring the balance of the whole body, having been developed and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic factors in aneurysmal subarachnoid hemorrhage during the clazosentan era: a multicenter study using multivariate analyses and machine learning model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Clinical status at aSAH onset and age are uncontrollable factors; therefore, improving prognosis requires targeted prevention of DCI and effective management of brain edema. The administration of therapies such as clazosentan, cilostazol, and statins may contribute to favorable outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and efficacy of a 12-mm trocar with integrated fascial closure for preventing port-site hernia in minimally invasive abdominal surgery: a multicenter prospective observational study among over weight patients with thick abdominal walls]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The VersaOne™ Fascial Closure System appears to be a safe and efficient method for fascial closure in minimally invasive surgery. Its use was particularly beneficial in patients with thick abdominal walls. Further randomized controlled studies are warranted to comprehensively validate these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PEX14 acts as a molecular link between optineurin and the autophagic machinery to induce pexophagy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pexophagy, the selective degradation of peroxisomes, is essential for removing excess or dysfunctional peroxisomes, and its dysregulation has been linked to various diseases. Although optineurin (OPTN), an autophagy receptor involved in mitophagy, aggrephagy, and xenophagy, has also been implicated in pexophagy in HEK-293 cells, the underlying mechanisms remain unclear. Using proximity labeling, we identified PEX14, a peroxisomal membrane protein, as a neighboring partner of OPTN. Microscopy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On time delay interpolation for improved acoustic reflector localization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The localization of acoustic reflectors is a fundamental component in various applications, including room acoustics analysis, sound source localization, and acoustic scene analysis. Time delay estimation (TDE) is essential for determining the position of reflectors relative to a sensor array. Traditional TDE algorithms generally yield time delays that are integer multiples of the operating sampling period, potentially lacking sufficient time resolution. To achieve subsample TDE accuracy,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyoxometalate-Directed Assembly of Robust Coordination Cages: Overcoming Kinetic Inertness and Conformational Mismatch]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The selective construction of kinetically robust coordination cages by self-assembly remains a significant challenge in supramolecular chemistry. Herein, we report an efficient polyoxometalate (POM)-directed self-assembly strategy enabling the selective assembly of robust Pt(6)L(4) cages under thermodynamic or kinetic control, which is inaccessible via untemplated methods. For a planar ligand (L1) with a dihedral angle (θ = 0°), the POM template promotes the formation of a thermodynamically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UV-A Radiation Impairs Sebaceous-Gland-Related Skin Barrier Function by Inducing Inflammation and Altering Intracellular Sebum-Like Lipid Composition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrated that UV-A radiation stimulated sebocytes to release inflammatory cytokines and altered gene expression. Additionally, UV-A irradiation modified the intracellular sebum-like lipid composition in a sex-dependent manner, contributing to skin barrier damage.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maximizing the Quality and Reporting Standards of Autism Intervention Science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although there are clear international standards for intervention science and reporting in healthcare, implementation and uptake have been limited within autism intervention research. To address this concern, a Special Interest Group (SIG) was convened at the International Society for Autism Research (INSAR) Annual Meetings in May 2023 and May 2024. This SIG comprised members of the autistic community, senior clinical scientists, clinicians, advanced researchers, and early career researchers,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simulation of Alzheimer's diagnostic flows with blood biomarker test options in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This study projected the diagnostic testing landscape for lecanemab treatment in Japan under different workflows.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intra-arterial fasudil infusion for symptomatic cerebral vasospasm following clipping of an unruptured middle cerebral artery aneurysm: A case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the first known case of symptomatic unruptured intracranial aneurysm-associated cerebral vasospasm (UIA-CVS) following surgical clipping that was successfully treated with intra-arterial fasudil infusion. UIA-CVS is a rare postoperative complication for which no standardized treatment has been established. A 67-year-old woman with a 5-mm saccular aneurysm at the bifurcation of the left middle cerebral artery (MCA) underwent microsurgical clipping via a distal transsylvian approach. On...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The inbred newt genome unveils molecular mechanisms of behavior, development, and regeneration in urodele amphibians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salamanders provide excellent models for studying vertebrate evolution, development, and regeneration. To further advance the newt as a model organism in biology, we conducted draft genome sequencing of 20 Gb of an inbred newt (Pleurodeles waltl). As part of this study, the Hoxd11-d13 intergenic region is expanded by over 1 Mb owing to the massive insertion of repetitive sequences including newt-specific satellite DNA. Interestingly, Myod and Bmp4, genes that are typically involved in vertebrate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of Enzymatic Extraction and Vacuum-Assisted Evaporation Parameters for Banana Syrup Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bananas are a widely cultivated fruit with significant nutritional and economic value; however, postharvest losses remain a major concern. This study is aimed at developing an optimized process for enzymatic extraction to produce banana syrup. This requires an assessment of the influence exerted by different concentrations of pectinase and cellulase, as well as the effects of incubation time and temperature. To optimize the conditions, a Box-Behnken design (BBD) was used, while juice yield and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors associated with treatment failure after discharge in inpatients with schizophrenia spectrum disorders: A retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Antipsychotic polypharmacy at discharge was associated with treatment failure in patients with schizophrenia spectrum disorders. Additionally, trial overnight stays at home during hospitalization potentially contributed to preventing treatment failure. Therefore, preventing treatment failure in patients with schizophrenia spectrum disorder requires optimizing pharmacotherapy and implementing social and environmental adjustments, focusing on the post-discharge period.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sol-gel synthesis and characterization of ZnO-SiO<sub>2</sub> nanocomposites: a comparative study with pure ZnO and SiO<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this investigation, pure SiO(2), ZnO, and ZnO-SiO(2) (10 : 90) nanocomposites were synthesized via the sol-gel method and systematically characterized in a comparative framework. Upon increasing the annealing temperature, the ZnO-SiO(2) composite predominantly retained its amorphous character, with the emergence of distinct ZnO diffraction peaks. Structural analysis using X-ray diffraction (XRD) confirmed the presence of the wurtzite phase in ZnO, alongside the intrinsically amorphous nature...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Small-molecule engineering of a PbS QD/ZnO nanowire interface and its impact on infrared PbS QD solar cell performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lead sulfide (PbS) quantum dots (QDs) are promising photovoltaic absorbers owing to their tunable absorption range from the visible to infrared regions. Realizing high efficiency in PbS QD/zinc oxide (ZnO) heterojunction solar cells requires precise energy-level alignment between the PbS QDs and ZnO, which significantly affects carrier transport and recombination processes, particularly when employing infrared-absorbing PbS QDs. In this study, we conducted systematic interfacial engineering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proton Conductivities of Stepwise Protonated Imidazole-Fused Tetraphenylene Derivatives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The control of crystal structure and proton conductivity was evaluated by stepwise protonation of tetraphenylene molecules (ImTP) containing a imidazole group. By controlling the degree of protonation from neutral ImTP to H(1)ImTP⁺, H(2)ImTP²⁺, and H(4)ImTP⁴⁺, we demonstrated that the balance between intermolecular hydrogen bonding and electrostatic interactions affects structural stability and proton conductivity. X-ray diffraction analysis revealed that neutral ImTP forms a 2D hydrogen bond...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The discovery of twilight length sensing in plants and its implications for models of plant photoperiodism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For centuries, we have known that plants exhibit different phenologies and growth patterns under differing photoperiods, accounting for both seasonality and traditional latitudinal limits in their cultivation. Decades of research in plant circadian biology have deciphered the role of the clock in controlling photoperiodic flowering through what is known as the 'external coincidence model'. However, past work has largely neglected to include another aspect of natural photoperiod change in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STREAM-PRS: a multi-tool pipeline for streamlining polygenic risk score computation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overall, STREAM-PRS provides an efficient framework for selecting the best PRS calculation strategy and helps bridge the portability gap within the PRS field. STREAM-PRS is available at https://github.com/SaraBecelaere/STREAM-PRS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrathoracic rupture of amebic liver abscess: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We reported the case of a patient with a rapidly progressive ALA with intrathoracic rupture. In cases of ALA with thoracic rupture, performing drainage is important, considering that pleural effusion may progress rapidly. This case highlights the need for comprehensive management involving timely antimicrobial and anticoagulation therapy in cases of vascular thrombosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Septins in the nervous system: from cytoskeletal dynamics to neurological disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adopting tailored interprofessional protocols in general practice: barriers, strategies, and lessons learned from a CFIR-guided qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The transition towards protocol-based interprofessional care is a complex but mandatory evolution in primary care. While practice-tailored protocols can enhance efficiency and collaboration, their success depends on a structured implementation strategy, effective practice management, and team alignment. Addressing challenges such as gaining trust and provider resistance are critical. Future research should explore scalable support mechanisms and policy adaptations to facilitate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ADSC-enriched adipose extract alleviates cartilage fibrosis in temporomandibular joint osteoarthritis by inhibiting chondrocyte senescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ARDE effectively alleviates cartilage fibrosis by suppressing chondrocyte senescence, significantly restoring cartilage structure and alleviating disease symptoms. The preparation process meets clinical requirements, and its demonstrated safety and efficacy indicate promising clinical translation prospects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What drives patient cost variability in psoriasis care: a single centre study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlighted substantial variability in consultation and yearly treatment costs for psoriasis patients. These findings emphasized the critical need for detailed cost data to optimise departmental workflows, support efficient resource allocation, and inform the design of equitable bundled payment models. Improving cost transparency was shown to strengthen clinical and financial decision-making. Future research was recommended to explore the cost implications of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of cholinergic white matter hyperintensity volume with cognitive decline and incident dementia in older adults: a cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cholinergic WMHV is associated with longitudinal cognitive decline and incident dementia in older adults, which might result from disruption of corpus callosum and corona radiata. These findings highlight the value of cholinergic WMHV as a potential indicator of cognitive deterioration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of regional medical network systems on emergency transport time for older patients in Japan: a retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tonetto registration was associated with a substantial reduction in emergency transport time for older patients over long distances. These findings demonstrate the potential of regional medical information networks to improve the efficiency of emergency care and support the development of a nationwide emergency medical information system in Japan.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retrospective analysis of 104 cases of pediatric severe pertussis in Southern China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In pediatric severe pertussis with oliguria, hypotension or shock, WBC ≥ 36.0 × 10⁹/L, neutrophil count ≥ 11.9 × 10⁹/L, or PAH, the survival rate decreases significantly, necessitating more aggressive treatments. Both hypotension and PAH have been identified as independent prognostic risk factors. We recommend monitoring for EBT and defining its indications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of methods for characterizing skin pigment diversity in research cohorts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Common methods for skin pigment characterization, especially the use of race or subjective scales, have significant limitations. When applied to the same cohort, different methods yield significantly different results, and some may overestimate diversity. Previously published ITA thresholds for defining 'dark' skin are too light and lead to underrepresentation of people with darker skin.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mobility Overestimation in Thin-Film Transistors: Effects of Device Geometry and Fringe Currents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amorphous oxide semiconductor-based thin-film transistors (oxide TFTs) were first demonstrated in 2004. These devices offer numerous advantages, including low-temperature processing, high carrier mobility, and ultralow off-current. As a result, oxide TFTs have already been adopted for backplane technologies in modern flat-panel displays. Furthermore, their ultralow off-current has attracted considerable attention for next-generation DRAM applications. However, device reliability remains a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the Ethos automated planning system for spatially fractionated radiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Ethos automated treatment planning demonstrated superior lattice dose conformity, enhanced OAR sparing, and significantly faster optimization compared to Eclipse. This automated optimization capability highlights the potential of Ethos for efficient and effective lattice radiotherapy in managing massive NSCLC tumors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detecting mind wandering via EEG and facial video features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings underscore the potential of multimodal approaches for MW detection and highlight the importance of individual differences and data diversity in classifier training. The study provides actionable insights into improving MW detection systems for real-world applications in educational settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global exploration of drought-tolerant bacteria in the wheat rhizosphere reveals microbiota shifts and functional taxa enhancing plant resilience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drought stress impacts plant-microbe interactions, reshaping microbial community composition and biogeochemical cycling, thereby reducing crop productivity and threatening food security. However, the specific microbial responses and roles of plant-derived metabolites remain underexplored. Here we reveal that drought stress shifts the composition of wheat-associated microbiota across the phyllosphere, rhizosphere and root endosphere by favouring Actinobacteria and Ascomycota while depleting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[B7-H3 in the tumor microenvironment: Implications for CAR T cell therapy in pediatric solid tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[B7 homolog 3 (B7-H3, CD276) has emerged as a promising target for chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) T cell therapy, with limited expression in normal tissues and high level cell-surface expression across various tumor types. Clinical studies are ongoing, with a focus on pediatric cancers. As an immune checkpoint molecule of the B7-CD28 family, B7-H3 has a proposed immune-modulatory role, though the precise nature of B7-H3-mediated cell interactions and functional contributions to immune responses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251011033454&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>