<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:21:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methyltransferase Detection Based on Target-Responsive Transcription Amplification of Light-Up Aptamer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The sensitive and accurate evaluation of DNA methyltransferases (MTases) is essential for biomedical and synthetic biology applications. However, existing approaches have limited applications because they are labor-intensive with low sensitivity, require sophisticated instruments, and involve complicated processes. Here, we developed a simple, label-free, and versatile strategy called MTase-responsive Transcription Amplification (MTA) assay for sensitive and specific MTase detection. We designed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[School nurse-involved sexual and reproductive health education for adolescents' students in high-income countries: a mixed-methods systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This mixed-methods systematic review evaluated the effectiveness of school nurse-involved educational interventions in promoting adolescents' sexual and reproductive health (SRH) in high-income countries. The review adopted the Joanna Briggs Institute (JBI) convergent segregated approach. A multi-database search was conducted between March and May 2024. Two researchers independently selected the relevant studies and assessed the risk of bias using RoB 2.0, RoB 2 for Cluster Randomized Trials...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Arteriopathic Effects of Hypertension by Signal Intensity Gradient from Time-of-Flight Magnetic Resonance Angiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The arterial wall SIG was significantly associated with hypertension and other vascular RFs. SIG may offer quantitative information on the arteriopathic effects of hypertension, especially intracranial cerebral arteries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Odontogenic Cutaneous Fistula-Induced Submandibular Abscess in a Dog: A Rare Presentation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Odontogenic cutaneous fistulas (OCFs) are relatively uncommon in veterinary patients. They are typically caused by chronic periapical infections of the maxillary teeth. Mandibular OCFs that extend through the cortical bone into submandibular soft tissues are extremely rare. This report describes the case of a 14-year-old male mixed-breed dog that presented with a submandibular cutaneous lesion initially misdiagnosed as a salivary mucocele. OCFs are frequently misdiagnosed because atypical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum Digital Signature Using Entangled States for Network]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose an entanglement-based quantum digital signature (QDS) protocol optimized for quantum networks. The protocol follows the Lamport-inspired QDS paradigm but eliminates QKD post-processing by signing and verifying with raw conclusive keys, thereby reducing latency and implementation complexity. We provide a finite-size security analysis of robustness, unforgeability, and non-repudiation. Under standard fiber-loss and detector models, simulations show a consistent signature rate advantage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thin-Film Batteries for On-Chip and Wearable Applications: Advances, Challenges, and Future Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thin-film batteries (TFBs) are vital for powering miniaturized electronics and Internet of Things(IoT) devices, offering compact size, long cycle life, and high safety. Utilizing solid-state electrolytes and thin-film deposition, TFBs integrate seamlessly with microelectronic systems. Advances in fabrication methods such as magnetron sputtering and atomic layer deposition, adapted from semiconductor manufacturing, have enhanced scalability, ionic conductivity, and electrochemical performance....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ATF5-Dependent GDF15 Expression Mediates Anesthesia-Induced Neuroprotection Against Stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perioperative stroke is a rare but serious complication with a rising incidence in aging populations. Although preclinical studies consistently demonstrate that anesthetics such as sevoflurane can induce neuroprotective preconditioning against ischemic injury, clinical results have remained inconclusive. In this study, it is demonstrated that sevoflurane-induced neuroprotection is associated with the upregulation of genes involved in the mitochondrial unfolded protein response (UPR^(mt)) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From muscle to motion: GaIn nanoparticle-TPU core/shell mesh electrodes for intelligent prosthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electromyography (EMG) electrodes are critical for detecting and interpreting muscle activity, which is essential for operating prosthetic devices and wearable robots. Traditional EMG electrodes, however, often face limitations such as being uncomfortable, lacking stretchability, and wearing out quickly. To overcome these challenges, we developed an innovative EMG wristband with mesh electrodes created using charge-reverse electro writing (CREW). The wristband is tailored to fit the unique...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of serum uric acid in survival prediction in patients with acute myocardial infarction accompanied by heart failure with preserved ejection fraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In a cohort with acute myocardial infarction, hyperuricemia was independently associated with all-cause mortality in patients with HFpEF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anodic NiO nanoparticles as high-performance asymmetric supercapacitor devices in hybrid electrolytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The energy storage capabilities of a supercapacitor are critically determined by the choice of electrode materials, electrolytes, and synthesis methods, making their appropriate selection indispensable for improving the electrochemical performance. This study presents the synthesis of nickel oxide (NiO) nanoparticles (NPs) by a low-cost, straightforward, and one-step anodization approach. FESEM, HRTEM, XRD, XPS, BET analysis, FTIR, and Raman spectroscopy were performed to determine the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tailored Xenogeneic-Free Polymer Surface Promotes Dynamic Migration of Intestinal Stem Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Regenerative therapy employing intestinal stem cells (ISCs) holds promise for epithelial restoration. However, it requires scalable and robust, but fully defined culture platforms free of xenogeneic components. Most existing systems, however, typically rely on Matrigel, which complicates clinical translation and limits understanding of stem cell-material interactions. Here, a poly(ethyleneglycoldimethacrylate) (pEGDMA)-based synthetic culture surface is exposed to N(2) plasma treatment for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative effects of sevoflurane and desflurane on postoperative renal function in patients with type 2 Diabetes mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Although sevoflurane is widely used for general anesthesia, its potential nephrotoxicity remains a concern, particularly in patients with type 2 diabetes mellitus (T2DM). This study compared the renal effects of sevoflurane and desflurane in T2DM patients, focusing on renal cortical fat fraction (RCFF) from preoperative magnetic resonance imaging (MRI). Methods: In this retrospective cohort study, adult T2DM patients who underwent non-cardiac surgery >3 h under sevoflurane or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inflammasomes and pyroptosis in cancer: mechanisms and therapeutic advances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammasomes are being increasingly recognized for their critical roles in regulating immune cell infiltration, antitumor immunity, and tumorigenesis in cancer biology. The expression and activation of inflammasomes, which vary according to the tumor type and stage, influence both tumor progression and elimination through pyroptosis. A deeper understanding of the complex functions and regulatory mechanisms of inflammasomes and pyroptosis in diverse aspects of tumor biology is crucial for the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fermented Porcine Placenta and Its Dipeptides Modulate Cellular Senescence in Human Keratinocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skin aging is primarily driven by oxidative stress, mitochondrial dysfunction, and cell cycle dysregulation. This study investigated the anti-senescence effects of fermented porcine placenta (FPP) and its dipeptides, leucine-glycine (LG) and proline-hydroxyproline (PH), in human epidermal keratinocytes (HEKs), using nicotinamide mononucleotide (NMN) as a reference for nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide (NAD^(+))-related pathways. FPP suppressed senescence-associated β-galactosidase (SA-β-gal)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combination Treatment of Carboxyl Esterase 2-Overexpressing hTERT-Immortalized Human Adipose Stem Cells Enhances the Inhibition of Tumor Growth by Irinotecan in PC3, a Castration-Resistant Prostate Cancer Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Castration-resistant prostate cancer (CRPC) remains difficult to treat with conventional chemotherapy. We evaluated a stem cell-based enzyme-prodrug strategy using hTERT-immortalized adipose-derived stem cells engineered to express rabbit carboxylesterase 2 (hTERT-ADSC.CE2) in combination with irinotecan (CPT-11). hTERT-ADSC.CE2 cells were generated via lentiviral transduction and confirmed to overexpress CE2. Their tumor-homing capacity toward PC3 prostate cancer cells was assessed, along with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lorlatinib in Tyrosine Kinase Inhibitor-Naive Advanced ROS1-Positive Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer: A Phase 2 Nonrandomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this nonrandomized clinical trial, lorlatinib demonstrated durable efficacy and manageable safety in TKI-naive advanced ROS1-positive NSCLC, supporting the potential for using lorlatinib in earlier treatment settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploratory Analyses of Patient Preferences for Atezolizumab Subcutaneous Versus Intravenous from the IMscin002 Study in Patients with Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Most patients preferred atezolizumab SC regardless of baseline characteristics, mean injection duration, and cumulative number of SC injections. The trend for a stronger preference was higher among patients who preferred SC than those who preferred IV. Our findings suggest that the proportion of preference for atezolizumab SC over IV is highest in patients aged > 74 years, and that administrator's experience could be an important factor influencing patient preference.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MicroRNA-124 induces AML differentiation and apoptosis through c-Myc suppression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: miR-124 acts as a tumor suppressor in AML by modulating a ROS-dependent c-Myc signaling pathway and inducing differentiation and apoptosis. These findings highlight miR-124 as a promising therapeutic and prognostic target in AML.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deciphering the molecular landscape of hepatopancreatic necrosis disease in Eriocheir sinensis using RNA-Seq meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study provides valuable insights into the causes and pathogenic mechanisms of HPND, identifies novel genetic factors and gene markers for detection, and offers a deeper understanding of the disease, highlighting potential biomarkers for its prevention in E. sinensis aquaculture.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High incidence of eating disorders in individuals with type 2 diabetes and their association with cardiovascular and mortality risks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS/INTERPRETATION: Type 2 diabetes mellitus and ED increased all-cause mortality, composite CVD, CV-related mortality and CV-related hospitalisation. ED incidence was higher among insulin users with type 2 diabetes. Therefore, early diagnosis and personalised interventions are crucial to improve outcomes in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac Remodeling After Transcatheter Tricuspid Valve Replacement: Insights From Multimodality Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Reduction in RVEDV with increase in LVEDV following TTVR is associated with reduction in LV eccentricity with an increase in forward SV. CT measures of RV function (effective RVEF) and RV coupling (SV/RVESV) both improve following TTVR. Patients with baseline higher LV eccentricity may derive more benefits from TTVR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Prevalence, Treatment, and Control of Cardiometabolic Risk Factors Among Adults With Hypertension in the United States, 1999-2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The burden of cardiometabolic risk factors among U.S. adults with hypertension has increased overall, with concurrent diabetes and hyperlipidemia now affecting more than 1 in 5. Only one-quarter of adults with hypertension, diabetes, and hyperlipidemia have all 3 conditions controlled-a proportion that has not improved in more than a decade.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Botulinum Toxin Type A for Pediatric Torticollis: A Review of Clinical Research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pediatric torticollis, predominantly resulting from congenital muscular torticollis, is characterized by unilateral shortening of the sternocleidomastoid muscle, leading to head tilt and limited cervical mobility. Conventional management primarily involves physical therapy and repositioning strategies, with most infants achieving full recovery. However, a subset of patients exhibits persistent symptoms despite conservative treatment. Botulinum toxin type A (BoNT-A) has emerged as a minimally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Readiness for Practice and Associated Factors Among Baccalaureate Nursing Students in Mongolia: A Mixed Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Readiness for practice is an essential outcome of nursing education, yet the factors influencing it among baccalaureate nursing students in Mongolia remain underexplored. This study aimed to provide a holistic understanding of factors influencing readiness for practice among baccalaureate nursing students in Mongolia, employing both quantitative and qualitative approaches. Methods: A convergent mixed-methods design was used. The study included 150 final-year baccalaureate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primary Prostatic Carcinoma with Metastasis to Epaxial Muscles and Myocardium in a Dog]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canine prostatic carcinoma is a highly aggressive neoplasm with a strong tendency to metastasize, most commonly to regional lymph nodes, lungs, and bones. However, skeletal muscle and myocardial involvement are rarely reported. This report describes an 11-year-old intact male Maltese dog with a two-month history of anorexia and lethargy, referred for further evaluation after failing to respond to piroxicam therapy. Diagnostic imaging revealed a prostatic mass and multiple rim-enhancing lesions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Ahmed et al. In Situ Transformed CoOOH@Co<sub>3</sub>S<sub>4</sub> Heterostructured Catalyst for Highly Efficient Catalytic OER Application. <em>Nanomaterials</em> 2024, <em>14</em>, 1732]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the original publication [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retrospective Analysis and Cross-Validated Forecasting of West Nile Virus Transmission in Italy: Insights from Climate and Surveillance Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background. West Nile Virus (WNV) represents a significant public health concern in Europe, with Italy-particularly its northern regions-experiencing recurrent outbreaks. Climate variables and vector dynamics are known to significantly influence transmission patterns, highlighting the need for reliable predictive models to enable timely outbreak detection and response. Methods. We integrated epidemiological data on human WNV infections in Italy (2012-2024) with high-resolution climate variables...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interim Vaccine Effectiveness Against Influenza and Hospitalization, Republic of Korea, 2024-2025 (HIMM Network)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Influenza cases have surged earlier than usual during the 2024-2025 season, with A/H1N1 (pdm09) being the dominant strain. We aimed to investigate early estimates of influenza vaccine effectiveness (VE) for the 2024-2025 season to enhance our influenza response strategies. Methods: From November 1 to December 31, 2024, we enrolled 990 individuals with influenza-like illness from the hospital-based influenza surveillance network (Hospital-Based Influenza Morbidity and Mortality,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Starfish-Derived Extracts Enhance Mitophagy and Suppress Senescence-Associated Markers in Human Dermal Fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While the starfish species Asterias pectinifera (Ap) and Asterias amurensis (Aa) are considered ecological threats to marine environments and the fishing industry, recent studies have identified them as rich sources of highly water-soluble, non-toxic collagen peptides. Mitochondrial dysfunction is a key driver of cellular senescence and skin aging, yet the therapeutic potential of marine-derived extracts in modulating mitophagy remains largely unexplored. In this study, we investigated whether...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex-Specific Risk Factors for Dynapenia in Korean Middle-Aged and Older Adults: A Cross-Sectional Study Based on the Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey 2014-2019]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Dynapenia, characterized by an age-related decline in muscle strength, has recently gained attention as a major public health concern. While prior studies identified individual risk factors, little is known about how these factors cluster differently by sex. This study investigated sex-specific risk factors and their combinations associated with dynapenia among Korean middle-aged and older adults. Methods: We analyzed 22,850 participants aged ≥ 40 years from the 2014-2019...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Few-Shot Adaptation of Foundation Vision Models for PCB Defect Inspection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Automated Optical Inspection (AOI) of Printed Circuit Boards (PCBs) suffers from scarce labeled data and frequent domain shifts caused by variations in camera optics, illumination, and product design. These limitations hinder the development of accurate and reliable deep-learning models in manufacturing settings. To address this challenge, this study systematically benchmarks three Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning (PEFT) strategies-Linear Probe, Low-Rank Adaptation (LoRA), and Visual Prompt...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical and Mechanical Characteristics of One-Shade Composite Resins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the optical and mechanical properties of two single-shade composite resins compared with a conventional multi-shade composite. Omnichroma (OM), Metafil Bulk Fill ONE (BO), and Filtek Z350XT (Z350) were tested. Color adjustment was assessed using A3, B1, and C4 background cavities, and ΔE00 values were calculated. The translucency parameter (TP) was measured, and the flexural strength, flexural modulus, and depth of cure (B/T ratio) were determined. OM and BO showed better...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of Machining, Polishing, and Glazing on Surface Properties and Biological Performance of Zirconia and Lithium Disilicate Dental Ceramics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface treatments play a crucial role in modifying the surface properties and biological performance of dental ceramics. This study investigated the effects of surface conditions on the wettability, cytocompatibility, and bacterial resistance of 4 mol% Y(2)O(3)-stabilized tetragonal zirconia polycrystal (4Y-TZP) and two lithium disilicate (Li(2)Si(2)O(5)) glass ceramics (Amber^(®) Mill (AM) and Amber^(®) Mill Abut-Crown (AC)). Human gingival fibroblast (HGF-1) responses and biofilm formation on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemically Defined, Efficient Megakaryocyte Production from Human Pluripotent Stem Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platelet shortage poses a significant barrier to research and transfusion therapies because native megakaryocytes (MKs) are scarce in blood. To overcome this limitation, pluripotent stem cell-derived MKs (PSC-MKs) offer a standardized, donor-independent platform for research and therapeutic development, including disease modeling and ex vivo platelet production. Here, we report a chemically defined, feeder-free protocol to generate MKs from human pluripotent stem cells (hPSCs). The protocol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Region-Specific Roles of TGF-β2 and Angiotensin II in Fibrotic and Inflammatory Remodeling of the Optic Nerve Head]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the region-specific roles of transforming growth factor-β2 (TGF-β2) and angiotensin II (AngII) in extracellular matrix (ECM) remodeling and inflammatory responses within scleral tissues surrounding the optic nerve head (ONH), using primary human fibroblasts from posterior sclera, peripapillary sclera (ppScl), and fibroblast-like cells from lamina cribrosa (LC). In vivo validation was performed in a chronic ocular hypertension rat model. Fibrotic and inflammatory markers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ferroptosis in Anaplastic Thyroid Cancer: Molecular Mechanisms, Preclinical Evidence, and Therapeutic Prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anaplastic thyroid cancer (ATC) is among the most lethal human malignancies, characterized by rapid progression, therapeutic resistance, and a median survival of less than one year. Conventional therapies, including surgery, radiotherapy, and chemotherapy, have limited effect, and targeted or immune-based treatments provide only transient benefit. Ferroptosis, a regulated form of cell death driven by iron-dependent lipid peroxidation, has recently emerged as a therapeutic vulnerability in ATC....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Na<sup>+</sup>/H<sup>+</sup> Exchanger 1 Inhibition Overcomes Venetoclax Resistance in Acute Myeloid Leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite advances with novel targeted agents (e.g., BCL-2 or IDH inhibitors) combined with chemotherapy for acute myeloid leukemia (AML), drug resistance persists. We investigated whether blocking Na^(+)/H^(+) exchanger 1 (NHE1) could enhance AML cell sensitivity to the BCL-2 inhibitor venetoclax and sought to determine the molecular mechanisms. Our results demonstrated that co-treatment with venetoclax and the NHE1 inhibitor 5-(N,N-hexamethylene) amiloride (HMA) synergistically induced apoptosis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design Optimization and Mechanical Performance Evaluation of a Modified Coronary IV-OCT Catheter Adapted for Intracranial Navigation: A Preclinical Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The application of intravascular optical coherence tomography (IV-OCT) in neurovascular interventions is constrained by the mechanical inadequacy of conventional catheters in navigating the complex intracranial vasculature. To address this, we modified a coronary IV-OCT catheter, enhancing its mechanical performance for neurovascular applications. The modified catheter featured a 300 mm over-the-microwire segment and a dual-structured shaft (distal 50 mm nonbraided, proximal 250 mm braided) to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Injectable and Self-Healing Boronic-Acid-Modified Succinoglycan Hydrogels: Dual-Stimuli-Responsive Platforms for Controlled Tannic Acid Release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, succinoglycan (SG), an anionic exopolysaccharide derived from Sinorhizobium meliloti Rm1021, was chemically modified to introduce boronic acid groups, creating a boronic-acid-functionalized polysaccharide (SG-APBA). The degree of substitution varied from 4.24% to 24.3%, depending on APBA concentration, with SG-APBA 2 identified as the optimal formulation. The properties of SG-APBA were characterized using ¹H NMR, FTIR, TGA, and XRD, along with rheological analysis to assess...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparation of Hydrogel by Crosslinking and Multi-Dimensional Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Functional hydrogels are cutting-edge materials that are important in various fields, such as biomedical engineering, agriculture, pollution control, artificial organs, electronics, and domestic products. They are essential to contemporary scientific and industrial advancements because of their adaptability and versatility. The new synthesis techniques and multidimensional applications of different kinds of hydrogels are the goals of this study. The special qualities of hydrogels are one of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precursor Concentration-Dependent Sol-Gel Dynamics in Neodymium Oxide: From Gel Framework to Electrochemical Functionality in Asymmetric Supercapacitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rare-earth oxides possess distinctive electronic configurations, tunable oxidation states, and inherent structural robustness, making them highly attractive for advanced energy storage applications. Among these, neodymium oxide (Nd(2)O(3)) stands out due to its high surface redox activity, structural stability, and favorable band alignment, enabling efficient charge storage in electrochemical devices. In this study, Nd(2)O(3) electrodes were synthesized via a sol-gel method with systematically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Rare Earth-Assisted Cobalt Oxide Gels Toward Superior Energy Storage in Asymmetric Supercapacitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rational design of transition metal oxides with tailored electronic structures and defect chemistries is critical for advancing high-performance supercapacitors. Herein, we report the engineering of cobalt oxide (Co(3)O(4)) gels through controlled sol-gel synthesis and rare earth (RE) incorporation using neodymium (Nd), gadolinium (Gd), and dual neodymium/gadolinium (Nd/Gd) doping. X-ray diffraction (XRD) confirmed the preservation of the cubic spinel structure with systematic peak shifts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical Coherence Tomography for Assessing the Severity of Dental Caries: An In Vitro Validation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Differentiating initial from moderate non-cavitated occlusal caries using intraoral radiography is challenging. This in vitro study aimed to verify the ability of Optical Coherence Tomography (OCT) to discern the extent of demineralization in non-cavitated carious lesions and discriminate between the exact caries stages. Methods: In total, 110 extracted molars and premolars with occlusal caries were examined by two calibrated examiners using OCT and radiography....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Variable Elastic Band with Adjustable Elasticities for Semi-Passive Exosuits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Active exosuits provide various assistive force profiles but are limited by battery life, weight, and complex maintenance requirements. Passive exosuits, by contrast, are economical and lightweight while also offering unlimited usage times; however, due to their fixed stiffness levels, they can provide only a limited set of optimized assistive force profiles for different movements. To address these issues, this paper proposes a new variable elastic band for semi-passive exosuits. It comprises...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Model Identification and Controller Design for a Fish Robot with Control Fins via Experiments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an experimental longitudinal mode control approach for a biomimetic underwater robot. Input-output models for surge velocity and pitch angle were derived through experiments, considering the fish robot body with servo motors and control pins as a single system to solve the problem of fish robots, which are complex and nonlinear, and also contain uncertainty. Closed-loop control systems were designed using PID controllers based on these models, and their performance was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Foot Melanoma Reconstruction Using Refined Perforator Flap: Safety, Function, and Subregional Surgical Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Free perforator flaps appear to provide reliable reconstruction for foot melanoma defects, with low rates of complications and secondary debulking, as well as favorable functional outcomes. Region-specific strategies for flap and recipient vessel selection may further optimize outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grandchild Care and Frailty in Later Life: Evidence From Older Koreans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Grandchild care is an enriching, joyful experience but can sometimes be stressful. This study was undertaken to investigate the effect of grandchild care on new-onset frailty among community-dwelling older Korean adults. Data from the Korean Longitudinal Study of Aging on 8744 individuals were subjected to analysis. Eight thousand three hundred thirteen were allocated to a non-care group and 431 to a care group. All were followed until frailty developed. A gender-stratified Cox proportional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical position-guided auto-segmentation and dosimetric evaluation of vestibular schwannomas in gamma knife radiosurgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study showed that embedding a VS-specific anatomical information significantly enhances DLAS accuracy and efficiency, supporting routine GK-SRS planning even on CPU-only workstations. APG can be integrated into various deep-learning networks through channel-wise concatenation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of peripartum cerebrovascular events in women with moyamoya disease: a multicenter cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights the protective effect of revascularization on peripartum CVEs and proposes a structured clinical protocol, recommending prepregnancy hemodynamic assessment and neurosurgical consultation. Women diagnosed with MMD during pregnancy and those in the 'non-revascularized or hemodynamically unstable' group should be considered a high-risk group for peripartum CVEs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modified suture-less flanged intrascleral intraocular lens fixation approach accessible for novice retinal surgeons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Optimizing needle engagement for symmetry in the Yamane technique and narrowing flange spacing while ensuring a circular polypropylene configuration in the Canabrava technique may reduce surgical complexity and improve postoperative outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond effective mass increase: Optimal range of carrier concentration for thermoelectric efficiency enhancement in Pb-doped Sb1.85In0.15Te3 alloys]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sb2Te3-based alloys have excellent thermoelectric transport properties in the medium-temperature range of 500-700 K, and In-doped Sb2Te3 compositions are widely recognized as having high thermoelectric-transport efficiencies. This study investigated the thermoelectric properties of systematically Pb-doped Sb1.85In0.15Te3 (Sb1.85-xPbxIn0.15Te3, where x = 0, 0.01, 0.02, 0.03, 0.04, or 0.05). It was found that Pb2+ substitution at Sb3+ sites generated holes very effectively; thus, significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interleukin-8 Overexpressing Collagen Microgel-Based Cellular Microtissue Accelerates the Healing of Diabetic Foot Ulcers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic foot ulcers (DFUs) represent a major clinical challenge due to impaired healing and limited therapeutic options. Although stem cell therapy offers regenerative potential, its efficacy is restricted by poor survival and engraftment at the injury site. To address this, collagen microgels (CMGs) are developed to assemble with cells to form CMG-based cellular microtissues (CCMs) with enhanced porosity, mass transfer, and viability. However, the diabetic microenvironment impairs healing by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cosmetogenomics unveiled: a systematic review of AI, genomics, and the future of personalized skincare]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI-driven cosmetogenomics is advancing dermatology into a predictive, personalized era. While the evidence base is expanding, clinical translation requires stronger validation, ethical safeguards, and regulatory oversight. This field holds significant promise for enhancing treatment efficacy, patient satisfaction, and long-term skin health. Broader validation, greater diversity in study populations, more transparent methodologies, and expanded ethical safeguards, including genetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoscale Observation of Nickel(II) Sequestration by Green Rust Sulfate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Green rust (GR) is a mixed-valent Fe-layered double hydroxide (Fe-(II)-Fe-(III)-LDH) mineral that is prevalent in reducing geochemical environments, where it exhibits high sorption and redox reactivity. Here, we examined the morphology and chemistry of individual GR particles with nanoscale resolution in the presence and absence of Ni-(II)(aq) at reaction times between 1 h and 3 months using scanning transmission electron microscopy coupled with energy dispersive X-ray spectroscopy (STEM-EDXS)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative regulation of middle cortex formation: from classic modules to emerging pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Generation of distinct cell types through asymmetric cell division (ACD) is a fundamental developmental process in multicellular organisms. Therefore, controlling when and where ACDs occur is essential for the production of new cells and tissues. The Arabidopsis (Arabidopsis thaliana) root has emerged as a powerful model for studying this process because its cell division patterns are highly stereotyped and easily observed. Within the ground tissue, periclinal ACDs in the endodermis generate the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Candida Spondylodiscitis After Transforaminal Epidural Steroid Injection: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transforaminal epidural steroid injection (TFESI) is a widely used intervention for lumbar radicular pain. Although rare, fungal spinal infections can follow such procedures and require prompt diagnosis and management. A 76‑year‑old male developed progressive back pain and bilateral leg weakness two weeks after bilateral L5 TFESI. He received empirical antibiotic therapy in an outside emergency department, but showed no progress. He subsequently presented to our outpatient clinic 11 weeks after...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Deep Learning-Based Automated Scoring System for Predicting Eyelid Rejuvenation Outcomes After Monopolar Radiofrequency Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This proof-of-concept study demonstrates the feasibility of an automated deep learning-based scoring system for eyelid MRF outcomes. By providing objective, consistent, and reproducible evaluations, the system has the potential to enhance patient counseling, guide individualized treatment planning, and enable standardized research comparisons across clinics. Larger and more diverse datasets with longer follow-up are needed for further validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antimicrobial susceptibility of <em>Porphyromonas</em> spp. isolated from dogs with periodontal disease in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Porphyromonas spp. are oral anaerobes that play a key role in the pathogenesis of canine periodontal disease. Despite their clinical relevance in veterinary medicine, data on the antimicrobial susceptibility of canine Porphyromonas isolates remain limited. Therefore, we assessed the antimicrobial susceptibility of Porphyromonas spp. isolated from the subgingival plaque of dogs with periodontitis in South Korea. Fifty-eight dogs diagnosed with periodontal disease were screened for Porphyromonas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of auricular acupressure on polysomnography-assessed sleep, blood glucose, and stress in elderly patients with type 2 diabetes and insomnia: a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Auricular acupressure is an effective and safe non-pharmacological intervention for improving objective sleep quality, lowering postprandial blood glucose, and reducing physiological stress in elderly patients with type 2 diabetes and insomnia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of cognitive behavioral therapy for stimulant use disorders: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings suggest that standalone CBT may increase short-term abstinence from stimulants. However, given the low certainty of the evidence, the effect estimate should be interpreted cautiously, and more high-quality research is needed. This research was funded by the Ministry of Health and Welfare, Republic of Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pairwise interaction of in-line spheroids settling in a linearly stratified fluid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the transport of particles in density-stratified fluids, a prevalent natural phenomenon. In the ocean, particles and marine snow descend through fluids with significant density variations due to salinity and temperature gradients. Such heterogeneity in the background fluid affects the settling or rising rates of particles, often leading to accumulation at transitional density layers. Previous research has primarily focused on spherical particles, examining their isolated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilization of cell-free DNA metagenomic analysis for early detection and microbial identification in prosthetic joint infections: a prospective cohort study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: cfDNA concentration was significantly higher in the PJI group, with synovial cultures showing substantial agreement. Additionally, cfDNA sequencing detected pathogens in patients who had received prior antibiotic therapy and identified multiple pathogens in polymicrobial infections. These findings highlight cfDNA analysis as a valuable diagnostic tool for PJI, with the potential to enhance current diagnostic approaches.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preclinical evaluation of 3D-Printed orthodontic aligners using an electro-typodont model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The electric typodont appears to be a reliable pre-clinical tool for evaluating the effectiveness of aligners. Furthermore, 3D-printed aligners successfully achieved incisor derotation without the use of attachments. Furthermore, while variations in aligner thickness influenced the dynamics of derotation, they did not alter the ultimate correction outcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chirality amplification in semiconductors for advanced optoelectronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Because circularly polarized light (CPL) uniquely carries spin-selective information, chiral optoelectronics offer a powerful platform for developing high-efficiency, spin-based optical devices and driving next-generation photonic technologies. Intrinsically chiral semiconductors can absorb or emit CPL through light-matter interactions, positioning them as highly attractive active materials for advanced optoelectronics. However, their weak chiroptical activities often hinder practical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effective Penetration of the Oxidized Keratin-Rebonding Materials Into Hair Shafts Based on Charge Conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Materials bearing multiple positive charges reinforce damaged hair fibers through ionic interactions with negatively charged sulfonate groups present in oxidized keratin. However, their strong surface binding often hinders deep penetration into the hair shaft. To address this limitation, we designed β-carboxylic acid amide moieties that are negatively charged at neutral pH but undergo charge conversion to cationic forms under mild acidification, thereby enhancing the penetration of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation Between Portable Photopic Electroretinography and Postoperative Best-Corrected Visual Acuity in Patients with Diabetic Vitreous Hemorrhage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Photopic ERG recorded using a handheld retinal ERG device equipped with skin electrodes can aid in predicting the visual prognosis in patients with severe VH caused by diabetes mellitus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Analysis of Drusen in Korean Patients: A 36-Month Follow-Up Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Drusen in Korean patients demonstrated dynamic morphological remodeling over time. Drusen regression was not a benign phenomenon but rather a potential high-risk marker for progression to advanced AMD. These findings highlight the importance of population-specific, quantitative SD-OCT monitoring for early risk stratification in East Asian eyes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a novel epicatechin-rich soybean variety, Aritaunkong, and its antioxidant and skin anti-aging properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Aritaunkong combines functional bioactivity with favorable agronomic traits, providing a valuable genetic resource for soybean breeding and biomarker discovery. © 2025 Society of Chemical Industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors affecting heat-related illness symptoms among school food service workers: a cross-sectional study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: School food service workers experience substantial heat exposure and a high prevalence of heat-related illness symptoms. The risk of heat-related illness symptoms was associated with extended duration of heat exposure. Increasing rest periods and reducing high-heat food preparation were effective preventive measures. These findings underscore the need for improved heat exposure management and implementation of effective preventive measures to protect the health of school food...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical Decannulation Using the Purse-String Technique in Venoarterial Extracorporeal Membrane Oxygenation Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The purse-string technique enables efficient and safe decannulation after V-A ECMO, offering a less invasive alternative to cross-clamp repair. This less invasive method may be particularly advantageous in critically ill patients or bedside settings where minimizing operative time and vascular trauma is essential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Throughput Screening of Photo-Cross-Linking Peptide Libraries for Site-Specific Conjugation of IgG]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An affinity-guided photo-cross-linking reaction based on Fc-binding peptide harboring p-benzoyl-l-phenylalanine (PEptide-DIrected Photo-cross-linking; PEDIP) enables site-specific modification of native antibodies but suffers from issues coming from long UV exposure and high peptide concentrations. In this study, we report a bacterial surface-display system of the photo-cross-linking peptide and high-throughput screening of its libraries with FACS for higher photo-cross-linking efficiency. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Affect valuations predict emotional response to satisfying and disappointing exam scores]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest motivational functions for ideal affect, particularly for positive affective states.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immobilization-free SELEX for aptamer discovery targeting colorectal cancer-derived small extracellular vesicles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings demonstrate the applicability of SELEX technology to native sEVs and highlight the diagnostic potential of the identified aptamers for sEV-based cancer detection. The EDGE-SELEX method and the G6 motif may serve as valuable tools for future clinical applications in non-invasive cancer diagnostics and aptamer engineering, although further validation with clinical samples is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urinary acetylated protein as a biomarker of lupus nephritis: a prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of gastrointestinal cancers in patients with primary Sjögren's syndrome in Korea: a nationwide retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: pSS was associated with increased risks of colorectal and pancreatic cancers, particularly among females and older adults. Further research should explore the underlying mechanisms and the impact of pSS duration and severity on cancer risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nurse triage in primary care: concept analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Restoration of BAP1 activity via base editing suppresses anchorage-independent survival in kidney cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BAP1, a deubiquitinase with a ubiquitin C-terminal hydrolase domain, functions as a tumor suppressor involved in diverse cellular processes, including DNA repair, genome stability, and apoptosis. Inactivating mutations in BAP1-particularly missense and deletion variants-are recurrent across multiple cancers, with a high prevalence in clear cell renal cell carcinoma (ccRCC), mesothelioma, and uveal melanoma. Among these, the Glu31Lys mutation in ccRCC impairs BAP1's enzymatic activity, protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domain and Language adaptive pre-training of BERT models for Korean-English bilingual clinical text analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinguishing bone marrow edema patterns on MRI between spondyloarthritis and diffuse idiopathic skeletal hyperostosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Characteristic BME patterns on spine MRI, particularly posterior location, marked hyperintensity, and accompanying fatty changes, could help distinguish SpA from DISH in diagnostically challenging cases with overlapping MRI manifestations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Care of Older Patients with Frailty in Primary Care (ICOOP-Frail): a pilot randomized controlled trial and cost-effectiveness analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This pilot RCT provides preliminary clinical evidence and demonstrates economic dominance of a structured, primary care-based frailty management program, supporting feasibility and the need for larger, longer trials. By integrating KFI-PC-based screening with telephone-based health coaching, the intervention reduced physician burden while addressing multidimensional needs of frail older adults. These findings support the feasibility of scaling frailty management in primary care,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical translation of photoacoustic imaging using exogenous molecular contrast agents [Invited]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoacoustic imaging (PAI) combines optical contrast with acoustic detection to enable high-resolution, molecular imaging at clinically relevant depths. This review outlines the current status and future potential of contrast-enhanced PAI in human applications. We begin by discussing regulatory considerations surrounding both imaging devices and exogenous contrast agents, highlighting safety concerns, lack of standardized validation protocols, and barriers to the approval of novel agents. To...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Peucedanum japonicum</em>-Derived Exosome-like Nanovesicles Alleviate Contact Dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Contact dermatitis is a common inflammatory skin disorder triggered by exposure to allergens or irritants and characterized by erythema, swelling, and immune cell infiltration. In this study, we investigated the anti-inflammatory effects of exosome-like nanovesicles derived from Peucedanum japonicum Thunb. (PjELNs) using a 2,4,6-trinitrochlorobenzene (TNCB)-induced mouse model of contact dermatitis. Intraperitoneal administration of PjELNs markedly reduced ear swelling and histopathological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulatory Effects of Coffee/Chlorogenic Acid and Tea/Epigallocatechin-3-<em>O</em>-Gallate on microRNA in Association with Their Anticancer Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epidemiological studies have provided evidence to show that the consumption of coffee and green tea has beneficial effects against cancer. Chlorogenic acid (CGA) in coffee and epigallocatechin-3-O-gallate (EGCG) in tea are involved in these effects. Research also suggests that the anticancer effects of coffee and tea may vary depending on the type of cancer, although the reasons for this remain unclear. As bioactive food factors, CGA and EGCG can contribute to epigenetic modification to exert...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Axial deviation of anastomosis: a risk factor for leakage in retrosternal gastric tube reconstruction after esophagectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The axial deviation of the esophagogastric anastomosis is a potential risk factor for anastomotic leakage during retrosternal reconstruction. Further studies incorporating three-dimensional imaging and biomechanical analysis are needed to clarify its impact and optimize the anastomotic geometry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examination of simple artificial intelligence-based analysis of dopamine transporter scintigraphy for supporting a diagnosis of Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our simple AI model for the interpretation of DAT SPECT images was accurate and robust. Its accuracy was equivalent to that of physicians.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world multicenter study of immune checkpoint inhibitors in advanced cervical cancer across HPV-associated and HPV-independent subtypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ICIs improved survival in advanced refractory cervical cancer across two real-world cohorts. HPVI may respond favorably, but further studies are needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes of endovascular therapy strategy based on thrombus location for acute superior mesenteric artery occlusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tailored endovascular strategies based on thrombus location may contribute to favorable clinical outcomes in patients with acute superior mesenteric artery occlusion.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of profiles of biomarkers of potential harm among healthy adults who used heated tobacco products, smoked combustible cigarettes, or who had never smoked: a cross-sectional, observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This cross-sectional observational study assessed exposure to a selected combustible cigarette (CC) smoke constituent and biomarkers of potential harm (BoPH) in healthy adults who exclusively used a heated tobacco product (direct heating tobacco system, platform 3, generation 3, version a [DT3.0a] group, n = 304), smoked CC (CC group, n = 102), or had never smoked CC (NS group, n = 102), to evaluate biomarker profiles relevant to health risks associated with smoking. Relative to the CC group,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diverse Effects of Various Toll-Like Receptor 2 Ligands on Neuronal Activity and Cell Death]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The role of Toll-like receptor 2 (TLR2) in the central nervous system (CNS) is critical in several conditions including neurological disorders such as pain, and neurodegenerative disorders such as Parkinson's disease. Therefore, understanding TLR2 function in the CNS is of considerable importance. In this study, we investigated neuronal responses to individual TLR2 ligands. The expression levels of cytokines increased in the culture in the presence of TLR2 ligands. Additionally, increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Altered enteric neurodevelopment in the Ncx knockout mouse model of intestinal neuronal dysplasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings demonstrate that Ncx deficiency leads to abnormal ENS development beginning during the fetal period, providing a mechanistic basis for postnatal hyperganglionosis and validating this model for studying IND pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Molecular insights into HER2/ERBB2 amplification and carcinogenesis in gallbladder cancer associated with pancreaticobiliary maljunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence of cough reflex and vagal response among various pulsed field ablation systems: a multicenter registry study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cough reflex may vary across PFA systems, while vagal response may remain consistent.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Change in the pathways of polymorphic transitions during colloidal heteroepitaxy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymorphic transitions between three hexagonal structures have been observed during the epitaxial growth of colloidal particles when the ratio of particle sizes of the epitaxial and substrate particles was a specific value. These polymorphic transitions were examined by performing Brownian dynamics simulations. In both the experiment and simulations, three types of hexagonal structures formed in the first epitaxial layer when the epitaxial particle size was chosen appropriately. The growth...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex Differences in Dilated Cardiomyopathy: Evidence Gaps and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dilated cardiomyopathy (DCM), which affects 1 in 250 people, is a leading global cause of heart failure and the most common indication for heart transplantation. Evidence suggests that DCM is more prevalent in men, but whether this reflects biological differences or underdiagnosis in women remains uncertain. This review explores the impact of sex on DCM, examining differences in epidemiology, etiology, clinical presentation, treatment response, and outcomes. Women often present with less severe...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nixtamalization of Maize to Reduce Mycotoxin Exposure: A Human Biomonitoring Intervention Study in Soweto, South Africa]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mycotoxin contamination is a global threat to food safety and human health, especially in regions facing food insecurity, such as Sub-Saharan Africa. This intervention study evaluates the effectiveness of nixtamalization, a traditional alkaline cooking method, in reducing mycotoxin levels in maize and corresponding urinary biomarkers of exposure. Forty adult healthy volunteers from an informal settlement in Kliptown, Soweto (South Africa), were randomly assigned to consume control maize or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dose-Dependent Analysis of Image Quality in Pediatric Head CT Scans Across Different Scanners to Optimize Clinical Protocols Using Phantom-Based Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Quantitative thresholds were determined as practical indicators for balancing diagnostic image quality with dose reduction. Further reduction may be achieved through advanced reconstruction methods, such as deep learning-based algorithms. These findings may contribute to standardizing pediatric head CT protocols and supporting safer and more effective diagnostic imaging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Immunogenicity of Rabies Pre-Exposure Prophylaxis in Japanese Adult Travelers: Comparison of Dosing Regimens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Antibody levels were strongly influenced by the number of vaccine doses, with reduced persistence in those who received only two. If testing confirms sufficient titers, PrEP booster doses may not be needed. However, for individuals with only two doses, older vaccinations, or those given PCECV-KMB, a risk-based assessment is recommended-especially for travelers to rabies-endemic areas.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Astaxanthin-Binding Ependymin-Related Purple Protein Responsible for the Coloration of a Marine Purple Sponge, <em>Haliclona</em> sp]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although marine sponges display strikingly diverse colors, the molecular basis of this color diversity remains largely unknown. Recently, the blue coloration of Haliclona sp. was attributed to a water-soluble carotenoprotein that binds orange astaxanthin (AXT) and mytiloxanthin (MXT) and belongs to the ependymin superfamily. Here, we investigated the coloration mechanism of a purple sponge, Haliclona sp. The purified purple protein was identified as a secreted glycoprotein, representing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Nizuka et al. A Pilot Study on the Use of Pumpkin Waste as Cattle Feed. <em>Metabolites</em> 2025, <em>15</em>, 511]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Errors in Tables [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Pilot Study on the Effects of Sweet Potato Petiole and Leaf Powder on Gut Microbiota and Aging-Related Biomarkers in an Aged Microminipig Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Although many healthy foods are used for elderly humans, there are no suitable animal models to test them. We reared microminipigs (MMPs) for over 10 years, establishing aged MMP models. Using this aged preclinical model, we evaluated the effects of a polyphenol-rich diet without sacrificing the animals. Methods: A polyphenol-rich diet containing sweet potato petioles and leaves was administered to the aged MMPs daily for one month. Changes in fecal microbiota and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Clever Composites to Credible Technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Composite membranes are a hot topic in the field of membrane research. With the continuous progress of technology, its development has advanced from the application of simple copolymers to diversified material combinations. This Perspective examines why many composite membranes that excel in the lab struggle to deliver credible, durable performance at scale. Our aim is to connect four issues that are often treated in isolation-interfacial stability, manufacturability, data quality, and circular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High Current Induction for the Effective Bending in Ionic Polymer Metal Composite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionic Polymer-Metal Composites (IPMCs) are promising electroactive polymers for artificial muscles, as their bending motion depends on the induced current-greater current leads to greater bending. While conventional IPMCs use cation exchange membranes, this study explores IPMCs containing both immobile positive and negative charges, resembling real muscle tissue. Considering that an IPMC consists of an ion-exchange membrane sandwiched between two thin metal coatings serving as electrodes, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum Shannon Information Theory-Design of Communication, Ciphers, and Sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[One of the key aspects of Shannon theory is that it provides guidance for designing the most efficient systems, such as minimizing errors and clarifying the limits of coding. This theory has seen great developments in the 50 years since 1948. It has played a vital role in enabling the development of modern ultra-fast, stable, and highly dependable information and communication systems. Shannon theory is supported by statistical communication theories such as detection and estimation theory. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41295001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cancer and Aging Biomarkers: Classification, Early Detection Technologies and Emerging Research Trends]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer and aging are two distinct biological processes with shared cellular pathways, such as cellular senescence, DNA damage repair, and metabolic reprogramming. However, the outcomes of these processes differ in terms of proliferation. Understanding biomarkers related to aging and cancer opens a pathway for therapeutic interventions and more effective prevention, detection, and treatment strategies. Biomarkers, ranging from molecular to phenotypic indicators, play an important role in early...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Label-Free Rapid Quantification of Abscisic Acid in Xylem Sap Samples Using Surface Plasmon Resonance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The phytohormone abscisic acid (ABA) plays a central role in organizing adaptive responses in plants to various abiotic stresses, helping the plant minimize the negative impact on growth and development. Rapid and direct detection of ABA is valuable for investigating plant responses to abiotic stress. In this work, we propose a novel label-free, non-competitive immunoassay for detecting and quantifying ABA easily and rapidly using a surface plasmon resonance (SPR) biosensor. The SPR sensor chip...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoscopic Stenting for Unresectable Malignant Hilar Biliary Obstruction: Where Do We Stand Today? A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Malignant hilar biliary obstruction (MHBO) is a complex clinical condition commonly observed in individuals with advanced cholangiocarcinoma and other hepatobiliary malignancies. Endoscopic stenting remains the primary palliative intervention for unresectable cases; however, the optimal strategy has not been clearly defined owing to the anatomical intricacies of the hilar region and the heterogeneity of disease presentation. This narrative review summarizes current evidence and ongoing debates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship Between Virulence Factor Activities, Cytotoxicity of <em>Candida albicans</em> Strains Isolated from Oral Cavity, and Cytokine Production by Oral Keratinocytes Exposed to Those Strains]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: Oral candidiasis is commonly caused by Candida albicans, which possesses virulence factors and shows cytotoxic activity that affects oral keratinocytes. On the other hand, oral keratinocytes are known to induce immune responses against C. albicans infection. The aim of the present study was to investigate the relationships of various cytokines produced from oral keratinocytes with virulence factor activities and cytotoxicity of C. albicans strains. Methods: Following the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[QTFPred: robust high-performance quantum machine learning modeling that predicts main and cooperative transcription factor bindings with base resolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has become an essential tool for identifying transcription factor (TF) binding sites, yet conventional approaches often struggle with limited training data for specific TFs. Here, we introduce QTFPred (Quantum-based TF Predictor), a quantum-classical hybrid framework that integrates quantum convolutional layers within neural networks to predict TF binding at base resolution. By leveraging the exponential feature space offered by quantum circuits and training from scratch via GPU...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermal boundary conductance at the myoglobin-water interface: Heme cooling mechanism in light and heavy water environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The molecular mechanism of heme cooling following the photoexcitation of heme proteins has been a central issue in biological chemical physics for several decades. We expect that such a non-equilibrium process is accompanied by a vibrational energy relaxation from one site (protein quake epicenter) to the other sites in the protein molecule and eventually to the solvent molecules surrounding the protein. Interestingly, a recent optical-pump THz-probe spectroscopy demonstrated that the energy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Probing the Triplet State by Cryogenic Ion Trap IR Spectroscopy─Application to Protonated Lumiflavin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flavins are essential biological cofactors and their protonation isomers (protomers) generated upon photoexcitation play a crucial role in their photochemical reactions. Here, we identify the triplet-state (T(1)) protomer of protonated lumiflavin (LFH^(+)) in a cryogenic ion trap by visible-pump infrared-probe photodissociation spectroscopy using H(2)-tagging (H(2)-tagging Vis-IRPD). This approach yields high-resolution IR spectra of cold triplet ions which, along with quantum chemical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41294108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transparency of Mental Anatomy: Morphology of Cobblestone Chin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cobblestone chin is a common aesthetic concern caused by contraction of the mentalis muscle; however, its anatomic basis remains poorly understood. This study aimed to clarify the fiber architecture of the mentalis muscle and its relationship with chin surface irregularities. Anatomic dissection was performed on 6 cadavers (4 males and 2 females). In fixed cadavers, lower facial blocks were processed using potassium hydroxide and hydrogen peroxide to create transparent specimens for analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A morphomolecular study of 175 'USP6-associated neoplasms': The USP6 fusion partner strongly depends on morphology and location]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A significant entity- and location-specific USP6 fusion partner diversity was revealed among the UAN members. This supports the hypothesis that this diversity may be linked to the cell of origin. Additionally, molecular analysis can be valuable in diagnosing non-classical NF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three-dimensional intestinal tube with a crypt-like uneven inner wall fabricated using electrolysis-generated microbubbles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a three-dimensional intestinal hydrogel tube with a crypt-like uneven inner wall fabricated using electrolysis-generated microbubbles. The uneven structure observed in crypt and villus intestinal epithelial tissue in vivo serves as crucial geometry for forming hierarchical tissue consisting of stem cells localized in the crypts and various differentiated cells located in the villi. Our approach utilizes electrically generated microbubbles on a wire mold during the fabrication of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Directed Vectors for Generation of Independent Subspaces in the Bio-inpired Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning, deep learning and neural networks are extensively developed in many fields, with neural networks playing an important role in a wide variety of applications. However, a sufficient explanation of the structure and functionality of complex and deep neural networks is still needed. In this paper, it is shown that bio-inspired networks are useful for the explanation of network functions. First, the asymmetric network is created based on the biological retinal networks. Second, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Image formation theory of optical coherence tomography with optical aberrations and its application to computational aberration correction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Computational corrections of defocus and aberrations in optical coherence tomography (OCT) offers a promising approach to realize high-resolution imaging with deep imaging depth, but without additional high hardware costs. However, these techniques are not well understood owing to a lack of accurate theoretical models and investigation tools. The image formation theory for OCT with optical aberrations is thus formulated here. Based on this theory, a numerical simulation method is developed, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel genotypes, phenotypes, and triggers in humans with OTULIN haploinsufficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human OTULIN haploinsufficiency predisposes to life-threatening necrosis of the skin and lungs. Disease is triggered by infectious agents, typically Staphylococcus aureus, as well as unknown etiologies. We describe and characterize six unrelated patients who carry rare, predicted deleterious variants of OTULIN in heterozygosity. In addition to staphylococcal infections, the disease in the patients is elicited by previously underappreciated triggers, including mechanical or iatrogenic traumas and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantifying Time-Dependent Predictors for the International Spatial Spread of Highly Pathogenic Avian Influenza H5NX: Focus on Trade and Surveillance Efforts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The multiple waves of intercontinental transmission of the highly pathogenic avian influenza (HPAI) H5Nx Gs/GD lineage since its identification in 1996 are testament to its resistance to control and prevention efforts. Knowledge of the predictors of HPAI international spread can help identify strengths as well as areas for improvement in surveillance and controlling HPAI. We used 10 years of data with quarterly granularity from the World Organization for Animal Health (WOAH), United Nations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparation of polysaccharide composite films using cyclodextrin-conjugated chitosan for sustained release of hydrophobic drugs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyclodextrin-conjugated polysaccharides are often used as functional materials for biological applications, such as drug carriers, because the hydrophobic cavity of the cyclodextrin moiety can encapsulate molecules. Herein, β-cyclodextrin (β-CD)-conjugated chitosan (CD-CHI) for loading and sustained-release of low-molecular-weight hydrophobic drugs was synthesized, and polysaccharide composite films containing β-CD units were prepared from polyion complexes consisting of chondroitin sulfate C...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A study on drug delivery and release kinetics of polyethylene glycol-functionalized few-layer graphene (FLG) incorporated into a gelatin-chitosan bio-composite film]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study develops a composite film by incorporating few-layer graphene (FLG) within a gelatin-chitosan polymer matrix for enhanced drug delivery. The FLG was functionalized in two steps to produce a secondary functionalized FLG (FLG-PEG), resulting in improved dispersion in water, as characterized using an optical microscope. Morphological analysis revealed that FLG-PEG nanosheets are well dispersed, resulting in a smoother, more uniform composite film with the polymer wrapping around them....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The precuneus and posterior cingulate gyrus support temporal orientation in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the classifications of 'past,' 'present,' and 'future' are considered abstract concepts, we naturally understand them. Those classifications were named 'A-series' time by McTaggart in 1908. Alzheimer's disease (AD) is the most common type of dementia, with initial symptoms generally including temporal disorientation. This study aims to (1) elucidate the impairment process of temporal cognition in AD by administering A-series temporal tasks to individuals with AD, mild cognitive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41293233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential association of hyperglucagonemia with C-peptide levels in diabetic ketosis/ketoacidosis and hyperosmolar hyperglycemic state]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Hyperglucagonemia was found in DK/DKA and HHS with pancreas-specific glucagon measurements. The results suggest that the causes of hyperglucagonemia differ in DK/DKA due to type 1 diabetes mellitus and HHS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Massive immune-related myositis and cytokine release syndrome during dual immunotherapy plus chemotherapy for recurrent lung adenocarcinoma: case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immune-related myositis (irMyositis) is a rare but potentially life-threatening immune-related adverse event (irAE) associated with immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs). We report a case of irMyositis presenting with massive unilateral enlargement of the periarticular hip muscles in a patient with recurrent lung adenocarcinoma after two courses of combination therapy with tremelimumab, durvalumab, and chemotherapy. Computed tomography scans revealed marked unilateral swelling of the gluteal and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction: Fluorine-Specific Interactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extension of the Cluster Jastrow (<em>k-</em>uCJ) Decomposition to Complex Hamiltonians: Applications to Relativistic Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose an extension of the k-uCJ decomposition for the treatment of complex Hamiltonians, specifically focusing on relativistic systems. The algorithm uses Takagi decomposition to initially provide a rank-one approximation of both the real and imaginary parts of the two-electron integral in the second quantization Hamiltonian, followed by optimization of the K and J matrices. We employ the algorithm to calculate the potential energy curves of molecules containing heavy atoms, particularly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electric-Field-Induced Increase in Permittivity in Uniaxial Antiferroelectric K<sub>3</sub>Nb<sub>3</sub>B<sub>2</sub>O<sub>12</sub> Polycrystalline Ceramics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Potassium niobate borate K(3)Nb(3)B(2)O(12) exhibits uniaxial antiferroelectricity, where polarization flipping occurs along only one crystallographic direction, while a linear dielectric response is observed in perpendicular directions. The present study investigates the temperature dependence of dielectric permittivity and electric-field-induced polarization of K(3)Nb(3)B(2)O(12) polycrystalline ceramics to clarify its potential for high-voltage applications. The results demonstrated a high...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing the silent epidemic of recreational nitrous oxide use: a position, call to action and recommendations by the European Federation of Clinical Chemistry and Laboratory Medicine Committee on Biological Markers of Nitrous Oxide Abuse]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recreational nitrous oxide (N(2)O) use has emerged as a growing public health concern, with increasing reports of neurological, psychiatric, and thrombotic complications. This position paper from the EFLM Committee on Biological Markers of Nitrous Oxide Abuse highlights the urgent need for clinical and laboratory awareness, alongside coordinated action from healthcare systems and the scientific community. Short-term recommendations focus on early clinical recognition, prompt biological testing,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication of Thin Ion-Gel Membrane by Interfacial Polymerization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose interfacial polymerization as a suitable methodology for the fabrication of thin-gel membranes containing ionic liquids (ILs). Tetra-armed poly(ethylene glycol) (tetra-PEG) is a key material that forms a gel network via click reactions between tetra-PEG prepolymers with different terminal functional groups. At the interface between the aqueous and IL phases, thiol-terminated tetra-PEG and maleimide-terminated tetra-PEG react to form a single-micrometer-thick ion gel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41292108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Induction Test-Guided Ablation Improves Clinical Outcomes in Recurrent Atrial Fibrillation and Durable Pulmonary Vein Isolation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In recurrent AF despite durable PVI, an induction test-guided ablation strategy was associated with greater freedom from AF recurrence compared to empirical PWI and this association remained after PSM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frequency, patient characteristics, and clinical management for extravasation with docetaxel: a descriptive study using a large Japanese medical claims database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DTX monotherapy-related EV occurs in 0.075% of cancer patients. The proportion of patients with a history of EV was higher among those who experienced EV than among the overall study population. Only a small proportion of patients who develop EV are prescribed topical steroids or receive consultation from the dermatology or plastic surgery department. The incidence and management of EV may change following the publication of the 2023 edition of the Japanese EV guidelines, and thus,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors affecting employment in Japanese patients with ankylosing spondylitis (AS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compared to global averages, the employment rate among Japanese patients with ankylosing spondylitis is relatively high. Patient-reported outcomes, BASDAI and BASFI, were more closely associated with employment status than objective disease measures, highlighting the importance of addressing functional limitations to improve work outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationship between subjective shoulder discomfort and quantitative humeral head translation in baseball players; cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While anterior translation appears to be an adaptation to support external rotation, posterior translation may related to subjective feelings of instability in baseball players with scapular dyskinesis. Ultrasound imaging enabled precise quantification of subtle translation differences, offering a valuable tool for detecting early signs of shoulder dysfunction. These findings highlight the importance of assessing posterior humeral head translation in athletes reporting discomfort,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased plasma concentrations of acyl-coenzyme A binding protein (ACBP) predict future lung cancer development in smokers at risk of cardiovascular disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings independently validate ACBP/DBI as a circulating biomarker of future LC development in at-risk individuals. Clinically, ACBP/DBI quantification could refine risk-adapted lung cancer screening strategies, guiding the frequency of low-dose CT scans and identifying candidates for preventive interventions, including potential ACBP/DBI-neutralizing therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anisometropia in bilateral hyperopic refractive amblyopia requires eye patching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of perioperative chemotherapy-mediated genomic changes in gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41291443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251126142055&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonclassical Two-Stage Pathways for the Formation of Amorphous Ferric Arsenate: Influence of Temperature, pH, and Stoichiometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amorphous ferric arsenate (AFA) is a vital sink of arsenic in acidic, As-rich environments. Although its properties and transformation into scorodite are well-documented, the precipitation process of AFA remains understudied. The present study investigates the precipitation kinetics of AFA in relation to pH, As/Fe ratio, and temperature using both in situ and ex situ techniques. In situ small-angle X-ray scattering revealed a two-stage AFA formation process irrespective of the controlled...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design and Preclinical Evaluation of First <sup>68</sup>Ga-Labeled Cathepsin D-Targeted Radiotracers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cathepsin D (CTSD), a lysosomal aspartic protease linked to cancer progression and poor patient outcomes, is underexplored as a diagnostic biomarker. This study developed the first CTSD-targeted radiotracers, identifying [^(68)Ga]Ga-NOTA-FZCD-3 as optimal due to its strong binding to CTSD (dissociation constant = 0.65 μM), rapid clearance from the body (elimination half-life = 16.61 min), and high tumor-specific uptake in mouse models. Imaging analysis revealed that tumors with higher CTSD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of Cross-Domain Chirality Transfer in Chiral Triblock Copolymers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The formation of the helical phase from the self-assembly of chiral diblock copolymers is attributed to the twisting and shifting of the microphase-separated domain. With the introduction of midblock in-between achiral and chiral blocks, the mechanism of twisting and shifting would be steered by the capability of cross-domain chirality transfer from the chiral block. This work aims to systematically investigate the cross-domain chirality transfer by synthesizing a variety of chiral diblock...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Piperlongumine Inhibits OSCC Epithelial-Mesenchymal Transition and Promotes Tumor Cell Apoptosis by Targeting TrxR1 to Activate ROS and Its Related Pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Piperlongumine (PL), a naturally occurring alkaloid isolated from Piper longum fruit, has been shown to selectively toxinate a variety of tumor cells. However, PL has received less attention when it comes to oral squamous cell carcinoma (OSCC), and its precise effects and mechanisms have not been completely clarified. We verified that thioredoxin reductase 1 (TrxR1) is highly expressed in OSCC cell lines and cancer tissues of OSCC patients; PL inhibited TrxR1 activity in a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Semaglutide on Insulin Sensitivity and Cardiometabolic Risk Factors in Adolescents With Obesity: The STEP TEENS Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These novel data support semaglutide 2.4 mg as an efficacious obesity treatment in adolescents with obesity and advance its application by showing associated improvements in insulin sensitivity, glycemic measures, ALT, and other cardiometabolic risk factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective Respiratory Motion Correction Using Machine Learning and Pilot Tone (PROMPT) in Cardiac MRI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed respiratory motion correction approach was successfully implemented. The LSTM-based predictive model outperformed linear and polynomial regression models. In LGE imaging, PROMPT significantly reduced in-plane motion and showed potential for limiting through-plane motion compared to the clinical protocol.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pyroptosis modulates multiple immune cell populations in targeted therapy-treated melanoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Treatment of melanoma with BRAF inhibitors plus MEK inhibitors (BRAFi + MEKi) stimulates an intratumoral immune response, in part through pyroptosis mediated by the pore-forming protein gasdermin E (GSDME/Gsdme). How GSDME mediates effects on tumoral immunity is not well characterized. Using single-cell RNA-sequencing (scRNA-seq) and flow cytometry in BRAFi + MEKi treated melanoma, we show herein that isogenic Gsdme knockout (KO) tumors show decreased infiltration with T cells, natural killer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zeroing in on Firearm Injury Prevention Efforts-Practice and Policy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal Use of Integrase Strand Transfer Inhibitors During Pregnancy and Infant Neurodevelopment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study, infants exposed in utero to INSTI-based ART regimens had mean neurodevelopmental scores similar to those for infants exposed to PI-based regimens but lower than those for infants exposed to NNRTI-based regimens, particularly when their mothers initiated ART after conception. Notably, adjusted mean cognitive domain scores for INSTI-exposed infants were close to the expected population mean of 100, while NNRTI-exposed infants scored 4 to 5 points...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergency Department Utilization by Veterans for Low-Acuity Conditions After Virtual Care Expansion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cross-sectional, national study of ED visits within the VA, low-acuity utilization declined following the expansion of virtual care; however, evidence of direct substitution was not detected. These findings highlight shifting care patterns within the VA and underscore the need for further research on quality, access, and system-level outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preference Card Optimization-Promise and Practical Considerations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smoking and Failure to Rescue From Pulmonary Complications After Lung Resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinicopathological Implications of Maspin, CD8, and PD-L1 Expression in Liposarcomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liposarcomas, the most common subtype of soft tissue sarcomas, show variable biological behavior and therapeutic response. Programmed death-ligand 1 (PD-L1) and cytotoxic T lymphocyte marker CD8 have been implicated in tumor immune evasion and prognosis in various malignancies, while Maspin, a tumor suppressor, has shown a negative prognostic impact in sarcomas. This study aimed to investigate the clinicopathological significance of PD-L1, CD8, and Maspin expression in liposarcomas. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interconnected Mechanistic Pathways, Molecular Biomarkers, and Therapeutic Approach of Oral Cancer in Patients with Diabetes Mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The complex bidirectional relationship between diabetes mellitus (DM) and oral cancer (OC) denotes that metabolic dysfunction and malignancy intersect at molecular, cellular, and systemic levels. This state-of-the-art review analyzes the most recent literature data on the multiple interconnected pathways linking DM and OC, including hyperinsulinemia/IGF-1 signaling, chronic hyperglycemia-induced cellular damage, persistent inflammation, immune dysfunction, and oral microbiota dysbiosis. These...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiosensitization Effect of PARP Inhibitor Talazoparib Involves Decreasing Mitochondrial Membrane Potential and Induction of Cellular Senescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Poly (ADP-ribose) polymerase (PARP) inhibitors (PARPis) with radiation therapy can enhance the sensitivity of cancer cells by inhibiting DNA repair pathways. To determine the most suitable PARP inhibitor for radiosensitization in cancer cells, we compared various types of clinically used PARPis in lung cancer A549 cells. We found that most PARP inhibitors showed radiosensitization effects on A549 cells. ER10 values for talazoparib, olaparib rucaparib, ABT888 and niraparib were 1.5, 1.8, 2.8,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in Multi-Omics Research on Biomarkers of Intrahepatic Cholangiocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intrahepatic cholangiocarcinoma (iCCA) is a rare yet aggressive malignancy characterized by late-stage diagnosis and poor prognosis. Recent advancements in multi-omics technologies have significantly enhanced the understanding of the molecular features and complex biological mechanisms of iCCA. These approaches have revealed disease molecular heterogeneity and identified biomarkers linked to disease progression, patient prognosis, and therapeutic outcomes. This review synthesizes findings from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41296409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251126142056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>