<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 19:22:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hexoctahedron in a Nanoframe: Tailoring Stationary and Open Nanogaps for Single-Particle Surface-Enhanced Raman Scattering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plasmonic nanostructures with sharp features and nanogaps have been of immense interest in surface-enhanced Raman scattering (SERS) applications due to their strong hot spots generated at such morphological features. Here, we report a synthetic route to produce Au hexoctahedron-in-a-nanoframe structures (Au HIAFs), in which the high-curvature vertices of the Au hexoctahedral nanocrystal core fit tightly into the frame corners without the aid of an anchoring linker, realizing stationary, open...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroprotective Effects of PEP-1-PGAM5 via the Attenuation of Oxidative Stress and Apoptosis in Parkinson's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parkinson's disease (PD) is driven by mitochondrial impairment and oxidative stress-induced dopaminergic cell death. Phosphoglycerate mutase 5 (PGAM5) augmented accelerating mitophagy and attenuating neuronal apoptosis. Here, we present a novel cell-penetrating PEP-1-PGAM5 fusion protein designed to suppress oxidative damage and apoptosis. We assessed its transduction efficiency and neuroprotective efficacy in vitro and in vivo. PEP-1-PGAM5 was efficiently transduced into SH-SY5Y cells without...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Determines Personality Impressions of Synthetic and Natural Voices? The Effects of Voice Quality and Intonation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study investigated how acoustic and phonetic characteristics of synthetic and natural voices affect personality impressions of the voices. To this end, we conducted a personality rating experiment in which 30 native Korean speakers judged the perceived personality of natural Korean utterances and their synthetic counterparts (voice clones) using the Big-Five personality model. Various acoustic parameters, including measures of voice quality, F0, and articulation rate, were then...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia Care Research and Psychosocial Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Successful implementation of an ACAD study depends on several factors including close collaboration with participants, community recruiters, data collectors, clinicians, and biological sample handling to ensure that any data collection times and locations are participant friendly. This pilot study offered new insight into Alzheimer's disease and related dementia studies with Korean American older adults including the feasibility of community engaged recruitment and data collection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Doping-Enabled Symmetry Control in BaCoO<sub>3</sub> for Enhanced Oxygen Reduction Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stabilizing crystal structure is a powerful route to unlock new functionalities in perovskite oxides. BaCoO(3) (BCO) derivatives are a versatile platform for designing mixed ionic-electronic conductors for solid oxide fuel cell (SOFC) cathodes, yet their stable hexagonal structure limits performance unless transformed into the cubic perovskite phase. Here, seven compositions are systematically investigated -undoped BCO and Sc-, Y-, Zr-, Hf-, Nb-, and Ta-doped variants-and show that the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlated Dual-Gradient Electrodes Enabling Spatially Synchronized Sulfur Redox in High-Mass-Loading Li-S Batteries Under High Current Densities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The practical deployment of Li-S batteries is hindered by sluggish redox kinetics and poor ion transport in high-mass-loading sulfur cathodes, especially under fast-charging and high-power-density conditions. Conventional electrocatalyst-based strategies partially mitigate electrochemical polarization by lowering reaction energy barriers but fail to address concentration and ohmic polarization, which become more pronounced in thick electrodes. Here, a coupled material-architecture approach is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A subnanolitre tetherless optoelectronic microsystem for chronic neural recording in awake mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The long-term recording of neural activity could be used to understand complex behaviours and disorders. However, the development of technology capable of such measurements faces a variety of technical challenges, including the relative motion between recording electrodes and tissue and the excessive displaced volume from implanted electronics. Here we report a subnanolitre-volume tetherless optoelectronic microsystem for neural recording. The system relies on light for photovoltaic power and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exosome enrichment from human serum using polyethylene glycol precipitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exosomes, nanosized extracellular vesicles that play key roles in intercellular communication, have great potential in diagnostic and therapeutic applications. However, isolating exosomes from complex biological matrices such as human serum remains challenging due to limitations in scalability, cost, and purity of current methods. In this study, we developed and optimized a polyethylene glycol (PEG) precipitation method as a cost-effective alternative to the commercial ExoQuick kit for efficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wearable Soft Ionic Tactile Controller for Virtual Reality: Decoupling Normal and Shear Forces without Motion Artifacts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[When soft wearable electronic devices are deployed on the body, body motion-induced artifacts pose a major challenge for accurately decoupling concurrent stimuli such as normal, shear forces, and elongational strain. This study introduces an ion-based multimodal sensor architecture augmented by machine learning algorithms to effectively differentiate the stimuli and compensate for motion-induced signal artifacts. By integrating a tailored sensor design with advanced algorithmic processing, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[REporting Guidelines for aCupuncture-Related AdverSe Event Case Reports (RECASE): Elaboration and Explanation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Case reports represent the earliest form of scientific literature to identify and describe adverse events (AEs) associated with medical interventions, and they still represent important educational resources for ensuring the safe practice of such interventions. Although case reports on AEs related to acupuncture continue to be published, detailed information about the acupuncture procedure is often insufficiently reported in these studies, which may introduce an overstatement or exaggeration of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia Care Research and Psychosocial Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight the moderating effects of extraversion and neuroticism on the relationship between dementia severity and caregiver burden, with higher extraversion buffering and higher neuroticism amplifying the burden. Additionally, BPSD severity strongly predicted caregiver distress, independent of personality traits. These results underscore the need to incorporate personality assessments into caregiver support programs to address individual differences and improve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drug Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among various task combinations, the combination of Task_1+Task_2+Task_3 consistently achieved the best results, with Task 3 being included in all high-performance combinations. Feature importance analysis and target variable distribution further emphasized the greater contribution of acoustic features compared to linguistic features in classification performance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basic Science and Pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings demonstrate that CU71 treatment ameliorates cognitive impairment by inhibiting BBB dysfunction and neuroinflammation in the 5XFAD mouse model of Alzheimer's disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Efficient methods of isolation and purification of extracellular vesicles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A swine model for surgical training in various types of robotic liver resection with surgical videos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This swine-based educational model provides a practical, high-fidelity, and reproducible environment for structured RLR training. When integrated with instructional surgical videos, it offers a comprehensive educational tool that supports early-career surgeons in achieving proficiency in robotic liver surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rice OsFKF1 Promotes Degradation of OsPRR37 for Short-Day Early Flowering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma NFL, GFAP, sTREM2, pTau231, and clinical severity in progressive supranuclear palsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated the feasibility of using four plasma markers simultaneously to determine PSP disease severity. To verify these findings, longitudinal analyses are necessary.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Paeony root prevents 6-hydroxydopamine-induced neurotoxicity by regulating autophagic dysfunction via AKT signaling in Parkinson's disease models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parkinson's disease (PD) is a neurodegenerative disease that primarily affects motor function. Dopaminergic cell death occurs progressively in the PD brain and autophagic dysfunction is critically implicated in the neuronal death. Therefore, modulating impaired autophagic flux is a promising strategy to treat dopaminergic neurodegeneration, addressing the unmet needs in PD. This study aimed to investigate efficacy and the underlying mechanism of Paeonia lactiflora extract (PLE) focusing on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prefrontal hypoactivity correlates with immediate extinction deficit following Pavlovian fear conditioning with a chasing threat]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is motor weakness in cervical radiculopathy an indication for surgery? Analysis of risk factors for poor recovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Most patients with motor weakness due to cervical radiculopathy recovered functional strength (≥ 4) within 2-3 months of conservative treatment. However, older age, severe initial motor deficits, and persistent pain were associated with a higher risk of incomplete recovery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Intensivist Authority on End-of-Life Practices in a Korean PICU]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Timely end-of-life decision-making is critical for ensuring quality care in the pediatric intensive care unit (PICU). We evaluated the impact of intensivist-led care on the timing and structure of end-of-life (EOL) practices. We retrospectively reviewed 39 PICU deaths over a 3-year period at a tertiary care hospital. Patients were categorized into pre-intensivist (no intensivist), passive-intensivist (intensivist without authority), and active-intensivist (intensivists with full decision-making...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fetal outcomes of antiseizure medication use during pregnancy: A nationwide retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: This study aims to evaluate the effect of maternal antiseizure medication (ASM) exposure on fetal malformations, accounting for specific periods of medication use during pregnancy and differentiating between monotherapy and dual therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Regardless of scoring method, global cognitive composites were similarly related to validity indicators of cognition/functioning and structural neuroimaging in a harmonized sample. MMSE(Composite) showed the strongest relationships with CDR but was less strongly associated with frontal lobe volume. Composites demonstrated stronger relationships with structural neuroimaging compared to standalone measures. Future work aims to evaluate similarities and differences between cohorts and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results highlight the potential of a digital twin neural marker to address the complexities of delineating mixed dementia etiologies. Most importantly, this work represents an international collaboration (Korea-UK) to develop a digital twin neural marker using large datasets while upholding data democracy principles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Head-to-head comparison between vibration-controlled transient elastography and histology in predicting liver-related events due to metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this large MASLD cohort, LSM by VCTE showed comparable prognostic accuracy to histology. As a non-invasive tool, LSM may serve as an alternative surrogate endpoint in clinical trials.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drug Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The scopolamine-induced cognitive impairment model demonstrated domain-specific deficits with task- and dose-dependent treatment responses. These findings emphasize the need for optimization and task refinement to enhance model reliability. Structuring these tasks into a comprehensive multi-domain battery could provide a robust preclinical platform for evaluating potential therapeutics and advancing our understanding of dementia's cognitive complexities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of Nivolumab Plus Ipilimumab After Atezolizumab Plus Bevacizumab in Advanced HCC: An International Multicentre Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nivo/Ipi demonstrated meaningful clinical activity in patients with advanced HCC, even after Ate/Bev failure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study confirmed the safety and efficacy of more frequent and extensive bilateral frontal BBB opening over multiple sessions in patients with AD. Furthermore, this is the first clinical trial to demonstrate improvement in neuropsychiatric symptoms through BBB opening alone, without concurrent administration of antibody medications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SILA produces a valid estimate of time-from-amyloid positivity in ADAD. This work allows for disease stage in ADAD to be compared to staging for broad forms of AD, which was not previously possible using EYO. However, this work also illustrates that there is a high degree of heterogeneity in preclinical disease duration that is not explained by amyloid alone.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved graft positioning and reduced extrusion using the bone-plug technique compared to the bone-bridge technique in lateral meniscal allograft transplantation: A comparative magnetic resonance imaging-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The bone-plug technique for lateral MAT showed improved graft positioning, reduced extrusion and shorter operative time compared with the bone-bridge technique, while achieving similar clinical outcomes, healing rates and osteoarthritis progression. Thus, it could be an effective and technically efficient alternative to lateral MAT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Benchmarking Protein Nanoparticles for Drug Delivery and Clinical Translation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein nanoparticles (PNs) are emerging as versatile, biocompatible platforms for drug delivery, leveraging their intrinsic biodegradability, molecular specificity, and structural tunability. They improve drug stability, prolong circulation, and enable targeted delivery, making them promising in cancer nanomedicine. This review classifies PNs into native-ordered, native-amorphous, and denatured categories, each distinguished by unique assembly strategies and pharmacokinetic behaviors. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical Threshold-Guided Harvesting of Microalgal Therapeutics via Designer Nanovesicles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microalgae encapsulate extensive concentrations of bioactive metabolites within structurally recalcitrant cell walls that impede conventional extraction methodologies. Here we demonstrate a biomimetic strategy that exploits cellular elasticity to generate microalgae-derived nanovesicles (MNVs) with preserved therapeutic functionality. Using representative microalgae species with distinct wall architectures, we establish through atomic force microscopy and micropipette aspiration that vesicle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Near-Infrared Ratiometric Fluorescent Probe for Monitoring Hypochlorous Acid in Ferroptosis Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferroptosis is an iron-dependent, regulated cell death caused by the disruption of the oxidation-reduction balance. The hypochlorous acid (HClO) levels are closely correlated with the onset and progress of ferroptosis. Hence, investigating the underlying relationships between HClO changes and ferroptosis is particularly vital. To this end, we presented a new near-infrared (NIR) ratiometric fluorescent probe (BV-HD) based on the oxidation of the phenothiazine moiety for imaging HClO variations in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomineralization-mimicking cooperative assembly for tailoring anisotropic hierarchically porous metal-organic frameworks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anisotropic hierarchically porous metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) with asymmetric morphologies hold great promise for improving the utilization efficiency of the MOF matrix, thereby expanding their applicability. However, imparting MOFs with precisely controlled porous architectures and morphologies remains challenging. Here, an ingenious soft/hard matter phase transition co-mediated assembly strategy is developed to mimic the biomineralization process for synthesizing anisotropic UiO-66-NH(2)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International Benchmark Values for Robotic Right Hepatectomy: Multicenter Study From 22 Expert Centers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This international benchmark study on robotic right hepatectomy (RRH) demonstrates that the robotic approach provides advantages compared with laparoscopic and open RH. RRH can be expected to become the minimally invasive approach of choice for tumors in the right liver.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multi-Country Study of the Clinical Course of Extensive-Stage Small Cell Lung Cancer: A Six-Study Analysis of Real-World Treatment Patterns and Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In our evaluation of real-world treatment patterns and outcomes among patients with ES-SCLC from six countries, we found that rwOS in 1L, 2L and 3L was consistently poor across countries, despite differences in patient characteristics and treatment patterns. These findings may support the generalizability of clinical evidence across geographies and highlight the need for further research to optimize treatment strategies to improve patient outcomes globally.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mother-child conversations and coping strategies as antecedents of children's recall accuracy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Considering that the level of stress during a distressing event can decrease children's abilities to encode and store event-related information, and thereby their recall accuracy of the event, it is imperative to identify factors that can reduce the risk of high stress. This study explored cascading relations from mother-child conversations to children's strategies for coping with stress to their recall accuracy regarding dental treatment to examine antecedents of recall accuracy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Full-face aesthetic treatment with onabotulinumtoxin A: Results from a retrospective real world analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Full-face onabotulinumtoxinA was effective in reducing facial lines and improving overall symmetry and jawline contour, with high levels of patient satisfaction, and a favorable safety profile.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Attentional responses to the color exposure sequence of landscape paintings: evidence from fNIRS and eye-tracking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Color is a critical determinant of esthetic experience, shaping both immersion and cognitive responses. However, the extent to which the sequence of color exposure modulates the interplay between neural activation and ocular behavior remains insufficiently understood.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between drinking initiation age and problematic smart device use: A large-scale nationwide survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diverse Cation Exchange in Layered Titanate Nanostructures for Tailored Catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Layered titanates (LTs) offer exceptional structural and chemical tunability, enabling precise modulation of their electronic states and catalytic properties. However, systematic studies on the range of cations that can serve as intercalants for LTs remain limited, and conventional synthesis methods often require additional treatments for cation intercaltion. In this study, we present a cation-free H^(+) (H(3)O^(+))-intercalated LT as a versatile platform for direct cation insertion. This LT can...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study demonstrates that the automatic classification of ADCI and DLBCI using speech is highly promising for large-scale screening of patients for clinical trials and interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights the potential modifiable factors influencing CR in EOAD patients, suggesting that enhancing leisure activities could improve CR in EOAD patients. These findings can inform strategies for dementia prevention and provide a foundation for further research into CR in EOAD patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating Role Challenges in School Healthcare Partnerships With Families: A Qualitative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study underscores health teachers' pivotal role in T1D management and the challenges they face. Institutional support, professional development, and strengthened collaboration between health teachers and parents are essential. These findings could inform the development of web-based partnership programs to enhance T1D care in schools.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Variations in digit span performance across languages illustrate the role of linguistic and numerical factors in cognitive assessments, even with tests targeting non-language domains using digit stimuli. These findings underscore the critical value of language diversity in cognitive research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We evaluated the correlation between GFAP and p-tau levels in human blood using a magnetic bead-based electrochemical sensor for AD diagnosis. We could determine the extent of astrocyte activation in individuals with NC, MCI, and AD using a GFAP protein. Moreover, the cross-validation of the impedance change rates indicates that the AUC value for the multi-biomarkers is superior to that of a single biomarker. Successful validation of a point-of-care platform for blood biomarkers such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone Marrow Failure as an Underrecognized Feature of KAT6A Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[KAT6A syndrome (Arboleda-Tham syndrome) is a rare disorder caused by heterozygous pathogenic variants in KAT6A, a histone acetyltransferase essential for chromatin remodeling and hematopoietic stem cell function. While neurodevelopmental features are well established, hematologic manifestations are underrecognized. We describe two pediatric patients from Canada and Korea who developed severe bone marrow failure and were successfully treated with hematopoietic stem cell transplantation. One...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regional and Cell-Type-Specific Activation of YAP/TAZ Underlies Glial Responses in LPS-Induced Neuroinflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Yes-associated protein (YAP) and transcriptional coactivator with PDZ-binding motif (TAZ), core effectors of the Hippo pathway, are emerging as mechanosensitive regulators of inflammation and tissue repair. However, their roles in neuroinflammation remain poorly understood. Here, we investigated the spatial and temporal expression of YAP/TAZ in glial cells under lipopolysaccharide (LPS)-induced neuroinflammation in mice. Immunofluorescence revealed selective upregulation and nuclear...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the letter to the editor: Effectiveness of intradiscal steroid injection for spinal stenosis: a retrospective cohort study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unpaired Learning-Enabled Nanotube Identification from AFM Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanotubes, particularly single-walled carbon nanotubes (SWCNTs), represent an important class of materials with valuable electrical, mechanical, and thermal properties. However, accurate characterization of nanotube network morphologies remains a significant challenge. We present a deep learning-based approach for extracting nanotube morphologies from atomic force microscopy (AFM) images utilizing an image-to-image (I2I) translation framework based on cycleGAN with a specialized loss function...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia Care Research and Psychosocial Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings demonstrate that animal fluency tasks may elicit culturally-distinct retrieval patterns in AD, consistent with previous findings in stroke aphasia. Culture-specific categories reflecting East Asian features were more strongly linked to cognitive decline in Korean-AD, suggesting that culturally-sensitive analyses of verbal fluency offer valuable clinical insights.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrostatic Ion Trapping in Organic Electrochemical Transistors for Record Neuromorphic Memory Performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic electrochemical transistors (OECTs) leverage the chemical tunability of polymeric semiconductors; however, their potential as memory devices remains constrained by insufficient ion retention. Previous studies on physical trapping of ions within polymer crystalline domains have generally reported memory windows below 5.3 V. Here, we achieve molecular-level hysteresis control by designing a dual-functional zwitterionic crosslinker that creates an electrostatic ion-trapping channel. Its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A deep learning-based pachychoroid index based on choroidal image patterns of central serous chorioretinopathy using enhanced-depth-imaging optical coherence tomography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: HUPI, a quantitative index of imaging patterns of pachychoroid, demonstrated a high ability to discriminate pachychoroid from normal eyes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intravitreal aflibercept 8 mg in patients from Japan with neovascular age-related macular degeneration: 48-week subgroup analysis of the PULSAR trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Aflibercept 8 mg has similar efficacy and safety to aflibercept 2 mg when administered at extended dosing intervals in both the Japan and non-Japan subgroups, consistent with the overall PULSAR results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cancer epidemiology in rare and hereditary colorectal diseases 2) anal canal cancer (cancer statistics)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In Japan, adenocarcinoma was the predominant type of ACC, while SCC was less common. However, the characteristics of HPV-associated SCC were similar to those observed in Western countries. Standardization of classification and staging criteria and the expansion of HPV vaccination may be essential to improve clinical management and facilitate international comparisons.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing electrode spacing of a pentaspline pulsed field ablation catheter for high-precision 3D mapping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Garland 1-11-1 mm configuration with Field Scaling provided the most accurate geometric concordance with CT anatomy. Optimized catheter display and FS correction can improve mapping fidelity and procedural safety in pulsed field ablation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comparison of poly(methyl methacrylate) and silorane-based cements as carriers for local doxorubicin delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orthopedic osteosarcomas and metastatic lesions can be difficult to treat with systemically delivered chemotherapy agents alone. Following removal of the primary tumor, implantation of cement to fill the lesion is often done to stabilize weight-bearing bones. One of the commonly used treatments to address osteosarcoma is systemic delivery of doxorubicin. Therefore, research on the incorporation and release of efficacious doxorubicin for local delivery from cement is important. Poly(methyl...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute effects of flossing band application on hamstring muscle mechanical properties and stretch tolerance: a randomized controlled crossover trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NGS and the design of an optimized phage display workflow for peptide discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phage display is a powerful technology that has demonstrated great potential in identifying peptides with high binding affinity and specificity toward a broad spectrum of biological targets. The undesired enrichment of nonspecific binders remains a major challenge in phage display selection. The integration of next-generation sequencing (NGS) into phage display has expanded the horizons of ligand discovery by significantly enhancing our ability to interrogate the massive sequence space of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Poor growth in multi-ethnic children with food allergy in Amsterdam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Children with FA, particularly those with asthma and non-IgE-mediated CMA, had lower Z-scores for BMI and weight as compared to Dutch growth references. Length gradually deteriorated from 5 to 11 months onwards, which stabilized around age three.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Accurate and Efficient Reaction Path Search with Iteratively Trained Neural Network Potential: Answering the Passerini Mechanism Controversy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Automated reaction path search based on quantum chemical calculations enables the construction of reaction path networks with minimal prior knowledge. When combined with kinetic simulation on the obtained network, essential mechanistic insights can be extracted to better understand and eventually design novel chemical reactions. However, the computational cost of such calculations can become a major obstacle, depending on the level of theory required for the exploration of reaction paths, such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The future of clinical trials? Monitoring mobility as an outcome measure in Parkinson's disease: The mobilise-D study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundA key challenge in trials targeting disease modification in Parkinson's disease (PD) is the lack of sensitive, precise, and patient-relevant outcome measures. Digital mobility outcomes (DMOs), captured using body-worn devices, offer a novel, objective means to assess real-world gait and mobility-domains often impaired early in PD. The Mobilise-D consortium was established to develop and validate DMOs in PD and other conditions.ObjectiveTo describe DMOs in a large, representative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crosstalk between the ribosome quality control-associated E3 ubiquitin ligases LTN1 and RNF10]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During gene expression, ribosome stalling frequently occurs and can lead to detrimental effects on cellular homeostasis. Several quality control mechanisms, including ribosome-associated quality control (RQC) and nonfunctional ribosomal RNA decay (NRD), have been identified to resolve these aberrant translation events. While the molecular mechanisms of each pathway have been extensively characterized, the mechanisms underlying the mutual regulation of the expression of pathway factors remain to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic regulation of the chloroplast SUFBC2D complex by SUFB and CLP protease in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chloroplast iron-sulfur (Fe-S) clusters, essential cofactors for Fe-S proteins, are assembled by the SUFBC2D complex, but their biogenesis regulation remains unclear. We show that during leaf senescence, SUFB transcription rapidly increases while SUFC/SUFD transcripts and the abundance of all three SUF proteins remain unchanged. Leaf necrosis with green color occurs solely upon SUFB RNA interference (RNAi) is induced, and the decrease of SUFs is obviously faster in SUFB-RNAi than SUFC-RNAi...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerebrospinal fluid proteome alterations related to depressive symptoms in cognitive decline and Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The identified proteome alterations may reflect shared biological mechanisms involved in both AD and depression in older people.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FastSurfer parcellation accuracy after lesion filling in moderate-to-severe traumatic brain injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Focal lesions in T1-weighted (T1-w) magnetic resonance images (MRIs) of patients with moderate-to-severe traumatic brain injury (ms-TBI) can introduce errors during image processing. We tested whether errors in FastSurfer cortical parcellation could be reduced using lesion filling (virtual brain grafting (VBG)).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health inequalities and trends in heart failure diagnosis in primary care in England, 2000-21: a national retrospective cohort data-linkage study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Heart failure is often diagnosed during unplanned admission to hospital, which is associated with poor outcomes. The aim of this study was to examine the potential for early heart failure identification in primary care, trends in diagnostic practices, sociodemographic inequalities, and the association between diagnostic pathways and outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heteroaryl iminothioindoxyl (HA-ITI) photoswitches <em>via</em> regioselective aza-Wittig synthesis: unifying red-shifted absorption, large <em>E</em>/<em>Z</em> band separation, and tunable thermal recovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein we introduce heteroaryl-substituted iminothioindoxyl (HA-ITI) photoswitches featuring N-heterocyclic moieties based on indole or benzimidazole. A regioselective aza-Wittig reaction of thioisatin, previously unexplored for the synthesis of imino-based photoswitches, enabled the obtention of HA-ITI derivatives and provides an alternative and versatile synthetic access to similar analogues. HA-ITIs undergo blue light-induced Z → E photoisomerization, followed by very fast thermal E → Z back...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoregulation of the Chiral Nematic Phase by Using a Hexa-Arylazopyrazole-Substituted Co(III) Complex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A photoresponsive hexa-arylazopyrazole-substituted tris-(β-diketonato) Co-(III) complex was synthesized, and the Λ- and Δ-enantiomers were isolated. The complex shows reversible E/Z isomerization using UV (λ(max) = 365 nm) and visible light (λ(max) = 520 nm), respectively. Using the Co-(III) complex as a dopant in the commercially available liquid crystal N-(4-methoxybenzylidene)-4-butylaniline (MBBA), the chiral nematic phase can be induced. Upon photoisomerization, the helical pitch of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dramatic clearance of periorbital lupus miliaris disseminatus faciei with tapinarof 1% cream]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41451029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Late-Stage Native Peptide Modification Approach to the Total Synthesis of Koshidacins A and B]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, the total synthesis of the antimalarial natural products, koshidacins A and B, is disclosed. We developed an inverse peptide elongation sequence to elaborate the linear tetrapeptide by leveraging a soluble hydrophobic tag (TCbz group) for liquid-phase peptide synthesis. The key advances involve head-to-tail macrocyclization to provide the carrier-supported cyclic tetrapeptide and photoinduced deaminative alkylation to edit the native peptide residue that enabled us to construct the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methane Synthesis from CO<sub>2</sub> and Ammonia over Supported Ni Catalyst via Isocyanate-Mediated Mechanism: Toward Carbon-Neutral Fuel Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Methane (CH(4)) synthesis using carbon dioxide (CO(2)) and green hydrogen (H(2)) is a promising means of increasing CO(2) utilization for the development of a more sustainable society. To mitigate the difficulties associated with the handling of H(2), ammonia (NH(3)) has been suggested as a suitable hydrogen carrier, meaning highly active catalysts for the one-step synthesis of carbon-neutral CH(4) from CO(2) and green NH(3) (CO(2) + NH(3) methanation) are needed. Here we show that supported Ni...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-Enduring Proteomic Fidelity in Over 30-Year-Old FFPE Tissues: Distinct Proteomic Signatures of Hepatocellular Carcinoma and Adjacent Non-Tumor Liver Tissue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Formalin-fixed paraffin-embedded (FFPE) tissues are crucial clinical archives linked with long-term follow-up data, yet the suitability of deep proteomic analysis on samples stored over 30 years remains largely unexplored. This study aimed to verify the feasibility of deep proteomic analysis on extremely long-term stored FFPE samples. We employed adaptive focused acoustics (AFA) technology for efficient protein extraction, combined with SP3 cleanup and data-independent acquisition (DIA) mass...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tellurophene-Induced Triplet-Singlet Spin-Flip Acceleration: An Advanced Design for Narrowband Organoboron Emitters with Fast Reverse Intersystem Crossing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organoboron narrowband emitters leveraging the multi-resonance (MR) effect have emerged as key material components for wide-color-gamut organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs) that offer high efficiency and excellent color reproducibility. However, conventional MR-type thermally activated delayed fluorescence (MR-TADF) emitters suffer from severe efficiency roll-off in OLEDs operated at high brightness due to slow reverse intersystem crossing (RISC). Here, we report the first MR-TADF emitters...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical efficacy of apalutamide in Asian patients with metastatic castration-sensitive prostate cancer: Bayesian reanalysis of the TITAN trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This analysis provides strengthened evidence that apalutamide plus ADT offers meaningful clinical benefit for Asian patients with mCSPC. Moreover, our findings support more informed and individualized clinical decision-making, helping clinicians communicate expected outcomes more clearly during shared decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physiological functions of seminal vesicle secretions in male fertility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In many mammals, accessory gland secretions are ejaculated into the female reproductive tract, along with sperm, and the prostates and seminal vesicles are the main glands responsible for these secretions. Cauda epididymal sperm can efficiently fertilize eggs in vitro; however, we found that seminal vesicle secretions improved sperm fertilization rates in vivo by artificial insemination. Furthermore, using the seminal vesicle-removed mice, other studies have shown that seminal vesicle secretions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41450194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Composition and nutritional role of gut microbiota on growth performance of pigs at different growth stages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study has investigated the relationship between the gut microbiota compotision and the growth performance in pigs from birth to the finishing stage, focusing on nutrient metabolism. Of 59 crossbred pigs [(Landrace × Large Yorkshire) × Duroc] from seven sows, individuals with high and low daily gain (DG) were assigned to high DG (HDG, n = 11) and low DG (LDG, n = 8) groups. Fecal samples collected at weaning (21 days), growing (95-106 days) and finishing (136-152 days) stages were analyzed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overt and covert processing of self-relevance information in dissociative identity disorder: controlled fMRI study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The present study showed increased cognitive control during overt self-relevant knowledge processing in the trauma-avoidant identity state of DID, in line with previous research. The slower reaction times and increased frontoparietal activation shown in individuals with diagnosed DID, as compared with both control groups, support the notion of cognitive avoidance of trauma-related information in DID and further reinforce the authenticity of DID experiences.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic nutritional index predicts the prognostic impact of avelumab maintenance therapy in patients with advanced urothelial carcinoma: results from the Chu-shikoku Japan Urological Consortium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pretreatment low PNI was associated with poor survival outcome in avelumab maintenance therapy. This finding provides support for the potential role of PNI as a prognostic factor of avelumab maintenance therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide analysis of olfactory neuroblastoma in Japan: evolving treatment approaches and prognostic outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Endoscopic surgery for ONB rose substantially, while younger age and female sex were associated with better OS, and postoperative radiotherapy was correlated with improved RFS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41449573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UHRMS Formula Assignment: Diophantine-Based Recalibration Yields Lorentzian Mass Error Distribution as the Limiting Factor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultrahigh-resolution mass spectrometry (UHRMS) is a well-established analytical method for characterizing complex molecular mixtures. It is usually performed with Fourier transform techniques, based either on ion cyclotron resonance (FTICR-MS) or mass-dependent oscillations in an ion trap (FT-Orbitrap-MS). In spite of the high technical level of these instruments, often spectral interpretation remains difficult, in particular in a nontargeted approach of complex samples. Here, we introduce a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ni-Based Alloy Catalysts for Liquid Organic Hydrogen Storage: Mechanistic Insights from First-Principles Calculations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of high-efficiency dehydrogenation catalysts for methylcyclohexane, a key medium for liquid organic hydrogen storage, is crucial for advancing the hydrogen economy. This study systematically investigates the dehydrogenation performance of methylcyclohexane (MCH) by DFT calculations, including eight types of Ni(x)Rh(y) surface and bulk alloys along with six Ni(3)M(1) (M = Ru, Rh, Pd, Os, Ir, or Pt) alloy catalysts. The study reveals that the optimal catalytic activity is achieved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Theoretical and Experimental Assessment of the Absorption and Dual Emission of Benzobisthiadiazole Conjugated Oligoelectrolyte Probes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The conjugated oligoelectrolyte COE-BBT and its neutral form, BBT-Br, are probes based on benzobisthiadiazole and thiophene-stilbene units with near-infrared emissions. Upon photoexcitation, these compounds exhibit a second emission band, suggesting anti-Kasha character of their fluorescence. Here, we disclose theoretical evidence in support of the non-Kasha behavior of BBT probes. We employ time-dependent density functional theory (TD-DFT) and nonadiabatic molecular dynamics to simulate and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia Care Research and Psychosocial Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: It is critical to understand the perspectives and challenges of caregivers who play a primary role in the diagnosis and care of individuals with FTD. These findings highlight the importance of raising public awareness regarding early symptoms of FTD. Continued FTD education efforts among healthcare professionals may also help to advance the early and accurate diagnosis of FTD and increase the support provided to caregivers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-Reported Outcomes Across Treatment Strategies in Papillary Thyroid Microcarcinoma: A Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This systematic review and meta-analysis found that patients whose PTMC was managed with active surveillance reported equal or better HRQOL than those undergoing surgery. These findings support the importance of incorporating PROs into shared decision-making for low-risk thyroid cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of Patient-Centered Lung Cancer Screening: The MyLungHealth Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this randomized clinical trial, integrating a patient-centered tool into primary care EHR workflows increased the identification of patients eligible for LCS and the ordering of low-dose CTs. The relative increases in these primary outcomes were substantial, but absolute increases were more modest. Research on more intensive interventions is warranted to evaluate their ability to further improve LCS screening.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is a Critical Mouth Opening for Macintosh Videolaryngoscopy? Results From a Prospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that among individuals with expected difficult airway management, interincisor distances below 21 to 23 mm indicate increased risk of Macintosh videolaryngoscopy failure and may warrant alternative or awake techniques. Caution should be exercised as the mouth opening frequently decreases after anesthesia induction. Results should not be extrapolated to routine intubations in noncomplex patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Factors and Nomogram-Based Prediction Models for Colorectal Cancer Patients With Synchronous Peritoneal Metastasis Undergoing Cytoreductive Surgery: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study identified key prognostic factors and developed reliable nomogram models for predicting OS and PFS in CRC-SPM. The findings highlight the importance of postoperative chemotherapy and intraoperative lymph node dissection and suggest focusing on high-risk factors such as age and N2 stage in clinical practice. The nomogram models provide a valuable tool for personalized prognosis assessment and treatment planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Cross-Sectional Study on the Impact of Diaper Distribution by Diaper Banks on Child Health and Economic Impacts to Society]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS FOR PRACTICE: The distribution of diapers by community diaper banks reduces the burden of pediatric illness and associated healthcare costs. Pediatric healthcare professionals and public practitioners are in an optimal position to screen for diaper need and refer to local diaper banks and diaper resources. Addressing diaper insecurity has implications for reducing the burden of social isolation and caregiver mental health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Application of HoloLens Mixed Reality Combined with Eye Tracking and Visual Perception Technologies in Pediatric Orthopedic 3D Education]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This narrative review evaluates the current status, potential value, key challenges, and future directions of Microsoft HoloLens 2 mixed reality (MR) technology, with a particular focus on its built-in eye tracking and visual perception functions, in the context of pediatric orthopedic three-dimensional model teaching. Relevant literature on medical education and surgical training was integrated to examine the technical features, teaching practices, and educational implications of HoloLens MR....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute cardiovascular events after discontinuation of xanthine oxidase inhibitors: a cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this large real-world cohort, early discontinuation of XOi therapy was linked to a small but significant elevation in cardiovascular risk. These findings support prior signals of potential harm from XOi withdrawal, particularly among patients with cardiovascular disease, and highlight the importance of sustained therapy adherence. Key Points • Xanthine oxidase inhibitor (XOi) discontinuation was associated with a modest but significant increase in acute cardiovascular events in a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia Care Research and Psychosocial Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results provide evidence for the efficacy and effectiveness of extended nursing roles in dementia care, demonstrating that extended nursing roles reduce unmet needs and improve quality of life.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ALI is a relevant marker for identifying cognitive impairment and understanding its relationship with chronic stress. Monitoring biomarkers such as systolic blood pressure and waist-to-height ratio can improve the characterization of dementia in LA populations. These findings highlight the importance of addressing chronic stress and its biological impacts in diverse settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered pluronic nanomicelles containing ATRA and sodium butyrate for selective TNBC differentiation therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We formulated a micellar nanosystem for selective differentiation therapy of breast cancer stem cells (BCSCs). Hyaluronic acid (HA) coating was used to target CD44^(+) BCSCs, while codelivery of all-trans retinoic acid (ATRA) and histone deacetylase inhibitor (HDACi) was used to revert epigenetic silencing of the RARβ gene, sensitizing resistant tumor cells to treatment. Nanomicelles were formulated using the thin‑film hydration (TFH) method. The anti-cancer effects of nanoparticles (NPs) were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bortezomib combined with autologous stem cell transplantation overcomes cytogenetic abnormalities in AL amyloidosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cytogenetic abnormalities are associated with poor prognosis in systemic light chain (AL) amyloidosis, but evidence on treatment options that might overcome this adverse impact remains limited. In this study, we investigated whether the combination of bortezomib and autologous stem cell transplantation (ASCT) could overcome the adverse prognosis of AL amyloidosis with cytogenetic abnormalities. The study included 134 patients. The 52 patients treated with a bortezomib-based regimen and ASCT were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Approach of an Automated Radiolabeling of Micro- and Nanoscale UiO-66 MOFs for Internal Radiotherapy of Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Development of automated radiolabeling strategies for perspective materials is in huge demand to reach the large-scale production of radiopharmaceuticals with unique features under good manufacturing practice (GMP) conditions. Inherent properties of metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) such as high loading capacity, chemical stability, and biocompatibility allow to recommend them as promising radionuclide carriers for cancer therapy but this area of research is poorly investigated. Herein, we first...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Talin1 modulates the Piezo1-YAP axis to regulate endothelial cell inflammation and atherosclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results of this study suggest that Talin1 plays a vital role in endothelial inflammation and may be a novel anti-inflammatory therapeutic target for atherosclerosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and glycemic outcomes of DBLG1 coupled to the DANA-i pump in adults and adolescents with type 1 diabetes mellitus. The SP8 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: During the two-week study period, DBLG1 was interoperable with the DANA-i pump. This result requires confirmation in future long-term studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antitumor effects of morphine and tramadol on lung metastasis of melanoma tumor cells in vitro and in vivo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KLHL4 upregulates EGFR signaling to promote the malignant progression of oral squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oral squamous cell carcinoma (OSCC) is the most prevalent form of head and neck squamous cell carcinoma (HNSCC), characterized by high incidence rates, frequent recurrence and metastasis, and low survival rates. KLHL4, a member of the Kelch-like family proteins, plays a significant role in cancer. However, the role of KLHL4 in OSCC remains largely unexplored. In this study, we first identified the aberrant overexpression of KLHL4 in OSCC tissues through Western blotting and immunohistochemistry....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring a Flow Cytometry-Based CFU Assay for Functional Assessment of Human HSPCs: a Robust Alternative to Morphological Colony Evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expert consensus on the combined screening of genes and biomarkers for neonatal diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This consensus establishes a practical framework for integrating marker and genetic screening, aiming to improve diagnostic accuracy and achieve rapid and effective interventions, thereby saving lives and reducing the occurrence of severe complications. Implementation requires interdisciplinary collaboration and ongoing quality control to maximize clinical utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alcohol consumption is prevalent among Chinese adolescents: a national survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Alcohol consumption is prevalent among Chinese adolescents, increasing with school grade; percentages of drunkenness are relatively lower. Drinking and drunkenness in some time frames has significantly decreased. Of note, boys demonstrate higher percentages across almost all patterns of alcohol use. Adolescents display disparities in alcohol consumption based on their urban-rural residence and geographical location.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Food insecurity, quality of life, and socioeconomic conditions of older adults: BRAZUCA Natal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results show that the household's FI condition can have a negative impact on older adults' perception of QoL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current state of bioceramic bone repair materials in immune regulation: a review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extensive bone defects represent a significant clinical challenge, often leading to severe impairment of patients function and quality of life. Traditional treatments, such as autografts and allografts, are widely used but have notable limitations, including donor site morbidity and immunogenicity. As a result, tissue engineering has attracted increasing attention as a viable alternative. Bioceramic bone repair materials provide both mechanical support and bioactive functions in the treatment of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequential development of three syndromes in a patient with m.3243A&gt;G mutation: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondrial disorders are highly heterogeneous and can manifest as a spectrum of clinically heterogeneous disorders that affect multiple organ systems. Herein, we report a Chinese female patient carrying mitochondrial DNA m.3243A>G mutation who sequentially experienced myoclonic epilepsy with ragged red fibers, mitochondrial neurogastrointestinal encephalomyopathy, and mitochondrial encephalomyopathy with lactic acidosis and stroke-like episodes. This report expands the current understanding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fatty acid metabolic signature reveals FASN as an immunosuppressive factor in DLBCL tumor microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diffuse large B-cell lymphoma (DLBCL) is the most common subtype of non-Hodgkin lymphoma (NHL). Targeting fatty acid metabolism pathway represents a promising therapeutic strategy, particularly for patients with refractory or relapsed DLBCL. In this study, fatty-acid metabolism index (FMI) signature including 20 genes was constructed by univariate Cox and LASSO-Cox regression analysis using transcriptomic data from Gene Expression Omnibus database to predict overall survival of DLBCL patients....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-tumor effects and mechanism of the histone demethylase inhibitor GSK-J4 in non-small cell lung cancer cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lung cancer is one of the leading causes of death worldwide. Cancer metastases are responsible for 90% of cancer-related deaths. In view of the high incidence and mortality of lung cancer, there is still an urgent clinical need to improve the early diagnosis of lung cancer and explore new therapeutic methods and targets to improve the prognosis of patients. By targeting promoter or enhancer regions of related genes, histone methylation modification dynamically regulates gene expression and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fibrates : Do They Still Have a Role in Therapy in 2025?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD) remains a leading cause of mortality despite optimal LDL-C control, leaving substantial residual risk in patients with atherogenic dyslipidaemia. This review re-examines the evolving role of fibrates in the management of dyslipidaemia, metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD), chronic kidney disease (CKD), and diabetic microvascular complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide analysis of Zoysia japonica REVEILLE family identifies ZjRVE8-1 as a positive cold-tolerance regulator]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Functional analysis in Arabidopsis revealed that ZjRVE8 -1 significantly enhances cold tolerance by activating the CBF pathway, identifying it as a promising gene for breeding cold hardy Zoysia japonica cultivars. REVEILLE (RVE) transcription factors regulate circadian rhythms and abiotic stress responses, but their roles in cold tolerance in the warm-season turfgrass Zoysia japonica remain uncharacterized. We identified 10 RVE family members through genome-wide analysis and performed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Posture-dependent assessment of whole-spine curvature with a rotatable cryogen-free 1.5T MRI and automated Cobb angle analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuous sPatial-temporal deformable image registration and 4D frame interpolation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: By leveraging the continuous representations, the CPT-DIR method enhances registration and interpolation accuracy, automation, and speed. The method achieves high accuracy on intra-fractional thoracic datasets and demonstrates improved performance over conventional methods in more challenging inter-fractional abdominal registration scenarios, highlighting its potential for robust applications in radiotherapy. The improved efficiency and accuracy of CPT-DIR make it particularly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-specific quality assurance at the Heidelberg Ion Beam Therapy Center: 10 years experience in treatment plan verification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PSQA at HIT demonstrated high dosimetric accuracy and delivery stability. Integration of IDCs and log file analysis may improve efficiency and allow to omit verification measurements in well-established cases without compromising patient safety and treatment quality, if the extensive machine QA program is maintained.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our analyses suggest that the presence of pathological amyloid and tau (A+T+) is associated with declines in the neurosensory domain of odor identification. Future studies should examine whether similar trends are observed for other neurosensory domains such as vision and gustation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Low-Load Blood-Flow Restricted Training Versus Heavy Slow Resistance Training in Unilateral Patellar Tendinopathy: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patellar tendinopathy (PT) is a debilitating overuse injury, and one of the current recommended treatments is heavy slow resistance training (HSRT); Recently, low-load resistance training combined with blood flow restriction (LL-BFRT) has been advocated as a clinically relevant rehabilitation tool for PT since it does not involve large joint and tissue stresses and may accelerate recovery. This study aimed to investigate the effect of LL-BFRT compared with HSRT at 3, 6, 12 (primary endpoint),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Youth Tobacco Prevention Ads: Meta-Analysis of a Decade's Worth of Copy-Testing Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings of this study provide evidence that ads from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's tobacco prevention campaigns have the potential to positively influence relevant beliefs and attitudes among their intended youth audiences. Patterns of variation in effect sizes largely support the success of belief targeting in campaign development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the Treatment Disparities in Canadian College Students Experiencing Mental Health Problems: A Regression Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Investigate the sociodemographic disparities in mental health treatment among Canadian college students through quantifying disparities at 2 critical stages of the treatment-seeking pathway: (1) perceived need for treatment and (2) service use, conditional on perceived need.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A 4-5 minute brief optimized cognitive test can dramatically outperform the 10-14 minute MoCA in detecting MCI, and it can predict future decline to dementia comparably to, or better than, a clinical diagnosis made by clinicians with access to extensive cognitive and clinical information. This test could improve MCI detection in the more than 52 million people in the US age 65 or over.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zinc-Mediated Loading and Release of His-Tagged Recombinant Proteins in Self-Assembling Peptide Coacervates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of tunable systems for subcutaneous injection is currently the focus of exploratory protein formulation. For the delivery of protein biologics intended for extended release, a high fraction of the drug that escapes from the deposition site ("burst release") may pose safety concerns. Herein, we report an injectable system of bioaffinity zinc-containing peptide coacervates in which recombinant proteins coexpressed with histidine (His)-tags can be captured and released over time....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mesoporous PdPt Nanozymes with Target Peptides and Cascade Reactive Oxygen Species Scavenging for Boosting Alzheimer's Disease Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is an age-related neurodegenerative disease that has become a major health problem nowadays. Inhibiting the aggregation of amyloid-β (Aβ) peptides has made progress in AD treatments. Here, we synthesized mesoporous PdPt nanozymes to immobilize target peptide KLVFFAED for high-efficiency AD treatment. Thanks to the high surface area of the mesoporous nanospherical structure of PdPt nanozymes, lots of KLVFFAED were grafted with a concentration as high as 439.2 μg mL^(-1),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convergent Recruitment of Cerebellar Purkinje Cells by Mechanistically Diverse General Anesthetics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[General anesthesia produces a rapid and reversible loss of consciousness, yet the neural circuits through which chemically unrelated agents achieve this state remain largely unknown. Here, we combined Targeted Recombination in Active Populations (TRAP), Clear, Unobstructed Brain/Body Imaging Cocktails and Computational analysis (CUBIC) tissue clearing, and light-sheet microscopy to generate a hemisphere-wide, single-cell atlas of neurons activated by three mechanistically distinct anesthetics in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hepatitis B Vaccination Histories in Persons with HIV Needing Revaccination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Regardless of past vaccine records, antibody titers should be checked in PWH for revaccination needs. The recently approved long-acting (LA) and injectable antiretroviral treatment (ART) lacks protective effect against HBV, unlike tenofovir-based ART. As the LA ART becomes more widely used, we recommend reassessing serologies and offering the recommended CpG-adjuvanted vaccine series with promising response durability to individuals without seroprotection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Vivo Skin 3-D Surface Reconstruction and Wrinkle Depth Estimation Using Handheld High Resolution Tactile Sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[3-D skin surface reconstruction offers promise for objective and quantitative dermatological assessment, but no portable, high-resolution device exists that has been validated and used for depth reconstruction across various body locations. We present a compact 3-D skin reconstruction probe based on GelSight tactile imaging with a custom elastic gel and a learning-based reconstruction algorithm for micron-level wrinkle height estimation. Our probe, integrated with a load cell for force sensing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We extend findings of a previously reported AD risk variant near SHARPIN to hippocampal volume and provide evidence of novel sex-specific genetic effects. While replication is warranted, our results suggest the importance of genetic predictors and sex differences on imaging biomarkers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptomic signatures in different tissues of anti-MDA5 positive dermatomyositis: Uncovering genes with predictive potential for RP-ILD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The activation of the IFN, virus-associated, and aberrant immune response pathways, as well as fatty acid metabolic processes may be involved in MDA5+ DM pathogenesis. IFI27, DEFA3, and RNASE2 may contribute to RP-ILD pathogenesis and serve as biomarkers of MDA5+ DM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electron Microscopy Approaches to Unraveling the Structure of Amorphous Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Determining atomic structures in crystalline materials-where atoms are arranged in rigid, periodic lattices-has been highly successful using probes such as electrons, X-rays, and neutrons. In contrast, amorphous materials, despite their ubiquity and technological importance, remain far more challenging to characterize with comparable accuracy and precision. This review highlights existing, emerging, and potential (scanning) transmission electron microscopy ((S)TEM) techniques for probing short-...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrically Tunable and Linearly Polarized Mid-Infrared Photoluminescence in 2D Tellurium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of electronic and photonic chips hinges on the availability of efficient light sources and modulators that are compatible with on-chip interconnects. Among these, mid-infrared (mid-IR) emitters are especially critical, as they enable low-loss transmission through atmospheric windows and unlock powerful capabilities for molecular fingerprinting and chemical sensing. In this study, we demonstrate that 2D tellurium (Te) nanoflakes can serve as highly efficient, electrically tunable,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation and Effectiveness Outcomes of a Pilot Comparative Effectiveness Randomized Controlled Trial Evaluating a Food Is Medicine Program Among At-Risk Pediatric Populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction: Food Is Medicine (FIM) programs have demonstrated effectiveness in improving diet quality and food insecurity. There remains a lack of evidence of their impacts in pediatric populations. This pilot comparative effectiveness randomized control trial assessed two FIM strategies on implementation and health outcomes in Medicaid-eligible children aged 5-12 years with a BMI ≥85th percentile. Methods: Participants (n = 150) were enrolled for a 32-week intervention through recruitment at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Homology-Guided Zwitterionic Interlayers for 21% Efficiency Non-Fullerene Organic Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The performance evolution of organic solar cells (OSCs) is increasingly constrained by a growing mismatch between state-of-the-art photoactive layers and conventional cathode interlayer materials (CIMs). Here, we report a homology-guided molecular design strategy to synchronize CIM with fused-ring electron acceptors (FREAs). Grafting zwitterionic sidechains onto the high-performance pentacyclic FREA, we created a novel CIM, SZ1. This design grants SZ1 a deeper lowest unoccupied molecular orbital...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High Performance 4.6 V LiCoO<sub>2</sub> Cathode Materials Enabled by Surface Lattice Modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Charging the cathode of LiCoO(2) (LCO) to higher voltages, typically 4.6 V, is able to increase reversible capacity, but meanwhile raises serious stability issues. Here, through a decomposition-induced reconstruction (DIR) process, we demonstrate the possibility of modulating the surface lattice of LCO with high precision in depth control, thereby enabling the 4.6 V LCO cathode to have both high capacity and structural integrity. Following the precise construction of a conformal Y(OH)CO(3)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Stress-Potential Coupled Interface on Ultrathin Lithium Anodes Toward 450 Wh Kg<sup>-1</sup>-Level Long-Cycling Lithium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dendrite-free lithium anodes are crucial for developing practical high-energy-density batteries (>400 Wh/kg) with extended cycle life, but conventional interface design lack self-adaptive adjustment against dendrite growth during Li plating. Herein, we obtain a dendrite-free ultrathin Li@FcCHO anode by engineering a stress-responsive nano-interface on lithium strips via a mechanochemical reaction between ferrocene carboxaldehyde (FcCHO) and metallic Li. As proved by in situ Kelvin probe force...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Consideration should be given to offering the 3-item short version of the questionnaire to improve the efficiency and accuracy of dementia screening in primary care settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcription Factor ROX1 Controls Oxidative Stress Homeostasis in <em>Saccharomyces cerevisiae</em> at Low pH]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Saccharomyces cerevisiae is widely used in food and beverage production but faces stresses such as acidity during processing. In our previous studies, the S. cerevisiae mutant strain TAMC, which can tolerate an acidic environment of pH 2.3, was isolated via adaptive laboratory evolution; however, the genetic basis underlying the acid tolerance of this strain remained unclear. Herein, we aimed to elucidate the genetic basis of TAMC's acid tolerance via genome sequencing and functional analysis....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Fibrosis and Cardiometabolic Risk Burden Increase Major Cardiovascular Events in Chronic Hepatitis C Patients With Steatotic Liver Disease After Viral Eradication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CMRFs burden, advanced fibrosis, and CKD predicted MACEs in CHC patients with MASLD after achieving SVR. CMRFs monitoring and management should be prioritised in high-risk patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Counterintuitively, in individuals at elevated risk of AD, more self-reported and objective insomnia symptoms were associated with better cognitive scores. This may reflect protective lifestyle factors that improve cognition but also disrupt sleep patterns and sleep satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective Evaluation of <em>KIT</em> Mutations and Long-Term Outcomes in Pediatric Core Binding Factor Acute Myeloid Leukemia: A Single Institutional Study in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The overall incidence of core binding factor acute myeloid leukemia (CBF-AML) in pediatric patients has been reported to be 19%-44.3%. However, the prognostic role of KIT mutations in pediatric CBF-AML remains controversial. This study aimed to investigate whether incorporating KIT mutation status into risk stratification improves long-term outcomes. A total of 114 pediatric CBF-AML patients treated under BCH-AML 2005 protocol and CCLG-AML 2015 protocol were enrolled. KIT mutations were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unbiased metagenomic exploration of transfusion-transmitted infections with nanopore sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Despite advances in blood safety, emerging infectious agents continue to pose risks to the blood supply. Traditional nucleic acid testing assays primarily target known pathogens, limiting the detection of novel microbes. Nanopore metagenomic sequencing enables agnostic identification of diverse pathogens, potentially enhancing transfusion safety surveillance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Normalization in similarity networks would allow for investigations of topological properties of these networks, improving our understanding of AD neurobiology, while RAD networks, which preserve magnitude of SUVr differences, would facilitate patient-centric multimodal network approaches. These participant-level PET networks show promise for future integration with MRI brain connectivity networks to develop precision approaches for diagnostic subtyping of AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying Extended-Release Naltrexone Treatment for Opioid Use Disorder in US Medicaid Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We found inconsistent patterns of XR-NTX codes across states indicating claim-based definitions should consider both drug and procedure codes to fully capture XR-NTX service delivery. Multiple definitions should be considered in sensitivity analyses given substantial variability in coding practices across states.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nearly all measures within the NIHTB-CB significantly differentiate between healthy controls and individuals with aMCI, and healthy agers and individuals with mDAT among older Spanish-speaking adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia Care Research and Psychosocial Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CI-PCM subjects saved an average of $1,609.63 and experienced improvements in BPSD whereas comparators spent 2.8 times more and had worsening BPSD. ACHI treatment did not differ significantly between the two groups or account for the improvement in CI-PCM group BPSD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting <em>P</em>-glycoprotein with novel halogenated 4<em>H</em>-pyran-coumarin hybrids: a combined experimental, computational approach to tumor-sensitive and -resistant (breast) cancer cell lines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The over expression of P-glycoprotein (P-gp) is a primary mechanism of multidrug resistance (MDR) in cancer, urgently necessitating the development of novel and effective inhibitors. This work presents a new series of halogenated 4H-pyran-coumarin hybrids designed to overcome this resistance. Six novel hybrids (4a-f) were synthesized and characterized using IR, MS, and 1D/2D NMR techniques. Their antitumor potential was evaluated against sensitive (MCF-7, Caco-2) and resistant (MCF-7/ADR) cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The evolution of character education in medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia Care Research and Psychosocial Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The program demonstrated feasibility and preliminary effectiveness in improving outcomes for PLWD and families. High participant satisfaction highlights its potential as a scalable psychosocial intervention model. A randomized controlled trial involving 120 pairs is underway to further evaluate its impact on dementia care practices and family support systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In former athletes, we confirmed that chronological age is associated with cerebral atrophy and identified an association between increased DNAmFitAA and a higher number of concussions. This finding requires validation in independent studies, along with an assessment of the relationship between DNAmFitAA and neurodegeneration. Our analysis did not reveal a link of the examined epigenetic clocks with brain volumes and cortical thickness. Exploration of other epigenetic clocks may...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These initial feasibility results in two sections in 24 brain donors encourage us to apply this pipeline to a larger dataset of paired postmortem MRI and serial histology sections (Ravikumar et al., 2024) and to study associations between tau pathology, neuronal loss, and MRI-based measures of atrophy, with the aim of better differentiating atrophy linked to LATE and AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Crosstalk of Epithelial Cells, Endothelial Cells, and Macrophages Orchestrates Inflammation in Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammation is associated with disease progression and frequent exacerbations of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD). The cell crosstalk plays a central role in initiating and maintaining inflammation. This study aimed to establish a cell coculture model simulating the inflammatory microenvironment, and investigate the mechanism of cell communication in COPD. The cell type, and cell crosstalk in normal and COPD were analyzed based on single-cell RNA sequencing data from GEO database....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-processed foods and CKD: a review of evidence, limitations, and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: To critically examine the emerging evidence linking ultra-processed food (UPF) consumption to chronic kidney disease (CKD), with a particular focus on prevention strategies, biological mechanisms, and implications for dietary guidelines and public health policy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of Brain Temporal Complexity During Treatment for Depression: A CAN-BIND-1 Study Report: Modulation de la complexité temporelle du cerveau pendant le traitement de la dépression: rapport de l'étude CAN-BIND-1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectivesCurrent pharmacological antidepressant treatments suffer from low remission rates and slow initiation of therapeutic effects. In addition, the development of new antidepressant treatments is confounded by the lack of consensus on efficient and valid neurophysiological targets. Temporal complexity is an alternative measure of dynamic brain activity that estimates brain signal variability at several timescales. It can be easily extracted from non-invasive brain recordings and provides...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jazz dance and concurrent training for menopausal symptom relief: evidence from the MenosPausa mais movimento project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although improvements in menopausal symptoms were observed over time within all groups, including the control group, no significant group×time interactions were found. Therefore, this study did not demonstrate a superior effect of JD or CT compared with the CG, only the results that compare the interventions and CG over time are interpretable.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41452037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251226142211&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>