<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 07:42:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World outcomes of oral anticoagulation in patients with atrial fibrillation at high risk of both bleeding anand Asia-Pacificd stroke: observational evidence from three international registries from middle East, Europe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the clinical course of patients with AF at high risk for both bleeding and stroke, according to OAC use. Data were analysed from three registries across the Middle East, Europe, and Asia-Pacific regions. The study only included 'high risk' patients with AF and CHA₂DS₂-VASc scores ≥ 2 and HAS-BLED scores ≥ 3, who were divided into two groups based on OAC use: OAC users and OAC non-users. Of the 2,535 patients (41.7% female; mean age 75.4 ± 7.8 years), 80.3% (n = 2,037) received OAC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brain metastasis from non-small cell lung cancer: crosstalk between cancer cells and tumor microenvironment components]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The majority of patients with lung cancer are diagnosed at an advanced stage, with a substantial proportion exhibiting signs of brain metastases (BMs). BM is associated with debilitating symptoms, including headaches, seizures and neurological or cognitive impairments, which severely impact the quality of life of patients. Despite considerable advancements in lung cancer treatment modalities, the management of BM remains challenging due to the complex cellular and structural nature of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-omics analysis identifies SMPD1 as a key contributor in sphingolipid pathway for Type 2 diabetes pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings strongly indicate that SMPD1, as part of the sphingolipid pathway, represents a promising therapeutic target for both T2D and MASLD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral KDS2010, a Monoamine Oxidase-B (MAO-B) Inhibitor, Slows the Deterioration of Motor Coordination in Genetic SCA1 Models by Inhibiting Astrocytic MAO-B-Mediated Inflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spinocerebellar ataxia type 1 (SCA1) is an autosomal dominant neurodegenerative disorder characterized by balance and gait disturbance, muscle coordination deficits, and dysarthria as a primary symptom. SCA1 is caused by the expansion of CAG repeats in the ATXN1 gene, leading to a polyglutamine(polyQ) tract in the Ataxin-1 protein. In this study, the effects of KDS2010, an inhibitor of monoamine oxidase-B (MAO-B), were evaluated in a transgenic mouse model of SCA1 (SCA1^(154Q/2Q)) disease model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Process Parameters on HNO <sub><em>y</em>=2,3</sub> and NO <sub><em>y</em></sub> <sup>-</sup> Formation in Plasma-Treated Water]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we investigate the effects of hydrodynamics and temperature on the formation of nitrous and nitric acids (HNO (y=2,3)) and their conjugate bases (NO (y) ^(-)) in plasma-treated water (PTW) in a surface dielectric barrier discharge (sDBD) reactor. The stirring rate and bulk water temperature were systematically varied from 200 to 1000 rpm and 20 to 80 °C, respectively, while the plasma was held constant. Species in both the gas and liquid phases were tracked in real time using synchronized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synchronous Succinate Dehydrogenase Subunit B (SDHB)-Deficient Gallbladder Paraganglioma and Periduodenal Well-Differentiated Neuroendocrine Tumor: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Paragangliomas are extra-adrenal neuroendocrine neoplasms (NENs), and those arising in the gallbladder are exceedingly rare. Pathogenic variants in the succinate dehydrogenase (SDH) complex are well-established drivers of paragangliomas and pheochromocytomas, and have also been implicated in epithelial neuroendocrine tumors (NETs). We report a 50-year-old woman with a likely pathogenic succinate dehydrogenase subunit B (SDHB) germline variant (p.D118Y, c.352G>T), who underwent surveillance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acupuncture for fibromyalgia syndrome: an overview of systematic reviews and meta-analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The current SRs and MAs provide low-quality evidence for the effectiveness of AT in treating FMS. Robust and well-designed studies using standardized methods are needed to provide more reliable and convincing evidence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Control of alkaline phosphatase activity and pH stability by taurine in liquid boar semen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alkaline phosphatase (ALP) is an enzyme present in various tissues and plays an important role in biochemical processes, by catalyzing the hydrolysis of organic phosphates and energy metabolism. Despite significant ALP activity in seminal plasma across species, its role in sperm function remains unclear. Several studies have revealed the important role of taurine in male reproductive functions, due to its antioxidant and membrane-stabilizing activity, and ability to enhance sperm quality....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of dietary organic acids in laying hens production: a comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The removal of antibiotic growth promoters from poultry diets has driven research into alternative feed additives to optimize production performance in laying hens. Among these alternatives, dietary organic acids (OAs) have gained significant attention due to their antimicrobial properties, ability to modulate intestinal acidity, and role in enhancing nutrient utilization. This review comprehensively examines the effects of OAs supplementation on egg production and quality, blood parameters,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary protein level in response to nitrogen balance along with production performance of laying hens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the effects of dietary crude protein (CP) levels on body weight (BW), laying performance, egg quality, and nitrogen (N) balance in laying hens from 18 to 62 weeks of age. A total of 84 Hy-Line Brown hens at 18 weeks old were randomly assigned to two groups, each with six replicates. The control group (CON) received diets with 17.5%, 16.5%, 15.5%, and 14.5% CP from weeks 18-38, 39-46, 47-54, and 55-62, respectively. The reduced protein group (RP) was fed diets with 1.5%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-based analysis algorithm incorporating nanoscale structural variations and measurement-angle misalignment in spectroscopic ellipsometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spectroscopic ellipsometry (SE) is a powerful, non-destructive technique for nanoscale structural characterization. However, conventional SE data analysis typically assumes perfectly periodic specimen structures, overlooking fabrication-induced structural variations and thereby reducing the accuracy of predicted structural parameters. We have developed an enhanced analysis framework that explicitly accounts for both nanoscale structural variations and measurement-angle misalignment by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pig regulatory macrophages as a donor-derived immune modulators in xenotransplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Xenotransplantation offers a potential solution to the critical shortage of donor organs; however, graft survival is limited by xeno-immune activation and coagulation dysregulation. Regulatory macrophages (Mregs) are known for their immunomodulatory capacity, yet their cross-species function in the context of xenotransplantation remains unclear. This study investigates the immunoregulatory properties of pig-derived Mregs (pMregs) as a potential donor-derived cellular therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On-chip polarization management for stable nonlinear signal generation in thin-film lithium niobate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonlinear signal generation requires precise control of the input polarization to satisfy phase-matching conditions. Conventional polarization management using external fiber polarization controllers or bulk wave plates increases coupling complexity and can degrade polarization fidelity and conversion efficiency in nonlinear photonic systems. Here, we demonstrate on-chip polarization control in thin-film lithium niobate nonlinear photonic circuits. Integrated polarization modulators enable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond limits: a tribute to Dai-Sik Kim's academic legacy and vision]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article is dedicated to the cherished memory of Prof. Dai-Sik Kim, a visionary leader and an inspiring mentor who profoundly shaped international as well as domestic landscape of optical science, and addresses topics that were central to his scientific passion in nanophotonics. Prof. Kim's research spanned surface plasmonics, near-field optics, and terahertz plasmonics and spectroscopy, each reflecting his enduring commitment to exploring the interaction between light and matter beyond...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Positional Isomerism Tunes Molecular Reactivities and Mechanisms toward Pathological Targets in Dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Positional isomerism offers a powerful strategy to fine-tune molecular reactivity toward diverse pathogenic factors in complex diseases. Here, we show that positional isomerism in phenylene-based compact molecules bearing electron-donating groups at the para, ortho, or meta positions engineers distinct chemical reactivities with key pathological targets, including reactive oxygen species, metal-free amyloid-β (Aβ), and metal-bound Aβ, which are implicated in Alzheimer's disease (AD)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feature-Selective Preprocessing with Electrically Robust Boron Nitride-Based Dynamic Memristors for Reliable Lightweight Neural Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reservoir computing (RC) has gained attention for its ability to improve the efficiency of artificial intelligence (AI) computations through dynamic preprocessing of input data. However, RC has an accuracy limitation due to data loss when mapping original inputs into a high-dimensional computational space. Furthermore, physical reservoirs switch frequently in RC systems, making switching endurance a critical factor that requires further investigation. Here, we report an electrically robust...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of Germline and Somatic Mutations of DNA Repair Genes in Korean Men with Prostate Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: BRCA2 was the most prevalent in germline mutations but CDK12 was out-numbered BRCA2 in somatic mutations in the present study. The higher frequency of DDR gene mutation was associated with advanced cancer stage and higher cellular grade group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex differences in long-term outcomes by platelet reactivity in patients with chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic kidney disease (CKD) is associated with increased platelet reactivity following stent implantation. However, the effect of sex on platelet reactivity remains unclear and requires further investigation. We evaluated the impact of high platelet reactivity (HPR) and sex on 5-year outcomes in patients with CKD undergoing percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI) using drug-eluting stents (DES). From the Platelet Function and Genotype-Related Long-Term Prognosis in Drug-Eluting Stent-Treated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to: Uncertainties in the phylogeny and biogeography of cave crickets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AcrIIA19 binds to the WED domain and inhibits various Cas9 orthologs at multiple stages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anti-CRISPR (Acr) proteins are natural inhibitors of clustered regularly interspaced short palindromic repeat (CRISPR)-CRISPR-associated protein (Cas) systems, providing valuable tools for regulating genome editing. Here, we present the crystal structure of AcrIIA19, a plasmid-encoded Type II-A CRISPR-Cas system inhibitor that targets Cas9. AcrIIA19 adopts a previously uncharacterized fold and forms a stable homodimer. Biochemical assays revealed that AcrIIA19 binds selectively to the wedge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional connectivity associated with severe upper limb impairment in resting-state electroencephalography among chronic stroke survivors: a machine learning approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our research highlights the association between alterations in connectivity within low-frequency bands and severe ULI across widespread brain regions, including areas outside the sensorimotor cortex and bilateral intrahemispheric and interhemispheric regions. Further research utilizing larger longitudinal datasets from early stroke survivors employing ML approaches could contribute to the development of more accurate predictive models for motor recovery and rehabilitation responses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synchronous uterine leiomyosarcoma and pulmonary adenocarcinoma in a meerkat (Suricata suricatta): a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of digital literacy and nursing informatics competency as job resources on nurses' burnout and work engagement: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical management of gastric mucosa-associated lymphoid tissue lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric mucosa-associated lymphoid tissue (MALT) lymphoma is often associated with chronic Helicobacter pylori infection. For an accurate diagnosis of gastric MALT lymphoma, clinical suspicion and careful endoscopic examination with multiple biopsies should be performed, and the final pathological confirmation should be provided. Gastric MALT lymphomas present with nonspecific symptoms and endoscopic findings. In most cases, H. pylori infection is the main cause of gastric MALT lymphoma....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From bench to bedside: adipose tissue fibrosis in obesity, anti-diabetic therapies, and bariatric surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review provides a comprehensive examination of the recent research findings concerning the pathophysiology and clinical implications of adipose tissue fibrosis in obesity and metabolic diseases. Recent large-scale studies, including a longitudinal study spanning 24 years (Swedish Obese Subjects), have demonstrated that weight loss in obese patients is directly correlated with reduced metabolic complications and mortality. Nonetheless, instances of weight regain and subsequent loss of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between high carbohydrate to dietary fiber ratio and risk of dementia in older adults: analysis from the UK biobank]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal position overlap disrupts feature binding in visual working memory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined how task-irrelevant spatial and temporal relationships influence feature binding in visual working memory (VWM). Participants viewed two sequential memory displays, each containing two distinct objects. Objects were presented either simultaneously at different locations (thereby sharing temporal position) or sequentially at the same location (thereby sharing spatial position). On each trial, a test probe either matched one of the four memory items or combined features from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of AI-CAD Software for Breast Cancer Detection in Automated Breast Ultrasound]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To assess the diagnostic performance and clinical usefulness of deep learning-based computer-aided detection (AI-CAD) for automated breast ultrasound (ABUS) across radiologists with varying ABUS experience. This retrospective study included 114 women (228 breasts) who underwent ABUS in 2019. Three radiologists interpreted images with and without AI-CAD. We evaluated sensitivity, specificity, positive predictive value (PPV), negative predictive value (NPV), accuracy, and area under the curve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel approach to design compact, wideband, and high-gain circularly polarized MIMO antenna using dual-polarized elements and hybrid couplers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel design approach for a compact, circularly polarized (CP) multiple-input multiple-output (MIMO) antenna that achieves wide bandwidth, high gain, and multi-port operation. Unlike conventional MIMO configurations, where each port feeds a single-polarized radiating element and gain enhancement relies on frequency-selective surfaces or T-dividers, the proposed design integrates dual-polarized CP radiating elements with hybrid couplers. Through this configuration, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal machine learning for 5-year mortality prediction after percutaneous coronary intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI) is a cornerstone treatment for coronary artery disease, yet accurate prediction of long-term mortality remains a critical challenge due to the complex interplay of risk factors. Existing prognostic models rely predominantly on structured clinical data, overlooking the rich, nuanced information embedded in diagnostic imaging and procedural narratives. To address this gap, we present a novel multimodal machine learning framework that integrates coronary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The efficacy of half saline in tumescent liposuction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Local anesthetic minimally invasive liposuction (LAMS) is a liposuction technique that uses tumescent fluid and involves connecting a syringe to a tiny blunt catheter to remove fat at low pressure. The clinical outcomes of LAMS were compared based on the type of tumescent fluid. This study aim to compare the efficacy and safety of LAMS using half saline and normal saline. A retrospective cohort study was conducted at the 365mc Gangnam LAMS center from August 2023 to February 2024. A total of 147...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploratory evidence of mitigated immune imprinting following concomitant COVID-19 and influenza vaccination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Concomitant administration of coronavirus disease (COVID-19) and influenza vaccination schedules has been widely adopted. However, long-term data on the immunological impact, particularly on variant-specific responses, remain limited. In this 10-month prospective study, 80 participants (40 per group) received either a concomitant bivalent COVID-19 mRNA booster and quadrivalent influenza vaccination (Group C) or separate vaccinations (Group S) at least 4 weeks apart. Immunogenicity was evaluated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors for Subaxial Kyphosis After Posterior C1-C2 Fusion for Atlantoaxial Dislocation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The correlation between the upper cervical spine (O-C2 angle) and the subaxial spine (C2-C7 angle) didn't change before and after surgery. After surgery, O-C1 angle was significantly correlated with C2-C7 angle. Women, decreased O-C1 ROM, and postoperative C1-C2 angle were significantly associated with PSK.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systemic Therapy for Advanced Biliary Tract Cancers in 2026: Current Standard of Care and Emerging Therapeutic Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biliary tract cancers (BTCs)-including cholangiocarcinoma and gallbladder cancer-are increasing in incidence worldwide and carry a poor prognosis, constituting a growing global health burden. Early-stage disease can be potentially cured with surgical resection; however, the majority present with advanced disease, and palliative systemic therapy is the mainstay of treatment. In the first-line setting, gemcitabine plus cisplatin (GemCis) chemotherapy served as the long-standing standard of care;...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "The Remarkable Journey of ANR: From Inception to Q1 Achievement" [Asian Nurs Res 19 (4) (October 2025) 323-324]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nursing's Distinctive Power in the Age of Artificial Intelligence: A Vision for Research and the Future of Asian Nursing Research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethics of authorship]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design of cyclic tissue engineering bioreactor based on alginate hydrogel responses to the stress of compression surface morphologies and texture profile and its finite element analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Effective design of bioreactors for soft tissue engineering requires a precise understanding of how biomimetic mechanical stimuli affect the behaviors of scaffolds. This work investigates the influence of cartilage-mimetic compressor head geometry and forces on the mechanical and rheological properties of alginate hydrogels under cyclic compression. We applied controlled strains using four distinct piston head shapes, i.e. flat-surface for uniform pressure, curved-edge for non-uniform pressure,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of susceptibility-matched antibiotic treatment of non-typhoidal Salmonella bloodstream infections: a prospective observational study in hospitalized children under-five in DR Congo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: NTS bloodstream infections were often extensively drug-resistant, leading to susceptibility-mismatched antibiotic treatment. When NTS were susceptible, third generation cephalosporin, ciprofloxacin and azithromycin treatment appeared to be effective.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fracture Risk by Post-Cessation Weight Change in Men With Newly Diagnosed Type 2 Diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In men with type 2 diabetes, smoking cessation did not reduce fracture risk, but weight maintenance after cessation was protective. Weight loss after cessation significantly increased fracture risk, highlighting the need for integrated weight management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tailored Postoperative Reconstruction for Low-Grade Cerebrospinal Fluid Leaks in Pituitary Neuroendocrine Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our graded reconstruction approach is an effective and efficient method to prevent CSF leaks after eTSA in PitNET patients with low-grade intraoperative CSF leaks. Further subdividing Grade 2 leaks based on defect size enables more precise and reliable skull base reconstruction. Moreover, autologous fat grafts, fascia lata, and perioperative LD appear unnecessary in low-grade cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Telemedicine in chronic lung disease management: progress and prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic lung diseases, including asthma, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, and interstitial lung disease, contribute significantly to morbidity and mortality worldwide. Telemedicine has emerged as a promising approach for addressing these challenges by enabling remote patient monitoring, virtual consultations, and digital health interventions. Advances in home spirometry, wearable devices, and mobile health applications have improved early detection of disease exacerbations, medication...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antimicrobial stewardship programs in sepsis treatment: principles, impact, and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sepsis continues to be a serious global health concern with increasing mortality rates owing to antimicrobial resistance (AMR). Antimicrobial stewardship programs (ASPs) have emerged as critical tools for optimizing antibiotic use and reducing AMR. This review examines the applications of ASPs in sepsis treatment, highlights their role in improving patient outcomes, and addresses the challenges posed by multidrug-resistant organisms. The review begins by exploring the global AMR crisis and its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unilateral Medial Rectus Recession Can Produce Incomitance in Patients with Acute Acquired Comitant Esotropia: A Case Series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal Time for Stabilization of Anterior Corneal Keratometry after Primary Pterygium Excision Adjusted for Horizontal Invasion Length]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Corneal keratometric stabilization after pterygium excision depends on preoperative HIL. A minimum of 16 weeks is recommended before cataract surgery planning, with at least 20 weeks for eyes with HIL ≥ 3.82 mm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Practice Patterns in Pediatric Myopia Control: Insights from a Nationwide Survey of Korean Pediatric Ophthalmologists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this survey of KAPOS members, topical atropine, particularly the 0.125% commercial formulation, was the most commonly prescribed single modality for myopia control. Topical atropine and optical interventions emerged as the most common treatment strategies, particularly in private clinics. These findings indicate a trend towards more proactive and multimodal approaches to myopia control compared with earlier practice patterns in Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The miRNA838-KCS2 module is involved in the fine regulation of Arabidopsis wax biosynthesis under water-deficient conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In terrestrial plants, the outer epidermal surfaces are enveloped by a hydrophobic cuticle, which acts as the primary defense barrier against both abiotic and biotic stresses. While cuticular wax biosynthesis is tightly controlled to protect plants from environmental challenges, its underlying microRNA-mediated regulatory mechanisms remain poorly characterized. Here, we report the function of microRNA838 (miR838) in the fine regulation of cuticular wax biosynthesis in Arabidopsis via controlling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complex wavelet-based Transformer for neurodevelopmental disorder diagnosis via direct modeling of real and imaginary components]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Resting-state functional magnetic resonance imaging (rs-fMRI) measures intrinsic neural activity, and analyzing its frequency-domain characteristics provides insights into brain dynamics. Owing to these properties, rs-fMRI is widely used to investigate brain disorders such as autism spectrum disorder (ASD) and attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD). Conventional frequency-domain analyses typically rely on the Fourier transform, which lacks flexibility in capturing non-stationary neural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green naphtha production via direct CO2 hydrogenation with renewable hydrogen: economic-environmental perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Global petrochemical leaders are increasingly prioritizing green naphtha as a strategic pathway toward carbon neutrality. In particular, naphtha production via direct CO(2) hydrogenation has received significant attention due to its potential to substantially reduce greenhouse gas emissions. This study proposed sustainable naphtha production processes via direct CO(2) hydrogenation and assessed their economic and environmental performance. To investigate the trade-offs between these aspects,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complex multiannual cycles of <em>Mycoplasma pneumoniae</em>: Persistence and the role of stochasticity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The epidemiological dynamics of Mycoplasma pneumoniae is characterized by poorly understood complex multiannual cycles. The origins of these cycles have long been debated, and multiple explanations of varying complexity have been suggested. Using Bayesian methods, we fit a dynamical model to half a century of M. pneumoniae surveillance data from Denmark (1958 to 1995, 2010 to 2025) and uncover a parsimonious explanation for the persistent cycles, based on the theory of quasicycles. The period of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating TERT Promoter Mutations into Risk Stratification of Papillary Thyroid Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TERT promoter mutations are associated with poor short-term outcomes in PTC, especially among intermediate- and high-risk patients. Incorporating TERT status into risk stratification can refine initial risk stratification and facilitate the efficient allocation of medical resources for follow-up care after primary treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Step-by-Step Procedure for Producing Germline Chimera in Chicken via Primordial Germ Cell Transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The generation of germline chimeras in chickens via transplantation of primordial germ cells (PGCs) provides a robust and reproducible platform for avian transgenesis, genome editing, and species conservation. Traditional approaches using blastodermal cells from EGK stage X embryos are limited by low germline transmission efficiency due to early cell lineage segregation. In contrast, PGC-mediated strategies exploit the intrinsic germline competency of these unipotent cells, enabling reliable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interethnic validation of artificial intelligence for prediction of atrial fibrillation using sinus rhythm electrocardiogram]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our artificial intelligence-powered sinus rhythm ECG interpretation model demonstrated excellent performance in predicting paroxysmal or incident atrial fibrillation, with valid performance in the Brazilian population as well. This suggests that the model has the potential for broad application across different ethnic groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing the Asia &amp; Pacific Bioinformatics Joint Congress: a historic milestone in regional bioinformatics collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In response to the need for greater cohesion among regional conferences, the Asia Pacific Bioinformatics Network (APBioNET) set out in 2015 to realize a long-held aspiration-a single, unifying bioinformatics "super conference" for the Asia & Pacific community. Nearly a decade of persistence, coordination, and coalition-building led to the inaugural Asia & Pacific Bioinformatics Joint Congress (APBJC2024) in Okinawa, Japan. Now established as a triennial event, APBJC stands as a testament to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolving electrocatalytic nitrate-to-ammonia conversion on Cu- and Co-based catalyst engineering with paired electrolysis approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electrocatalytic nitrate (NO(3)^(-)) reduction reaction to ammonia (NH(3)) offers a sustainable pathway for wastewater remediation and distributed NH(3) synthesis, presenting a capable alternative to the energy-intensive Haber-Bosch process. Copper (Cu)- and cobalt (Co)-based catalysts are among the most promising for this reaction due to their favourable electronic structure for NO(3)^(-) activation and cost-effectiveness. However, their propensity for rapid deactivation caused by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of transition probabilities in multi-state models with nested case-control data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multi-state models are widely used to study complex interrelated life events. In resource-limited settings, nested case-control (NCC) sampling may be employed to extract subsamples from a cohort for an event of interest, followed by a conditional likelihood analysis. However, conditioning restricts the reuse of NCC data for studying additional events. An alternative approach constructs pseudolikelihoods using inverse probability weighting (IPW) for inference with NCC data. Existing IPW-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnosis of gout using monosodium urate (MSU) crystal binding peptides screened from Fv-antibody library]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The diagnosis of gout was developed through the detection of monosodium urate (MSU) crystals in the synovial fluid of patients with gout using MSU-binding peptides. Amino acid sequences with a high binding affinity to MSU crystals were screened from the Fv-antibody library using MSU crystals as probes. Five CDR3 sequences were successfully screened as MSU-binding sequences from the Fv-antibody library, and these were synthesized into 11-residue peptides. Among these, two MSU-binding peptides...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Macrophage Accumulation and Polarization in Patients with Obesity and Diabetes with Diabetic Remission After Bariatric Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting molecular types of adult-type diffuse gliomas based on MRI reports with large language models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LLMs may provide preoperative information on the tumor types of adult-type diffuse gliomas from MRI reports by providing relevant knowledge in the prompt. Informative and descriptive reports could further enhance LLMs' performance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Mediating Role of Eating Behaviors on the Relationship Between Sensory Processing and Maternal Stress: A Comparative Study of Children with ASD and Typical Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reshaping the robotic learning curve in anatomic lung resection: the role of prior video-assisted thoracoscopic surgery experience in a multi-surgeon single-center series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The adoption of robotic-assisted thoracoscopic surgery for lung cancer has steadily increased; however, the learning curve and influence of prior video-assisted thoracoscopic surgery (VATS) experience remain underexplored. This study investigates the impact of prior VATS experience on the learning trajectory of robotic anatomic lung resection. We conducted a retrospective, single-center study analyzing 341 consecutive robotic anatomic lung resections performed by three surgeons between January...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Capivasertib (AZD5363), a Potent, Oral Pan-AKT Inhibitor, in Patients with Relapsed or Refractory B-Cell Non-Hodgkin Lymphoma (CAPITAL)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study was terminated early with a small sample size, limiting interpretation, although antitumor activity was limited. Future studies of capivasertib in hematologic malignancies would likely require biomarker-directed patient selection and/or combination therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[INDUCE-3: A randomized Phase II/III study of first-line feladilimab plus pembrolizumab in patients with recurrent/metastatic head and neck squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This analysis does not support the combination of feladilimab plus pembrolizumab due to lack of superiority over placebo plus pembrolizumab.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of gut microbiota on host stem cells across the gastrointestinal tract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The gut microbiota plays a pivotal role in maintaining gastrointestinal (GI) homeostasis by influencing epithelial integrity, immunity, and metabolism. Recent studies have uncovered that gut microbiota can directly or indirectly modulate the behavior and function of adult stem cells across the GI tract, which are essential for tissue regeneration and disease prevention. Moreover, key microbial metabolites including short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs), tryptophan-derived indoles, succinate, secondary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between retinal vascular disease and subsequent stroke risk: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RVDs, particularly RVO, were significantly associated with elevated risks of both IS and HS. These findings highlight the potential value of retinal assessment in early identification of high-risk individuals and underscore the importance of tailored stroke prevention strategies, particularly in younger and socioeconomically vulnerable populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bagasse-Derived Hard Carbon Anode with a Synergistic Sodium Storage Mechanism Induced by Temperature Gradient for High-Performance Sodium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biomass-derived hard carbon has wide sources, low cost, and natural hierarchical pore structure and surface functional groups, holding huge potential for sodium-ion batteries (SIBs). Nevertheless, it still faces the challenges including unclear Na-storage mechanism and inaccurate match between diverse microstructures and desirable electrochemical performance. Herein, a novel biomass-derived hard carbon with balanced graphite crystallites and defect sites, appropriate carbon interlayer spacing,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethoxy/Amide-Functionalized UiO-66-(OH)<sub>2</sub> MOF Composite Separators Enabling Water/HF scavenging and Li<sup>+</sup> Regulation for Stable Lithium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To overcome the disadvantages of commercial polyolefin-based separators, such as inadequate electrochemical properties and dendrite growth, in lithium metal batteries, nanofiber separators coated with MOF are prepared using the electrospinning technique and a vacuum surface coating method. The Zr-based MOF (UiO-66-(OH)(2)) materials that scavenge H(2)O/HF in the electrolyte are synthesized via hydrothermal synthesis, and ethoxy/amide groups are introduced onto the MOF surface through a reaction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive Value of Sleep Architecture and Arousal Index for Surgical Outcomes in Obstructive Sleep Apnea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings may offer more reliable predictors of which OSA patients will benefit from sleep surgery and underscore the importance of incorporating detailed PSG analysis into preoperative evaluations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Malignancy risk in AUS thyroid lesions: comparison between FNA and CNB with implications for NIFTP diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fendo.2025.1692071.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of cold waves on diabetes-related morbidity and mortality: a meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cold wave exposure significantly increases diabetes-related health risks, highlighting the need for enhanced public health strategies. Further research is needed to address the gaps in understanding cold wave morbidity impacts and related socioeconomic factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and safety of ultrasound-guided needle-knife therapy for patients with spinal pain disorders: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: US-NKT demonstrates superior efficacy in reducing pain and improving PF compared with recommended therapies or conventional NKT, with a favorable safety profile. However, sustained benefits beyond 3 months remain inconclusive.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Rumex</em> Species: Phytochemistry, Pharmacology and Nutritional Potential for Food and Health Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The genus Rumex (Polygonaceae), comprising about 193 species, is widely distributed across temperate and subtropical regions of Europe, Asia, Africa, and North America, and has long been used in traditional medicine worldwide. These species are rich in diverse phytochemicals, including anthraquinones, flavonoids, tannins, naphthalenes, and stilbenes, which contribute to a broad range of biological activities. This review provides an updated synthesis of current knowledge on the taxonomy,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transformer-based models for ADR detection: cross-drug validation and benchmarking against large language models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Fine-tuned transformer-based models demonstrated reasonable performance in ADR detection from GLP-1 receptor agonist tweets, with BERTweet-base performing best. However, state-of-the-art LLMs, particularly ChatGPT 4o-mini, substantially outperformed these models, highlighting their potential for pharmacovigilance tasks.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Derivation and Definitions of Clinical Study Variables for Multiple Long Term Conditions in Patients with Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease: Protocol for a Modified Delphi Methods and Consensus Study on Behalf of the International Cardiovascular and Respiratory Alliance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Standardized variables and their definitions are essential for robust delivery and reporting of clinical studies and quality improvement in chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD). This protocol describes the rationale and methodology for the derivation and definition of clinical study variables for patients with multimorbidity or at high risk of multimorbidity in COPD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supplementation effects of feed additive containing eggshell, <em>Schisandra chinensis</em> by-products combined with multi-probiotics strains in laying hens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eggshell waste and Schisandra chinensis by-products are natural sources rich in beneficial nutrients and bioactive compounds. However, their combined effects with multi-probiotics on poultry productivity and health remain unexplored. This study assessed the immediate effects of a feed additive-eggshell waste (ES), Schisandra chinensis by-product (SC), and multi-probiotics (M)-administered for four weeks to aged laying hens before slaughter, evaluating the improvements of laying performance, egg...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applying and adapting the welfare quality<sup>®</sup> protocol for assessing animal welfare in Korean cattle and pig slaughterhouses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to review the applicability of the Welfare Quality^(®) protocol to evaluate animal welfare in cattle and pig slaughterhouses in Korea. A total of 6 cattle and 7 pig slaughterhouses were studied and evaluated by applying the Welfare Quality^(®) protocol. To ensure the reliability and reproducibility of the results, the three investigators were first trained in Welfare Quality^(®) protocol and took video and photographs during the initial field assessment. A reassessment was then...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inverse-designed gyrotropic scatterers for non-reciprocal analog computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While conventional von Neumann based machines are increasingly challenged by modern day requirements, electromagnetic analog computing devices promise to provide a platform that is highly parallel, efficient and fast. Along this paradigm, it has been shown that arrays of subwavelength electromagnetic scatterers can be used as solvers of partial differential equations. Inverse design offers a powerful tool to synthesize such analog computing machines, utilizing engineered non-local responses to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical see-through augmented reality via inverse-designed waveguide couplers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Waveguide-based augmented-reality (AR) displays offer compact, optical see-through form factors but remain limited by chromatic dispersion, ghosting from parasitic diffraction orders, distortion of the see-through scene, and a restricted eyebox. We present triple-function metasurface couplers designed using adjoint-based optimization, which overcome these limitations and establish computational performance bounds. The out-coupler simultaneously preserves zeroth-order transmission of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultranarrow polaritonic cavities formed by one-dimensional junctions of two-dimensional in-plane heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose two-dimensional (2D) in-plane heterostructures, composed of a 2D crystal adjoining a perfect electric conductor (PEC) plane, that enable ultranarrow polaritonic resonant cavities. Specifically, we theoretically investigate the interaction of 2D surface polaritons (2DSPs) with the junction between the 2D crystal and a PEC plane. We reveal that when 2DSPs are strongly confined, the reflected 2DSPs experience a phase shift of 3π/4, which exhibits π/2 deviation from the so-called edge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multicolor nanoring arrays with uniform and decoupled scattering for augmented reality displays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For vivid, immersive overlay of virtual images onto background scenes in augmented reality (AR) applications, it is crucial for the display element to achieve controllability of spectral selectivity and transmittance level. At the current stage, the transmittance of self-emissive transparent displays is limited to at most ∼60 %, constrained by the fill factor of emissive regions, restricting their scalability for immersive experiences. Although projection-based transparent screens using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable unitary computing using time-parallelized photonic lattices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exploiting alternative physical dimensions beyond the spatial domain has been intensively explored to improve the scalability in photonic computing. One approach leverages dynamical systems for time-domain computation, enabling universal and reconfigurable unitary operations. Although this method yields O(N) scaling in both device footprint and gate count, the required computation time increases by O(N ²), which hinders practical implementation due to limitations in quality factors and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Promoting Equity in Transplant Research by Addressing the Exclusion of Patients With Glomerular Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Dialysis to Destinations: Safe Travel Strategies for Patients With CKD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic kidney disease (CKD) and end-stage kidney disease (ESKD) represent growing global health burdens, driven by aging populations and increasing prevalence of diabetes and hypertension. Patients with ESKD face significant lifestyle limitations, particularly regarding mobility and travel, because of treatment schedules, medical complexity, and heightened vulnerability to complications. Air and long-distance travel pose distinct risks-cardiovascular stress, infection, and logistical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes according to absolute value vs. percentage reduction in low-density lipoprotein cholesterol levels after acute myocardial infarction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study involving 6,248 AMI patients demonstrated that the greater the LDL-C reduction from baseline, the lower the risk of MACE. However, there was no clear decreasing trend in the risk of MACE when absolute follow-up LDL-C levels were lowered from around 70 mg/dL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neonatal gut microbiota stratification and identification of SCFA-associated microbial subgroups using unsupervised clustering and machine learning classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Unsupervised clustering combined with classification analysis effectively predict SCFAs-associated subgroups and paving the way for future research on longitudinal tracking and functional genomic integration in early-life metabolic health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal dynamics of IgG-mediated immunometabolic dysfunction: from acute obesity to chronic aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immunoglobulin G (IgG) is traditionally recognized as a circulating immune effector; however, recent discoveries have revealed that IgG accumulates in adipose tissue-up to 16-fold above plasma levels-and functions as a critical mediator of metabolic dysfunction in obesity and aging. This review summarizes evidence showing that adipocyte IgG accumulation occurs via neonatal Fc receptor (FcRn)-mediated uptake and directly competes with insulin for receptor binding through Fc-CH3 domain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design and immunogenicity of a quadrivalent mRNA vaccine targeting HSV-2 with comparative evaluation of co-formulated and admixed formulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The globally prevalent herpes simplex virus 2 (HSV-2) establishes lifelong latent infections in sensory neurons and causes recurrent genital disease. However, no vaccine is available to prevent HSV-2 infection. The mRNA vaccine platform offers distinct advantages over protein-based approaches, including rapid antigen design, scalable production, and efficient intracellular expression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Midterm Outcomes of Transcatheter Aortic Valve Implantation vs Surgical Aortic Valve Replacement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TAVI and SAVR demonstrated comparable midterm survival in the real-world entire population from 2015 to 2019 in Korea. Comparable midterm survival was also demonstrated between all age-subgroups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision Closure of Postsurgical Bronchopleural Fistulas Using Vascular Plugs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AVP closure is a safe, effective, and minimally invasive approach for managing BPF, offering a promising first-line treatment option for patients unsuitable for traditional surgery. Further studies are required to validate these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Needle-free Subcision and Hyaluronic Acid Injection Using CureJet for Horizontal Neck Fold Reduction Assessed by Ultrasound and 3-dimensional Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: HA injections effectively increased dermal and subcutaneous fat thickness, reducing the appearance of HNF without complications such as nodules or lumps. The combination of needle-free subcision for adhesion release and subsequent HA volumization provided both structural and aesthetic benefits, making it a promising approach for noninvasive neck rejuvenation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Multi-modal remote sensory learning for multi-objects over autonomous devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fbioe.2025.1430222.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41425153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cavity-mediated coupling between local and nonlocal modes in Landau polaritons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The multimode ultrastrong coupling (USC) regime has emerged as a novel platform for accessing previously inaccessible phenomena in cavity quantum electrodynamics. Of particular interest are cavity-mediated correlations between local and nonlocal excitations, or equivalently, between modes at zero and finite in-plane momentum, which offer new opportunities for controlling light-matter interactions across space. However, direct experimental evidence of such interactions has remained elusive. Here,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuronal mitochondrial disaggregase CLPB ameliorates Huntington's disease pathology in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Huntington's disease (HD) is a devastating neurodegenerative disorder caused by CAG repeat expansion in the HTT gene, resulting in a polyglutamine-expanded huntingtin (HTT) protein that forms toxic aggregates. Although heat-shock proteins are known to facilitate the refolding or clearance of misfolded proteins, their precise role in modulating protein aggregation in HD remains unclear. Here, we explore the function of caseinolytic peptidase B (ClpB), a mitochondrial AAA+ ATPase and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of New IL-1R Antagonists with Improved Anti-inflammatory Efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Anakinra, a recombinant human interleukin-1 receptor antagonist (hIL-1Ra), is a widely used anti-inflammatory biologic for conditions like rheumatoid arthritis and gout. However, its limited potency and dose-dependent side effects restrict broader therapeutic application, highlighting a need for more potent and stable IL-1R antagonists. Methods: To develop improved IL-1R antagonists, we rationally designed six hIL-1Ra variants using structure-guided mutagenesis. Molecular dynamics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clearance of amyloid plaque via focused ultrasonication in a mouse model of Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The success of anti-amyloid-β (Aβ) monoclonal antibodies in recent clinical trials validates the promising approach of clearing amyloid-β in Alzheimer's therapy. Building on these successes, focused ultrasound (FUS), a non-invasive therapeutic modality that delivers acoustic energy to targeted brain regions with high precision, has emerged as a potential technique to modulate Aβ pathology, either in combination with drugs or as a standalone treatment. This study focused on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex Disparity in Cancer and Non-cancer Mortality among Korean Cancer Survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study assessed sex disparities in the causes of death (CODs), both related to cancer and non-cancer, in a nationwide database of cancer survivors in South Korea. Our database included cancer cases diagnosed in Korea between 2009 and 2016, and their CODs up to 2021. Deaths were classified into three categories: index-cancer, non-index-cancer, and non-cancer causes. Male-to-female age-standardized mortality ratios (M/F SMRs) were computed by dividing the male-specific mortality rate by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyaniline as an Integrated Amine-Redox Platform for Reversible Electrosorption and Energy-Efficient PFAS Remediation: From Molecular Mechanisms to System Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advanced water treatment technologies must integrate material function with mechanistic understanding to achieve effective and sustainable contaminant remediation. Here, we introduce polyaniline (PANI) as an integrated amine-redox platform that enables reversible electrosorption of per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS). By tuning its redox and protonation states, PANI switches between electrostatic and hydrophobic binding modes, allowing controllable capture and release. Spectroscopic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Wearable Exoskeleton for Gait Recovery in Patients With Stroke: A Multicenter Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overground gait training using an exoskeleton was not superior to conventional rehabilitation for improving ambulatory function in subacute stroke patients; however, it could provide additional lower extremity motor improvement. These findings suggest that the overground gait training with an exoskeleton might be a potential intervention for patients with subacute stroke.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning and CRISPR-Based Validation Elucidate OsWOX13 Involvement in Rice Heat Stress Tolerance and Flowering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rice (Oryza sativa) is a staple food for billions of people globally, but it faces significant yield losses due to heat stress. However, rice responses to heat stress remain understudied as compared to other stress factors. In this study, we combined meta-transcriptomics, machine learning, functional validation, and proteomic analysis to identify the key genes involved in heat stress tolerance in rice. We identified 409 meta-differentially expressed genes (meta-DEGs) between heat-tolerant and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spontaneously resolved pseudoaneurysm after valve-sparing aortic root replacement in Marfan syndrome: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pseudoaneurysm after valve-sparing aortic root replacement is uncommon but potentially life-threatening. We report an unusual case of spontaneous resolution of an aortic root pseudoaneurysm that developed in a 14-year-old boy with Marfan syndrome following valve-sparing aortic root replacement. This case suggests that, in carefully selected situations, non-surgical management with intensive follow-up may be beneficial.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sweet relief: the role of glucopuncture in neuropathic pain management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuropathic pain remains a major challenge in pain management because of its complex mechanisms and suboptimal response to conventional treatments, which often provide incomplete relief and carry the risk of adverse effects. Injections of 5% glucose in water (D5W) delivered via intradermal, subcutaneous, fascial, or perineural glucopuncture have emerged as a minimally invasive and safe therapeutic option. Although the exact mechanism has not been fully elucidated, the proposed pathways include...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene Editing of Pluripotent Stem Cell-Derived Hepatic Cells for Liver Disease Modeling and Therapeutic Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing demand for physiologically relevant human liver models has driven significant progress in generating hepatic cells and organoids derived from pluripotent stem cells. These regenerative cell sources serve as powerful platforms for elucidating the mechanisms underlying liver diseases and for evaluating drug responses under human-relevant conditions. Moreover, they hold tremendous promise as cell-based therapeutics for various hepatic disorders. The utility of these regenerative cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting YAP-TEAD Interaction with Honokiol to Inhibit Melanoma Progression and Metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Hippo-YAP/TEAD pathway plays a central role in melanoma progression by regulating tumor cell proliferation, survival, and migration. Using a NanoLuc Binary Technology (NanoBiT) protein-protein interaction assay, we screened honokiol-based small molecules and identified several analogues that disrupt the YAP-TEAD interaction. HK03 was the most effective analogue, leading to a pronounced reduction in Cyr61 levels and diminished Erk and Akt phosphorylation in B16-F10 melanoma cells. HK03 also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving Ionic Conformality Across Polymer Electrolyte|Electrode Interfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maintaining uniform ionic transport at electrode|electrolyte interfaces, i.e., ionic conformality, remains challenging in polymer electrolyte (PE)-based solid-state batteries. Morphological conformality does not necessarily imply ionic conformality. In PEs, which typically consist of a mechanically supporting component and distinct ionically conductive components, the rearrangement or depletion of mobile ion-conductive domains at interfaces can disrupt ionic transport pathways. Such localized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gapmer Antisense Oligonucleotide Targeting E-Cadherin Rescues Abnormal Keratinization in X-Linked Ichthyosis Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[X-linked ichthyosis (XLI) is an inherited disorder of keratinization resulting from a deficiency of steroid sulfatase (STS), for which no effective therapy is currently available. E-cadherin, a key upstream regulator of keratinocyte differentiation, has been found to be markedly overexpressed in STS-deficient HaCaT cells, suggesting its potential as a therapeutic target in XLI. To investigate the functional role of E-cadherin and explore its therapeutic potential, we introduced mutations into...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of a De Novo MAGEL2 Pathogenic Variant in Schaaf-Yang Syndrome and the Importance of Paternal Allele Confirmation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study underscores the importance of combining genomic sequencing with methylation assay to accurately diagnose SYS, especially for de novo variants. The proposed diagnostic workflow facilitates reliable identification of pathogenic MAGEL2 mutations and their parental origin, improving diagnostic precision in clinical settings. Further research is needed to elucidate the molecular mechanisms underlying MAGEL2-related disorders and develop targeted therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving Performance of Fully Vacuum-Evaporated Perovskite Photovoltaics via Dry Additive Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate a "dry additive" strategy to enhance fully vacuum-deposited perovskite solar cells (PSCs) by co-evaporating diphenyl sulfoxide (DPSO) as a volatile solid additive during film formation. Vacuum-processed perovskite films often exhibit high nucleation densities and small grain sizes, which limit crystallinity and increase defects. Introducing DPSO-a Lewis base that temporarily binds perovskite precursors and slows their reaction, modulates nucleation, and enables the growth of much...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamics of Apolipoprotein J Levels and Metabolic Parameters Following Bariatric Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that although overall ApoJ levels did not change significantly, individual temporal variations were associated with changes in leptin levels, indicating that ApoJ may serve as a potential biomarker after RYGB. Larger studies are needed to validate these observations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hematological inflammatory indices and Long-Term risk of depressive symptoms: a korean cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Hematological inflammatory indices including SII, SIRI, and MLR appeared to have a potential in predicting depressive symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41423792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexible monolithic 3D complementary circuits based on 2D semiconductor inks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emerging flexible and wearable electronic systems require high-density, low-power circuits that can seamlessly integrate with soft substrates. Monolithic 3D (M3D) integration using 2D semiconductors offers a compelling route in fulfilling these requirements by enabling vertical stacking without compromising mechanical compliance. However, current M3D approaches utilizing 2D semiconductors often require high-temperature processing or transfer steps that hinder their scalability on flexible...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Internal protein motion in a rough model potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proteins are understood to exhibit complex internal motions on multiple time scales in their rugged free energy landscapes and often show subdiffusive behavior that significantly influences their biochemical functions. In this study, we employ the fractional Fokker-Planck equation and continuous-time random walk models to investigate the anomalous diffusion of particles within rough confining potentials, drawing inspiration from protein internal dynamics. Our analysis reveals that the dynamics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanogap-enhanced terahertz suppression of superconductivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Superconductivity collapses when all Cooper pairs acquire energies exceeding the superconducting gap. Breaking these pairs requires photons with energy greater than the superconducting gap or strong terahertz (THz) electric fields, which has limited the practical use of superconducting devices at THz frequencies. Here, we show that GdBa(2)Cu(3)O(7-δ) (GdBCO) film integrated with 15-nm metal nanogaps exhibit Cooper pair breaking at 20 K, which is lower than its critical temperature T (c), under...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41426135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-state six-channel polarization multiplexing in reconfigurable metasurfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dynamically tunable metasurfaces based on phase-change materials (PCMs) have become important platforms for realizing reconfigurable optical systems. Nevertheless, achieving multiple independent functionalities within a single device, particularly under polarization multiplexing, remains difficult due to limited design flexibility. In this study, we present a metasurface design framework that reaches the theoretical maximum of six independent phase modulation functions by simultaneously...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41424876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Axonal Eif5a hypusination controls local translation and mitigates defects in FUS-ALS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Local protein synthesis is vital for neuronal function, but its dysregulation in neurodegenerative diseases remains poorly defined. Here we applied spatial transcriptomics to adult mouse motor nerve axons and cell bodies to enable subcellular mapping. Among transcripts found in mature axons, the most enriched biological process is protein translation, and localization of translation machinery was confirmed using multiplexed single-molecule spatial transcriptomics combined with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful re-administration after nano-liposomal irinotecan-induced severe hypersensitivity reaction: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The novelty of this report lies in presenting, for the first time, the detailed course and process by which treatment was successfully continued in a patient experiencing severe HSR upon initial nal-IRI administration, through enhanced supportive care tailored to the characteristics of the drug and stepwise dose adjustment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regeneration of the pulp-dentin complex in mature teeth using autologous demineralized dentin matrix and dental pulp stem cells: two case reports]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These cases suggest that autologous DPSCs combined with DDM can support dentin-like bridge formation and functional recovery in mature incisors, offering a potential biologically based alternative or adjunct to conventional root canal therapy for preserving structurally compromised teeth.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-invasive biomarkers in pediatric MASLD: utility of gamma-glutamyltransferase for steatohepatitis and the FIB-4 index for fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings of this study suggest that the FIB-4 index may have some utility in identifying advanced fibrosis in pediatric MASLD, although its performance might be limited compared to adult cohorts. Furthermore, GGT shows promise as a simple and non-invasive biomarker for distinguishing MASH from simple steatosis in children. Integrating GGT into future screening protocols could contribute to improved risk stratification, potentially aiding in the identification of high-risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of predictive factors for hospital admission in elderly patients transported by emergency medical services: a retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first study to identify clinical and situational factors associated with hospital admission among older patients receiving home call medical services at home or in the NH who were transported by EMS. Among these patients, hospital admission was associated with suspected infection; cardiovascular, cerebrovascular, and digestive diseases; oxygen therapy in the ED; and reduced consciousness. These findings may help guide triage and decision-making in emergency care for this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physician-reported outcomes associated with collaboration between home healthcare institutions and after-hours house-call services in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[L-ascorbate prevents non-alcoholic steatohepatitis-based hepatocarcinogenesis in Sod1/Prdx4 double-knockout mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Superoxide dismutase 1 (Sod1) and peroxiredoxin 4 (Prdx4) double knockout (DKO) causes symptoms similar to non-alcoholic steatohepatitis (NASH) even at younger ages. This study revealed that DKO mice exhibited high mortality, and surviving DKO mice developed hepatocellular carcinoma within the first year of life. Administration of physiological doses of L-ascorbate (Asc; 1.5 mg/mL) in drinking water reduced mortality and effectively prevented tumor development. Oxidative stress due to SOD1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The overlapping impacts of heat and COVID-19 on mortality in Flanders, Belgium: a time-stratified case-crossover analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The compound occurrence of extreme heat and the COVID-19 pandemic may have increased mortality risk beyond the impact of each factor alone. However, the interaction between these two risk factors and their combined effect on mortality has not been adequately quantified. We conducted a time-stratified case-crossover analysis of daily all-cause mortality, minimum temperature, and COVID-19 case counts in Flanders over the period 2018-2021. We applied a distributed lag nonlinear model (DLNM) with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation for acquired pure red cell aplasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acquired pure red cell aplasia (PRCA) affects only the red blood cell lineage and responds to immunosuppressive therapy. Few reports describe the outcome of allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation (allo-HSCT) for refractory PRCA. This study investigated the outcomes of allo-HSCT for PRCA using Japanese nationwide registry data. Eight patients aged 16 years or older who underwent allo-HSCT for acquired PRCA were analyzed. Median ages at diagnosis of PRCA and HSCT were 39.5 (range...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term progression-free survivors ("super responders") to olaparib maintenance in recurrent ovarian cancer: a multicenter real-world study (KCOG-G2101s)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this real-world cohort, a subset of patients with recurrent ovarian cancer achieved durable, potentially curative responses with olaparib maintenance, regardless of their BRCA mutation status. When evaluating PARP inhibitor therapy, long-term progression-free survival should be considered a key endpoint.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41430003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infant social withdrawal and rapid infant weight gain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We found an association between infant social withdrawal and subsequent rapid infant weight gain independently of an array of known risk factors, which may expand our understanding of the developmental origins of excess weight gain and its association with early childhood mental health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding cnidarian cell type gene regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Animal cell types are defined by differential access to genomic information-a process orchestrated by the combinatorial activity of transcription factors that bind to cis-regulatory elements (CREs) to control gene expression. Changes in these gene regulatory networks (GRNs) underlie the origin and diversification of cell types, yet the regulatory logic and specific GRNs that define cell identities remain poorly resolved across the animal tree of life. Cnidarians, as early-branching metazoans,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blockade of CC chemokine receptor 2 suppresses pancreatic cancer progression through the interaction with macrophages in the tumor microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Annealing strategy for enhancing the fracture toughness of MoSiBTiC alloys]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An optimal annealing process for enhancing the room-temperature fracture toughness of MoSiBTiC alloys was investigated in this study. The alloy with a composition of Mo-5Si-10B-10Ti-10C (at%) was subjected to three annealing conditions to control its microstructure. Quantitative microstructural analysis and mechanical testing revealed that the toughness of the MoSiBTiC alloys increased with the size of the Mo(ss) phase and decreased with its hardness. Annealing at 1800 °C for 24 h promoted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morpholino-RNA duplex exhibits robust, sustained, and safe steric-block antisense activity by intracerebroventricular and intrathecal injection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intrathecal injection of steric-block antisense oligonucleotides (ASOs) provides therapeutic opportunities for targeting the central nervous system (CNS). Phosphorothioate backbone with 2'-O-methoxyethyl (MOE) is widely used in ASO drugs, with concerns about toxicity and potency. Phosphorodiamidate morpholino oligomer (PMO) is another chemistry with a favorable safety profile but less persistent effect due to its ineffective cellular uptake and poor binding affinity to serum proteins. Here, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resident alveolar macrophages are highly susceptible to the induction of RIPK1/RIPK3-mediated necroptosis which promote efficient pulmonary immune response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alveolar macrophages (AMs) play a crucial role in protecting the lungs from pathogens by inducing immunogenic cell death (ICD). However, the type of cell death that effectively induces protective immunity remains to be fully understood. In our investigation of the mechanisms regulating AM activation and lung immune responses, we found that AMs are highly susceptible to necroptosis, a form of ICD. Treatment with pan-caspase inhibitors, such as emricasan or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multifunctionality analysis of serine hydroxymethyltransferases from human and Escherichia coli]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Serine hydroxymethyltransferase (SHMT) catalyzes the conversion of l-serine and tetrahydrofolate (THF) to glycine and 5,10-methylenetetrahydrofolate, respectively. In a previous study, we found that human and Escherichia coli SHMTs possess THF-dependent d-serine dehydratase activity, which degrades d-serine to pyruvate and ammonia. Some activities including aldolase and racemase activities have also been reported for SHMTs. In the present study, we investigated the multifunctionality of E. coli...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The comet assay as a tool in human biomonitoring studies: Effects of confounding factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The comet assay is widely used in human biomonitoring studies of environmental and occupational exposures. However, it is clear from multiple studies that various types of confounding factors might affect the direct relationship between exposure and DNA damage in the comet assay. In addition to common confounders such as age, sex, and smoking, other factors considered to be important determinants for background levels of DNA damage in the comet assay include exhaustive physical exercise, chronic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling regions associated with acute and late breast side-effects from breast radiotherapy using voxel-wise image-based data mining analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We found regions within the breast where the local dose associates with breast side-effects after breast RT. This result opens a new hypothesis which could help reduce side-effects after breast radiotherapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Feasibility of AI-Driven Automated Virtual Dental Implant Placement: A Cross-Sectional Comparative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The AI tool showed clinically valid implant selection, matched expert placement and planning in virtual implant positioning for missing mandibular premolars and molars while being highly consistent and 10 times faster compared to human expert planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating stimuli-responsive liposomes for cutaneous applications: a guide to stimuli recognition and characterization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent years, stimuli-responsive liposomes have been proposed as advanced nanocarriers for cutaneous drug delivery. These liposomes are designed to release their cargo in response to specific triggers. A critical challenge in their development is the robust characterization of this responsive behavior to validate their performance. This review provides a methodological guide for comprehensively characterizing stimuli-responsive liposomes. The proposed guide systematically discusses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Binding Investigation of Non-Toxic Compounds from Plant-Based Repellents Targeting Aedes aegypti Odorant-Binding Protein 1 using Molecular Dynamics Simulations and Density Functional Theory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Due to the effects of global warming, dengue and chikungunya virus infections have become significant global health concerns. Aedes aegypti is a known vector of these viruses. Based on the known mosquito repellents, there are many drawbacks and side effects in either human or environment. In this study, the disruption of the olfactory system targeting on Aedes aegypti odorant-binding protein 1 (AaegOBP1) by using the new candidates from nine plants which are known plant-based repellents was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Positive childhood experiences and adulthood loneliness and social participation in Japan: Exploring their mitigating effects for adverse childhood experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Community-based PCEs can protect against loneliness and promote social engagement, even among those with childhood adversity. These findings support strengthening community support systems to enhance long-term social well-being.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal and neonatal outcomes after infection with monkeypox virus clade I during pregnancy in DR Congo: a pooled, prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Monkeypox virus (MPXV) has been linked to vertical transmission, but systematic data are scarce. We aimed to describe the sociodemographic, clinical, and virological characteristics and assess the frequency and determinants of adverse outcomes in pregnant women with MPXV clade I infection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ecological momentary assessment in hearing healthcare: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: EMA offers a complementary approach for assessing real-world hearing experiences. Future research should focus on consistent methods, protocol standardisation, cultural adaptation, demographic diversity, and multimodal input to enhance EMA's clinical value.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis and structure-activity relationship of azithromycin derivatives against non-tuberculous mycobacteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-tuberculous mycobacteria (NTM), particularly Mycobacterium avium complex (MAC), have emerged as significant pulmonary pathogens. Current first-line treatments for pulmonary MAC disease typically involve the macrolide azithromycin (AZM). However, the increasing prevalence of drug-resistant MAC has created an urgent need for new therapeutics. Here, we present a novel series of Glc-AZM derivatives, KU15 to KU27, featuring C11 glucosyl moieties designed to anchor the macrolide to the ribosome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modification of Alkylpyridine Ligands in the Reactions of Osmium(III) Complexes with Anions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osmium(III) complexes supported by N-methyl-di(pyridin-2-ylmethyl)amine (DPA), 4,4'-dimethyl-2,2'-bipyridyl (Me(2)-bpy), and N¹,N¹,N³,N³-tetrakis(pyridin-2-ylmethyl)propane-1,3-diamine (TPPN) ligands were synthesized, and their reactivities toward a fluoride anion were examined. Crystal structures of the osmium(III) complexes showed that the metal centers adopted octahedral iso-structures with the osmium(II) centers of the one-electron reduced complexes. In the reaction with a fluoride anion,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41429018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visualization of Experience Sampling Method Data in Mental Health: Qualitative Study of the Physicians' Perspective in Germany]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings underline the importance of designing digital tools that align with clinical needs while addressing potential barriers to implementation by exploring the opportunities and challenges associated with ESM visualizations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chiral Plasmonic Surface Temperature Switching by Several Tens of Kelvins in Titanium Nitride Nanostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The strong asymmetric optical response of plasmonic metal nanostructures to right- and left-handed circularly polarized light has attracted great interest in nanotechnology. However, when considering heat generation in these structures, the surface temperature distribution becomes nearly isothermal regardless of which handedness of circularly polarized light is used. This is because of the high thermal conductivity of noble metals and the diffusive nature of heat transfer. In this study, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tip-Scan High-Speed Atomic Force Microscopy in Organic Solvent: A Versatile Tool for Visualizing Dynamic Behaviors of Soft-Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-speed atomic force microscopy (HS-AFM) is a powerful tool for video recording the nanoscale dynamics of samples. Its applications have recently expanded to various fields from biology to chemistry, including supramolecular chemistry and polymer science. Furthermore, the development of a stand-alone tip-scan HS-AFM has offered greater flexibility in installation. As it can be mounted on an optical microscope for integration with optical techniques, it holds great promise for supramolecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical significance of t(11;14) translocation in systemic AL amyloidosis in the era of daratumumab therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The chromosomal translocation t(11;14)(q13;q32) is frequently observed in systemic light-chain (AL) amyloidosis, yet its clinical significance in the era of daratumumab-based therapy remains unclear. To compare clinical and cytogenetic characteristics, we retrospectively analyzed 68 patients with systemic AL amyloidosis and 107 patients with multiple myeloma (MM) newly diagnosed at Kumamoto University Hospital, with the MM cohort serving as a reference cohort. t(11;14) was detected in 55.9% of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibacterial Activity, Phytochemical Composition, and Cytotoxicity Evaluation of Select Medicinal Plants from Bangladesh]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bangladesh's rich plant diversity offers an underexplored source of plant-based antibacterials with the potential to strengthen sustainable aquaculture. This study evaluated the in vitro antibacterial efficacy of 55 Bangladeshi plants against five key fish pathogens, including Aeromonas hydrophila, Pseudomonas fluorescens, Pseudomonas aeruginosa, Flavobacterium columnare, and Streptococcus iniae. The findings revealed numerous plant extracts with potential antibacterial activity against test...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preclinical characterization of 3p-C-DEPA<sub>-NCS</sub> and 3p-C-DEPA<sub>-TFP</sub>-PEG<sub>4</sub> as potential Actinium-225 bifunctional chelators using DOTA<sub>-NCS</sub> and macropa<sub>-NCS</sub> as benchmarks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: 3p-C-DEPA(-TFP)-PEG₄ demonstrated excellent potential as a bifunctional chelator for ^(225)Ac, showing high radiolabelling efficiency under mild conditions and outstanding in vitro stability of the resulting ^(225)Ac-labelled bioconjugate. Further preclinical studies are warranted to validate its therapeutic potential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The efficacy of intraoperative external biliary drainage tubes for late benign biliary strictures in hepaticojejunostomy after pancreaticoduodenectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with CHD diameter < 7 mm, an EBD tube should be placed in the H-J during PD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of autonomic dysfunction on sleep disturbance in drug-naïve patients with Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multiple autonomic domains may contribute to SD in drug-naïve patients with PD. Early identification and management of autonomic dysfunction could improve sleep quality and overall quality of life in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel sheath system to improve target access for preoperative mapping biopsy: A randomized trial to inform surgical planning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite comparable ITT success due to rescue crossover, SS achieved reliable duct access and may inform surgical planning. When selective biliary access is difficult with the conventional method, novel SS is a useful alternative for preoperative MB.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41428008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut Microbiota Modulation by Pomegranate Extract: Insights from a Controlled Supplementation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Regular consumption of pomegranate, a polyphenol-rich fruit, is associated with multiple health benefits. As polyphenols reach the colon, they interact with the gut microbiota, influencing both its composition and metabolic activity. This study investigated the impact of a one-week supplementation with two doses of the commercial pomegranate extract Oxylent^(®) (1.3 and 2.6 g/day) on gut microbiota and metabolite production using the SHIME^(®) system. Bacterial metabolite production, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41427997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251223024250&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>