<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 07:38:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilising multi-modal data-driven network analysis to identify monotherapy and combinational therapy targets in SOX2-dependent squamous cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drug discovery requires understanding disease mechanisms, making the integration of multi-modal data essential. These data types, including omics, disease-associated, and pathway information, must be combined to uncover therapeutic insights. We developed iPANDDA, a computational pipeline that integrates these data through a network-based approach to predict candidate drug targets for specific diseases. We applied iPANDDA to lung squamous cell carcinoma (LUSC), a subtype of non-small cell lung...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SwinCLNet: a robust framework for brain tumor segmentation via shifted window attention and cross-scale fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting relapsed/refractory and MRD + Ph + ALL: olverembatinib-venetoclax bridging enhances allo-HSCT outcome​]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Olverembatinib is a novel third-generation TKI available in mainland China. However, there are only a few published clinical reports. In this study, we aimed to investigate the efficacy and safety of an olverembatinib-venetoclax regimen before bridging to HSCT in adult Ph/BCR-ABL1 + ALL patients with refractory/relapsed disease (n = 2) or persistent minimal residual disease (MRD) (n = 15). Seventeen Ph + ALL patients who were admitted to our center between February 2022 and January 2023 were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrolyte-Engineered Photoelectrochemical Ammonia Oxidation Enabling Sustainable Hydrogen Production via Catalyst Regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ammonia oxidation reaction (AOR) offers a promising carbon-free hydrogen production pathway under ambient conditions, yet practical implementation faces critical challenges from catalyst deactivation and competing side reactions in aqueous systems. We present an electrolyte-engineered approach to photoelectrochemical (PEC) AOR that enables both enhanced hydrogen production and reversible catalyst regeneration. By employing a non-aqueous acetonitrile electrolyte at the BiVO(4) photoanode, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interferon-stimulated gene GALNT2 restricts respiratory virus infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The innate immune response involves interferons (IFNs), antiviral cytokines that upregulate numerous IFN-stimulated genes, many of which have uncharacterized functions and mechanisms. Here we performed transcriptomic profiling of lung tissues from wild-type and IFNAR^(-/-) mice infected with SARS-CoV-2 and single-cell RNA sequencing of bronchoalveolar lavage fluid and peripheral blood mononuclear cells from patients with COVID-19. We identified O-GalNAc transferase 2 (GALNT2), an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling noise reduction mechanism of serrated orifices from hydrodynamic-acoustic decoupling perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study experimentally unveils the noise reduction capabilities of serrated orifices, focusing on the hydrodynamic-acoustic pressure fluctuations decoupling perspective during the noise reduction process. Acoustic measurements were performed on orifices with varying percent open areas (φ = 11%, 20%, and 31%) and serration counts. Two distinct pressure fluctuation reduction regions were identified: a rapid growth region, characterized by efficient pressure fluctuation reduction, and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of a novel compound that induces oligomer disassembly of the pyruvate dehydrogenase E2 complex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pyruvate dehydrogenase complex (PDC) is a multienzyme system that links glycolysis to the tricarboxylic acid cycle via oxidative decarboxylation of pyruvate. Among its catalytic components, the E2 subunit forms a 60-mer oligomeric core that provides both structural and functional support. While PDC activity is classically regulated through phosphorylation of the E1α subunit by pyruvate dehydrogenase kinase, this mechanism often fails under pathological conditions such as pancreatic ductal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In silico virtual screening of natural small molecules for dual inhibition of Aβ and tau aggregation in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is defined by the accumulation of amyloid beta (Aβ) plaques and twisted fibers of hyperphosphorylated tau, with their aggregation driving neurodegeneration and cognitive decline. Presently, the majority of therapies in development are largely single-targeted, focusing either on Aβ or tau aggregation. This highlights a significant gap in strategies that can simultaneously modulate aggregation of both proteins in AD. This study employed an integrated in silico approach to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simulations of low-frequency vibration pattern at the inner ear for activation of the vestibular system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vestibular stimulation is a promising method for mitigating motion sickness and assessing vestibular function. However, conventional methods such as galvanic, caloric, or bone conduction (BC) stimulation lack the spatial selectivity needed to replicate the precise inputs of natural head movements. In this study, a novel approach is proposed using multiple BC transducers with coordinated magnitude and phase to generate targeted vestibular motions. A validated finite element model of the human...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Measurement of the Quadrupole Moment of the 2_{1}^{+} State in ^{110}Sn]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Sn isotopic chain, exhibiting double shell closures at ^{100}Sn and ^{132}Sn, is a key testing ground for theoretical models of the atomic nucleus. It was originally predicted that the transitional matrix elements between the first 2^{+} state and the 0^{+} ground state for the even-even isotopes in this chain should show a simple dependence on the neutron number. This prediction was, however, disproven experimentally in some of the first experiments with postaccelerated radioactive beams, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two-Dimensional Nucleic Acid Brushes on Colloidal MXene Sheets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA immobilization on nanoparticle surfaces enables programmable assembly, gene sensing, and intracellular delivery. However, dense, direct functionalization of atomically thin two-dimensional (2D) materials remains challenging due to their inert basal planes. In contrast, 2D transition metal carbides (MXenes) possess highly polar, chemically active surfaces terminated with -OH, -O-, and -F groups, offering a unique platform for biofunctionalization. Herein, we exploit MXene's surface chemistry...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Metabolic Surgery for Obese Type 2 Diabetes: Korean Multicenter Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep-learning analysis of speech using mel-spectrograms for the assessment of mild cognitive impairment and Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundSpeech abnormalities are recognized as early indicators of Alzheimer's disease (AD) and mild cognitive impairment (MCI).ObjectiveTo determine whether deep-learning models trained on mel-spectrograms of brief speech tasks can (i) discriminate individuals with MCI and AD from cognitively normal controls (NC) and (ii) estimate cognitive status with clinically useful accuracy.MethodsSpeech from 594 participants (185 NC, 231 MCI, 178 AD) was recorded through a mobile application that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Near-Infrared Responsive Ionoelastomer Junction Enabling Switchable Ionic Logic Gate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the significant progress in the development of ionic junctions of two types of ionic conductors for ionic current rectification, reminiscent to electronic p- and n-type junctions, stimuli-responsive ionic junctions wherein stimuli reversibly control current rectification are seldom demonstrated. Here, we present a near-infrared (NIR)-responsive ionic junction and its application as a switchable logic gate. The NIR- responsive ionic junction is developed with a bilayer of ionoelastomers:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-Step Synthesis of Open Hierarchical ZSM-5: Influence of the Temperature Ramping Rate on Morphology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exploration of zeolites with various morphologies has received significant attention as a strategy to enhance their catalytic performance and elongate their lifetime. This study presents open hierarchical ZSM-5 which consists of micropores and mesopores, with a further extension to macropores owing to the presence of open structures. A one-step facile synthetic strategy features utilization of tubular reactors for precise and rapid temperature control, where faster ramping rates play a critical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined Metal-Metal and Metal-Ligand Cooperativity in Dicopper-Catalyzed Azide-Alkyne Cycloaddition Reactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mechanism of the copper-catalyzed azide-alkyne cycloaddition (CuAAC) reaction has been under investigation for over two decades. While catalytically relevant dicopper intermediates have been proposed and a few suspected intermediates have been isolated, the mechanism remains poorly understood. In this work, we describe the synthesis and characterization of neutral dicopper complexes bearing the proton-responsive dinucleating ^(iPr ) PNNP "expanded pincer" ligand, which are demonstrated to be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amino-Functionalized Surface Engineering of Elastomers for Robust PEDOT:PSS-Based Stretchable Electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stretchable devices have attracted significant attention due to their mechanical versatility and potential applications in wearable electronics, soft robotics, and biomedical devices. However, their practical implementation is often hindered by challenges in surface engineering, particularly at the interface between stretchable elastomers and conducting polymers like poly(3,4-ethylenedioxythiophene):poly(styrenesulfonate) (PEDOT:PSS). This study introduces a novel strategy to enhance the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[N-acetylcysteine Restores Impaired Dentate Gyrus Neurogenesis in a Neonatal Maternal Separation Rat Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early-life stress (ELS) is a major contributor to neurodevelopmental vulnerability, particularly within the dentate gyrus (DG), where oxidative burden and microglial activation disrupt adult neurogenesis. Here, we examined whether N-acetylcysteine (NAC), a cysteine prodrug and glutathione precursor, could counteract impaired neurogenesis induced by neonatal maternal separation (NMS). Adolescent NAC administration restored the number of Ki67^(+) proliferating progenitors and DCX^(+) immature...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extended Follow-Up Analysis of First-Line Atezolizumab in Extensive-Stage Small Cell Lung Cancer: A Real-World Multicenter Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study outlined the real-world effectiveness and safety of first-line atezolizumab immunochemotherapy for ES-SCLC patients over an extended follow-up, noting that local treatment and post-progression therapy were associated with improved survival.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A 32-Year-Old Male Patient Presented With Symptoms of Indigestion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optogenetic regulation of chloride ions in reactive astrocytes may mitigate Parkinson's disease pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent investigations underscore the pivotal role of reactive astrocytes in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease (PD). As PD advances, reactive astrocytes lose their ability to degrade α-Synuclein (α-Syn) aggregates while concurrently increasing r-aminobutyric acid (GABA) secretion, which heightens inhibition of DA neurons and worsens the disease. This study explored optogenetic manipulation of reactive astrocytes as a therapeutic strategy. Halorhodopsin (NpHR), a chloride pump, was expressed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide study of income-based disparities in diabetic limb preservation in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Income-based disparities has a profound impact on health outcomes by limiting access to preventive care, early diagnosis, and effective treatment with chronic conditions such as diabetes. Our aim was to investigate the impact of income-based disparities on diabetic foot amputation rates, focusing on disparities in outcomes among income levels. This retrospective cohort study used data from the Korean National Health Insurance Service database that tracked 2,580,585 diabetic patients between 2009...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal resistance training strategies for knee osteoarthritis symptom relief: a systematic review and network meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identifies high-speed RT as the most effective type for managing KOA and provides optimal RT dosages for different symptoms. These findings emphasize the need for tailored RT programs and provide crucial insights for clinical guidelines and individualized patient care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vancomycin heteroresistance (hVISA) in MRSA links to treatment failure and supports a revised PAP-AUC threshold]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heteroresistance to vancomycin among methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA) remains a diagnostic and therapeutic problem in clinical microbiology. In this prospective cohort study of 842 adult patients with MRSA bacteremia in S. Korea, we investigate the prevalence, risk factors, and clinical implications of the heteroresistant vancomycin-intermediate S. aureus (hVISA) phenotype. The hVISA phenotype is detected in 22% of cases. Multivariable regression analysis reveals strong...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Super El Niño events drive climate regime shifts with enhanced risks under global warming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate regime shifts (CRSs), characterized by abrupt and persistent transitions between alternative stable states in the climate system, pose serious threats to ecosystems and human well-being. Understanding the potential drivers of CRSs is crucial, particularly in a warming world where CRSs are becoming more frequent. Here, using multiple observations and model simulations, we find that the likelihood of CRS occurrence significantly increases in the context of super El Niño events due to their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ubiquitin-Specific Protease 20 Promotes CCCP-Induced Mitophagy Through Deubiquitination and Stabilization of Serine/Threonine Protein Kinase PINK1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While Parkinson's disease (PD) is predominantly sporadic, various mutations in the PTEN-induced putative kinase 1 (PINK1) gene have been linked to the autosomal recessive form of PD. PINK1, a serine/threonine protein kinase, holds a pivotal role in mitophagy - a process that selectively eliminates damaged mitochondria, overseeing mitochondrial quality control and ultimately safeguarding against neuronal cell loss in PD. Understanding the regulation of PINK1 stability is essential in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring New Dimensions in Longitudinal Rosacea Management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rosacea is a common, chronic, inflammatory disease of the skin, which predominantly (but not exclusively) affects the centrofacial region. Clinical features may include transient or persistent facial erythema, recurrent flushing, telangiectasia, papules, pustules, phymatous changes, and ocular disturbances. These can lead to significant physical and psychological burden and discomfort, which adversely affects a patient's quality of life (QoL). While current guidelines provide recommendations on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Software belief reliability growth model incorporating change point and imperfect debugging based on uncertain differential equation approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many software reliability growth models (SRGMs) have been proposed by researchers within the context of probability theory to estimate software reliability, remaining number of faults and optimal release time. The Fault Detection Rate (FDR) may vary because of changes in testing strategies. Due to lack of knowledge of software code, the testing team might be unable to rectify the detected faults thereby introducing new faults during the fault correction process. The debugging process is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Native CFTR codon bias controls translation rate to balance off-pathway aggregation and channel function by conformational imprinting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein folding in vivo is biologically tuned to minimize off-pathway events and optimize native folding outcomes. A key factor in this process is biased synonymous codon usage, in which synonymous codons modulate local translation rate while maintaining the native amino acid sequence. Here, we demonstrate that native codon usage within the first nucleotide-binding domain (NBD1) of the cystic fibrosis transmembrane conductance regulator (CFTR) induces a translational pause during a critical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacological activation of SERCA2 reverses ER calcium dysregulation and depression-like behaviors in hyperglycemic mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Family responses and influencing factors in raising children with developmental disabilities: A cross-sectional study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Family responses, which encompass how families respond to raise children with developmental disabilities (DDs) and manage their child's condition, have a profound impact on both the child and the family as a whole. Demographic and contextual factors contribute to shaping family responses and overall experiences. Gaining a comprehensive understanding of family responses to raising children with DDs and the influencing factors is essential. This study examined how families responded to caring for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[n-doping of organic semiconductors catalysed by organometallic complexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Molecular doping is essential for optimizing carrier concentration, charge mobility, and energy levels of organic semiconductors (OSCs), thereby enhancing device performance. However, efficient n(electron)-type doping remains challenging, as conventional techniques often fail to achieve high doping efficiency with minimal counterion-induced disorder under mild conditions. Here, we present a catalysed n-doping strategy for OSCs using air-stable, cost-effective, and commercially available soluble...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residue-free peeling of EGaIn oxide enabled by contact angle control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gallium-based liquid metals (GBLMs) are widely used in soft machines and stretchable electronics, but their nanometer-thick surface oxide layer induces strong adhesion to substrates, making residue-free removal challenging. Conventional methods rely on harsh chemical treatments, limiting practical applications. Here, we show that the oxide layer of eutectic gallium-indium (EGaIn) can be cleanly peeled from a substrate when a sufficiently large contact angle is maintained during slow...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxide-hybridized carbon as a catalyst support for efficient anion exchange membrane water electrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The performance of anion exchange membrane water electrolysis, a key technology for achieving net-zero carbon emissions, can be improved by introducing an appropriate catalyst support. However, the ideal support material for water electrolysis remains debatable. Recent efforts focused on enhancing the corrosion resistance by using highly crystalline carbon as a carbon-based support. Despite this progress, the defects intrinsic to carbon emphasize the need for effective passivation strategies to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Mechanistic and Morphologic Approach to Managing Benign Central Airway Obstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrastrong Plasmon-Phonon Coupling Enabled by Acoustic Graphene Plasmons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vibrational ultrastrong coupling (USC) opens new opportunities for controlling chemical reactivity and advancing mid-infrared nanophotonics. Here, we demonstrate USC in an ultrathin polar dielectric using acoustic graphene plasmons (AGPs). Unlike conventional graphene plasmons, whose coupling weakens with a reduced dielectric thickness, AGPs maintain strong coupling through enhanced field confinement in narrow dielectric gaps. This enables strong coupling in a polar film as thin as λ/8,000 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preclinical Proof of Concept for the Single-Protein Anticancer Molecule Targeting Both a Tumor Surface Antigen and an Intracellular Oncoprotein]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs) are a widely used platform for developing various anticancer immunotherapeutics, the use of cancer non-selective chemicals is recognized as a drawback of ADC development. To address the issues regarding the safety and manufacturing complexity of ADCs, this study conceptualizes a single-protein platform, named dual-targeting anticancer therapeutics (DTAT), that links a cancer cell-selective cytotoxic peptide to an antibody via a linker peptide cleavable on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hot Electron-Assisted Noble-Metal-Free Synergistic Photothermal Catalyst for Solar-Driven Wastewater Remediation and Microbial Disinfection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The escalating challenge of water contamination by recalcitrant organic pollutants and pathogens calls for sustainable, solar-powered technologies that operate without external energy or chemical inputs. Such systems require multifunctional materials capable of harvesting broad-spectrum sunlight to generate reactive oxygen species (ROS) for simultaneous degradation and disinfection. Conventional photocatalysts are hindered by their limited spectral absorption and rapid charge recombination,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetic and Crystal Symmetry Control on Spin Hall Conductivity in Altermagnets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Altermagnets combine zero net magnetization with spin splitting, opening new opportunities for next-generation spintronic devices. In this work, the unconventional spin Hall conductivity (USHC) in three representative materials-RuO(2), CrSb, and MnTe is explored. It is clarified how distinct magnetic and crystal symmetries modulate their spin Hall responses. RuO(2) exhibits only trivial USHC under a tilted geometry, demonstrating that symmetry projections alone can induce apparent unconventional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cascade System Bridging Xanthine Oxidation and L-Arginine for Highly Effective and Non-Toxic Surface Microbial Decontamination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study proposes highly efficient microbial decontamination, employing the synergy between nanobiocatalysis, allowing for highly stable and highly loaded enzyme system, and in situ generation of antimicrobial nitric oxide (NO) from amino acid (l-arginine). Xanthine oxidase (XO) catalyzes the oxidation of xanthine to produce hydrogen peroxide, which reacts with l-arginine, releasing potent antimicrobial agents of nitric oxide. Both loading and stability of the XO enzyme are enhanced by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<sup>*</sup>OH Adsorption-Mediated Electrochemical Oxidation of 5-Hydroxymethylfurfural to Selective 2,5-Furandicarboxylic Acid at pH 12]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Strongly alkaline electrolytes are typically used for electrochemical 5-hydroxymethylfurfural oxidation (HMFOR) to selective 2,5-furandicarboxylic acid (FDCA) production, despite HMF degradation. Although HMF remains stable in weakly alkaline media, slow kinetics due to limited OH^(-) concentration hinder active FDCA formation. Herein, unlike the CuO or NiOOH catalyst, significantly improved direct aldehyde oxidation is demonstrated via the utilization of adsorbed OH (^(*)OH) on the CuO/NiOOH...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Evidence of Long-Term Dulaglutide Use: Sustained Glycemic and Weight Improvements Beyond Three Years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dulaglutide provided durable improvements in glycemic control and weight reduction for more than 3 years, even in patients with long-standing T2DM and comorbidities. These results support its role as a long-term treatment option in real-world clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toxicity Comparison between a Four-Week Moderate Hypofractionation and a Six-Week Conventional Fractionation in the Post-Prostatectomy Salvage Radiotherapy for Prostate Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Four-week HFRT for SRT showed favorable long-term toxicity outcomes, sustained for up to 2 years and comparable to those of 6-week CFRT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interlocking sectional custom tray technique for closed-mouth impression with simultaneous occlusal registration in maxillofacial defect restoration: A dental technique]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Impression making for obturator fabrication in patients with a maxillectomy and extensive maxillary defects can be challenging because of anatomic complexity, restricted mouth opening, and difficulty in achieving an effective seal. This article presents an interlocking sectional tray technique in which the intaglio surface of an existing obturator is merged with intraoral scan data to design a custom tray without a cast. The interlocking sectional tray system enables separate recording of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of metabolic health and obesity with apolipoprotein B and low-density lipoprotein cholesterol discordance in a large Korean cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ApoB-LDL-C discordance is common, even among metabolically healthy individuals, and is primarily driven by metabolic dysfunction rather than by obesity. ApoB measurements should be included in routine cardiovascular risk assessments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linvoseltamab in Patients With Relapsed/Refractory Multiple Myeloma in the LINKER-MM1 Study: Longer Follow-Up and Subgroup Analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Long-term treatment with linvoseltamab 200 mg provided deep and durable responses, with no new safety signals, and thus represents an effective therapeutic option in RRMM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exercise-focused wellness interventions for middle-aged adults: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Exercise-focused wellness interventions for middle-aged adults encompass varied content and outcome variables, contributing to improvements in physical, psychological and social dimensions of health. Delivery modes are diverse, demonstrating flexibility and adaptability for tailored interventions. There is a need to develop a validated, midlife-specific measurement tool that reflects the multidimensional nature of wellness. Moreover, exercise-focused interventions tailored for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilisation of in-person and telehealth care among US adults with loneliness and social isolation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compared with adults who are not lonely or socially isolated, adults experiencing loneliness and social isolation are more likely to use telehealth and less likely to use in-person care. Telehealth may serve as a viable alternative for individuals facing social challenges in accessing in-person services.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the Complexity of Chinese Nonengaged Youths' Career-Related Competencies Through Latent Class Analysis: Examining Their Profiles, Mental Health, and Social Well-Being]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings highlighted the significance of CLCs for the mental health and social well-being of NEYs during their school-to-work transition. Despite limitations, this study contributed to understanding the subtypes of NEYs regarding CLCs and offered insights for intervention services aimed at enhancing NEYs' CLCs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effective Degradation of Wild-Type and Mutant EGFR Using Self-Assembling Peptide-Derived PROTAC Nanoparticles (NanoTACs) for Cancer Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR)-targeted therapeutics, including monoclonal antibodies (mAbs) and tyrosine kinase inhibitors (TKIs), have achieved clinical success but are limited by drug resistance and off-target toxicity. Herein, self-assembling peptide-derived PROTAC nanoparticles (NanoTACs) engineered for effective degradation of both wild-type and mutant EGFR for cancer therapy is reported. The NanoTACs are constructed from three peptide components: EGFR-binding peptide (EHGAMEI), a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postobstructive Diuresis in a Cat Associated With Traumatic Urethral Rupture and Abdominal Compartment Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: To describe abdominal compartment syndrome (ACS) associated with postobstructive diuresis (POD) in a cat with urethral rupture.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Clinical Diagram to Guide Optimal Coronoapical Positioning of Bone-Level Implant Relative to Orofacial Placement in the Esthetic Zone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The visual diagram supplements digital workflows by providing a practical, geometry-based reference for implant depth relative to the prosthetic implant platform. It is particularly valuable in esthetically demanding cases, enabling clinicians to make objective decisions that integrate prosthetic and biologic considerations, in line with the bio-restorative concept.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial for: "A Time-Efficient Alternative to 3-Scan Trace DWI for Breast Lesion Evaluation at 3.0 T-Phantom Study and Clinical Assessment"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of chronic lung disease, socioeconomic status, and family history on lung cancer risk in never-smokers: a matched case-control study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: While lung cancer screening programs aimed at high-risk smokers have effectively reduced mortality rates, the risk factors for lung cancer in never-smokers (LCINS) remain poorly understood.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-short-term effects of fine particulate matter (PM2.5) exposure on heart rate variability in susceptible and vulnerable individuals using real-time personal monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While epidemiological studies have examined the effects of exposure to particulate matter with diameter ≤2.5 μm (PM2.5) on heart rate variability (HRV) on a daily basis, there is a need for more granular data to better understand the ultrashort-term effects of PM2.5 on HRV. This study aimed to investigate the minute-level association between PM2.5 exposure and HRV using real-time personal monitoring data, focusing on time-lagged effects in vulnerable populations. We collected minute-by-minute...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Carotid Plaque Progression and the Role of Intraplaque Hemorrhage: A Deep Learning-Based Analysis of Longitudinal Vessel Wall Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Deep learning-based segmentation pipelines were utilized to identify IPH, quantify IPH volume, and measure their effects on carotid plaque burden during long-term follow-up. Findings demonstrated that IPH may persist for extended periods. While arteries without IPH demonstrated minimal progression under contemporary treatment, presence of IPH and greater IPH volume significantly accelerated long-term plaque growth.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VEGF-B: A multifaceted modulator with emerging therapeutic applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Long overshadowed by VEGF-A, vascular endothelial growth factor B (VEGF-B) has emerged as a critical regulator of vascular, metabolic, and immune cross-talk. Unlike the potent angiogenic factor VEGF-A, VEGF-B does not induce vascular leakage but modulates tissue-specific functions, including fatty acid transport, neuronal survival, and immunometabolism, through its receptors VEGFR1 and NRP1. Its roles are often paradoxical, suppressing angiogenesis in some cancers while promoting metastasis and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical coherence tomography-derived biomarkers for disease severity in choroideremia and choroideremia carriers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The total number of HF and choroidal HF in the fovea showed significant associations with disease severity measures in CHM, suggesting potential utility as structural biomarkers alongside established OCT parameters. No OCT-derived biomarkers were significantly associated with disease severity among the CHM carriers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disease burden attributable to intimate partner violence against females and sexual violence against children in 204 countries and territories, 1990-2023: a systematic analysis for the Global Burden of Disease Study 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Violence against women and against children are human rights violations with lasting harms to survivors and societies at large. Intimate partner violence (IPV) and sexual violence against children (SVAC) are two major forms of such abuse. Despite their wide-reaching effects on individual and community health, these risk factors have not been adequately prioritised as key drivers of global health burden. Comprehensive x§and reliable estimates of the comparative health burden of IPV...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging multimodal large language model chatbots in oral radiology: a comprehensive evaluation using questions from a korean dental university]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provided timely insights into the capabilities and limitations of general-purpose multimodal LLM chatbots in the oral radiology, and will serve as a foundation for more safe and effective applications of AI chatbots in the oral radiology field in the future.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly porous SnO<sub>2</sub>-SiO<sub>2</sub> composite microspheres with interconnected pores for long-cycle-life lithium-Iion batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The simultaneous suppression of volume changes through pore structure design and the control of surface side reactions using passivating materials is critical for achieving high electrochemical performance and structural stability in lithium-ion battery anodes. In this study, highly porous SnO(2)-SiO(2) composite microspheres with interconnected pores (p-SnSi) were prepared using a simple, one-step spray pyrolysis process. Fine and spherical polystyrene beads, which were burned off during the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging internal states with music: An exploratory analysis of music-induced embodied emotion regulation in autistic youth and young adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emotion dysregulation in autistic individuals often manifest as atypical reactivity or maladaptive expressions, frequently accompanied by dissociation or detachment from self-experiences, avoidance, suppression, or rigidity in response to external and internal experiences. These challenges highlight the need for population-specific approaches to emotion regulation (ER). This study explored the potential of music to integrate interoceptive and exteroceptive processes for embodied ER. We proposed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of machine learning to predict employment attainment among individuals with intellectual and developmental disabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Promoting desirable employment outcomes for individuals with intellectual and developmental disabilities has been an important task for decades. However, the statistics indicate inequitable employment outcomes still exist; including underrepresentation in the workforce and employment in a part-time, low-wage, and segregated setting. One way to address the gap is to review and promote individual and environmental characteristics that are related to enhanced employment outcomes. For this study, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Occurrence, formation, and treatment implications of N-Nitrosamine risks in harvested waters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With growing freshwater scarcity, alternative sources such as harvested rainwater, atmospheric water, and stormwater are attracting increasing attention. However, their use may pose health risks due to contamination and the formation of carcinogenic N-Nitrosamines. This study systematically evaluated the occurrence and formation potentials (FPs) of nine N-Nitrosamines detected in harvested waters. Five N-Nitrosamines-N-Nitrosodimethylamine, N-Nitrosodiethylamine, N-Nitrosomorpholine,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance evaluation of deep-ultraviolet laser-assisted Invizo 6000 and near-ultraviolet laser-assisted LEAP 5000 for a range of material systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atom probe tomography (APT) enables near-atomic-scale, three-dimensional elemental mapping through controlled field evaporation of surface atoms, triggered by the combined application of a DC voltage with either voltage or laser pulses. As selected laser wavelengths in atom probes transitioned from near-infrared (1050-1064 nm) toward shorter wavelengths, such as green (532 nm) and near-ultraviolet (NUV 355 nm), the quality of data improved and the range of analyzable materials expanded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable self-aligned fabrication of nanoscale vertical a-IGZO TFTs utilizing angled deposition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amorphous indium-gallium-zinc oxide (a-IGZO) thin-film transistors (TFTs) are promising for nanoscale logic and memory devices, including vertical-channel and monolithic 3D DRAM, owing to their high mobility, uniformity, and compatibility with low-temperature processing. However, nanolithographic definition of a-IGZO channels remains difficult because of their sensitivity to plasma damage and the poor volatility of In, Ga, and Zn etch by-products. Here, we present a scalable self-aligned...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated With Suicidal Ideation Among Persons With Disabilities in South Korea: Retrospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights critical predictors of suicidal ideation in persons with disabilities in South Korea, underscoring the necessity for focused mental health interventions. The results demonstrate the potential of machine learning to identify these factors, which can aid in the development of future suicide prevention strategies. Future work is warranted to investigate if the factors identified in this study are causal.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Framework to prioritize health outcomes of particulate matter exposure using national claims data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This structured, multidisciplinary approach broadened the scope of PM-related clinical research beyond commonly studied clinical area. This scalable framework can be adapted in other regions with similar claims data systems to guide evidence-based research agendas and inform public health policies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shift from visceral to subcutaneous adipose tissue in Cyp17a1-knockout rats prevents the progression of metabolic syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigated the effects of Cyp17a1 gene knockout (KO) on obesity and metabolic syndrome. Cyp17a1 KO in rats using CRISPR-Cas9 resulted in sex dimorphism and obesity, and interestingly, site-specific accumulation was found in subcutaneous adipose tissue (SAT). Surprisingly, an insulin tolerance test and oral glucose tolerance test did not show any issues with insulin sensitivity and secretion despite hyperglycemia. In addition, Cyp17a1 KO rats showed normal plasma insulin and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photographic evaluation of clinical activity score in thyroid eye disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Periocular photography provides a reproducible and clinically valuable adjunct for assessing TED activity. The redness-related items showed higher agreement than swelling-related ones, and integrating demographic variables enhances diagnostic performance. This approach may contribute to standardizing TED assessment and serve as a foundation for future automated or image-based evaluation tools.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide copy number profiling enhances risk stratification in multiple myeloma by shallow whole-genome sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Comprehensive detection of copy number aberrations (CNAs) is critical for precise prognostic risk stratification in multiple myeloma (MM), but conventional cytogenetic methods remain limited. We developed LeukoPrint, a shallow whole-genome sequencing (sWGS) assay for genome-wide CNA profiling. Using this platform, we analyzed CNA profiles of 423 MM patients from three hospitals, comparing LeukoPrint with karyotyping and fluorescence in situ hybridization (FISH) to evaluate its diagnostic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunosuppressant use and adverse pregnancy outcomes in women with systemic lupus erythematosus: a retrospective cohort study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Continuity of hydroxychloroquine use from preconception through pregnancy reduces preterm birth risk in SLE. Conversely, early exposure to teratogenic immunosuppressants heightens the risk of spontaneous abortion. These findings underscore the importance of preconception medication planning in women with SLE.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vegetable Juice Fermented with Lactiplantibacillus plantarum WB3813 and Lactiplantibacillus plantarum WB3814 Alleviates H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub>-induced Oxidative Stress in Respiratory Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the oxidative stress alleviating effects of vegetable juice (VJ) fermented with Lactiplantibacillus plantarum WB3813 and L. plantarum WB3814 using a H(2)O(2)-induced A549 cell model. Both WB3813 and WB3814 strains exhibited stable fermentation characteristics in VJ, supporting their suitability as starter cultures for developing plant-based probiotic products. Fermentation enhanced antioxidant activity, with WB3814-VJ showing the highest total polyphenol content (TPC)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Invasive fungal infections in hematologic diseases: evidence, challenges, and clinical practice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patients with acute leukemia, particularly those undergoing allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation, are at a high risk of contracting invasive fungal infections (IFIs). These IFIs substantially increase morbidity and mortality. Over the past decade, the paradigm of IFI management has shifted markedly, with an increased emphasis on prevention and treatment. Expanded use of antifungal agents and advances in novel therapies have prolonged survival in patients with hematologic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Root‑preferential OsPUB36 modulates ROS levels and regulates root development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OsPUB36, a root-preferential E3 ubiquitin ligase, modulates reactive oxygen species homeostasis and regulates rice root development, affecting primary root and root hair growth. Root development is tightly regulated by spatial gradients of reactive oxygen species (ROS), which coordinate transitions from cell division to elongation and differentiation. Through phylogenetic meta-analysis, we identified a root-preferential subclass of class III PUB E3 ubiquitin ligases (OsPUB31-OsPUB37). Among...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational Investigation of Hafnium Carbide MXenes (Hf<sub>3</sub>C<sub>2</sub>T<em><sub>x</sub></em>) for Ultra-Sensitive Detection of Targeted Volatile Organic Compounds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early detection of gastric cancer (GC) is critical for improving patient survival rates, yet the current diagnostic techniques are invasive and costly. Efficient detection of the targeted volatile organic compounds (VOCs) in patients' exhaled breath could be a promising method for timely GC diagnosis. In this study, we employ first-principles density functional theory (DFT) calculations to investigate the sensing potential of hafnium carbide MXenes (Hf(3)C(2)T(x); T(x) = O, S, F) toward...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Joint Bayesian additive regression trees for multiple nonlinear dependency networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Identifying protein-protein interaction networks can reveal therapeutic targets in cancer; however, for heterogeneous cancers such as colorectal cancer (CRC), a pooled analysis of the entire dataset may miss subtype-specific mechanisms, whereas separate analyses of each subgroup's data may reduce the power to identify shared relations. To address this limitation, we propose a hierarchical Bayesian model for the inference of dependency networks that encourages the common selection of edges across...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of an Aspen Plus model for catalytic transesterification with different reactor arrangements and kinetic mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The era of dependence on fossil fuels will come to an end in a few decades, with a rising demand for alternative energy resources like biofuels. Major challenges in the preservation of the environment and ecosystem, i.e., air pollution, waste disposal, greenhouse effect, and climate change, are brought by fossil fuels only. Therefore, mankind must rebuild and upgrade its energy sector by introducing biofuels, which will not only reduce the carbon footprint but also meet the energy demands of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum AI for psychiatric diagnosis: enhancing dementia classification with quantum machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early detection of dementia is a key requirement for effective patient management. Therefore, classification of dementia is pertinent and requires a highly accurate methodology. Deep learning (DL) models process immense amounts of input data, whereas quantum machine learning (QML) models use qubits and quantum operations to enhance computational speed and data storage through algorithms. QML is a research domain that investigates the interactions between quantum computing concepts and machine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of maternal pre-existing atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease and neonatal and long-term offspring outcomes: a nationwide mother-child paired cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[STUDY QUESTION: Is maternal pre-existing atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD) associated with neonatal and long-term offspring outcomes?]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical complexity of the right-lobe grafts: influence on the outcomes in living donor liver transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Anatomical complexities of right-lobe grafts do not affect graft survival in LDLT, despite higher BD complications. Notably, multiple IHVs may be a positive factor for graft survival after LDLT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical study of the paracaval branch of the caudate lobe: implications of paracaval portion-preserving right hepatectomy for donors with marginal remnant liver volume]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our paracaval branch classification suggests that more than half of the donors could potentially benefit from paracaval portion-preserving DRH, particularly for large LPV or bifurcation types reaching the liver surface, thus enhancing donor safety for marginal donors with a small RLV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-based prediction of response to Janus kinase inhibitors in patients with rheumatoid arthritis using clinical data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings suggest that ML models can accurately predict treatment response to Janus kinase inhibitors in rheumatoid arthritis and may support personalized therapy selection to improve clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antioxidant Potential of Polyphenolic Compounds, Sources, Extraction, Purification and Characterization Techniques: A Focused Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyphenolic compounds, which are abundant phenolic metabolites in plants, have attracted significant attention because of their diverse biological activities and robust antioxidant properties. This review uniquely describes the extraction characterization, and application pipeline for polyphenols, emphasizing their mechanistic antioxidant actions and translational challenges. Between 1979 and 2025, approximately 141 relevant studies were critically examined, covering the sources, extraction and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyterrylenes: synthesis and regioregularity effect on p-type charge transport and deep-red light photodetection in OFETs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymers of higher rylene dyes remain largely unexplored despite their promising photophysical properties, due to the synthetic challenges and poor solubility, in contrast to their well-studied lower homologs, perylene and naphthalene derivatives. In this study, we report the first synthesis of terrylene-based regioregular and regioirregular homopolymers, namely rr-Polyterrylene and ri-Polyterrylene, respectively. Selective bromination of our previously synthesized 7,8-bis(hexadecyloxy)terrylene...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovations in Bioactive Materials for Dental Pulp Vitality Preservation in Children and Adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preserving dental pulp vitality is crucial in pediatric and adolescent dentistry to promote long-term oral health and reduce the need for invasive procedures. Vital pulp therapy (VPT) enhances pulp healing and dentin formation through advanced pulp capping materials. While calcium hydroxide-based materials laid the foundation for VPT, calcium silicate-based materials like mineral trioxide aggregate, Biodentine, and TheraCal offer superior biocompatibility and sealing properties. Recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-species validation of a 6-miRNA blood signature for Parkinson's disease: from MPTP mice to human PBMC and serum exosomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Early detection of Parkinson's disease (PD) remains challenging due to the lack of reliable blood-based biomarkers. While microRNAs (miRNAs) show promise as circulating biomarkers, translating preclinical discoveries to clinically applicable panels requires rigorous validation across platforms and populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancements in Biological Dose Assessment for Radiation Emergency Medicine in the Korea Institute of Radiological and Medical Sciences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate radiation dose measurement is crucial for medical intervention and protective actions. Biological dose assessment directly measures radiation-induced molecular and physiological changes, providing information about the absorbed dose and potential health risks. The Korea Institute of Radiological and Medical Sciences (KIRAMS) has performed biological dosimetry using cytogenetic assays since 2010. These assays are used for individual dose estimation in various situations, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polygenic risk score predicts pathologically confirmed cerebral amyloid angiopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Cerebral amyloid angiopathy (CAA) and Alzheimer's disease (AD) both involve amyloid beta (Aβ) accumulation in vessels and brain parenchyma, respectively. As Aβ-targeting therapies emerge, CAA draws attention due to its link with amyloid-related imaging abnormalities (ARIA), underscoring the need for biomarkers beyond magnetic resonance imaging (MRI).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National System of Medical Preparedness and Response to Radiation Emergencies in Korea: Current Status and Sustainable Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Continuous advancements in medical response, training, and international cooperation enhance Korea's radiological emergency preparedness. Ongoing research and technology integration ensure effective emergency interventions and long-term public health protection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research and Development Programs in Radiation Epidemiology for Public Health in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The characterization of ionizing radiation as a human carcinogen affecting most organs was a major achievement in epidemiological studies. Although high-dose or high-dose rate radiation effects are well established, the health impacts of low-dose or low-dose rate exposure (<100 mSv) remain controversial, which brings significant social attention and scientific inquiry. This paper outlined the current status and future plans of radiation epidemiology in Korea, focusing on research developments...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41383040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Self-Regulation-Incorporated Digital Health Literacy Scale for Older Adults: Instrument Development and Validation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The SR-DHLs is a valid and reliable tool for assessing digital health literacy in older adults. It integrates self-regulation and resource management-essential aspects for navigating digital environments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serial KL-6 Changes in PD-1/PD-L1 Inhibitor-Related Pneumonitis in NSCLC: A Single-Center Prospective Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this pilot cohort, baseline KL-6 was not clearly associated with PD-1/PD-L1 inhibitor-related pneumonitis in patients with NSCLC, whereas post-baseline increases were more frequently observed among patients who developed pneumonitis (including all-cause pneumonitis cases).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Helicobacter pylori Treatment on Gastric Cancer Incidence and Mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superficial Esophageal Cancer Completely Cured With Radiotherapy Alone: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surgery is the definitive treatment for superficial esophageal cancer. However, the risks and complications associated with surgery often lead to further complications. Endoscopic resection is an effective treatment option for superficial esophageal cancer. However, if the cancer invades more than three-quarters of the esophageal lumen, the risk of complications is high from both the procedure and potentially troublesome post-endoscopic esophageal stricture. To mitigate these issues, neoadjuvant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Unusual Cause of Hematemesis in a Patient Previously Treated for Cholangiocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 75-year-old woman presented with hematemesis and a history of perihilar cholangiocarcinoma treated with left lobectomy, caudate lobectomy, and Roux-en-Y hepaticojejunostomy. Esophagogastroduodenoscopy revealed a 3×3-cm polypoid lesion accompanied by active bleeding. Biopsy revealed adenocarcinoma, favoring metastasis over primary gastric cancer, considering the patient's medical history and previous endoscopic evaluations. Despite endoscopic hemostasis, anemia persisted, prompting laparoscopic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toxic Epidermal Necrolysis Induced by First-Line Helicobacter pylori Eradication Therapy: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stevens-Johnson syndrome and toxic epidermal necrolysis (TEN) are rare, life-threatening adverse drug reactions. Here, we report a fatal case of TEN in an 80-year-old patient who developed diffuse bullous eruptions and multiorgan failure following first-line Helicobacter pylori eradication therapy with a proton pump inhibitor, amoxicillin, and clarithromycin. Initial symptoms appeared four days posttreatment. Despite intensive care, including corticosteroids and supportive treatment, the patient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of the Prognostic Value of the ABC Score in Non-Variceal UGIB Showing Superiority to Traditional Scores, With Room for Improvement: A Retrospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ABC score outperformed conventional risk models at predicting the 30-day mortality among patients with non-variceal UGIB. However, its predictive power for the need for intervention was inferior to that of the GBS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current Trends in Gastric Cancer Surgery and Postoperative Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The surgical management of gastric cancer has evolved rapidly, with minimally invasive, function-preserving, and fluorescence-guided techniques increasingly adopted as standard practice. Laparoscopic and robotic gastrectomies have shown comparable long-term oncologic outcomes while providing improved perioperative recovery, and individualized reconstruction methods further enhance postoperative quality of life. Recent trials support the use of neoadjuvant chemotherapy for locally advanced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of a Karaoke-Based Digital Therapeutic in Mild Cognitive Impairment: A Randomized, 12-Week Pilot Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this randomized controlled trial, a karaoke-based DTx appeared feasible and effective in enhancing global cognition in MCI. The findings support its potential as a complementary intervention for cognitive improvement in MCI patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suicide Risk in Individuals With Psychiatric Disorder: Population-Based Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Psychiatric disorders were associated with a significantly elevated suicidal risk in South Korea, which was substantially greater than the risk of non-suicidal deaths.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum Cocaine- and Amphetamine-Regulated Transcript Levels and Cooperativeness in Adolescents With Internet Gaming Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The present findings suggest serum CART levels might serve as a neurobiological marker for cooperativeness function in adolescents with IGD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Employment Status and Suicidal Ideation in Korean Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that unemployed status was significantly associated with increased suicidal ideation. These findings suggest that further research and policy attention are warranted to better understand and address the mental health needs of unemployed individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Gene Polymorphisms of RSPO2 of the Wnt Signaling Pathway and Schizophrenia in the Korean Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings indicate that RSPO2 gene polymorphisms, particularly rs374810 and rs423940, may contribute to schizophrenia susceptibility. Therefore, RSPO2 expression may be associated with the susceptibility to schizophrenia in the Korean population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41382343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phosphatase and tensin homolog mRNA complexed with hyaluronated lipid nanoparticles for transdermal cancer immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The loss of phosphatase and tensin homolog (PTEN) can lead to resistance to immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) in melanoma, thereby promoting immune evasion and tumor progression. These effects can be reversed by restoring PTEN expression, reactivating antitumor immunity, and enhancing therapeutic responses. Here, we develop a hyaluronate-conjugated lipid nanoparticle (HA-LNP) with HA-dimyristoyl glycerol (DMG) for the non-invasive, transdermal delivery of PTEN mRNA. This amphiphilic lipid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microfluidic droplet cultivation preserves microalgae diversity in screening systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient screening of microalgae is critical for their research and industrial applications. However, conventional methods of microalgae screening are often considered inefficient and are applicable to a narrow range of species. We conducted a proof-of-concept study on the applicability of a water-in-oil droplet (WODL)-based microfluidic system to high-throughput screening of microalgae and effect of microfluidic droplet cultivation on the species diversity within microalgal samples. First, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel glycerol-containing exopolysaccharide from the ropy strain Lactiplantibacillus plantarum KY5-ES5 and its impact on medium viscosity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exopolysaccharides (EPS) produced by lactic acid bacteria (LAB) contribute to the texture of fermented foods and offer potential health benefits. In this study, a ropy Lactiplantibacillus plantarum strain, KY5-ES5, was isolated from shibazuke, Japanese traditional fermented pickles. The strain exhibited significantly higher viscosity in synthetic medium compared to the non-ropy type strain L. plantarum JCM1149^(T). EPS extracted from KY5-ES5 contained glucose, galactose, and glycerol, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of rehabilitation dose heterogeneity for improving functional outcomes of patients with acute stroke: a nationwide observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To examine heterogeneity in the impact of increased early rehabilitation intensity and to identify which ischemic stroke patients benefit most. We analysed 39,140 propensity score-matched ischemic stroke patients using Diagnosis Procedure Combination database. Patients who received ≥ 60 min of daily rehabilitation within the 14 hospital days were compared with those who received less, in terms of achieving a modified Rankin Scale (mRS) score of 0, 1, or 2 at 60 days. We employed a causal forest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41388015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal changes in Angkorian ironmaking technology in Northern Cambodia during the 10th-14th centuries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Khmer people constructed numerous monuments from the 9th to 15th centuries (Angkor period) using iron tools. Ancient ironmaking sites have been identified as slag mounds near Khmer monuments. However, details of the ironmaking technology used during the Angkor period remain unknown. Herein, we show the temporal changes in ironmaking technology in northern Cambodia, which was a major iron-producing region of the Angkorian Empire. The chemical and Nd-Sr-Pb isotopic compositions of slag and ore...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for persistent decline in eGFR of Japanese patients with diabetes: Analysis using a large-scale diabetes registry J-DREAMS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Beyond retinopathy and advanced kidney disease, anemia, hypoalbuminemia, and heart failure independently contributed to persistent eGFR decline, supporting the clinical relevance of cardio-renal anemia syndrome in diabetic populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Green manure-induced shifts in nematode communities associated with soil bacterial and fungal biomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Green manures are widely used to enhance soil health and suppress plant-parasitic nematodes, and their effects on the broader soil food web have been studied. Beyond direct suppression, the role of green manures in supporting and sustaining soil food webs has attracted increasing attention. In this study, we evaluated the use of DNA sequencing to identify various nematode genera and their microbial associates in a field trial using oat (Avena sativa) and hairy vetch (Vicia villosa) as green...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification and removal of contamination in palaeoproteomic analysis of dental enamel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Analysis of archaeological and palaeontological dental enamel allows for the study of taxonomy, phylogenetic relationships, and genetic sex of Pleistocene fauna and hominin remains. However, high-quality data is required for the study of degraded, chemically modified ancient proteomes. Protein contamination may hinder acquisition of such data due to the abundance and more intact state of modern contaminating proteins, risking suppression of low-abundance, damaged peptides during fragment ion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subchondral bone strength of the metacarpal head and its related factors in patients with rheumatoid arthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Factors affecting bone strength have not been elucidated in patients with rheumatoid arthritis (RA) undergoing silicone implant arthroplasty. In this observational study, we aimed to investigate factors affecting bone strength. We measured toughness in terms of bone strength, bone mineral density, and bone quality of 105 resected metacarpal heads (I:32, II:36, III:33, IV:2, V:2) obtained during silicone implant arthroplasty at the metacarpophalangeal (MP) joint in patients with RA. Bone strength...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the impact of bariatric surgery on cardiovascular risk in type 2 diabetes: a systematic review and meta-analysis using OMICs data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Type 2 diabetes (T2D) is a complex, multifactorial metabolic disorder, and while bariatric surgery has emerged as a promising intervention for obesity-related T2D with significant metabolic benefits, its long-term durability and potential for remission vary among patients. This systematic review and meta-analysis explore how omics modalities-such as genomics, epigenomics, transcriptomics, metabolomics, proteomics, and gut microbiome-can reveal potential biomarkers linked to cardiovascular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Taxonomic distribution of alkane synthesizing aldehyde dehydrogenases across bacteria, fungi, plants, and animals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We cloned several aldehyde dehydrogenases (ALDHs) from bacteria and yeast that have aldehyde decarbonylase activity to convert aldehydes to alkanes. Alkane-synthesizing activity was observed through the assays using resting cells and cell-free extracts of the E. coli transformants expressing ALDH. This novel function of aldehyde dehydrogenase introduces a new pathway for hydrocarbon fuel production and offers novel insights into microbial processes that may explain the natural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards smart farming: a real-time diagnosis system for strawberry foliar diseases using deep learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Developing an effective machine vision system is crucial to successfully deploying robotic inspection in open field conditions and controlled environments like greenhouses. Robotic arms with vision-based deep learning models offer an efficient, real-time, non-invasive crop monitoring solution. In agricultural settings, they enable consistent, automated inspection under varying conditions, reduce labor dependency, and support early disease detection, enhancing productivity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical recognition of frontotemporal dementia with right temporal predominance: a consensus statement from the International Working Group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate diagnosis of frontotemporal dementia (FTD) with right anterior temporal lobe (RATL) predominance remains challenging due to lack of clinical characterization, and standardized terminology. The recent research of the International Working Group (IWG) identified common symptoms but also unveiled broad terminologies lacking precision and operationalization, with risk of misdiagnoses, inappropriate referrals and poor clinical management. Based on the published evidence (91267 articles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expert View: Wim Teughels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient apical breakdown during orthodontic incisor intrusion treated with non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transient apical breakdown (TAB) may occur during pulp repair after dental traumatic injury, including orthodontic force. Herein, we describe TAB in the maxillary right central incisor of a 24-year-old woman during orthodontic treatment for a severe gummy smile. Eight months after initiating intrusion of the maxillary anterior teeth using temporary anchorage devices, the maxillary right central incisor showed discoloration and was non-responsive to electric pulp tests. The orthodontic force on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Collision-induced ribosome degradation driven by ribosome competition and translational perturbations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Individual stalling of catalytically inactive ribosomes at the start codon triggers ubiquitination of ribosomal protein uS3 and subsequent 18S rRNA decay. While collisions between ribosomes during translation elongation represent a more widespread form of translation perturbation, their impact on ribosome stability remains unknown. Here, we clarify a bifurcation in ubiquitination-mediated ribosome turnover, identifying a collision-induced branch of uS3 ubiquitination and small subunit...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Network pharmacology and molecular docking reveal antiviral mechanisms of silver nanoparticles synthesized by Oscillatoria sp. against HCV pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explored the green synthesis of silver nanoparticles (AgNPs) using eco-friendly aqueous and methanolic extracts from Oscillatoria sp. algae. Characterization techniques (Fourier transform infrared spectroscopy, Transmission electron microscopy, Dynamic light scattering technique, and Zeta potential) confirmed the successful synthesis and stability of the AgNPs. Untargeted metabolic profiling via LC-MS tentatively identified 22 potential metabolites (1-22) in the extracts, primarily...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluorothiazynes as SuFEx Ambiphiles: Interconversion to Amino-sulfurdiimidoyl Fluorides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sulfur(VI) functional groups are ubiquitous in medicinal chemistry, valued for their stability and ability to modulate molecular properties. While sulfonamides, sulfones, and sulfates dominate existing drug scaffolds, more complex, multidirectional sulfur(VI) cores remain underexplored. Here, we show a viable route from amino difluorothiazynes to aminosulfurdiimidoyl fluorides (ASDFs), via sequential alkylation and imination. Leveraging the ambiphilic character of fluorothiazynes-acting as both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41387193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagonal DWI: A Time-Efficient Alternative to 3-Scan Trace DWI for Breast Lesion Evaluation at 3.0-T MRI-A Phantom Study and Clinical Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Diffusion-weighted imaging (DWI) in breast MRI requires balancing image quality with acquisition time. Reducing scan time without sacrificing diagnostic performance could improve patient comfort and workflow.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Levan induced the resistance of tomato against Botrytis cinerea and pepper against Phytophthora capsici]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pathogenic challenges constrain plant growth, and the application of pesticides remains the primary approach to control plant diseases worldwide. However, overuse of chemical fungicides can lead to pathogen resistance and environmental contamination. In recent years, compounds that act as induced resistance stimuli have gained increasing attention. Levan, a β-2,6-linked fructan, has been reported to induce disease resistance in several plant species, though its effect on solanaceous plants and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Qualitative Study on Pharmacy Students' Motivation, Academic Performance, and Career Intentions Using Self-Determination Theory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Fulfilling pharmacy students' basic psychological needs: autonomy, competence, and relatedness is essential for fostering intrinsic motivation and academic engagement. Addressing barriers such as limited academic autonomy, restricted practical training, and feelings of isolation can enhance motivation, reduce burnout, and support academic success. These findings highlight the importance of creating supportive, student-centered learning environments in pharmacy education.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of different iron compounds on the acclimation of Feammox sludge: Nitrogen-iron transformation, sludge physicochemical properties, and microbial communities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anaerobic ammonium oxidation coupled with Fe(III) reduction (Feammox) plays a critical role in the natural nitrogen cycle, but the differential regulatory mechanisms of various iron sources that influence Feammox sludge acclimation remain systematically unexplored in wastewater treatment. In this study, four iron compounds (FeCl(3), Fe(2)O(3), Fe(3)O(4), and Fe(OH)(3)) were individually introduced into anaerobic sequencing batch reactors to initiate Feammox processes. After 126 days of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilizing the dynamic gastrointestinal model (DGM) to evaluate the gastric integrity of Capsugel® Enprotect® capsules in fasted and fed states]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to evaluate if the Dynamic Gastrointestinal Model (DGM) is able to simulate the gastro-resistant behavior of Capsugel® Enprotect® capsules under physiologically relevant fasted and fed conditions. Enprotect® capsules were filled with a caffeine powder blend and tested under three conditions: fasted state, a light meal (∼500 kcal), and the FDA high-fat meal (∼900 kcal). Results showed that the capsules remained intact in the stomach across all conditions and released their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nitrated products formed on α-synuclein are preferentially incorporated into oligomers but excluded from fibrils: A mechanism for accumulation of neurotoxic species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Post-translational modifications (PTMs) such as nitration of Tyr (Y) residues and di-tyrosine (DT) formation are known to impact the aggregation behavior of α-synuclein (α-syn), a protein closely linked to Parkinson's disease. Using tetranitromethane (TNM) as a model nitrating agent, we systematically investigated the chemical modifications of α-syn and their consequences for aggregation. Mass spectrometry analysis revealed site-selective nitration of all four Tyr residues, with Y39 and Y125...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elucidating the roles of TM7SF3 and LHFPL6 in the putative H<sup>+</sup>/OC antiporter function in the human brain capillary endothelial cell line, hCMEC/D3]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study suggests that the H+/OC antiporter operates via two distinct mechanisms: a high-capacity, TM7SF3- and LHFPL6-independent pathway and a low-capacity, TM7SF3- and LHFPL6-dependent pathway. These findings underscore the complexity of the H^(+)/OC antiporter molecular composition and highlight the need for further research to fully elucidate its identity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping the inflammatory origins of lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[How early precursor cells and their surrounding microenvironment cooperate to drive oncogenic progression in lung adenocarcinoma (LUAD) remains elusive. In this issue of Cancer Cell, Peng et al. conducted multimodal spatial-omics to comprehensively profile precancerous lung and LUAD tissues, uncovering alveolar progenitors and proinflammatory niches that co-evolve during cancer progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fixations during recognition of rotated familiar and unfamiliar single characters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Character recognition forms the foundation of reading comprehension, yet the underlying visual processing mechanisms during single-character recognition are not fully understood. While character rotation is known to increase cognitive load, its effects on eye movement patterns and the role of language familiarity in these processes have not been systematically investigated. We hypothesized that character rotation would disrupt fixation patterns, with larger disruptions for familiar scripts due...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regional equity and declining laryngeal surgery in Japan: A nationwide claims-based analysis from 2014 to 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This nationwide analysis identified distinct demographic trends and modest regional disparities in otolaryngological surgical care in Japan. The consistent decline in laryngeal surgery across major demographic groups suggests a systemic shift in clinical practice, rather than an isolated reduction in disease incidence. These findings highlight the importance of continued support from academic societies and coordinated policy efforts to maintain equitable access to surgical care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adapting sanitation systems to demographic transitions: Optimizing hybrid configurations of sewered and non-sewered solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-sewered sanitation systems play a vital role in achieving global sanitation goals by providing resource-efficient and flexible solutions, particularly in resource-constrained settings. When effectively integrated with infrastructure of centralized systems, they offer multiple advantages, including reduced asset redundancy, improved economic feasibility, intergenerational equity, and better public health outcomes-ultimately maximizing overall system performance. This study presents a novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From rock waste to reactive surfaces: Natural gabbro rocks for solar remediation of gaseous and aqueous contaminants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[- This study investigates the structural, optical, and catalytic properties of mafic rock grains derived from Gabbro collected in the United Arab Emirates are to evaluate their potential as alternative catalysts for environmental applications. Nitrogen adsorption and desorption analysis revealed mesoporous and macroporous structures with low specific surface area (0.56-4.96 m²/g). UV-Vis spectroscopy showed that the analyzed gabbroic rocks have band gap energies that are suitable for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41386016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning Curve for Rat Intestinal Transplantation: Milestones From a Single Surgeon's Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our methodology, based on stepwise milestones, enabled the development of the rat ITx model. Following the completion of milestones 1 and 2, 34 ITx procedures were required to complete the LC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early life fecal microbiota transplantation enhances fermentation potential by changing the microbial profiles in broiler chickens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The early gut microbiota of broiler chickens plays a critical role in shaping physiological functions later in life. Broilers have a limited capacity to utilize dietary fiber at an early stage of life. Fecal microbiota transplantation (FMT) can modify the gut microbial composition of broilers, potentially enhancing their fiber utilization capability. In this study, fecal samples from different chicken donors (broilers, laying hens, and broiler breeders) were collected and used for in vitro...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical stage in the era of molecular profiling of endometrial cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Molecular classification has reshaped risk stratification in endometrial cancer (EC), yet the relevance of tumor spread within molecular subgroups has not been reported so far.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Charge Radii Measurements of Exotic Tin Isotopes in the Proximity of N=50 and N=82]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report nuclear charge radii for the isotopes ^{104-134}Sn, measured using two different collinear laser spectroscopy techniques at ISOLDE-CERN. These measurements clarify the archlike trend in charge radii along the isotopic chain and reveal an odd-even staggering that is more pronounced near the N=50 and N=82 shell closures. The observed local trends are well described by both nuclear density functional theory and valence space in-medium similarity renormalization group calculations. Both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WIMP Dark Matter Search Using a 3.1 Tonne-Year Exposure of the XENONnT Experiment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report on a search for weakly interacting massive particle (WIMP) dark matter (DM) via elastic DM-xenon-nucleus interactions in the XENONnT experiment. We combine datasets from the first and second science campaigns resulting in a total exposure of 3.1 tonne-years. In a blind analysis of nuclear recoil events with energies above 3.8 keV_{NR}, we find no significant excess above background. We set new upper limits on the spin-independent WIMP-nucleon scattering cross section for WIMP masses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of rAAV-shRNA treatment targeting mechanosensitive Ilk1 and Fermt2 in a mouse model of sepsis-induced muscle weakness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sepsis induced upregulation of integrin-receptor-complex-related genes but attenuating the upregulation of Ilk1 or Fermt2 did not affect the development of muscle weakness, although muscle fiber size was better preserved, arguing against a key role for Ilk1 or Fermt2.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A high-quality genome assembly of angel-wing mushroom Pleurocybella porrigens that causes acute encephalopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In 2004, 59 cases of food poisoning linked to the consumption of the mushroom Pleurocybella porrigens were reported in Japan, resulting in 17 fatalities due to acute encephalopathy. In 2023, we found three components of this mushroom-a lectin (PPL), pleurocybelline (PC), and pleurocybellaziridine (PA)-which are collectively implicated in its toxicity in mice. Although we reported the genomic data for P. porrigens in 2013, detailed annotation was not provided at that time. In addition, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41385033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The prognostic value of serum lactate dehydrogenase levels in patients with carcinoembryonic antigen (CEA)- and carbohydrate antigen 19-9 (CA19-9)-negative colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The serum LDH level is a valuable prognostic marker for predicting the outcomes of CRC patients, even those with negative CEA and CA19-9 levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An in silico mechanoregulatory model of depth-dependent adaptations to mechanical loading in intact and damaged cartilage: a proof of concept study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoarthritis induces profound structural degeneration of articular cartilage, with existing treatments remaining largely ineffective. This study pioneers a mechanoregulatory model utilizing histology-based finite element analysis to predict depth-dependent glycosaminoglycan (GAG) adaptations in both intact and damaged human cartilage under mechanical loading. Uniquely calibrated through rigorous one-week longitudinal in vitro experiments in intact cartilage, our model correctly predicts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designing Cross-Linked Nanogel Microfibers for the Fabrication of Hybrid Cell Spheroids with Potential Biomedical Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell spheroids are three-dimensional spherical aggregates of cells that show advantages for mimicking living tissues, owing to their structure. However, issues such as cell necrosis often result in limited cell survival and functional expression. The introduction of biocompatible functional material spacers into cell spheroids can not only improve cell survival by facilitating free diffusion of oxygen, nutrients, and waste products but also enables the incorporation of novel functions into the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redox potentials of carotenoids associated with type-II photosynthetic reaction centers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carotenoids play dual roles in photosynthesis, extending light absorption and providing photoprotection through radical cation formation. Their ability to act as electron donors is defined by their redox potential for one-electron oxidation (Em). Here, we determine Em for carotenoids whose Em values are missing or inconsistently established in type-II reaction centers or associated antenna complexes, using a quantum chemical approach. The highest occupied molecular orbital (HOMO) energy levels...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disruption of a hydrogen-bond network at an Si/PNMPy/electrolyte interface for accelerated ion transfer in solar rechargeable devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Si/poly(N-methylpyrrole) (PNMPy)-based two-electrode solar rechargeable devices using HClO(4) as the electrolyte exhibit 3-fold and 7-fold higher current densities during photo-charging and dark-discharging processes than does the corresponding H(2)SO(4)-based device. This enhancement originates from a ClO(4)^(-)-induced disruption of the interfacial hydrogen-bond network, where this disruption can significantly accelerate ion transfer at the PNMPy/HClO(4) interface.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From fluorine chemistry to noncovalent interactions: celebrating Prof. Giuseppe Resnati]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electron spin-lattice relaxation in triplet-state oligoacenes: a first-principles-based approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic chromophores in photo-excited triplet states can transiently exhibit uneven population distribution among spin sublevels, which is called spin polarization. Spin polarization can be realized even at room temperature and low magnetic fields, and it has recently attracted much attention due to its potential for application in quantum technologies such as quantum sensing and quantum computing. Molecular spin polarizing agents offer tunability of their physical properties through molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[pH-Triggered Coassembly of Cello-oligosaccharides and Hyaluronic Acid into Hydrogels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polysaccharides are valuable building blocks for constructing functional hydrogel materials for diverse applications. Although many polysaccharides with high water solubility require cross-linking to be formulated into hydrogels, physically cross-linking ionic polysaccharides with biocompatible substances under mild aqueous conditions remains a significant challenge. Herein, we report the physical cross-linking of hyaluronic acid with crystalline cello-oligosaccharides via bottom-up coassembly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SALT OVERLY SENSITIVE 1 Na<sup>+</sup>/H<sup>+</sup> Exchanger Operates in Mature Root Zone and Is a Major Contributor to Root Na<sup>+</sup> Exclusion During Shoot-to-Root Na<sup>+</sup> Recirculation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Na^(+)/H^(+) antiporter SALT OVERLY SENSITIVE 1 (SOS1) is a key component of Na^(+) exclusion and plant salt tolerance. Although previous studies have suggested that SOS1 functions in both the root apex and mature root zone, their contributions remain unclear due to limited methodological resolution and originated mostly from transcriptional analysis. Here, we performed isotopic tracing techniques to visualize and quantify Na^(+) exclusion. Real-time imaging of shoot-applied ^(22)Na^(+)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41384330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251213023758&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>