<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:40:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapidly progressive destructive arthrosis (RPDA) of the glenohumeral joint: a radiologic classification and mid-term outcomes following shoulder arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two-year outcomes of denosumab treatment for osteoporosis comparing the effects of calcium and vitamin D supplementation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Calcium and vitamin D supplementation is commonly recommended in conjunction with osteoporosis treatment. However, some patients are unable to tolerate or take these supplements due to various factors. This study aims to assess the impact of calcium and vitamin D supplementation on bone mineral density (BMD) changes over a two-year period in patients treated with denosumab, comparing those who received supplements with those who did not. This retrospective study included 344 patients who had...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable polyolefin upcycling using liquid organic hydrogen carrier based hydrogen delivery and hydrocracking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Globally, 89% of post-consumer plastic waste is landfilled or incinerated, exacerbating environmental pollution, while less than 0.1% is chemically recycled. Polyolefin plastics, nearly half of global plastic production, can be converted into liquid fuels via hydrogenolysis or hydrocracking but require external hydrogen gas. Here, we report a tandem catalytic process combining decalin dehydrogenation with polyethylene hydrocracking, eliminating the need for external hydrogen by using decalin as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward single-cell control: noise-robust perfect adaptation in biomolecular systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Robust perfect adaptation (RPA), whereby a consistent output level is maintained even after a disturbance, is a highly desired feature in biological systems. This property can be achieved at the population average level by combining the well-known antithetic integral feedback (AIF) loop into the target network. However, the AIF controller amplifies the noise of the output level, disrupting the single-cell level regulation of the system output and compromising the conceptual goal of stable output...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative assessment of blood-brain barrier permeability using biotechnological imaging analysis in contrast-enhanced magnetic resonance imaging during post-resuscitation care: Stratified associations by illness severity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrated no significant relationship between non-invasive ΔCon derived from CE-MRI and invasive Qa when illness severity remained unstratified. After stratifying by illness severity, a subtle association between ΔCon and Qa emerged, specifically in patients with moderate severity of cardiac arrest.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isobavachalcone reduces blood glucose and promotes muscle development via dipeptidyl peptidase-4 inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) regulates insulin secretion; however, GLP-1 is rapidly degraded by dipeptidyl peptidase-4 (DPP4). Synthetic DPP4 inhibitors are used to treat type 2 diabetes (T2D); however, safer alternatives are required owing to the side effects of these inhibitors. Given the well-documented health advantages of flavonoids, this study computationally screened flavonoid compounds (n = 241) and performed in vitro and in vivo studies to determine the potential of these compounds...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolation, structure elucidation, and absolute configuration of 5,6-dioxygenated aaptamine derivatives from the marine sponge Aaptos sp]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A chemical investigation of the Vietnamese marine sponge Aaptos sp. identified eight previously undescribed aaptamines (1-8) and two known analogs (9-10). In particular, derivatives (1-6) feature unusual oxygen-generated stereocenters at C-5 and C-6, rendering them the first examples of optically active aaptamines. The planar structures of 1-8 were elucidated based on interpretation of the 1D and 2D NMR spectra, combined with HRESIMS data. The relative and absolute configurations of 1-6 were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Humoral Immunity for Durable and Broad Protection in Flavivirus Vaccines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flavivirus infections, including dengue, Zika, West Nile, and Japanese encephalitis, remain a major global health concern. Although several vaccines are licensed, the durability and qualitative features of vaccine-induced antibodies differ substantially across platforms, leading to incomplete cross-protection and the risk of antibody-dependent enhancement. Long-term durability is exemplified by YF-17D, which induces protective antibodies that have been detectable for decades, whereas the JE...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lightweight 3D CNN for MRI Analysis in Alzheimer's Disease: Balancing Accuracy and Efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder characterized by subtle structural changes in the brain, which can be observed through MRI scans. Although traditional diagnostic approaches rely on clinical and neuropsychological assessments, deep learning-based methods such as 3D convolutional neural networks (CNNs) have recently been introduced to improve diagnostic accuracy. However, their high computational complexity remains a challenge. To address this, we propose a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel System for Measuring Tension Force in Eyeball Movement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate assessment of extraocular muscle mechanics is crucial for diagnosing and treating ocular motility disorders, yet current methods, such as the forced duction test, rely on subjective tactile sensation and gross visual observation. To overcome the limitations of subjectivity and the impracticality of previous quantitative devices, we developed a novel biosensing system capable of simultaneously and objectively measuring passive ocular tension and rotation angle during forced duction. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling Drug and Radiation Resistance with Patient-Derived Organoids: Recent Progress, Unmet Needs, and Future Directions for Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Chemotherapy, targeted therapy and radiotherapy are the cornerstones of cancer treatment. However, therapeutic resistance-not only to these classic modalities but also to novel therapeutics like immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) and antibody-drug conjugates-remains a major hurdle. Resistance significantly limits efficacy and increases recurrence rates. A deep understanding of the molecular mechanisms driving this resistance is critical for developing personalized therapeutic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Foretinib Alleviates Osteoblast Senescence and Protects Against Bone Loss in Ovariectomized Mice by Promoting Osteoblast Differentiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoporosis is a major global health challenge, causing millions of fragility fractures each year and imposing an escalating socioeconomic burden worldwide. Despite advances with antiresorptive and anabolic therapies, substantial residual fracture risk persists, and targeting aging biology may yield disease modifying benefits beyond current standards of care. Senescent cells secrete senescence-associated secretory phenotype (SASP) factors, which impair osteoblast differentiation and contribute...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Carborane-Fused Lactones via Electrochemical C(<em>sp</em><sup>3</sup>)-H Lactonization: Access to Benzofused Lactone Bioisosteres]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The replacement of the benzene ring with its bioisosteres is a powerful strategy in drug discovery, yet the development of ortho-disubstituted benzene bioisosteres, particularly fused-ring systems, remains underexplored. Herein, we report an electrooxidative protocol for the synthesis of carborane-fused lactones via C(sp³)-H lactonization. This protocol provides concise access to carborane-fused γ- and δ-lactone frameworks, which closely mimic the geometric features of benzofused lactones,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical Vortex Harmonic Generation Enabled by Confinement-Induced Photonic Spin-Orbit Coupling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Strong photonic spin-orbit coupling arises under tight optical confinement in a subwavelength waveguide, where propagating fields exhibit spin-orbit entanglement. To date, while the confinement-induced spin-orbit coupling has been investigated only in linear optics, its role in nonlinear optical processes remains largely unexplored. Here, we report the first experimental demonstration and theoretical analysis of unconventional nonlinear optical frequency conversion enabled by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of enzymatic browning in blanched potato slices using combined hyperspectral imaging and hyperspectral microscopy imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inadequate blanching in fresh-cut potatoes causes browning during storage, but it cannot be detected immediately post-processing. Moreover, browning patterns during storage vary with blanching conditions. Therefore, predictive models based on hyperspectral imaging (HSI) and hyperspectral microscopy imaging (HMI) were developed to investigate blanching-dependent alterations in polyphenol oxidase (PPO) activity and total phenolic content (R(p) ² = 0.71-0.87). HSI visualization maps showed a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The biomechanical impact of glenosphere tilting, inferior translation, and humeral retroversion in reverse total shoulder arthroplasty: A 3D modelling study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Implantation of the glenosphere with 3 mm inferior translation without inferior tilt, combined with a humeral prosthesis positioned at 0° retroversion, showed the most favourable combination in terms of range of motion until impingement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is routine Doppler sonography needed to detect deep vein thrombosis after total knee arthroplasty? A real-world comparison of two clinical pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Routine Doppler after TKA detected more DVTs, but these were small, incidental, and had no impact on outcomes. PE was almost always linked with symptoms, and its incidence was similar in both pathways. Routine screening for all patients had little value, while a symptom-guided approach was more practical and clinically relevant.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basic Science and Pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our integrative analysis of single-cell and spatial transcriptomes provides insights into the shared and unique molecular signatures underlying neurodegenerative diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basic Science and Pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings demonstrate that NPTX2 loss of function instigates SCRD by disrupting sleep architecture, orexin signaling, and neuronal synchronicity. This supports the effector role of NPTX2 in sleep regulation and highlights its potential as a therapeutic target for sleep and circadian dysfunction in aging and neurodegenerative conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia Care Research and Psychosocial Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While knowledge of alcohol as a risk factor and the potential to slow dementia progression through treatment was associated with more positive attitudes, awareness that dementia is a brain disease was linked to lower comfort levels. To improve attitudes toward dementia, it may be more effective to focus on delivering knowledge that positively shapes attitudes rather than providing information indiscriminately.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intramuscular neural distribution of the soleus for botulinum neurotoxin injection: application to spasticity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the nerve distribution within the soleus muscle concerning anatomical landmarks is crucial for botulinum neurotoxin injections in managing spasticity. This study advocates an anatomically informed approach for administering botulinum neurotoxin injections in the soleus muscle. Utilizing a modified Sihler's method, investigation encompassed both soleus muscles (20 specimens), revealing the distribution of nerves within concerning a transverse line crossing the fibular head and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SLC6A14-mediated glutamine promotes SYTL4-CXCL8 axis activation to drive gemcitabine resistance and immune evasion in pancreatic cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chemoresistance remains a major challenge in pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC). Glutamine sustains drug resistance and shapes the immunosuppressive tumor microenvironment; however, the underlying mechanisms remain unclear. Identifying key regulators that drive both gemcitabine resistance and immune evasion is crucial for improving theapeutic outcomes in PDAC. Here we identified solute-carrier family 6 member 14 (SLC6A14) as the central regulator of glutamine metabolism that drives...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic and environmental effects on weight gain from young adulthood to old age and its association with body mass index in early young adulthood: an individual-based pooled analysis of 16 twin cohorts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Genotype influences BMI changes across adulthood, with its effect varying by age and sex. Environmental effects are the main drivers of adult BMI changes, highlighting the role of modifiable factors in long-term weight regulation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-CAD for diagnostic mammography: comparison to radiologists according to different indications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI-CAD demonstrated diagnostic performance comparable to radiologists in mammography and, at an optimized threshold, offered superior specificity, PPV, and accuracy. Especially in symptomatic patients, a higher threshold increased diagnostic performance without compromising sensitivity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trichosanthes kirilowii Maximowicz attenuates dexamethasone induced atrophy in C2C12 myotubes through a Sirtuin 1 associated mechanism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glucocorticoids such as dexamethasone (DEX) are commonly used clinically but can induce skeletal muscle atrophy with prolonged or high-dose exposure. Trichosanthes kirilowii Maximowicz (TK), a traditional medicinal herb, has known pharmacological effects, but its impact on muscle atrophy remains unclear. This study investigated the anti-atrophic potential of TK in DEX-induced muscle atrophy models. In C2C12 cells, TK improved cell viability and restored myotube diameter and number, downregulated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visual spatial relationship sensitive transformer for image captioning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Image captioning is a cross-modal task that combines computer vision and natural language processing to generate natural language descriptions of visual content. Recent advances have explored the integration of both grid-based and region-based visual features to better capture relational and contextual information, such as interactions between objects and their surrounding environment. However, combining multiple types of features often results in spatial misalignment, which hinders the model's...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of bisphosphonates after denosumab discontinuation and treatment effect heterogeneity using causal machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Discontinuation of denosumab is associated with a rebound increase in osteoporotic fracture (OF) risk, and bisphosphonates (BPs) are commonly recommended as sequential therapy to mitigate this risk. However, their real-world effectiveness-and whether certain patients benefit more than others-remains unclear. To address this question, we employed a causal machine learning approach capable of estimating heterogeneous treatment effects. We conducted a nationwide retrospective cohort study using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analyzing the impact of the automatic ball strike system in professional baseball through a case study on KBO league data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in professional baseball have led to the introduction of the Automated Ball-Strike (ABS) system, or "robot umpires," which utilize machine learning, computer vision, and precise tracking technologies to automate ball-strike calls. The Korean Baseball Organization (KBO) league became the first professional baseball league to implement ABS during the 2024 season. Leveraging pitch data from 2515 KBO games across multiple seasons and employing mathematical modeling, we examine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SIMD: Synergistic integration mutualistic platform based on single-cell and proteotranscriptomics for drug repositioning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to introduce a synergistic integration platform based on single-cell and proteotranscriptomics for drug repositioning (SIMD) to repurpose breast cancer drug candidates by considering the bidirectional nature of molecular dynamics in protein transcriptomics and tumor heterogeneity at the single-cell level. SMID consists of two core methods: the anti-correlated proteotranscriptome perturbation score (ACPS), which measures the negative correlation between perturbagen-induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered extracellular vesicles reprogram T cells by targeting PD-1 and PHB1 signaling in inflammatory bowel disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current therapies for inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) often fail to achieve complete remission and are associated with systemic toxicity owing to their broad immunosuppressive effects. To overcome these limitations, we developed a bioengineered extracellular vesicle (EV) platform that modulates key immune signaling pathways to efficiently restore the T-cell balance in inflamed intestinal tissues. EVs derived from Wharton's jelly mesenchymal stem cells were engineered to display PD-L1 on their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The presence of amyloid plaques in PSCI patients is associated with a faster cognitive decline, as evidenced by the lower MMSE and worsening CDR-SOB scores in the amyloid-positive group. Although donepezil shows short-term cognitive benefits, its impact diminishes over time. Early identification of amyloid deposition could be crucial in guiding personalized therapeutic strategies for managing PSCI effectively.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Results show variability in normative cognitive aging patterns between research study participants in United States and Korean imaging studies. APOE ε4 was more influential in rates of decline among Korean participants. These findings underscore the importance of replicating findings, diversifying study populations, and of considering ethnic and racialized backgrounds when examining genetic risk and cognitive aging, as different populations may show distinct patterns of decline.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Restoring Cell-Cell Junctions in DSPP-Deficient Odontoblasts Through Nanofibrous Topography and Wnt5a-Cdc42 Activation: A Laboratory Investigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results provide evidence that Dspp contributes to the structural integrity of dentine by modulating ZO-1 and Cx43 expression and suggest that biomaterial and molecular interventions may offer supportive strategies to restore dentine structure and function in DGI-affected teeth, though they do not address the underlying genetic defect.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Good People, Good Memories, Good Life!]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings support that astrogliosis, reflected by GFAP, mediates or moderates the key neuropathological processes related to AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Disturbing dreams predicted incident dementia and AD among individuals aged 60-69 years, and incident AD among men aged 60-89 years. Disturbing dreams may be a pre-clinical indicator and possible prodrome of dementia and AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing and Evaluating Guidelines to Prevent Overdependence on Digital Therapeutics in Children and Adolescents: Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both caregivers and children and adolescents demonstrated the need for guidelines to prevent overdependence on DTx distinct from smartphone usage. Tailored guidelines may be acceptable for use in real-world therapeutic protocols. Guidelines to prevent overdependence on DTx in children and adolescents and to achieve a balance between their benefits and risks need to be established.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Plasma NfL is more strongly linked to MRI markers of diffuse structural neurodegeneration than FDG-PET markers of functional decline, underscoring the importance of considering these relationships when using NfL for AD diagnosis or monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic performance of a video-assisted cardiac arrest recognition protocol by emergency medical dispatcher in out-of-hospital cardiac arrest]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Use of video-assisted cardiac arrest recognition protocol helped recognize additional cardiac arrest cases that could not be recognized with the audio-call in the dispatch center. Technological and operational improvement should be continuously studied for better cardiac arrest recognition using video-assisted protocol during emergency call taking.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brain MRI-based prognostication after cardiac arrest: qualitative assessment outperforms variable voxel-wise ADC thresholds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Qualitative visual assessment remained a robust predictor, both independently and as part of multimodal prognostication, whereas quantitative ADC thresholds showed substantial variability across aetiologies and MRI protocols, underscoring the limitations of a universal threshold.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomic Signatures and Early Biomarkers Predicting Veno-Occlusive Disease in Pediatric Patients Undergoing Haploidentical HSCT with Busulfan-based Conditioning and Post-Transplant Cyclophosphamide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatic veno-occlusive disease (VOD), or sinusoidal obstruction syndrome, is a life-threatening complication following hematopoietic cell transplantation (HSCT). In pediatric patients, busulfan-based myeloablative conditioning is a major risk factor. This study aimed to identify plasma proteomic biomarkers predictive of VOD development in children undergoing haploidentical HSCT with busulfan-based conditioning and post-transplant cyclophosphamide. Plasma samples were collected from 51 children...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Similar hepatic outcome by SGLT2i vs. DPP4i for at-risk cohort with CHB &amp; T2DM: a nationwide target trial emulation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The overall hepatic prognosis was comparable between the SGLT2i and the DPP4i groups. Further prospective studies are required to reach robust conclusions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Physiotherapy on Clinical Outcomes in Patients with Brain Injury: A Post-hoc Analysis of the ENIO Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Physiotherapy was frequently applied in patients with acute brain injury, but no significant association was observed with extubation failure, mortality, or ICU stay. These findings underscore the need for prospective studies addressing timing, intensity, and modality of physiotherapy in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Converging Influenza Threats: Seasonal A(H3N2) (including subclade K) Dynamics and the Persistent Pandemic Risk of A(H5N1)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A practical workflow for fixation and autofluorescence reduction in correlative light and electron microscopy of postmortem human brain tissue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We established an adaptive workflow for postmortem human brain tissue that balances ultrastructural preservation and antigenicity. Fixation with 4 % PFA + 0.2 % GLA followed by cryopreservation creates a flexible, high-quality tissue archive. For high-fidelity CLEM or electron microscopy analysis, solvent-based quenchers like Sudan Black B must be omitted. This protocol enhances the utility of irreplaceable human brain samples for multimodal neuropathological studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-arm longitudinal study to assess changes in insula functional connectivity following a mobile-based lifestyle intervention in adults with metabolic abnormalities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The mobile-based lifestyle intervention significantly reduced weight and alleviated binge eating in adults with metabolic abnormalities. FC enhancement between the posterior insula and the frontoparietal regions was also observed after mobile-based lifestyle intervention. The relationship between these FC changes and strengthening weight control through mobile-based lifestyle intervention should be investigated through future research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of BAP1 activity by novel cancer-associated glutamate residues through ubiquitin binding and PARylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BAP1 is a deubiquitinase with a ubiquitin C-terminal hydrolase domain that functions as a tumor suppressor and regulates key cellular processes, including DNA repair. Mutations in BAP1 are prevalent in cancers such as mesothelioma, uveal melanoma, and clear cell renal cell carcinoma, yet the functional consequences of individual residues remain incompletely defined. Here, using structural analysis, mutational screening, and cellular and in vitro assays, we identify three cancer-associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNA granule-associated regulation of antiviral RNA interference by the RNA-binding E3 ubiquitin ligase in Fusarium graminearum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA interference (RNAi) is a major antiviral defense in fungi, yet the regulatory mechanisms governing this pathway remain incompletely characterized. In this study, we identified GzC2H056 as a host factor required for the induction of FgDICER-2 and FgAGO-1 in Fusarium graminearum during infection by the Fusarium graminearum virus 2 (FgV2). GzC2H056 expression is transcriptionally induced upon FgV2 infection and exhibits both RNA-binding and E3 ubiquitin ligase activity in vitro. Fluorescence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings provide valuable insight into the progression of AD and underscore the importance of the recent 30-90 Hz gamma band research. This frequency band shows potential as a cost-effective and comprehensive biomarker for differentiating individuals with AD from HC in dementia research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings emphasize the importance of tailoring plasma p-tau217 cutoffs based on kidney function, BMI, and anemia status to enhance diagnostic accuracy, especially in populations with more severe kidney dysfunction (eGFR <45).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SCT and Gaze Instability measurements demonstrated effective differentiation in mobile contexts. The redefined self-correction parameters and Gaze Instability metrics, combined with the RCF phase, enhanced measurement precision under ambient noise. These methodological advances established an economical approach for amyloid pathology detection. Enabling potential applications for earlier Aβ identification at preclinical AD stages, it presented opportunities for expedited clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CBF was sensitive to differences between eGFR stages, higher in Stage 1 compared to Stages 2 and 3, suggesting its utility as an early marker for brain integrity changes. Its positive correlation with eGFR and inverse relation with creatinine support its role in monitoring early cerebral perfusion changes linked to renal function. This study underscores the interconnectedness of renal and brain health, proposing CBF as a potential early biomarker for cerebral changes in a healthy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings suggest that brain resilience, as measured by the difference between brain age and chronological age, may be a critical factor in the development of post-stroke dementia. These results indicate that brain age and resilience could serve as valuable biomarkers for predicting post-stroke dementia and guiding clinical interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autonomous Nanoparticle Synthesis Guided by <em>In Situ</em> Multiscale Structural Characterization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autonomous synthesis platforms promise rapid exploration of vast parameter spaces; yet, integrating in situ structural characterization in closed-loop synthesis optimization remains challenging. We demonstrate a realization of such a closed-loop platform coupled with a droplet-flow microreactor, in situ X-ray scattering methods (SAXS/WAXS), and Gaussian process optimization to synthesize citrate-reduced Au nanoparticles with targeted characteristics. The system efficiently explored ∼19,000...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: By reducing reliance on cost-intensive PET scans and handling missing data more effectively, our framework could substantially broaden access to early AD screening in diverse clinical settings. Future work will involve testing in larger, more varied cohorts, applying different tracers, and further evaluate its real-world impact on AD management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DM influences cerebellar volume differently across the AD spectrum. Anterior lobe atrophy in normal cognition suggests early cerebellar vulnerability to DM, while posterior lobe atrophy in amyloid-positive MCI indicates accelerated degeneration in advanced amyloid pathology. The absence of significant changes in preclinical AD may reflect compensatory mechanisms. These findings highlight the complex interaction between DM and AD, with DM potentially exacerbating cerebellar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The association between brain tissue volume loss and levels of IL1β and T-tau suggests that IL1β and T-tau in the blood are potential biomarkers for cognitive impairment in elderly people. Thus, they could be used for future assessment of disease severity and response to treatment after diagnosis in elderly people who might progress to cognitive impairment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study introduces a deep-learning based approach for detecting lacunes from highly imbalanced dataset using encoder pretrained with supervised contrastive learning. Future work will focus on expanding the current approach to include lacune localization within specific brain regions and conducting external validation across multiple centers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An introduction to BASIC Guide: human biomonitoring and surveillance of chemical exposure in occupational settings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human biomonitoring (HBM) complements air and surface measurements by integrating exposure from all routes and sources, strengthening occupational exposure assessment and control. In occupational settings, HBM can quantify exposure during routine work and nonroutine activities, evaluate controls, investigate incidents (potential overexposures), and support medical surveillance. To use HBM to its full potential, occupational health and safety professionals (OHPs) should adopt harmonized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Awareness and real-world practices in chronic lymphocytic leukemia: insights from a nationwide survey of Korean hematologists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This survey highlights gaps between international recommendations and Korean real-world practice, emphasizing the need for improved diagnostic availability, timely reimbursement of targeted agents, and development of Korea-specific clinical guidelines tailored to the Korean context.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic performance of lung perfusion SPECT/CT using perfusion defect and decrease criteria: a comparative study with CTPA in pulmonary thromboembolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic performance of shear-wave dispersion imaging and shear-wave elastography for differentiating benign and malignant breast masses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SWD improves the diagnostic performance across varying lesion size, depth, and breast thickness, addressing SWE's limitations. It is particularly effective for small lesions (≤ 20 mm) and BI-RADS 4B masses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Newly-engineered angiopoietin-1 as a cell-priming agent for CVD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human peripheral blood stem cells (PBSC) that have been most frequently used for repair or regeneration in ischemic cardiovascular disease (CVD) showed limitations in their efficacy. We previously reported that angiopoietin-1 (Ang1) is the cell-priming agent to enhance the vasculogenic potential of PBSC. The limitation was the difficulty to produce Ang1 protein with high efficiency. In this study, we engineered Ang1 structure and made FVA3-Ang1 by adding VASP and COMP sequence for stable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vaccine Platform-Dependent Differential Impact on Microbiome Diversity: Potential Advantages of Protein Subunit Vaccines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The COVID-19 pandemic accelerated the development of diverse vaccine platforms, including mRNA, adenoviral vector, and protein subunit vaccines. Given the growing evidence that the gut microbiome modulates vaccine-induced immunity, this study compared the effects of a protein subunit vaccine (NVX-CoV2373), an mRNA vaccine (BNT162b2), and an adenoviral vector vaccine (ChAdOx1) on gut microbiome diversity following booster vaccination. Methods: We conducted a prospective cohort study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunological Considerations of Polysorbate as an Excipient in Botulinum Neurotoxin Type A Formulations: A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent botulinum neurotoxin type A (BoNT/A) formulations have shifted towards the use of polysorbate 20 (PS20) and polysorbate 80 (PS80) as a non-human-derived excipient to enhance product stability. Polysorbates are a distinct class of synthetic non-ionic surfactants with high heterogeneity in chemical structure and properties. Accumulating mechanistic and clinical evidence suggests that they may trigger immunological reactions, including hypersensitivity and immunogenicity. Such risks are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pilot Evaluation of a Deep Learning Model for Nasogastric Tube Verification on Chest Radiographs: A Single-Center Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The DL model performed well in identifying correctly positioned NG tubes but demonstrated limited and unstable performance for detecting incomplete placements. Given the safety implications of misclassification, the model should be used only as an assistive tool with mandatory physician oversight. Larger, multi-center studies with greater representation of incomplete cases are required to obtain more reliable estimates and support safe clinical implementation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Angiovolume and Peak Enhancement on Preoperative CAD-Derived MRI as Prognostic Factors in Primary Operable Triple-Negative Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: To identify preoperative MRI features using computer-assisted diagnosis (CAD) that are associated with invasive disease-free survival (IDFS) and distant metastasis-free survival (DDFS) in patients with primarily operable triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC). Methods: This retrospective study was approved by the institutional review board with informed consent was waived. Between January 2012 and December 2014, 74 consecutive women with primary TNBC (mean age, 51 years;...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning for Predicting Human Drug-Induced Cardiotoxicity: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This review underscores the importance of integrating heterogeneous data and rigorous validation for improving cardiotoxicity prediction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of Lifestyle and Dietary Factors with Urinary Bisphenol A, S, and F: Evidence from the Korean National Environmental Health Survey IV (2018-2020)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bisphenol A, Bisphenol S, and Bisphenol F are widely used plastic additives and endocrine-disrupting chemicals with potential adverse health effects. Limited research has examined lifestyle and dietary factors influencing human exposure to these compounds. This study investigated associations between urinary bisphenol concentrations and demographic, lifestyle, dietary, and food-handling factors in 4239 Korean adults aged 19 to 82 years (1889 men, 44.6%; 2350 women, 55.4%) from the Korean...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of Fouling in Hollow Fiber Membrane Distillation Modules for Desalination Brine Reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Membrane distillation (MD) is a promising technology for reducing the volume of high-salinity brines generated from desalination plants, yet limited knowledge exists regarding its fouling behavior under long-term operation. In this study, fouling was investigated through the autopsy of a hollow fiber MD module operated for 120 days in a direct contact membrane distillation (DCMD) configuration using real desalination brine. Despite stable salt rejection exceeding 99%, a gradual decline in flux...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41441074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[6-Isoprenylindole-3-carboxylic Acid with an Anti-Melanogenic Activity from a Marine-Derived <em>Streptomyces</em> sp. APA-053]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we report the isolation of the known compound 6-isoprenylindole-3-carboxylic acid (SJ196), a prenylated indole derivative, from a marine Streptomyces sp., APA053, and its potent anti-melanogenic activity. SJ196 showed ABTS and DPPH radical scavenging activities and cellular antioxidant activities, significantly suppressing cytoplasmic and mitochondrial reactive oxygen species (ROS) in B16F10 murine melanoma cells. Furthermore, SJ196 reduced both intracellular and extracellular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Practice to Reflection: A Systematic Review of Mechanisms Driving Metacognition and SRL in Music]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metacognition and self-regulated learning (SRL) are widely recognized as key mechanisms for academic achievement and skill development, yet in music education they have rarely been examined through explicit instructional interventions to enable causal testing and effect evaluation. To address this gap, this study followed PRISMA guidelines and conducted a systematic review of 31 studies (including seven for meta-analysis) to identify intervention types and mechanisms, and to quantify their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Immersion in Quaternary Ammonium Methacryloxy Silane Mixed Monomer on the Mechanical Properties and Antibacterial Activity of a 3D-Printed Urethane Dimethacrylate Denture Base Resin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Denture base resins are susceptible to microbial colonization, and current antibacterial additives often lose effectiveness and may weaken material properties. This study evaluated whether immersion in a quaternary ammonium methacryloxy silane (QAMS)-containing monomer can enhance antibacterial activity without compromising the mechanical properties of digital light processing-printed urethane dimethacrylate denture base resin. Specimens of printed denture base resin were immersed in mixtures of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of Structural Stability and IgG Affinity of a <em>Z34C</em>-Derived α-Helical Peptide via Lactam Stapling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results confirm the successful design and development of structurally reinforced Fc-binding peptides that overcome the inherent limitations of short linear sequences through both high-affinity sequence optimization and lactam-based stapling. Among them, (s)SpA h1 demonstrates the most promising characteristics as a compact yet stable Fc-binding ligand, suitable for applications such as antibody purification and site-specific bioconjugation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Childhood Obesity on Adult Dental Caries: A Mendelian Randomization Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study investigates the association between childhood obesity and the incidence of dental caries in adulthood. The primary objective is to determine whether metabolic disorders experienced during the developmental years can have long-term impacts on oral health, thereby contributing to a more comprehensive understanding of dental growth and development. Methods: The research was conducted using single nucleotide polymorphisms (SNPs) from European populations within a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Metabolite-Responsive Transcription Factor Systems as Modular Platforms for Gene Expression Control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditional inducible systems typically induce the simultaneous expression of all genes controlled by similar promoters, thereby limiting their use. In this study, we used two metabolite-inducible systems, MarR from the Escherichia coli mar operon and TtgR from the Pseudomonas putida ttg operon, to assess their use as gene regulation platforms beyond reporter assays. Ligand-dependent transcription was validated using eGFP. The reporter was replaced with two flavonoid O-methyltransferases (OMTs),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opportunities and Challenges in Gas Sensor Technologies for Accurate Detection of COVID-19]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gas sensors provide versatile opportunities for detecting volatile organic compounds (VOCs) such as acetone, methanol, ethanol, propanol, isoprene, and aldehydes in exhaled breath (EB) associated with COVID-19 respiratory infections. These VOCs provide valuable information about metabolic markers linked with COVID-19. They have opened opportunities to develop sensors for COVID-19 screening based on breath analysis. These sensors have the potential to provide the rapid detection of viruses in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Fear to Adaptation: The Journey of Patients with Liver Cancer Living with the Fear of Cancer Recurrence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The study aimed to understand how patients with liver cancer experience and adapt to the fear of cancer recurrence, providing insights into psychological processes and strategies that can inform psycho-oncology research and interventions. In-depth interviews were conducted with 13 patients with liver cancer from December 2019 to February 2020 and analyzed using Colaizzi's phenomenological method. Four theme clusters emerged: (1) "Inevitable reality of recurrence," which highlighted the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resilience as a Mediator Between Childhood Trauma and Adult Psychopathology: The Moderating Role of Harm Avoidance in Korean Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Childhood trauma is a well-established risk factor for adult psychopathology, yet the underlying neuropsychiatric mechanisms remain unclear. Therefore, this study examined whether resilience mediates the relationship between childhood trauma and depressive and anxiety symptoms, and whether this pathway is moderated by harm avoidance (HA). Methods: A total of 218 Korean adults (aged 19-50 years; 79 men and 139 women) completed validated measures of childhood trauma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of EphA2 Silencing on Inhibiting the Progression of Renal Cell Carcinoma in an Orthotopic Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: We investigated whether EphA2 inhibition can attenuate the progression of renal cell carcinoma (RCC) in an orthotopic mouse model of kidney tumor cells (Renca). Materials and Methods: 16 BALB/c mice were divided into two groups and implanted with either control or shRNA-mediated, EphA2-knockdown Renca-Luciferase cells via injection under the right renal capsule. Tumor progression was followed by in vivo bioluminescence imaging (BLI). Tumor growth was evaluated via ex vivo BLI and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41440001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Bioenergetics: Emerging Roles of Mitochondrial Fatty Acid Oxidation in Stress Response and Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondrial fatty acid oxidation (FAO) has long been recognized as a central pathway for energy production, providing acetyl-CoA, NADH, and FADH(2) to sustain cellular growth and survival. However, recent advances have revealed that FAO exerts far broader roles beyond bioenergetics. FAO contributes to redox balance by generating NADPH for antioxidant defense, regulates protein acetylation through acetyl-CoA availability, and modulates stress signaling pathways to support cellular adaptation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Placental-Derived Mesenchymal Stem Cells Triggers Lipid Metabolism in a Rat Model Thioacetamide-Induced Ovarian Disease via Increased CPT1A Expression for Mitochondrial Dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipid accumulation disrupts mitochondrial dynamics, leading to dysfunctional energy metabolism and increased oxidative stress. However, the relationship between mitochondrial dynamics and ovarian function in therapeutic contexts is still not fully elucidated. Therefore, the objective of this study was to demonstrate whether increased carnitine palmitoyltransferase 1A (CPT1A) expression induced by placenta-derived mesenchymal stem cells (PD-MSCs) improves ovarian function in ovaries of a lipid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NDFNGO: Enhanced Northern Goshawk Optimization Algorithm for Image Segmentation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The gradual deterioration of fresco pictorial information presents a formidable obstacle for conservators dedicated to protecting humanity's shared cultural legacy. Currently, scholars in the field of mural conservation predominantly focus on image segmentation techniques as a vital tool for facilitating mural restoration and protection. However, the existing image segmentation methods frequently fall short of delivering optimal segmentation results. To address this issue, this study introduces...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomimetic Artificial Muscles Inspired by Nature's Volume-Change Actuation Mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial muscles translate the biological principles of motion into soft, adaptive, and multifunctional actuation. This review accordingly highlights research into natural actuation strategies, such as skeletal muscles, muscular hydrostats, spider silk, and plant turgor systems, to reveal the principles underlying energy conversion and deformation control. Building on these insights, polymer-based artificial muscles based on these principles, including pneumatic muscles, dielectric elastomers,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Core-Shell Silk Fibroin Hydrogel Microneedles Functionalized with Antibody-Binding Domains for Transdermal Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microneedle (MN) patches comprise a promising platform for transdermal delivery of macromolecular therapeutics. However, achieving sufficient mechanical strength for skin penetration while maintaining high biocompatibility and efficient antibody loading remains a major challenge. In this study, we designed and developed a core-shell-structured hydrogel MN patch composed of a silk fibroin core and a protein-based shell layer for antibody loading and potential transdermal release. The latter was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of a Modified Island Groin Flap for Microsurgical Training: An Experimental Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The modified groin flap is easy to recreate in a rat model and well-suited for microsurgical training among novice trainees. This flap design also serves as a reliable platform for studying ischemic-reperfusion injury.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Amino acid-modified G-quartet hydrogel for glucose-responsive insulin release <em>in vivo</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Correction for 'Amino acid-modified G-quartet hydrogel for glucose-responsive insulin release in vivo' by Dharmesh Jinagal et al., Chem. Commun., 2025, 61, 19477-19480, https://doi.org/10.1039/D5CC05351J.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An integrated bioinformatics and multi-omics investigation of the sirtuin family to identify their prognostic importance in human cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundIn recent years, the significance of sirtuins in cancer biology has become increasingly evident, but their molecular mechanisms and prognostic impacts remain elusive.ObjectiveThe present study aimed to investigate the differential expression of the sirtuin gene family across cancers and to evaluate their prognostic value.MethodsWe used various bioinformatics databases and methodologies, including Oncomine, GEPIA, OncoDB, cBioPortal, R2 Kaplan-Meier Scanner, STRING, etc., to determine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basic Science and Pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although significant relationships between systemic inflammation, brain amyloid and neuroinflammation were limited, the data show an overarching trend bias in broad brain regions, suggesting that further analyses are needed, possibly with larger sample sizes, to assess the relationship of regional neuroinflammation and amyloid to systemic inflammation. Future analyses could also regress out factors like sex, age, and genotype to further proinflammatory cytokine research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Learning-Based Brainstem Segmentation and Multi-Class Classification for Parkinsonian Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Brain segmentation using structural MRI is effective for identifying regional atrophy in Parkinsonian syndromes. However, clinical validation of the automated deep learning-based brainstem segmentation model has been limited.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why do children and adults believe others apologize?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Apologies are a fundamental social mechanism for repairing harm and maintaining relationships, yet little is known about how individuals infer the motives behind them. This study examined how 5- to 6-year-old children (N = 64, 48.4% female; all participants were Korean) and adults (N = 132, 52.3% female; all Korean) attribute motives to wrongdoers' apologies, focusing on internal motives (guilt, shame) and external motives (relational concern, avoidance of punishment). Participants were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrical Transport of Nb-Doped MoS<sub>2</sub> Homojunction P-N Diode: Investigating NDR and Avalanche Effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[2D transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDCs) are promising candidates for next-generation nanoelectronics and optoelectronics. Yet, controlling layer number, stacking angle, and interfacial quality in van der Waals (vdW) heterostructures remains challenging, often limiting device performance and reproducibility. Homojunctions formed within a single 2D material can circumvent these issues, but their reliable fabrication and systematic exploration of exotic quantum phenomena remain elusive. Here,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validating the Effectiveness of a VR-based and Haptic Technology-based Operating Room Simulation Program Among Nursing Students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to validate the effectiveness of a virtual reality (VR) and haptic technology-based simulation program for operating room nursing education among undergraduate nursing students. Providing students with hands-on experience in the operating room is challenging due to safety, ethical, and logistical constraints. Therefore, this study explored immersive simulation as a viable alternative. We used a nonequivalent control group pretest-posttest design, with 78 nursing students divided...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between the Rate of Intraoperative Crystalloid Infusion and Postoperative Outcomes in Older Patients Undergoing Spinal Surgery: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Liberal fluid therapy was associated with a higher risk of postoperative in-hospital complications and 1-year morbidity compared with restrictive fluid therapy in patients aged ≥70 years who underwent spinal surgery. Further studies are necessary to verify our findings for the establishment of appropriate intraoperative fluid management for geriatric patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does Using Mobile Phones Make You Less Attractive? Phubbing and Perceptions of Warmth, Competence, and Social Attractiveness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phubbing has become a prominent phenomenon in today's digital landscape, with detrimental effects on relational well-being. Beyond its negative impact on various types of relationships, scholarly interest has been paid to the influence of phubbing on impression formation. Drawing on the Stereotype Content Model, which highlights the roles of warmth and competence in social perception and evaluation, this study examined how phubbing affects these dimensions and subsequently influences social...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Challenging Case of Dermatofibrosarcoma Protuberans (DFSP) Presenting With a Cone-Shaped Scalp Mass]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dermatofibrosarcoma protuberans (DFSP) is a rare cutaneous malignancy characterized by extensive subclinical extension. Because of its locally destructive nature, most dermatologic surgeons perform Mohs micrographic surgery (MMS) to ensure negative margins. Undergoing multiple stages of MMS can be burdensome, and the subsequent reconstruction of massive cutaneous defects remains highly challenging. Here, we report a case of a 44-year-old man with a recurrent DFSP of the scalp who developed a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41439049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of high-intensity focused ultrasound for treating upper and lower eyelid sagging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HIFU is a safe and effective noninvasive option for improving both upper and lower eyelid sagging, with high patient satisfaction and minimal adverse effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptions and utilization of telemedicine for hair loss treatment: A survey-based analysis of Korean consumers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vessels That Encapsulate Tumor Cluster+ Unresectable Hepatocellular Carcinomas Benefit of Antiangiogenic Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: VETC+ predicts a significantly longer OS in patients with unresectable HCC treated with TKI/BEVA and can be used as surrogate marker on liver biopsy of angiogenesis-driven molecular class.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between asthma control and health-related quality of life in severe asthma: a cross-sectional study from KoSAR]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Uncontrolled asthma, particularly its impact on daily functioning, was associated with HRQoL impairment in patients with SA. Enhancing asthma control may significantly reduce the disease burden and improve HRQoL in SA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bayesian Model Calibration and Sensitivity Analysis for Oscillating Biological Experiments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the oscillating behaviors that govern organisms' internal biological processes requires interdisciplinary efforts combining both biological and computer experiments, as the latter can complement the former by simulating perturbed conditions with higher resolution. Harmonizing the two types of experiment, however, poses significant statistical challenges due to identifiability issues, numerical instability, and ill behavior in high dimension. This article devises a new Bayesian...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boron Neutron Capture Therapy in Recurrent High-Grade Gliomas: Safety, Efficacy, and Pharmacokinetics From a Multicenter, Dose-Escalation Phase 1 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates the acceptable safety profile of BNCT and suggests potential survival benefits in recurrent high-grade glioma. However, given the limited sample size and follow-up period, extended observation is required to validate long-term efficacy and safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Contralateral Acupuncture (Geoja Technique) in Musculoskeletal Disorders Stratified by Pulse Strength Differences: A Retrospective Study [Response to Letter]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental health in female breast cancer survivors post-mastectomy: A structural model based on Roy's adaptation model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Effective mental health assessment and intervention for breast cancer survivors undergoing mastectomy requires an integrated approach that considers coping processes, body image, role performance, and social support. Nurses should focus on strengthening adaptive coping strategies, fostering a positive body image, managing role-related stress, and enhancing social support systems to improve survivors' overall mental well-being.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal aerobic exercise dose for pain relief in fibromyalgia syndrome: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This meta-analysis confirms the efficacy of AE in reducing pain in FMS. AE significantly alleviates pain in fibromyalgia, with moderate-intensity, water-based, showing the most effective results. These findings provide strong evidence for incorporating AE as a key non-pharmacological strategy in the management of fibromyalgia, especially for patients with more severe pain. The identified optimal exercise parameters offer clear guidance for clinical practice, supporting the use of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunoregulatory protein-hybrid extracellular vesicles via self-loadable backbone cyclization for oral inflammatory bowel disease therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the potential of extracellular vesicles (EVs) and therapeutic proteins as carriers and cargos for oral delivery, their precise functional integration remains a persistent challenge, thereby limiting synergistic therapeutic outcomes. Here, we present a protein-hybrid, orally delivered EV strategy that integrates naturally bioactive EVs with self-loadable, backbone-cyclized immunoregulatory proteins for inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) therapy. Through computationally guided design and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An RbohC and RbohE-mediated ROS oscillatory circuit regulates root cap turnover in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the primary interface between the growing root and the soil, the root tip experiences continuous mechanical and environmental stress. The root cap protects this region through dynamic turnover, in which outer cells are regularly shed and replaced by new cells derived from inner initials. This turnover proceeds via two distinct pathways: programmed cell death in the lateral root cap and detachment of the outermost columella root cap. Focusing on the latter, we show that reactive oxygen species...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41438069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basic Science and Pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first reported case of a PSEN2 and SLC20A2 double mutation in the literature.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Donor age and type in allogeneic haematopoietic stem cell transplantation: Strong effect in MDS, limited in AML]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Donor age is an important factor influencing outcomes after allogeneic haematopoietic stem cell transplantation (allo-HSCT), but its relevance across donor types and distinct disease biology in acute myeloid leukaemia (AML) and myelodysplastic syndrome (MDS) remains unclear. We analysed 320 patients with AML/MDS who underwent first allo-HSCT between 2016 and 2024. Donors were categorized as matched or mismatched and further stratified as young (<35 years) or old (≥35 years). Matched donors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Halogenated Chiral Spacer Integration in Silver Bismuth Double Perovskites for Efficient and Selective CPL Photodetection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chiral double perovskites (DPs) have emerged as a versatile class of materials for detecting circularly polarized light (CPL), offering sustainable alternatives to toxic Pb-based systems. Despite their superior oxidative stability, the interplay between A-site chiral cations and B-site metal cations in DPs remains poorly understood, particularly regarding its influence on the electronic structure and chiroptical activity. In this study, we propose a rational chiral cation design strategy in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidural Steroid Injections for Pain Management in Spinal Metastases: Clinical Predictors of Effectiveness in a Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ESI may be beneficial in reducing pain and attenuating opioid escalation in patients with spinal metastases, especially when the performance status is relatively preserved, and before the initiation of high-dose opioid therapy. These results support early integration of ESI into multimodal cancer pain management strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robot-Based Cognitive Intervention Effects on Brain Function and Cognition in Patients With Mild Alzheimer's Disease Dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that robot-assisted CIs may be associated with enhanced cognitive and brain function in patients with mild AD dementia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Everyday Discrimination With Drug Use During the COVID-19 Pandemic in the All of Us Research Program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This relationship was observed across various types of drugs and different reasons for discrimination, and it was particularly pronounced in specific subgroups. These findings provide critical evidence for developing targeted preventive interventions; however, further longitudinal studies for causality are warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41437550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[k-dependent modulation of intrinsic spin-orbit interaction in MoSe<sub>2</sub> induced by proximity to amorphous Pb]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuning the strength of spin-orbit interaction (SOI) is pivotal for developing next-generation spintronic and quantum devices. Proximity-induced SOI is a promising route toward this goal, but its experimental characterization with resolution in k-space using ARPES remains challenging. We advance previous ARPES investigations of proximity-induced SOI in graphene-based systems to transition-metal dichalcogenides (MoSe(2)) in proximity to an amorphous overlayer of high-Z metal (Pb) whose disordered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal exercise modalities and doses for improving pro-atherogenic lipid profiles in patients with metabolic syndrome: a systematic review with pairwise, network, and dose-response meta-analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Structured exercise may improve pro-atherogenic lipid profiles in MetS. CAREX and HIIT appear promising at moderate doses, while MBE could serve as a feasible low-impact alternative for individuals with reduced exercise tolerance. These findings suggest preliminary dose-based targets that may help guide personalized exercise prescriptions in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integration of polygenic risk score with measured blood pressure reveals hidden risks of cardiovascular disease mortality: A Japanese prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although previous studies reported that BP PRS is associated with CVD, it is less explored whether BP PRS and BP are jointly associated with CVD, especially among non-European populations. Therefore, we examined joint associations of BP control and BP polygenic risk score (PRS) with CVD mortality in a Japanese population. Data were obtained from the Japan Multi-Institutional Collaborative Cohort (J-MICC) Study, the multi-centered cohort study with 14 study areas throughout Japan. Of which, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of protocol-based pharmacotherapy management in switching of antibiotic administration routes and dose adjustment based on renal function: a before-after study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[State-transition trajectories in out-of-hospital cardiac arrest: neurological outcomes beyond myocardial activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cytotoxic and senescence-inducing effects of BLU554 in pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma: an in vitro study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This two-step strategy may represent a novel therapeutic approach for the treatment of therapy-resistant PDAC through senescence induction and subsequent senolysis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid laboratory detection of ustalic acid in freshly collected Tricholoma Kakishimeji using probe electrospray ionization tandem mass spectrometry (PESI-MS/MS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of transanal tube placement in preventing anastomotic leakage in rectal cancer surgery with sufficient perfusion confirmed by indocyanine green fluorescence imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The placement of a TA may offer additional benefit in reducing the risk of AL after rectal cancer surgery when adequate perfusion is confirmed using ICG fluorescence imaging, particularly in cases of middle rectal cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-port robotic restorative proctectomy with ileal pouch-anal anastomosis for ulcerative colitis: first clinical experience and technical insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SP robotic proctectomy with IPAA is feasible and safe in unselected patients with UC, supporting further large prospective evaluation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design and analysis of high-k wrapped underlap induced GaN multi-channel GAA nanosheet FET for enhanced performance with cut-off frequency in THz range]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A multi-channel Gallium Nitride (GaN) based Gate-All-Around (GAA) Nanosheet Field Effect Transistor (NS FET) having 2 nm gate underlap wrapping of high-k dielectric spacer are designed, explored and analysed for inclusion in future wireless application systems. The integration of GaN as the channel material provides superior electron mobility and high breakdown voltage, making it extremely suitable for high-frequency applications. The inclusion of the gate underlap region effectively reduces...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcutaneous auricular vagus nerve stimulation reduces error amplitude during force field learning in healthy adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transcutaneous auricular vagus nerve stimulation (taVNS) has gained increasing attention as an expected new clinical application for motor disease due to its synergistic effect with post-stroke rehabilitation. On the other hand, there are still few reports regarding the effects of taVNS on motor learning in healthy subjects. In the present study, we investigated how taVNS affects a reaching movement task under a force field condition (i.e., force field learning). A total of 32 healthy,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The extent of alpha-synuclein aggregate accumulation in neurons varies depending on the type of neurotransmitter they release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alpha-synuclein (aSyn) is a highly conserved 140-amino acid presynaptic protein involved in neuronal plasticity and recognized as the pathogenic protein in Parkinson's disease. Aggregated aSyn propagates transsynaptically between neurons in vivo, impairing the cellular function of affected cells. However, it remains unclear whether aggregated aSyn propagates similarly across all neuronal cell types. In this study, we injected sonicated aSyn preformed fibrils into the striatum of mice and used...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results demonstrated that the severity of VOI atrophy measured using VSRAD was significantly decreased in patients treated with lecanemab in actual clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41444130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A call for ethical, equitable, and effective artificial intelligence to improve care for all people with epilepsy: A roadmap. A report by the ILAE Global Advocacy Council and Big Data Commission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The artificial intelligence (AI) revolution is upon us. It will inevitably form a central component of epilepsy workflows and patient advocacy. Therefore, it behooves us as health care providers to ride the crest of this wave and guide its direction for the benefit of all people with epilepsy. Emerging AI-based solutions include decision support tools, automated interpretation of electroencephalography (EEG) and brain imaging, and wearable devices that detect seizures and improve patient safety....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lemborexant does not worsen cognitive function and WASO, and does not accentuate RBD, in patients with DLB.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We observed an anterior-posterior effect of TDP-43 and tau on the MTL with TDP-43 affecting anterior MTL volumes and tau posterior MTL volumes. Hippocampal head atrophy could help distinguish between AD patients with/without comorbid LATE.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between the Expression of Monocarboxylate Transporters in Tumors and Surrounding Stromal Cells and Cancer Prognosis: A Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[l-Lactate is not merely a metabolic product of glycolysis but also a molecule that plays an important role in intercellular interactions. Monocarboxylate transporters (MCTs) 1-4 are membrane proteins responsible for transporting monocarboxylic acids, such as l-lactate, across the plasma membrane. MCTs have been suggested to be involved in cancer cell invasion, metastasis, and immune evasion. Several studies have reported the relationship between MCT expression in tumor tissues and cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of Surfactants on the Stability of Cannabidiol, Formulated as a Water-Soluble Product, in Simulated Gastric Fluid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explored the degradation of water-soluble cannabidiol (CBD) products in surfactant-containing gastric fluid. It was hypothesized that various surfactants would catalyze CBD degradation, and their chemical properties were investigated in detail. CBD products (CBD oil and two water-soluble CBD products) were dissolved in water containing nine surfactants: C(8)H(17)SO(4)Na, C(10)H(21)SO(4)Na, C(12)H(25)SO(4)Na (sodium dodecyl sulfate; SDS), C(14)H(29)SO(4)Na, C(16)H(33)SO(4)Na,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient Education to Prevent Exposure to Anticancer Drugs among Patients and Caregivers during Outpatient Chemotherapy in Japan: A Cross-Sectional Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In Japan, education on preventing exposure to anticancer drugs should be conducted for outpatients receiving chemotherapy, based on the "Guideline for Preventing Occupational Exposure in Cancer Chemotherapy Drugs, 2019 Edition (guidelines 2019)." However, the educational content at each facility remains unclear. This study aimed to investigate the educational system and content in 461 cancer hospitals nationwide. We conducted a cross-sectional survey using a web questionnaire consisting of 27...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Manifestations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Seven items separated placebo from donepezil in five pivotal clinical trials of donepezil compared with placebo for Alzheimer's disease. The current study contributes to knowledge on Alzheimer's disease by identifying tasks that discriminate cognitive impairment levels, with potential use for treatment monitoring in moderate-stage Alzheimer's disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Harmonizing cutoffs, reporting, and interpretation across various clinical contexts will facilitate the incorporation of this biomarker into routine clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Secreted protein acidic and rich in cysteine-guided biomimetic delivery of nano-antioxidants reverses muscle atrophy in a mouse model of sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenia is currently classified as an unmet medical need with an increasing incidence because of population aging. Excessive reactive oxygen species (ROS) production plays a critical role in the pathogenesis of muscle atrophy, a key feature of sarcopenia, whereas edaravone has been identified as a potent ROS scavenger in screening assays using C2C12 myocytes. In this study, we established an injured muscle-targeted drug delivery system (imDDS), which mimics the secreted protein acidic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alanine-serine-cysteine transporter-targeted small-molecule boron carriers for neutron capture therapy of L-4‑boronophenylalanine-refractory tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Boron neutron capture therapy (BNCT) requires the selective delivery of sufficient amounts of ^(10)B to tumors. However, its clinical efficacy remains limited because the approved ^(10)B agent L-4‑boronophenylalanine (BPA) relies primarily on the L-type amino acid transporter 1 (LAT1), leaving LAT1-low tumors refractory to treatment. Here, we report GluB-2, a water-soluble, alanine-serine-cysteine transporter (ASCT2)-targeted small-molecule ^(10)B carrier that expands BNCT applicability beyond...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling human embryo implantation in vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Implantation of a human embryo into the endometrium is a crucial event in gestation, as it marks the initiation of a pregnancy and is prone to high failure rates. We have limited understanding of these stages because of the inaccessibility of implanting embryos and the lack of suitable model systems. Here, we establish an in vitro model that recapitulates the luminal, glandular, and stromal compartments of the superficial layer of receptive human endometrium. Human embryos and blastoids implant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal association between pulmonary function and incident cognitive decline : Results of the SONIC cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reduced pulmonary function may contribute to cognitive decline in older adults; however, few longitudinal studies adjust for frailty, lifestyle, and comorbidities. This study examined whether baseline spirometry predicts 3-year cognitive decline in community-dwelling older Japanese adults. Data were derived from the SONIC Study, a longitudinal cohort of older Japanese adults. This 3-year follow-up included community-dwelling adults in their 70 s and 80 s, stratified by age and sex. Baseline and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship between microbiota and healing status in diabetes-related foot ulcers treated with Trigona honey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings suggest that the honey's effects might differ based on the composition of the wound microbiota, and they highlight the bacterial interactions with the changes in the wound and peri-wound skin environment induced by the honey. These results also imply that honey therapy on its own may not be enough for treating DFUs. This study is limited by the small sample size and short follow-up period; further research will need to explore combined treatment strategies and long-term...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of aroma compound formation in traditional Japanese sake brewing by natural lactic acid fermentation: Insights from solvent-assisted stir bar sorptive extraction with GC-MS and bacterial flora analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Yamahai-brewed sake, a traditional Japanese rice wine fermented with naturally occurring lactic acid bacteria, has been understudied regarding its aroma compound profiles and bacterial dynamics during brewing. This study aimed to clarify the relationship between aroma compounds and bacterial communities throughout the sake brewing process, using solvent-assisted stir bar sorptive extraction with gas chromatography-mass spectrometry (SA-SBSE-GC-MS) and 16S rRNA sequencing. Seventy-four aroma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41443070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PS19 mouse tauopathy is associated with sex-dependent sleep loss and hyperarousal, and predicts cognitive performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a major public health concern in societies with increasingly ageing populations. Accumulating evidence implies a specific link between the development of tauopathy, cognitive impairment, and sleep loss in AD patients. P301S mutant tau-transgenic (PS19) mice, modelling frontotemporal dementia (FTD) and AD tauopathy, demonstrate sleep loss and cognitive impairment. We aimed to assess the progression of sleep loss and cognitive decline longitudinally in both sexes of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of time to craniotomy on outcomes in patients with severe traumatic brain injury: A nationwide cohort study using the Japan Trauma Data Bank]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Short-term outcomes in patients with severe TBI were not significantly associated with time from hospital arrival to craniotomy. This finding highlights the importance of flexible, individualized clinical decision-making in patients with TBI. Further studies are warranted to identify specific patient subgroups that may benefit from early craniotomies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Harmonization mitigates batch effects in the rsEEG posterior power spectrum. LBD is characterized by pronounced oscillatory frequency slowing and increased aperiodic activity, while AD displays both oscillatory and aperiodic abnormalities with smaller effect sizes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human papillomavirus genotype distribution in cervical intraepithelial neoplasia grade 2+ from childhood vaccinated women: The Trial23 cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HPV16/18 vaccination reduced the risk of HPV16/18-related CIN2+ lesions, but a substantial burden remained from non-vaccine high-risk types. The substantial protection against HPV16/18-related CIN2+ and the consequential shift in HPV genotype distribution of CIN2+ among vaccinated women underline the need for adaptation of screening strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of myosin light chain 1 from a forensic biological material to identify human striated muscle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In forensic practice, it may be necessary to identify the source of the tissue at crime scenes and elsewhere. We examined the physiological presence of myosin light chain 1 (MLC1), a structural protein in striated muscle, and designed a method that can identify human skeletal muscle from tissue fragments with very small sample consumption by quantitative analysis of MLC1. The MLC1 content in human muscles was compared with that in 13 different animal muscles and human organs, excluding horse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results demonstrated that while the deviations in performance metrics due to correction may be modest, they would not be negligible, particularly in cohorts with a higher proportion of CKD participants. This highlights the importance of establishing a robust correction equation for renal function to ensure the accurate real-world application of BBMs. Furthermore, it may be recommended that when reporting BBM performance the proportion of CKD within the examined samples is also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: It was demonstrated that the APOE Genotyping SNP Array is a valuable tool for assessing the risk of ARIA in patients receiving anti-Aβ antibody drugs. In the future, it is anticipated that the test will be widely utilized to evaluate the risk of ARIA prior to the administration of anti-Aβ antibody drugs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basic Science and Pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our data indicates that the genetic structure underlying the association of the TMEM106B locus with neurodegenerative diseases is driven by the effect of multiple haplotypes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased Disease Burden in Irritable Bowel Syndrome With Comorbid Conditions and Psychiatric Diagnoses in a Multinational European Cohort: Results From the DISCOvERIE Project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This large pan-European study highlights the significant impact of psychiatric and somatic comorbidities in IBS, and their strong link with outcomes and disease burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results indicate that plasma p-tau217 alone, or combinations of plasma Aβ biomarkers and p-tau217, are effective in predicting Aβ-PET positivity in preclinical and prodromal AD. The ability of the p-tau217 plasma assays to prescreen eligible patients and monitor the efficacy of anti-Aβ antibodies and other DMTs is also being tested in a real-world setting in the Japanese early symptomatic AD patient registry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41442120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251225024022&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>