<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 07:36:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Individual Differences in Policy Precision: Links to Suicidal Risk and Network Dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Behavioural modelling of decision-making processes has advanced our understanding of impairments associated with various psychiatric conditions. While many studies have focused on models that best fit behavioural data, the extent to which such models reflect biologically plausible mechanisms remains underexplored. To bridge this gap, we developed a probabilistic two-armed bandit task model grounded in the active inference framework and evaluated its performance against established...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the bioavailability and therapeutic efficacy of nintedanib-loaded novasomes as a therapy for non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nintedanib (NTD) is a tyrosine kinase inhibitor used in the treatment of non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC). However, the limited aqueous solubility of oral NTD contributes to its low bioavailability and absorption through the epithelial surface of the airways. A nebulized formulation of NTD-loaded novasomes (NLN) was developed as a potential therapy for NSCLC, with the goal of enhancing the delivery, sustainability, bioavailability, and efficacy of NTD. Utilizing design expert software, various...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Michaelis-Menten: A Modified Enzyme Kinetics Equation Improves Drug Metabolism Prediction in Bottom-Up PBPK Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Physiologically based pharmacokinetic (PBPK) models are widely used methodology that dynamically integrates diverse biological parameters to predict pharmacokinetic profiles of drugs and their metabolites. Traditionally, PBPK models rely on the Michaelis-Menten (MM) equation to describe enzymatic rate processes such as transport, metabolism, and secretion in terms of intrinsic clearance. However, the MM equation assumes that enzyme concentrations (E(T)) are substantially lower than the MM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of syngas production via plastic gasification in low-concentration CO<sub>2</sub> by using spent lithium-ion batteries-derived black mass]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the thermochemical and co-thermochemical conversion of black mass (BM), derived from spent lithium-ion batteries, with and without polyethylene (PE) under various atmospheric conditions (N(2), 25 % CO(2), and 99.999 % CO(2)) at temperatures ranging from 700 °C to 900 °C. In an inert N(2) environment, gas emissions were minimal, while significant CO production was observed under CO(2)-rich conditions due to the Boudouard and catalytic reactions facilitated by Ni-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuromorphic olfaction with ultralow-power gas sensors and ovonic threshold switch]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With increasing demand for gas sensors in mobile devices, research on developing an electronic nose (E-nose) is actively conducted. However, conventional E-nose systems based on von Neumann computing have encountered challenges such as high hardware costs and power consumption because of the necessity of hardware-intensive circuits and processors. This work implements low-power artificial olfactory neuron modules within a spiking neural network (SNN) to address this issue. The artificial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in prey selection and fitness of non-native Erythroculter erythropterus following estuarine restoration in the Nakdong River, South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Estuarine ecosystems globally are being restored through re-naturalization efforts, including the Nakdong River Estuary (NRE) in South Korea, which partially re-opened in 2019 after decades of disconnection. We investigated how this restoration affected the feeding ecology and fitness of Erythroculter erythropterus (Skygager), a non-native cyprinid that became dominant in the upper NRE following barrage construction. We surveyed fish populations, analyzed stomach contents using Next Generation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated Resectability Classification of Pancreatic Cancer CT Reports with Privacy-Preserving Open-Weight Large Language Models: A Multicenter Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the effectiveness of open-weight large language models (LLMs) in extracting key radiological features and determining National Comprehensive Cancer Network (NCCN) resectability status from free-text radiology reports for pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC). Methods. Prompts were developed using 30 fictitious reports, internally validated on 100 additional fictitious reports, and tested using 200 real reports from two institutions (January 2022 to December 2023). Two radiologists...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Succinic Acid Production by Engineered Mannheimia succiniciproducens and Its Use in Chemoenzymatic Poly(Butylene Succinate) Synthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amid growing concerns about climate change, environmental pollution, and fossil resource depletion, bio-based chemicals and materials have garnered significant attention. Succinic acid (SA), a four-carbon dicarboxylic acid, is a key platform chemical for producing industrially important compounds such as poly(butylene succinate) (PBS), a biodegradable polymer. In this paper, we demonstrate the enhanced production of SA using metabolically engineered Mannheimia succiniciproducens PALK (pMS3-gltA)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridges in social networks: current status and challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In social network analysis, bridges play a critical role in maintaining connectivity and facilitating the dissemination of information between communities. Despite increasing interest in bridge structures, a systematic classification of their roles across various network types remains unexplored. This study introduces a categorization of bridges into structural and functional types. Structural bridges maintain connectivity by preventing network fragmentation, whereas functional bridges...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantification of left ventricular mass in multiple views of echocardiograms using model-agnostic meta learning in a few-shot setting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Reliable measurement of left ventricular mass (LVM) in echocardiography is essential for early detection of left ventricular dysfunction, coronary artery disease, and arrhythmia risk, yet growing patient volumes have created critical shortage of experts in echocardiography. Recent deep learning approaches reduce inter-operator variability but require large, fully labeled datasets for each standard view-an impractical demand in many clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring AI tool adoption in higher education: evidence from a PLS-SEM model integrating multimodal literacy, self-efficacy, and university support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Framed within the technology acceptance model, this study examines how multimodal literacy, self-efficacy, and university support affect students' attitudes toward artificial intelligence tools and the students' intentions to adopt them.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cancer-related Dysfunctional Beliefs and Attitude about Sleep-6 (C-DBAS-6): a practical and accurate shortened version using XGBoost and SymScore]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We aimed to develop a practical, data-driven, shortened version of the Cancer-related Dysfunctional Beliefs and Attitudes about Sleep (C-DBAS) scale that maintains diagnostic accuracy while minimizing assessment time and efforts for both patients and clinicians. A sample dataset of 564 cancer patients was collected. Responses to 18 items were organized into six groups based on response similarity using exploratory factor analysis and K-means clustering. The most representative item from each...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of aquarobics on back pain, sleep, and memory in older women with chronic pain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Aquarobic exercise significantly improved functional mobility, sleep quality, and memory in older women with CLBP. These findings support aquarobics as an effective, holistic, and non-pharmacological intervention that enhances both physical and cognitive health in the elderly population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Adhesion and Reducing Charge Extraction Barrier Achieves 19.32% Efficiency in Inverted Organic Solar Cells with a Laminated Active Layer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Laminated film transfer has emerged as a promising technique for fabricating multilayer stacked structures in organic solar cells. However, challenges such as film transfer failure, loss of film integrity, and restricted charge transfer have limited its broader application. Herein, the focus is on optimizing the interfacial work of adhesion and energy levels to overcome these limitations, aiming to develop highly efficient inverted organic solar cells with laminated active layers. By selecting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isomer-driven supramolecular polymorphism of 4-hydroxytamoxifen modulating nanostructure-dependent cellular uptake and cytotoxicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Geometric isomerism in small-molecule drugs has traditionally been studied in the context of receptor binding or metabolic stability. However, its influence on supramolecular behavior and downstream biological function remains underexplored. Here, we investigate how the (Z)- and (E)-isomers of 4-hydroxytamoxifen (4-OHT) self-assemble in aqueous environments and how this supramolecular divergence impacts anticancer activity. The (Z)-isomer forms small, amorphous nanoflake assemblies that display...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stem cell mining: urine cells to biobanking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facilitated α-synuclein oligomer sharing among glial cells by a centrally acting connexin inhibitor attenuates a rapidly progressive multiple system atrophy-cerebellar type model by reducing the neuronal α-synuclein burden]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glial connexins (Cxs) that make up astrocyte/oligodendrocyte gap junctions are extensively altered in multiple system atrophy-cerebellar type (MSA-C). Here, we investigated how Cx alterations affect the propagation of α-synuclein (α-syn) oligomers and phosphorylated (p)-α-syn aggregates in MSA-C using a centrally acting pan-Cx blocker, INI-0602. Our Plp1-tTA::tetO-SNCA*A53T transgenic (Tg) mice express mutant human A53T α-syn in oligodendrocytes after dietary doxycycline withdrawal at 8 weeks of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long non-coding RNA PWRN4 associated with post-SVR hepatocellular carcinoma: a genome-wide association study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A subset of patients still develops hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) even after eradication of the hepatitis-C virus (HCV) by anti-HCV treatment. We conducted a genome-wide association study (GWAS) to identify host genetic factors associated with HCC development following HCV eradication in Japan. In this GWAS (n = 517), the discovery cohort included 118 patients without HCC and 67 who developed HCC following HCV eradication with interferon-based therapy. A genome-wide scan for HCC-associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patterns of health literacy among vulnerable unemployed citizens: a cross-sectional study in a Danish municipality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Based on the findings interventions may be developed to improve 1) the HL in vulnerable unemployed citizens and 2) the system's ability to accommodate citizens with poor HL. Such interventions could improve the health of the citizens and thus their labor market prospects. Depending on the target group, these should have a broad HL focus or a more specific focus on navigating the healthcare system.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal sociodemographic characteristics of short and long interpregnancy intervals in Japan: an analysis using national birth data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study showed that maternal sociodemographic characteristics such as employment status, educational attainment, and household income were associated with short and long interpregnancy intervals in Japan.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of antibiotic use, biosecurity and mortality in semi-intensive broiler farms in Kenya]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The indiscriminate use of antibiotics in food-producing animals contributes to antimicrobial resistance (AMR), posing a global threat. Understanding the factors associated with antibiotic use is critical to combat resistance while maintaining animal health. This study examined antibiotic use practices, mortality rates, biosecurity levels, as well as the associations between biosecurity and antibiotic use, and between biosecurity and mortality, in semi-intensive broiler farms in Kenya.The study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Videoconference-delivered cognitive behavioral therapy in patients with symptomatic panic disorder following primary pharmacotherapy: a randomized, assessor-blinded, controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Thus, videoconference-based cognitive behavioral therapy is an effective treatment for patients with panic disorder who remain symptomatic following pharmacotherapy. The results suggest that videoconference-based cognitive behavioral therapy, which can be used at home, may be effective for patients with panic disorder or chronic panic disorder who have difficulty accessing cognitive behavioral therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Belgium program Enhancing the uptake and Effectiveness of a Multifactorial falls Prevention intervention in Older community-dWElling peRsons (BE-EMPOWERed): A study protocol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative efficacy and safety of denosumab biosimilar and originator in postmenopausal osteoporosis: a meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The denosumab biosimilars demonstrated efficacy and safety profiles comparable to the originator in the treatment of postmenopausal osteoporosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry-compatible silicon spin-qubit unit cells exceeding 99% fidelity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Among the many types of qubit presently being investigated for a future quantum computer, silicon spin qubits with millions of qubits on a single chip are uniquely positioned to enable quantum computing. However, it has not been clear whether the outstanding high-fidelity operations and long coherence times shown by silicon spin qubits fabricated in academic settings^(1-8) can be reliably reproduced when the qubits are manufactured in a semiconductor foundry^(9-11). Here we show precise qubit...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meso-macroporous hydrogel for direct litre-scale isolation of extracellular vesicles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles are cell-originated lipid bilayer membrane vesicles that play vital roles in cell-to-cell communications. While extracellular vesicles hold substantial biomedical potential, conventional methodologies for isolating extracellular vesicles require elaborate preprocessing and, therefore, remain labour intensive and limited by throughput. To overcome these challenges, we present a facile fabrication route for generating a meso-macroporous hydrogel matrix with pores of ~400 nm...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Preliminary Study Introducing Electronic Patient-Reported Outcome (ePRO) Using Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) in Post-marketing Surveillance in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our two-week pilot indicates that ePRO can achieve data completeness comparable to paper in motivated clinics. The points to consider when using ePRO in actual PMS were confirmed. Further assessment in actual studies conducted in compliance with local regulations is needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preclinical Prediction of Resistance Mutations and Proposal of Sequential Treatment Strategies for ALK-positive Lung Cancer Using Next-generation ALK Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This PCR-based platform provides a valuable approach for anticipating resistance mutations and guiding the design of optimized sequential therapies. Zotizalkib, gilteritinib, and neladalkib might represent promising alternatives to lorlatinib as second-line treatments for ALK-positive NSCLC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Biodiversity Cell Atlas: mapping the tree of life at cellular resolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell types are fundamental functional units that can be traced across the tree of life. Rapid advances in single-cell technologies, coupled with the phylogenetic expansion in genome sequencing, present opportunities for the molecular characterization of cells across a broad range of organisms. Despite these developments, our understanding of eukaryotic cell diversity remains limited and we are far from decoding this diversity from genome sequences. Here we introduce the Biodiversity Cell Atlas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Active vision-based real-time aquaculture net pens inspection using ROV]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aquaculture is vital in ensuring a sustainable protein supply for economic purposes. Timely identification of damage to net pens poses a notable challenge in the aquaculture environment. Detecting damaged net pens in underwater environments using remotely operated vehicles (ROVs) offers a safe and efficient solution, eliminating the need for human divers to face potential dangers. Underwater inspections with optical cameras face challenges due to reduced visibility caused by floating particles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A consensus guide to preclinical indirect calorimetry experiments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the complex factors influencing mammalian metabolism and body weight homeostasis is a long-standing challenge requiring knowledge of energy intake, absorption and expenditure. Using measurements of respiratory gas exchange, indirect calorimetry can provide non-invasive estimates of whole-body energy expenditure. However, inconsistent measurement units and flawed data normalization methods have slowed progress in this field. This guide aims to establish consensus standards to unify...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical outcomes of ventrally located cervical spinal meningiomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite the higher risk of nerve root sacrifice and limited neurological recovery associated with the posterior approach, considering the functional improvements from baseline, it remains a viable surgical option for ventrally located cervical meningiomas. Further studies comparing different surgical approaches are needed to optimize treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-compassion mediates the influence of mindfulness on subsequent self-forgiveness in a Polish sample]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mindfulness is widely recognized for its effectiveness in addressing life challenges, with self-compassion increasingly explored as a potential mechanism underlying its benefits. This study examines whether self-compassion mediates the relationship between mindfulness and self-forgiveness. A three-wave longitudinal study of 164 Polish participants (aged 18-65) assessed mindfulness, self-compassion, and self-forgiveness using validated measures. Structural equation modeling tested the mediation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diesel particulate matter-induced proteomic changes in three-dimensional spheroids derived from human primary cells of various tissue origins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the effects of diesel particulate matter (DPM) on multiple human organs using 3D spheroids derived from eight human primary cell types. To assess the impact of DPM, we exposed these spheroids to varying concentrations of standardized DPM (Standard Reference Material, SRM 2975) and measured their viability, followed by proteomic analysis using tandem mass tag (TMT) labeling with liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry (LC-MS/MS). A total of 9,707 proteins were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kinetic selectivity in metal-organic framework chemical sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Selective detection of specific volatile organic compounds (VOCs) is crucial for health, safety, and environmental applications, but current sensors suffer from poor selectivity and struggle to measure specific VOCs in the presence of interfering compounds and water vapor. To address this issue, we introduce the kinetic selectivity achievable in nanoporous crystals, specifically metal-organic frameworks (MOFs), into the domain of chemical sensors. In well-selected MOFs, similar molecules can...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Change of Neurotransmitter Amine with CO<sub>2</sub> in Water: Formation of Covalently Bound Carbamic Acid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structural transformation changes the activity of biological reactions. Neurotransmitter aralkylamines, such as phenethylamine, tyramine, dopamine, tryptamine, serotonin, and histamine, absorb aerial CO(2), and heteronuclear multiple bond connectivity (HMBC) correlations between the carbon derived from CO(2) and the α-hydrogen of the several amines were confirmed in the D(2)O solution. The isolation of methyl carbamate from phenethylamine and CO(2) in water with TMSCHN(2) also supported the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Melittin-Derived Peptide with Improved Cytosolic Delivery Efficiency through Caveolae- and Actin-Mediated Endocytosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient cytosolic delivery of functional proteins such as therapeutic antibodies remains a major challenge in drug development. In this study, we sought to optimize the cytosolic delivery peptide Mel-V8G12, a melittin derivative, through structure-guided design and functional screening of its amino acid substitutions. Among seven derivatives, VG-6, featuring A10L, T11E, and S18K substitutions demonstrated superior cytosolic delivery efficiency compared with the parental Mel-V8G12, while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Fluorogenic Reagent that Enables Simultaneous Detection and Labeling of Hydropersulfide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Real-time detection and identification of modified cysteine sulfhydryl (Cys-SH) residues are important because supersulfidation (S-sulfhydrylation) alters protein function and thereby modulates the activity of biological systems. Although fluorescence probes for rapid, sensitive detection and biotin tag-switch methods for comprehensive labeling of modified residues at the proteome level have been developed, simultaneous detection and labeling have not been achieved in a single system. Herein, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of the Ac/N-degron recognition domain in the MARCHF6 E3 ubiquitin ligase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nα-terminal (Nt-) acetylation is a prevalent post-translational modification that regulates protein stability and turnover. The Ac/N-degron pathway, a branch of the N-degron pathways, recognizes Nt-acetyl groups as degradation signals (Ac/N-degrons), mediating proteolysis. MARCHF6, an endoplasmic reticulum (ER)-transmembrane E3 ubiquitin ligase, acts as a principal Ac/N-recognin, targeting Ac/N-degron-bearing substrates for polyubiquitylation and subsequent proteasomal degradation. However, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum calprotectin and complement factor C3 are superior biomarkers of inflammation in early psoriatic arthritis as compared with C-reactive protein]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: C3 and calprotectin are elevated in early PsA and are responsive to treatment. These markers outperform CRP in obese and CRP-negative patients and may support improved diagnosis and disease monitoring in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation evaluation of a pharmacist-led complex intervention: a mixed-methods analysis embedded within the ASPIRE randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The ASPIRE intervention was successfully implemented and considered feasible and acceptable by the stakeholders, highlighting its potential to improve care for geriatric patients. The high level of implementation provide a strong basis for the further evaluation of its effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conservative treatment has a role in elderly patients with Chronic Limb-Threatening Ischemia, especially in very elderly patients (≥ 85 years)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study showed that conservative treatment should be considered as an appropriate treatment option in frail high-risk elderly patients, particularly those with a predicted survival of less than two years. The findings emphasize the significance of integrating patient specific factors into the process of treatment and shared decision making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Whole genome sequencing reveals the role of the ribosome protein complex in salt stress in Bacillus subtilis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soil salinity is one of the most critical environmental factors that restricts bacterial growth and plant productivity throughout the world. Bacteria have evolved sophisticated regulatory mechanisms to adapt to diverse ecological conditions and overcome various stresses. Soil salinity prevents bacterial growth, but the genetics underlying tolerance are unknown. To identify these mechanisms, we attempted to screen and isolate salinity-resistant bacteria and performed whole-genome sequencing to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BOS172738, a selective RET inhibitor, for the treatment of patients with RET-altered tumors including RET-fusion-positive non-small-cell lung cancer and RET-mutant medullary thyroid cancer: a phase I dose-escalation/expansion multicenter study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: BOS172738 showed preliminary efficacy and a manageable safety profile in RET-altered tumors, including those resistant to prior therapies and in patients with brain metastases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generation of a human iPSC line (NUMNi002-A) from a patient with nephrotic syndrome harboring an INF2 gene variant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A variant of INF2 has been identified as a risk factor for nephrotic syndrome (focal segmental glomerulosclerosis; FSGS). The mechanism by which this variant contributes to FSGS onset remains unclear. Furthermore, treatment for FSGS remains to be established.We generated induced pluripotent stem cells (iPSCs) from a patient with FSGS caused by the INF2 variant. These iPSCs express stemness markers and can differentiate into the three germ layers in vitro. These iPSCs will be useful tools for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental determination and observations of molecular diffusion coefficients of oligonucleotides via the Taylor-Aris method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oligonucleotides (ONs) are a rapidly emerging class of therapeutics, with the potential to treat a wide range of diseases by targeting RNA and DNA sequences with high specificity. Their complex structures and manufacturing processes generate closely related impurities that must be meticulously monitored, necessitating techniques such as High-Performance Liquid Chromatography (HPLC). However, the analysis of ONs remains highly challenging, and a deeper understanding of ON separations and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-detector based at-line nanofractionation strategy accelerates discovery of influenza PA endonuclease inhibitors from Terminalia chebula Retz]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The highly conserved N-terminal domain of polymerase acidic endonuclease (PA(N)) makes it an attractive target for the development of anti-influenza virus drugs. This study developed an innovative multi-detector based at-line nanofractionation platform by coupling an HPLC system containing triple-detector (diode array detector (DAD), charged aerosol detector (CAD) and MS) with fluorescence resonance energy transfer (FRET)-based bioassays to systematically identify potential PA(N) inhibitors from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep-sea-inspired bottom-up nanoemulsification of alkyl esters in water]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monodisperse nanodroplet generation in quenched hydrothermal solution (MAGIQ) represents a bottom-up strategy for nanoemulsion preparation. In this process, a homogeneous alkane solution in supercritical water is rapidly quenched by mixing with cold, surfactant-containing water, triggering phase separation and spontaneous self-assembly of oil molecules into nanodroplets. Inspired by the dynamic thermal environments of deep-sea hydrothermal vents, this method ensures only transient exposure of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI in critical care: A roadmap to the future]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has the potential to revolutionize critical care medicine by enhancing patient care, improving resource allocation and reducing clinician workload. Despite this promise, many AI applications remain confined to scientific research rather than being integrated into everyday clinical practice. This manuscript aims to help intensivists prepare themselves and their intensive care units (ICUs) for AI implementation. It provides a comprehensive yet practical roadmap,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Geographic variation in bronchoscopy use across Japan: A nationwide analysis using administrative claims data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bronchoscopy is a widely used diagnostic procedure in respiratory medicine. Despite recent advances in techniques and an ongoing aging population, detailed information regarding current bronchoscopy procedural patterns and practice settings remains limited for Japan. We analyzed bronchoscopic procedure volumes and settings across 47 Japanese prefectures over the 2023 fiscal year, using NDB Open Data. A total of 177,317 procedures were performed, with a nationwide rate of 142.6 per 100,000...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of inhalation device prescribing trends: A retrospective database study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The shift toward combination therapies and newer inhaler devices in Japan highlights the critical need for personalized treatment strategies that balance patient characteristics with economic factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cluster analysis of seasonal KL-6 variations in interstitial lung diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: KL-6 fluctuations were categorized into four seasonal patterns, which may provide insights for diagnosing ILD etiology and predicting the prognosis of patients with ILD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Humic acid enhances adsorption of antibiotic ciprofloxacin on polylactic acid microplastics, leading to reproductive and mitochondrial toxicity in Daphnia magna: Quantitative analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biodegradable microplastics (BMPs), which undergo incomplete degradation in freshwater environments, have emerged as potential vectors of micropollutants. However, their adsorption behavior and combined toxicity with coexisting micropollutants in the presence of natural organic matter (NOM) remain poorly understood. This study investigated the interaction of polylactic acid (PLA) microplastics (MPs)-humic acid (HA), adsorption of ciprofloxacin (CIP), and the combined toxicity to Daphnia magna...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40992053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How sighing regulates pulmonary surfactant structure and its role in breathing mechanics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pulmonary surfactants reduce the work of breathing, enhance compliance, and prevent alveolar collapse. Yet, their role extends beyond that of a simple surfactant; otherwise, exogenous surfactant therapy would fully restore compliance in acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS) by increasing surface concentration alone. Here, we show that interfacial microstructure and mechanics, regulated by spontaneous or ventilator-induced sighs, play a critical role. Using interfacial rheometry and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Changing Paradigm in Infectious Diseases - Host-Directed Medicine: Implications for the Next Generation of ID Physicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Adjunctive Istradefylline on Dyskinesia Onset in Patients with Parkinson's Disease Exhibiting Wearing-Off: An Open-Label Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adjunctive IST showed no difference in the onset of dyskinesia compared with adding another or increasing the dose of other anti-PD drugs, and displayed equivalent efficacy and tolerability, while maintaining a lower LEDD in this long-term study of patients with PD exhibiting WO. These findings support the use of adjunctive IST as a viable treatment option for patients with PD exhibiting WO.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Lactobacillus Strains Alleviate E. coli-induced Inflammation in a Urinary Tract Infection Rat Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Urinary tract infections (UTIs) are common bacterial infections that are predominantly caused by uropathogenic Escherichia coli. Chronic recurrence of UTIs, particularly in women, seriously affects the quality of life of infected individuals. Antibiotics are still the first-line treatment for UTIs; however, side effects and increasing antibiotic resistance emphasize the need for alternative therapies. In this study, we explored the in vitro and in vivo anti-E. coli effects of heat-inactivated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40991100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The diagnostic value of the syncope-to-ILR interval on syncope etiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The number of syncope-to-ILR days significantly affected syncope diagnosis, indicating that early hospital attendance following syncope is critical. Public awareness campaigns and the presence of family or friends may be useful.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Histological analysis of the semitendinosus muscle in young children with cerebral palsy compared to age matched typically developing children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cerebral palsy (CP) is a neurological disorder caused by a non-progressive lesion in the developing fetal or infant brain associated with structural muscle alterations. Despite its relevant function in walking, the semitendinosus (ST) structure has been poorly investigated in CP, especially in (very) young children, although this could help determine early events and whether these alterations differ between age groups. This study aimed at defining the histological characteristics of the ST...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Positron binding in large water clusters: insights into cage-structured systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a computational quantum chemical study of positron binding to cage-structured large water clusters (H(2)O)(n) with selected sizes in the range from n = 8 to 36. Positron binding energies for various conformations of each cluster size were calculated using the density functional theory-based electron-positron correlation-polarization potential method. We obtained that the positron binding energies of the lowest energy structures of water clusters overall tend to increase with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating high mobility group box protein 1 (HMGB1) single nucleotide polymorphisms among hepatitis B virus infected patients of Pakistan origin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[HMGB1 is nuclear non-histone protein and unique member of cytokines. In viral hepatitis infection HMGB1 serum level increases and translocates towards cytoplasm and extracellular spaces where it activates single stimulating hepatic stellate cell proliferation which induces fibrogenic protein expression and causes hepatocellular carcinoma. In this study, total 150 subjects were recruited to assess the association between HMGB1 SNPs and HBV. Three types of genotypes were found visible in rs3742305...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lymphopenia as a diagnostic biomarker in clinical COVID-19: insights from a comprehensive study on SARS-CoV-2 variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The enduring SARS-CoV-2 pandemic necessitates robust tools for severity assessment. This study, conducted at Islamabad Diagnostic Center across Pakistan from January 2021 to August 2022, aimed to investigate hematological abnormalities among suspected SARS-CoV-2 subjects. Initial enrollment included 130,347 cases, with 53,078 confirmed positive and 77,269 negative. An additional 11,786 samples expanded the dataset to 142,133. The Omicron and Centaurus variants, in confirmed positive patients,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating the risk of living donor liver transplantation from older donors: analysis of 4,035 cases from a multicenter cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LDLT using grafts from old donors (≥ 50 years) showed poorer graft survival, especially when two or more of the following were present: CIT ≥ 150 min, MELD ≥ 20, or recipient BMI ≥ 25 kg/m2. These risk factors should be carefully considered when selecting old living donors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of three-dimensional fast spin echo t2-weighted magnetic resonance imaging (cube) for evaluating the longitudinal spread of perihilar cholangiocarcinoma after endoscopic biliary stenting: a diagnostic study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cube may be the preferred choice to guide surgical planning for PHC in patients without high-quality MDCT images before stent placement,. Collectively, these findings suggest that Cube could bring about a paradigm shift in imaging-based diagnosis of PHC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automatic Molecule Fragmentation for Density Matrix Embedding Theory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In quantum chemical calculations, the computational cost of highly accurate ground-state energy calculations for large-scale molecules is exceedingly high. To reduce the computational cost while sustaining high accuracy, quantum embedding methods, such as the density matrix embedding theory (DMET) and bootstrap embedding (BE), have been developed. In DMET, we need to manually determine how to fragment a target molecule, and both the accuracy and computational cost strongly depend on it. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40990438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic value of superb microvascular imaging in cardiac metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the efficacy of chlorous acid water and sodium hypochlorite solution against SARS-CoV-2 in the presence of organic matter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chlorous acid water and sodium hypochlorite solution are effective disinfectants against severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus-2 (SARS-CoV-2), the virus that caused the pandemic. Recent studies have shown that both compounds have equivalent inactivation effects when tested on purified viruses. However, in practical applications, the presence of organic matter is common and can significantly affect disinfectant performance. We conducted several experiments comparing these two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ankle sprain history and clinical outcome have limited influence on walking and running biomechanics among runners: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results highlight the importance of considering self-reported function and perceived instability when assessing LAS and CAI. The absence of gross running gait alterations suggests that rehabilitation could safely integrate running early in recovery. However, more demanding tasks or advanced biomechanical modeling techniques may be needed to identify residual gait impairments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detailed examination of a double-dividend case in a recent two-engine growth model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An important recent achievement in environmental macroeconomics is that reported by Cheng et al. [J. Macroecon. 81, 103614 (2024)]. Their model implements multiple growth engines and realizes the double dividend of economic growth and environmental improvements. However, regarding the environmental aspect, the situation could change drastically in general cases, and so a detailed understanding of the mechanisms in such cases is important for future similar studies. This paper presents additional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Occupational exposure and its mechanistic link to allergic asthma and lung function decline; a data-driven approach coupled to mining of adverse outcome pathway signatures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Within occupational epidemiology, the establishment of associations between chemical exposures and health outcome, in particular of individual chemicals present in the exposome, is difficult. Epidemiological studies are valuable but may be prone to confounders, or lack detailed exposure characterisation. Rodent studies may suffer from interspecies differences in comparison to humans. Here, we explore if a data driven approach can leverage human relevant mechanistic information to inform presumed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A T1-isointense meningeal melanocytoma mimicking meningioma: Case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Meningeal melanocytomas are rare, benign, melanocytic neoplasms of the pia mater, typically characterized by a high T1-weighted signal intensity on MRI. We report the case of a 47-year-old female with a T1-isointense tentorial lesion initially diagnosed as a meningioma, but histologically confirmed as a melanin-containing meningeal melanocytoma. Despite extensive intraoperative and pathological evidence of pigmentation, the tumor did not display the expected T1 hyperintensity, emphasizing that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40989053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic graph neural networks for UAV-based group activity recognition in structured team sports]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Understanding group actions in real-world settings is essential for the advancement of applications in surveillance, robotics, and autonomous systems. Group activity recognition, particularly in sports scenarios, presents unique challenges due to dynamic interactions, occlusions, and varying viewpoints. To address these challenges, we develop a deep learning system that recognizes multi-person behaviors by integrating appearance-based features (HOG, LBP, SIFT), skeletal data...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How is loneliness orientation implicated in the relationship between sleep problems, loneliness intensity, and school refusal in adolescents?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prolonged loneliness adversely affects mental and physical health. Even if feelings of loneliness are high, the association between loneliness intensity, mental health, and school refusal may differ depending on how loneliness is framed (i.e., loneliness orientation). In this study, we aimed to develop a Loneliness Orientation Test to examine the relationship between loneliness intensity and loneliness orientation; examine the differential impact of sleep problems on loneliness...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between insufficient sleep and constipation among elementary school children in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A cross-sectional study was conducted between October 2019 and January 2020 in seven Japanese municipal elementary schools in Higashiyamato City, Tokyo. A questionnaire was distributed to 922 children enrolled in the 1st and 2nd grades. After excluding incomplete questionnaires, 629 (52.3% male) children were included in the analysis. Both sleep disorders and constipation are highly prevalent among elementary school children and could be associated with each other since sometimes they coexist in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High job stress evaluated using the Brief Job Stress Questionnaire as an independent factor for nonrestorative sleep among Japanese workers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonrestorative sleep (NRS) is clearly more associated with objective indices than primary insomnia symptoms. Stress is a comorbid factor for NRS. In 2015, the Stress Check Program was launched in Japan as a new occupational health policy. This study aimed to clarify whether the presence or absence of high job stress (HJS), as determined by Brief Job Stress Questionnaire (BJSQ), is related to the comorbidity of NRS. The subjects were 23,813 Japanese office workers who were 20 to 59 years old. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A New Genus and Species of the Springendemic Ostracoda (Cypricercinae, Cyprididae) and its Genetic Population Structure among Rheocrenic Springs in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We describe the ostracod Lissostrandesia fonticola gen. et sp. nov. in the subfamily Cypricercinae McKenzie, 1971, collected from six rheocrenic springs in Japan. The populations sampled were separated by up to 1000 km, and some of them by one or two marine straits, which comprise significant barriers for freshwater animals. Lissostrandesia differs from the other 13 cypricercine genera in (1) lacking a groove and inner list on the anterior inner margin of the left valve; (2) having b and d setae...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocadherin alpha gene cluster variants are potentially associated with short root anomaly in Japanese]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988636/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that the PCDHA gene cluster may be one of the genetic factors involved in the onset of SRA and that variants in this gene cluster could potentially affect tooth root development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988636/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex Differences in Prognosis of Patients With Genetic Dilated Cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The genetic architecture and sex are critical predictors of left ventricular reverse remodeling and long-term prognosis in DCM. These factors should be integrated into individualized risk prediction models to enhance clinical outcomes in patients with DCM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiple metal exposure and renal tubular damage of residents in a metal-polluted region in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the correlations among urinary metals, the effects of co-exposure to multiple metals, and the relative importance of each metal in renal tubular damage (RTD) among residents of a metal-contaminated area. Urine sampling and health surveys were conducted for 120 participants living near a smelter for the Forensic Research via Omics Markers (FROM) study. Nine urinary metals (V, Cr, Mn, Ni, Mo, Cd, Sb, Pb, and Hg) and RTD markers such as beta-2-microglobulin (β2-MG) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Simple and Affordable CZE-UV Method for Quality Control of Insulin in Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient and Formulations Using Quadruple Polymer-Coated Capillary]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Substandard and falsified medicines pose a significant public health threat, particularly in low-income countries. Ensuring pharmaceutical quality is crucial to mitigate risks associated with ineffective and harmful medications. Among others, developing and implementing robust and cost-effective analytical methods is an important and quick strategy for ensuring the quality of medicines. This study aimed to develop a robust and cost-effective capillary zone electrophoresis method with UV...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40988470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced synaptic vesicle protein 2A in extracellular vesicles and brains of Alzheimer's disease: associations with Aβ, tau, synaptic proteins and APOE ε4]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SV2A levels in brain tissues and BDEVs are reduced in AD patients, particularly in those carrying the APOE ε4 allele, and are correlated with Aβ and tau pathologies. SV2A may serve as a valuable biomarker for monitoring synaptic dysfunction and progression in AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of a KRT9 gene variant and preimplantation genetic diagnosis in a Chinese family with KRT9-palmoplantar epidermal differentiation disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We identified the c.503T > C (p. Leu168Ser) missense mutation in exon 1 of the KRT9 gene as the cause of KRT9-palmoplantar epidermal differentiation disorder (KRT9-pEDD) in a Chinese family. Under the guidance of comprehensive genetic counseling, employing PGT-M, we successfully prevented the transmission of the KRT9-pEDD pathogenic variant, resulting in the birth of a healthy child.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of tetraspanins in organ fibrosis: mechanisms and therapeutic perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the presence of neuropathic pain and/or central sensitization in patients with radiographic axial spondyloarthritis followed at a tertiary hospital]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNF168 dephosphorylation ameliorates cognitive decline in Aβ-based mouse models of Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is the most prevalent neurodegenerative disorder among the elderly, with limited effective treatments available in clinical practice. Impaired glucose metabolism has long been observed in the brains of AD patients, yet the mechanisms linking metabolic signals to AD pathogenesis remain elusive. Our previous study demonstrated that growth signals regulate genomic stability through RNF168 phosphorylation. Here, we report that phosphorylation of RNF168 at Ser60 is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An improved ovitrap-based surveillance framework: facilitating cost-efficient monitoring and efficacy assessment of integrated vector management strategies for dengue outbreak control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In the present study, the IMT was developed and evaluated for field surveillance of Ae. albopictus mosquitoes. The core usage parameters of the IMT-based surveillance system, including the working radius and area deployment density, have been determined using systematic field investigations combined with mathematical modelling assessments. Furthermore, a novel strategy utilizing the IMT for evaluating the efficacy of integrated mosquito vector management in CATI during dengue...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of methods for identifying the optimal treatment duration in randomized trials for antibiotics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We conclude that the success of the next era in TB therapeutics duration evaluation trials, and antibiotics duration-ranging more broadly, will meaningfully rely on the ability to simultaneously pair innovative model-based statistical methods with re-imagined study designs such as MAMS-ROCI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of vitamin D supplements on bone metabolism in kidney transplant recipients: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Vitamin D supplementation does not improve overall BMD or prevent fracture in KTRs. Vitamin D supplementation may effectively reduce serum PTH and BAP level. However, it may also increase the risk of hypercalcemia, necessitating the monitoring of serum calcium level.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A mouse model of stereotactic radiosurgery-induced neuroinflammation and blood-brain barrier compromise]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stereotactic radiosurgery (SRS) is a procedure that delivers high-dose single fraction, targeted radiation to treat brain pathologies. Brain radiation necrosis is a significant side effect of SRS, resulting in severe clinical sequelae such as seizure, hemorrhage, stroke, and neurological deficit. While focused radiation causes DNA damage and cell death, radiation necrosis is mostly mediated by vascular injury. Yet the effects of SRS on the neurovascular unit (NVU) cells-microglia, astrocytes,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allogeneic bone marrow-derived mesenchymal stem cells in the aging kidney: secondary results of a Parkinson's disease clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In older adults with PD and preserved kidney function, repeated allo-hMSC infusions were associated with improved kidney function measures. While promising, these findings are preliminary and may be specific to PD. Further studies are needed to assess potential benefits in the broader aging population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasound-guided nerve block anesthesia improves perioperative pain in patients undergoing free flap reconstruction for head-and-neck tumor: a randomized, controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ultrasound-guided iliac fascia combined with trigeminus block anesthesia is an effective method for pain management in patients who underwent head-and-neck tumor surgery in conjunction with the simultaneous repair using the vascularized anterolateral femoral free flap.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social risk profiles and diabetic kidney disease: prevalence and mortality in US adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic kidney disease (DKD) is a severe and prevalent complication of diabetes. Social contexts have been increasingly recognized as critical factors in the escalation and ongoing management of chronic diseases, including DKD. This study aimed to evaluate the connection between social risk profile (SRP) and DKD in United States. METHODS: Data were sourced from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (1999-2018). DKD was defined as the coexistence of diabetes and chronic kidney...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tdap, MenACWY, HPV, seasonal influenza, and COVID-19 vaccination status among US teens aged 13-17 years in 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nearly 2 out of 5 adolescents aged 13 to 17 years in 2022 were not fully UTD for Tdap, MenACWY, and HPV vaccines by age 13. Being UTD by age 13 for these vaccines was significantly associated with subsequently receiving seasonal influenza and COVID-19 vaccines.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A dual-branch deep learning network for circulating tumor cells classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The proposed framework enhances CTC identification accuracy and efficiency, demonstrating strong clinical applicability. Its output results can be directly utilized for prognosis without manual intervention, offering significant potential for personalized therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Holobiont-holobiont interactions across host-ectoparasite systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Holobionts - hosts together with their resident microorganisms - provide a framework for studying life as a network of interdependent partners. Within host-ectoparasite holobionts, the dialogue between the two microbiomes offers powerful clues to ecological balance, disease dynamics and evolution. Because each holobiont is structurally and functionally compartmentalised, microbes exchanged at the interface can elicit highly local, niche-specific effects that ripple through the system. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting the glymphatic system: Aβ accumulation and phototherapy strategies across different stages of Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The glymphatic system serves as the brain's clearance system. It deteriorates with age and is a significant contributor to the onset and progression of Alzheimer's disease (AD). Modulating cerebrospinal fluid (CSF)-based clearance and targeting key components of the glymphatic system, such as aquaporin-4, can enhance amyloid-beta (Aβ) clearance. Light therapy is emerging as a potential AD treatment approach, which involves the use of visible and near-infrared light at specific wavelengths...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potential biomarkers of idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis: metabonomics driven lipid profiling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study clarified that metabolic reprogramming and lipid metabolism disorder are significant characteristics of IPF. PEA and 2-Amino-1,3,4-octadecanetriol May be potential biomarkers for patients with IPF and have diagnostic and prognostic evaluation value for IPF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SH3BP5-driven metabolic-immune crosstalk in DLBCL: a prognostic biomarker and therapeutic target for reshaping immunosuppressive microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that SH3BP5 may serve as a prognostic biomarker and a potential therapeutic target in DLBCL, particularly within the ABC subtype. By delineating its associations with immune evasion and metabolic reprogramming, these findings provide a mechanistic basis for further exploration of SH3BP5-targeted interventions to help overcome therapy resistance. Future studies in larger clinical cohorts and functional models are warranted to validate these results and assess the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The clinical outcomes of joint-preserving endoprosthesis reconstruction for primary sarcomas about the knee]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The joint-preserving endoprosthesis reconstruction (JPER) is a reliable technique to reconstruct massive bone defects after primary sarcoma resection about the knee with acceptable oncological outcomes, function, and satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening for Leishmania spp. infection in patients treated with biologic agents for immune-mediated inflammatory diseases: results of an Italian multicentric prospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study showed a high prevalence of asymptomatic Leishmania infection in Italian patients with IMID under treatment with biologic agents, with a north-to-south gradient. Given the risk of disease reactivation, these patients may benefit from close monitoring. Further research is warranted to clarify the clinical implications of these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revolutionizing Wilson disease prognosis: a machine learning approach to predict acute-on-chronic liver failure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ML-based model effectively predicts WD-ACLF risk, with XGBoost demonstrating superior performance. TBA, APTT, diagnosis age, onset age and Hb emerged as critical biomarkers, offering actionable insights for early clinical intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gestational trophoblastic neoplasia with pancreatic metastasis: clinical characteristics, treatment strategies, and outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Pancreatic invasion in GTN is a high-risk condition often associated with poor outcomes. Advanced imaging techniques enhance diagnostic accuracy, while endoscopic ultrasound-guided fine-needle biopsy provides essential histopathological confirmation. Multi-agent chemotherapy remains the cornerstone of treatment, with surgical interventions carefully tailored to the individual patient's condition. For better management and prognosis, an initial treatment strategy integrating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PlyNJ3: a three-domain endolysin with broad-spectrum anti-streptococcal activity and synergistic efficacy against multidrug-resistant Streptococcus suis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings establish SMphage-derived lysins as a conserved, therapeutically valuable class of antimicrobials with inherent broad-spectrum potential across diverse streptococcal pathogens. Building on the previously demonstrated in vivo efficacy of PlySK1249 against S. dysgalactiae and S. agalactiae, we show that its structural homolog, PlyNJ3, exhibits robust therapeutic activity against S. suis infections. Together, these results validate the SMphage lysin platform for generating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of short-term exposure to ambient air pollution on cardiovascular disease outpatient visits: a time-series study in Yichang, China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Short-term exposure to NO₂, SO₂, and CO demonstrated statistically significant positive associations with cardiovascular disease outpatient visits. Environmental policies reduced ambient air pollutant levels and attenuated health impacts, supporting continued air quality interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive models for live birth outcomes following fresh embryo transfer in assisted reproductive technologies using machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study presents a significant advancement in predicting live birth outcomes prior to embryo transfer, moving beyond traditional assessments. The findings underscore the potential of machine learning to improve clinical decision-making and enhance patient counseling in ARTs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of color stability and material surface stability of different types of clear aligners under curcumin staining in vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aesthetics play a crucial role in patients' choice of orthodontic clear aligners, as poor color stability can compromise their appearance during wear. This study aimed to evaluate the color and surface stability of different types of orthodontic clear aligners exposed to various concentrations of curcumin solutions in vitro. Four types of clear aligners (Invisalign, Angelalign, Spark, and Dreve), along with non-thermoformed Dreve film, were cut into 5 mm × 5 mm squares and immersed in curcumin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insecticide resistance and the role of target-site insensitivity mutations among malaria vectors in China: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Of An. sinensis, 36% had kdr mutations, and 78% had ace-1 mutations. These vectors were resistant to pyrethroid, organochlorine, carbamate, and organophosphate insecticides. To prevent the development of resistance to alternative insecticides, it is critical to target Anopheles mosquitoes with novel chemical insecticides or biocontrol approaches.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FTO regulates testosterone secretion in Leydig cells: insights into the role of m<sup>6</sup>A modifications and the therapeutic potential of hCG]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study provides new evidence that FTO plays a critical role in regulating testosterone secretion in LCs. Additionally, we demonstrate that hCG treatment can restore testosterone production impaired by FTO inhibition. These findings offer valuable insights into the molecular mechanisms underlying testosterone secretion and may inform therapeutic strategies for male infertility and hypogonadism.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA['I won't make it without this program': the impact of safer opioid supply program closures in Ontario]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights participants' concerns that SOS program closures may force them back into an increasingly dangerous unregulated market, ultimately putting their lives at risk, along with reversing the many benefits SOS programs provided, such as connections to essential health and social services. By replacing harm reduction programs with treatment services, the government is not reducing the demand for opioid use; instead, it forces a return to the unregulated drug market,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quadrant asymmetry alteration of retinal degeneration in thyroid-associated ophthalmopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Alterations in quadrant asymmetry of RPC density occurred in TAO, particularly decreased RPC density in the nasal subfield, which was significantly associated with visual field abnormalities in TAO.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond additive effects: examining the combined impact of air pollutant interactions on pulmonary tuberculosis in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: To reduce biases in air pollution control policies and maximize their health benefits, it is essential to assess both the additive and interactive effects when evaluating the health impacts of air pollutant mixtures. Furthermore, the influence of greenness should be considered in the context of these air pollutant mixtures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiological shifts in 23 acute infectious diseases in Southwest China (2005-2024): trends and implications for surveillance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Acute infectious disease patterns in Sichuan have continuously shifted due to evolving prevention strategies and epidemiological trends. Priority diseases requiring enhanced surveillance include seasonal influenza, pertussis, infectious diarrhea, hepatitis E, brucellosis, typhus, and dengue fever. Reducing the disease burden effectively requires targeted strategies that integrate seasonal and regional patterns and intensify surveillance during high-risk periods.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex and age-specific multimorbidity profiles among working-age inpatients in China: a comparative network analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Multimorbidity networks in working-age inpatients exhibited greater complexity in males than females, growing with age. Hub diseases' associated multimorbidity patterns dominated the network and multimorbidity patterns shifted toward endocrine/nutritional/metabolic and circulatory disease-associated patterns with age. Our study could contribute to the development of clinical interventions targeting working-age inpatient multimorbidity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Occupational stress and associated factors among couriers: A Cross-Sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Couriers are susceptible to elevated levels of occupational stress. Urgent action is required to address the problem of occupational stress among couriers. It is advised that the government, businesses, and trade unions work together to create a comprehensive "prevention-intervention-guarantee" system for occupational health protection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical characteristics and outcomes of COVID-19-Associated acute encephalopathy in pediatric patients during the Omicron wave in beijing: a single-center prospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Omicron-associated AE in young children is characterized by rapidly progressive neurological deterioration, with 60% mortality in this cohort and persistent deficits in survivors. Symmetric MRI lesions, elevated procalcitonin, and CSF cytokine elevation may serve as early diagnostic indicators. Vaccination gaps and innate immune dysregulation likely contribute to severe outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health literacy and self-management of people living with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease or type 2 diabetes in Greenland: a qualitative interpretive description study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: There was a great desire for more knowledge about COPD and T2D and for information in Greenlandic. The study showed considerable individual variation in knowledge about disease and health literacy, and involving the informants' network in management of the disease was found essential. The study's results can support the development of a culturally adapted patient education intervention. The intervention must be multifaceted, accessible to all citizens in Greenland, targeted to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Factors Influencing HIV pre-exposure prophylaxis adherence among men who have sex with men in Western China: a data-driven exploration using bayesian networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The efficacy of Pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) is highly dependent on adherence. This study aimed to explore the factors influencing adherence among men who have sex with men (MSM) and their interrelationships, providing theoretical basis for the development of personalized intervention strategies. The data for this study came from a two-phase study of the PrEP demonstration project conducted among MSM in Western China from 2013 to 2023. Participants were given once-daily oral PrEP medication,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating preferences for a trouble-free transition: a grounded theory study among older residents in nursing homes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study developed a theory on how contextual conditions and residents' cognitive and emotional challenges shape HPCN preferences. It highlights the diversity, variability, and individuality of these preferences, underscoring the need to enhance cultural sensitivity and care environments in Chinese NHs and comparable settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between adhering to 24-hour movement guidelines and anxiety among adolescents across intersectional identities: KYRBS 2020-2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Identifying preventive measures for adolescent mental health is a global public health priority, as poor mental health heightens the risk of early death from related issues, including suicide. This study examined the associations between adherence to the 24-Hour Movement Guidelines and anxiety among a nationally representative sample of South Korean adolescents, using an intersectional identity framework.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing strategies for integrating Hepatitis B Virus infection testing and treatment into routine PMTCT services in Ghana's Upper West Region: a rapid qualitative study applying the CFIR-ERIC matching tool]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Integrating HBV infection testing and treatment into routine PMTCT services is both viable and essential for improving maternal and child health outcomes in Ghana's Upper West Region. Despite significant challenges, the identified facilitators and proposed interventions provide a comprehensive roadmap for addressing implementation barriers. Achieving successful integration requires coordinated efforts among stakeholders, including policymakers, healthcare professionals, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An analytical pipeline for dose-response effect: laboratory tests assessment and early pregnancy preeclampsia risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The proposed pipeline was rigorously validated for its efficacy across two independent cohorts, achieving consistent outcomes. Furthermore, the laboratory tests identified mostly align with conclusions from prior studies. We believe it both advances our understanding of the mechanisms during early pregnancy disorder and offers vital insights for early preeclampsia detection and preventive interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening for individuals with postpartum depression by an attenuated and delayed niacin skin flushing response: a case control study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identified the characteristics of impaired niacin response in women with PPD, and established a potential screening standard for PPD, which is highly objective and operable. The niacin-blunted subgroup of PPD may imply a common biological basis, which provokes new thoughts in elucidating the pathological mechanisms of postpartum depression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of primary oral health-related factors predicting depression before and after the COVID-19 pandemic using KNHANES data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights persistent disparities in oral health among individuals with depression before and after the COVID-19 pandemic in South Korea. These findings suggest the need for public health strategies that incorporate oral health into broader mental health frameworks, especially in pandemic contexts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the feedback effects of incentive methods on HIV rapid self-testing among men who have sex with men in Chongqing, China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results show no significant differences in feedback rates across groups at follow-up time points. Significant differences in feedback rate trends among the three groups were observed, with the extra lottery incentive providing more sustained motivation for feedback. And privacy concerns are crucial for expanding HIVST among MSM via social apps.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Membrane sweeping in term pregnancy to promote spontaneous labor and prevent post-term pregnancy: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that membrane sweeping may be an effective and relatively safe method for labor induction. Given the low certainty of the evidence, high-quality randomized controlled trials are urgently needed to corroborate these exploratory findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and determinants of quality of life among Rohingya older adults residing in the refugee camp in Bangladesh]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993530/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993530/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic performance of the systemic immune-inflammation index (SII) and sarcopenia index (SI) in sarcopenia and their prognostic value for clinical outcomes in hospitalized older patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The combination of SII with CC and SI with CC demonstrated advantageous diagnostic accuracy in diagnosing sarcopenia compared to SII and SI used independently. SII may serve as a serum indicator for predicting all-cause mortality in hospitalized older patients, though this requires further external validation. Additional well-designed prospective studies with larger sample sizes are needed to confirm our findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Network analysis of sleep disorders, depression and anxiety symptoms among community older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The central symptoms and their intricate connections in the network play an importance role in gaining the underlying pathological mechanisms, as well as potential interventions for comorbidity in community older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic accuracy of T-SPOT.TB and TST in detecting active tuberculosis in patients with rheumatic immune diseases: a fully matched comparative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In RD patients with suspected ATB symptoms, both T-SPOT.TB and TST offer valuable diagnostic assistance. T-SPOT.TB demonstrates superior diagnostic accuracy, particularly in terms of sensitivity. Higher spot counts on T-SPOT.TB or larger induration diameters on TST should raise clinical suspicion for the presence of concurrent ATB.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[γδ T Cell Infiltration Predicts the Prognosis of Lumbar Disc Herniation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lumbar disc herniation (LDH) is a common degenerative spinal disorder traditionally attributed to mechanical compression. However, growing evidence suggests that the immune system plays a crucial role in its pathogenesis. The role of alterations in the T cell receptor (TCR) clonal repertoire in LDH and their correlation with neurological recovery was investigated in this study. Immunohistochemical analysis was performed to assess T cell infiltration in nucleus pulposus tissue from patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional assessments of short-term spatial memory in the Dog Aging Project identify strong associations with age that are not moderated by body mass]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Companion dogs have emerged as a valuable model in the study of cognitive aging, but assessments of cognitive function in large, diverse, and geographically distributed samples of dogs are challenging to obtain. We developed two novel functional assessments of short-term spatial memory that were administered by community science participants in a sample of 6,753 dogs through the Dog Aging Project. We compared data generated by community scientists to those gathered by research professionals,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Next-Generation Imaging Techniques for Surgical Guidance in Pediatric Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Complete surgical resection remains the mainstay of cure for many childhood solid tumors. However, certain cancers exhibit intensely invasive growth patterns, often encasing vital structures such as blood vessels and invading adjacent organs. Furthermore, the degree of metastatic or regional spread may not be clear to the surgical oncologist at the time of resection. Intraoperative real-time imaging has the potential to improve successful localization and resection, with conservation of adjacent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Financial Outlook thRough CAncer STorytelling (FOReCAST): Development of a Novel Video-Based Storytelling Intervention to Mitigate Financial Hardship Among Young Women with Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in haplotype phasing and genotype imputation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Haplotype phasing - to determine which genetic variants reside on the same chromosome - and genotype imputation - to infer unobserved genotypes - have become indispensable steps to improve genome coverage for genomic analyses such as genome-wide association studies. Several tools exist for haplotype phasing and genotype imputation, all of which have continuously evolved to accommodate the increasing sample sizes of genomic studies and rapidly improving sequencing technologies. To fully leverage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The biomedical engineer's pledge: overview and context]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although biomedical engineering (BME) is a profession with ethical responsibilities comparable to those in medicine, it has, until now, lacked a counterpart to the Hippocratic Oath. While professional societies have established codes of ethics for biomedical engineers, these documents lack the symbolic and ceremonial significance of an oath or pledge. By contrast, the recitation of the Hippocratic Oath, or its modern version, the "Physician's Pledge," serves as a powerful rite of passage for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social networking agency and prosociality are inextricably linked in economic games]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The awareness of individuals regarding their social network surroundings and their capacity to use social connections to their advantage are well-established human characteristics. Economic games, incorporated with network science, are frequently used to examine social behaviour. Traditionally, such game models and experiments artificially limit players' abilities to take varied actions towards distinct social neighbours, thereby constraining their social networking agency. Here we designed an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the semantic priming effect across many languages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Semantic priming has been studied for nearly 50 years across various experimental manipulations and theoretical frameworks. Although previous studies provide insight into the cognitive underpinnings of semantic representations, they have suffered from small sample sizes and a lack of linguistic and cultural diversity. In this Registered Report, we measured the size and the variability of the semantic priming effect across 19 languages (n = 25,163 participants analysed) by creating the largest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of radiotherapy in primary mediastinal diffuse large B-cell lymphoma: a systematic review and meta-analysis of 1,392 patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary mediastinal B-cell lymphoma (PMBCL) patients who achieve a complete response (CR) following first-line immunochemotherapy tend to have favorable outcomes, even without subsequent radiotherapy (RT). However, it remains unclear whether the survival of patients who do not achieve CR after first-line therapy and subsequently receive radiotherapy is comparable to that of CR patients who undergo observation alone. To address this gap, we conducted a systematic review and meta-analysis to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systematic discovery of CRISPR-boosted CAR T cell immunotherapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) T cell therapy has shown remarkable success in treating blood cancers, but CAR T cell dysfunction remains a common cause of treatment failure¹. Here we present CELLFIE, a CRISPR screening platform for enhancing CAR T cells across multiple clinical objectives. We performed genome-wide screens in human primary CAR T cells, with readouts capturing key aspects of T cell biology, including proliferation, target cell recognition, activation, apoptosis and fratricide,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tailoring polymer electrolyte solvation for 600 Wh kg<sup>-1</sup> lithium batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymer electrolytes paired with lithium-rich manganese-based layered oxide (LRMO) cathodes and anode-free cell design are considered one of the most promising high-energy-density and high-safety systems^(1-4). However, the unstable anode morphological changes and the irreversible anionic reactions at the electrolyte-cathode interfaces induce oxygen escape and catalytic decomposition of polymer electrolytes, resulting in severe interfacial degradation and poor cycling stability. Here we design...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design of facilitated dissociation enables timing of cytokine signalling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein design has focused on the design of ground states, ensuring that they are sufficiently low energy to be highly populated¹. Designing the kinetics and dynamics of a system requires, in addition, the design of excited states that are traversed in transitions from one low-lying state to another^(2,3). This is a challenging task because such states must be sufficiently strained to be poorly populated, but not so strained that they are not populated at all, and because protein design methods...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-overhead transversal fault tolerance for universal quantum computation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fast, reliable logical operations are essential for realizing useful quantum computers^(1-3). By redundantly encoding logical qubits into many physical qubits and using syndrome measurements to detect and correct errors, we can achieve low logical error rates. However, for many practical quantum error correction codes such as the surface code, owing to syndrome measurement errors, standard constructions require multiple extraction rounds-of the order of the code distance d-for fault-tolerant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proximal cooperative aerial manipulation with vertically stacked drones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enabling vertical-stack proximal cooperation between multirotor flying robots can facilitate the execution of complex aerial manipulation tasks. However, vertical-stack proximal flight is commonly regarded as a dangerous condition that should be avoided because of persistent and intense downwash interference generated between flying robots^(1,2). Here we propose a cooperative aerial manipulation system, called FlyingToolbox, that can work stably with sub-centimetre-level docking accuracy under...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diverging fish biodiversity trends in cold and warm rivers and streams]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Worldwide, freshwater systems contain more than 18,000 fish species^(1-3), which are critical to the functioning of these ecosystems⁴ and are vital cultural and economic resources to humans^(5-7); despite this value, fish biodiversity is at risk globally^(8,9). In the USA, leading threats to fish communities in rivers and streams include climate change and invasive fish introductions and game fish stocking by humans^(10-14). Here we harmonized US federal biomonitoring datasets with 389 species...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The formation and propagation of human Robertsonian chromosomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Robertsonian chromosomes are a type of variant chromosome that is commonly found in nature. Present in 1 in 800 humans, these chromosomes can underlie infertility, trisomies and increased cancer incidence^(1-5). They have been recognized cytogenetically for more than a century⁶, yet their origins have remained unknown. Here we describe complete assemblies of three human Robertsonian chromosomes. We identified a common breakpoint in SST1, a macrosatellite DNA located on chromosomes 13, 14 and 21,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isothermal solidification for high-entropy alloy synthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kinetically trapping the high-temperature states through rapid cooling solidification is widely used for the synthesis of high-entropy alloys (HEAs), especially those with intrinsically immiscible elemental combinations^(1-4). However, strategies need to be developed to overcome the fundamental limitations of rapid cooling solidification in controlling the crystallinity, structure and morphology of HEAs. Here we introduce an isothermal solidification strategy for the synthesis of HEAs by rapidly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vivo CRISPR screens identify modifiers of CAR T cell function in myeloma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) T cells are highly effective in haematological malignancies¹. However, progressive loss of CAR T cells contributes to relapse in many patients^(2-4). Here we performed in vivo loss-of-function CRISPR screens in CAR T cells targeting B cell maturation antigen to investigate genes that influence CAR T cell persistence and function in a human multiple myeloma model. We tracked the expansion and persistence of CRISPR library-edited T cells in vitro and at early and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LRP8 is a receptor for tick-borne encephalitis virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tick-borne encephalitis virus (TBEV) causes tick-borne encephalitis (TBE), a severe and sometimes life-threatening disease characterized by viral invasion of the central nervous system with symptoms of neuroinflammation^(1,2). As with other orthoflaviviruses-enveloped, arthropod-borne RNA viruses-host factors required for TBEV entry remain poorly defined. Here we used a genome-scale CRISPR-Cas9-based screen to identify LRP8, an apolipoprotein E and reelin receptor with high expression in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Restoration of pancreatic beta cell identity and autophagy in K<sub>ATP</sub>-induced diabetes by intermittent fasting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS/INTERPRETATION: This study provides the first evidence of autophagy impairment in non-obese, insulin secretory-deficient, K(ATP)-induced diabetes mice and demonstrates that IF restores both autophagic flux and beta cell identity. This finding suggests that similar mechanisms may contribute to beta cell dysfunction in other forms of diabetes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac adaptation to endurance exercise training requires suppression of GDF15 via PGC-1α]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endurance exercise promotes adaptive growth and improved function of myocytes, which is supported by increased mitochondrial activity. In skeletal muscle, these benefits are in part transcriptionally coordinated by peroxisome proliferator-activated receptor gamma coactivator 1-alpha (PGC-1α). The importance of PGC-1α to exercise-induced adaptations in the heart has been unclear. Here we show that deleting PGC-1α specifically in cardiomyocytes prevents the expected benefits from exercise training...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925033649&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>