<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:42:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of switchable radiative cooling using real-time transmittance measurement system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiative cooling offers a passive and energy-efficient approach to thermal regulation, yet most conventional implementations lack dynamic tunability under varying environmental conditions. Recent advances in switchable radiative cooling materials have shown potential for practical applications, but their transient optical behaviors remain underexplored due to the limitations of conventional spectrophotometers. In this study, a real-time transmittance measurement system is developed that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skin-conformal PMN-PT ultrasonic sensor for cuffless blood pressure sensing via eutectic solder integration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wearable ultrasonic systems are emerging as promising tools for noninvasive cardiovascular monitoring, enabling the real-time assessment of vascular dynamics without the need for cuff-based measurements. However, the integration of high-performance piezoelectric materials into flexible, skin-conformal arrays poses challenges in terms of mechanical stretchability, acoustic fidelity, and scalability. In this study, we present a flexible 5 × 4 ultrasonic transducer array (UTA) based on 1-3 lead...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development for soft actuator with multilayer structure and its application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Most actuators require considerable degrees of freedom to perform tasks effectively, which often leads to larger size and reduced portability. As an alternative, soft actuators have been introduced, offering compact form, high maneuverability, and multiple modes of motion. In this study, a Hydraulically Amplified Self-Healing Electrostatics (HASEL) actuator was configured in a layered structure to achieve practical usability and efficient movement. The actuator operates through hydraulic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of Dementia Platform Korea and the Trial Ready Registry to advance Alzheimer's disease research in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is an abundance of high-quality clinical data and resources for Alzheimer's disease (AD) in Korea. To investigate therapeutic targets and biomarkers, and to progress the AD research field in Korea by standardizing the dementia dataset in Korea, the Trial Ready Registry (TRR) and Dementia Platform Korea (DPK) were developed. We designed the minimum common dataset (MCD) to collect data on patients with AD and human-derived materials, which consist of clinical data and positron emission...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capture and Release of Molecules with Liquid Metals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper reports the capture and release of target molecules on gallium-based liquid metal (LM). Functionalizing the native oxide of the LM with (3-aminopropyl)triethoxysilane (APTES) creates an amine-terminated surface capable of binding and thereby capturing a model analyte, fluorescein isothiocyanate. These captured surface molecules can be released by electrochemically reducing the oxide layer. This approach captures ≈81% of the dye from solution and ≈92% of the captured molecules can be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoinduced skeletal editing of oxetanes: light-driven pathway connecting four-membered heterocycles and beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial Multi-Omics in Precision Medicine: Integrating Biological Insights Through Multidisciplinary Collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spatial multi-omics has emerged as a transformative approach in biomedical research, enabling the integration of diverse molecular modalities while preserving their native spatial contexts. This review provides an overview of spatial multi-omics technologies, focusing on data acquisition, quality management, and integration strategies across transcriptomic, genomic, epigenomic, proteomic, and metabolomic layers. Spatial transcriptomics is highlighted as a foundational framework for aligning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolomic analysis reveals stepwise metabolic adaptation to extended photoperiods in developing pea sprouts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoperiod strongly influences early seedling metabolism; however, its role during initial development remains unclear. We analysed 100 primary and secondary metabolites and phytohormones in pea sprouts grown under short-day (SD; 8 h light), long-day (LD; 16 h light), and all-day (AD; 24 h light) conditions. Principal component analysis revealed distinct photoperiod-dependent clustering, indicating stepwise metabolic reprogramming from SD to AD. SD enhanced amino acid accumulation and auxin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-reactive immunity within pneumococcal serogroups: Implications for next-generation vaccine development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The inhibition OPA enabled a precise assessment of serogroup-level cross-reactive immunity, revealing heterogeneous patterns of cross-reactivity. These findings underscore the need for careful serotype selection and epitope evaluation in next-generation vaccine formulations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hidden Workers in Aging Australia: Protocol of Intersectionality-Informed Mixed Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study will generate the first intersectional evidence on the health and employment challenges of hidden aging workers in Australia. These insights will inform tailored policy interventions that can support re-engagement, reduce inequities in health and well-being, and strengthen workforce participation. Ultimately, the findings will contribute to addressing skills shortages while promoting social and economic inclusion of aging Australians.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning for deep learning performance: How much data is needed for segmentation in biomedical imaging?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) models are widely adopted in biomedical imaging, where image segmentation is increasingly recognized as a quantitative tool for extracting clinically meaningful information. However, model performance critically depends on dataset size and training configuration, including model capacity. Traditional sample size estimation methods are inadequate for DL due to its reliance on high-dimensional data and its nonlinear learning behavior. To address this gap, we propose a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Interpersonal Needs and Attitudes Toward Suicide on Suicide Risk in Middle-Aged Korean Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Urban residence, perceived poor mental health, and maladaptive attitudes toward suicide are key determinants of suicidal risk among middle-aged Korean women. Findings emphasize the need for a comprehensive suicide risk assessment addressing psychological distress and sociocultural perceptions to enhance suicide prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetic Skyrmion Neurons with Homeostasis for Spiking Neural Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in spiking neural networks (SNNs) have drawn inspiration from the human brain's distinctive capabilities, leading to significant impacts on various aspects of our lives and scientific endeavors. The development of hardware-based Spiking Neural Networks (H-SNNs) is a crucial aspect of the progress in neuromorphic computing, particularly in the context of on-chip implementations. H-SNNs involve the hardware realization of specific functionalities used in SNN algorithms, such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning-Guided Discovery of Sterically Protected High Triplet Exciplex Hosts for Ultra-Bright Green OLEDs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) has been widely used to accelerate the discovery of organic light-emitting diode (OLED) materials, but its application to improving device-level performance has been limited. Here, we develop an ML workflow that explicitly incorporates exciplex-specific design criteria, including exciplex-considered high triplet energy criteria, deep lowest-unoccupied molecular orbital (LUMO) alignment, high bond dissociation energy (BDE), and proper reorganization energy, as factors that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of Microtubule Radial Structure by Competition between Tau and Paclitaxel: Binding and Synchrotron X-ray Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microtubules (MTs) are a major component of the eukaryotic cytoskeleton. MT architecture is highly regulated by microtubule-associated proteins (MAPs) such as Tau as well as a number of MT-targeted chemotherapeutic agents such as paclitaxel (PTX). In this study, we examined the ability of each of the six different alternatively spliced isoforms of human wild-type (WT) Tau (4R2N, 4R1N, 4R0N, 3R2N, 3R1N and 3R0N) and PTX to bind to MTs as well as their effects upon MT structure. MTs were assembled...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the Reliability of Calibration Constants in Heat Flux Meters Using an ISO 5660-1 Cone Heater]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates the reliability of calibration constants for heat flux meters (HFMs) using a secondary standard under controlled thermal conditions provided by an ISO 5660-1 cone heater. Six HFMs (three new and three previously used) were examined by comparing manufacturer-provided (MFG) and secondary-standard-based (SEC) calibration constants. The bias between the MFG and SEC calibration constants varied substantially depending on the manufacturer, calibration method, service history, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Therapeutic Effect of a Biodegradable Long-Acting Intravitreal Implant Containing CGK012 on Neovascular Age-Related Macular Degeneration by Promoting β-Catenin Degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Neovascular age-related macular degeneration (nAMD) poses a serious threat to the eyesight of older adults, representing a leading cause of irreversible vision loss. Anti-vascular endothelial growth factor (anti-VEGF) treatments are effective but require repeated intraocular injections and show poor responses in some patients. CGK012 is a novel derivative of decursin that inhibits the Wnt/β-catenin pathway. This study aimed to elucidate the mode of action of CGK012 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Molecular Detection of Orthohantaviruses (<em>Orthohantavirus hantanense</em> and <em>O. jejuense</em>) in Trombiculid Mites from Wild Rodents in the Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orthohantaviruses are zoonotic pathogens that cause severe diseases in humans primarily through inhalation of aerosols from rodent excreta. Recent studies suggest that ectoparasites may be potential vectors for Orthohantaviruses. This study aimed to obtain molecular evidence of Orthohantavirus in trombiculid mites collected from wild rodents. In April 2025, 4963 trombiculid mites were collected from 128 wild rodents captured in 17 regions of the Republic of Korea (ROK). Among them, 1660 mites...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and Challenges in Vaccination and Therapeutic Strategies Against Japanese Encephalitis Virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Japanese encephalitis virus (JEV) remains a major cause of viral encephalitis in Asia, and recent epidemiological shifts driven by the predominance of genotype I and the re-emergence of genotype V have renewed concerns regarding control efforts. Licensed vaccines have a reduced incidence of more than 90% in several endemic regions; however, evidence of reduced cross-neutralization against heterologous genotypes indicates that vaccines derived from genotype III strains may not fully match the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic Landscape and Interaction Potential of SGLT2 Inhibitors: Bridging In Vitro Findings and Clinical Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sodium-glucose cotransporter 2 (SGLT2) inhibitors are widely used in type 2 diabetes and cardiometabolic diseases, and their pharmacokinetic characteristics generally confer a low risk of clinically relevant drug-drug interactions (DDIs). Most clinical studies demonstrate that these agents can be co-administered safely with commonly prescribed medications without dose adjustment, although strong enzyme inducers such as rifampin can reduce systemic exposure, and pharmacodynamic interactions may...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic Evaluation of GB-5001, a Long-Acting Injectable Formulation of Donepezil, in Healthy Korean Participants: Population Pharmacokinetics with Phase 1 Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Oral donepezil, an acetylcholinesterase (AChE) inhibitor for Alzheimer's disease, faces adherence challenges. Long-acting injectable (LAI) formulations like GB-5001 aim to enhance adherence by reducing dosing frequency. This Phase 1, open-label, active-controlled, dose-escalation study evaluated the safety, tolerability, pharmacokinetics (PK), and pharmacodynamics (PD) of GB-5001 in healthy male adults. Methods: Participants were assigned to cohorts receiving GB-5001A or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Packed-Type Reconfigurable Air Filtration System for Removal of Particulate Matter and HCHO]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A flexible and packed-type air filter ball (AFB) system was developed for the efficient removal of particulate matter (PM) and formaldehyde (HCHO). The Mg/Si-embedded AFB (Mg/Si-AFB) was synthesized through sequential physical etching of a sponge, oxidation of glass fiber, and subsequent formation of Mg-Si components. The resulting Mg/Si-AFB exhibited a highly porous and roughened architecture with enhanced surface reactivity. A disk-type filtration device loaded with Mg/Si-AFBs demonstrated a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRISPR/Cas9-Targeted Gene Editing of Allergenic Profilin-Encoding <em>Lyc e1</em> in Tomato Fruit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tomato (Solanum lycopersicum L.), one of the most widely consumed horticultural crops worldwide, is also a notable source of food allergens, with a higher prevalence of allergic reactions in pollen-sensitized patients. Profilin, a small actin-binding protein, is a major allergen in tomato fruits encoded by two homologous genes, Lyc e1.01 and Lyc e1.02. Although various strategies have been proposed to reduce allergenicity in foods, no prior study has successfully achieved the complete...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of High-Power Laser Cleaning on Oxide Layer Formation on 304L Stainless Steel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a kW-level high-power Nd:YAG nanosecond laser was adopted to eliminate a corrosion layer on a 304L stainless steel (SS304L) surface. Four different laser cleaning (LC) processes with various hatch distances and loop counts were adopted. The energy-dispersive X-ray spectroscopy (EDX) analysis revealed that the corrosion layer was successfully eliminated via the LC process. However, the electron probe X-ray microanalysis (EPMA) analysis confirmed that a Cr-based oxide layer with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving the Cycling Stability of Next-Generation Si Anode Batteries Using Polymer Coatings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silicon is widely recognized as a next-generation anode owing to its exceptional theoretical capacity, yet its practical deployment in lithium-ion batteries is constrained by severe volume expansion, particle fracture, loss of electrical percolation, and solid electrolyte interphase layer instability. Polymer-based strategies have emerged as accessible solutions to engineer extensive volume changes and interfacial compatibility, while preserving pathways for charge transport. Viscoelastic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nano Carbon-Based Hybrid Strategies for Mitigating Silicon Anode Expansion in Lithium-Ion Batteries: A Comprehensive Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silicon is considered one of the most promising anode materials for lithium-ion batteries because of its high theoretical capacity and low lithiation potential. However, its practical application is limited by significant volume expansion, unstable solid-electrolyte interphase formation, and poor intrinsic conductivity. This review summarizes recent advances in hybrid strategies using multi-walled carbon nanotubes (MWCNTs), single-walled carbon nanotubes (SWCNTs), graphene, carbon nanofibers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Accuracy of Non-Contrast CT for Acute Appendicitis in the Emergency Department: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Contrast-enhanced computed tomography (CT) is widely regarded as the gold standard for diagnosing acute appendicitis. However, the use of contrast agents may be contraindicated in patients with renal impairment or a history of allergic reactions. Non-contrast CT (NCCT) offers a potential alternative, but its diagnostic performance has been variably reported across studies. This systematic review and meta-analysis aimed to evaluate the pooled diagnostic accuracy of NCCT...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of adjusting the baseplate size to the glenoid on primary fixation stability in reverse total shoulder arthroplasty: a finite element analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared with the 29‑mm baseplate, the 25‑mm baseplate improved primary fixation stability in small glenoids through increased bone-screw contact and LSBS of the anterior and posterior screws. In the large glenoid, baseplate size did not significantly affect the primary fixation stability of the glenoid component. In the small glenoid, adjusting the baseplate size using a small baseplate matching the anatomical size may improve primary fixation stability of the glenoid component....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated lithium niobate photonic devices for photonic quantum information science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Integrated thin-film lithium niobate (TFLN) photonics has emerged as a powerful platform for quantum information science, offering its outstanding nonlinear, electro-optic (EO), and integration capabilities. In this review, we present the latest advances in TFLN-based integrated photonics tailored to quantum technologies. We first explore state-of-the-art quantum light sources realized in both straight waveguide and resonator configuration, including high-brightness photon pair generations,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of post-liposuction edema on body composition and weight reduction efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personality and impulsivity traits associated with problematic online gaming and poker playing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Native-like GPCR Antigens Enables Discovery of an LPA2-Blocking Antibody for Ovarian Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[G-protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs) are high-value therapeutic targets, yet antibody discovery remains limited by difficulties in preparing antigens that preserve native conformations. Here, we engineered a native-like, full-length human LPA2 antigen by combining N-terminal P9* fused with amphipathic poly-γ-glutamate (APG) stabilization, affording an antigen suitable for the selection of antibodies with therapeutic efficacy. By screening a large synthetic human scFv library, we isolated an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical drawing of two-dimensional transition metal dichalcogenides on paper for ultrasensitive gas sensing devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maximizing sensitivity while minimizing manufacturing complexity and costs remains a challenge in the development of flexible gas sensors. Two-dimensional transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDCs) have emerged as potential candidates; however, further enhancement of their gas sensitivity is required without increasing fabrication complexity. Here, we report ultrasensitive and selective gas sensors fabricated by mechanically drawing compressed TMDCs on flexible cellulose paper. This method rapidly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extending multilevel analysis of individual heterogeneity and discriminatory accuracy to time-to-event outcomes: an application of survival MAIHDA to Korean health data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Applying a multilevel survival (shared frailty) model within MAIHDA enables examination of when disparities emerge, not just whether they exist. This approach retains MAIHDA's interpretability while leveraging time-to-event data, offering advantages in settings with incomplete follow-up or irregular observation windows.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triglyceride-glucose index and risks of suicide mortality in young adults: a nationwide population-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TyG index can be useful in identifying young individuals at an increased risk of suicide mortality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proton pump inhibitors use and risk of inflammatory bowel disease in children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Design of cyclic tissue engineering bioreactor based on alginate hydrogel responses to the stress of compression surface morphologies and texture profile and its finite element analysis" [Int. J. Biol. Macromol. 338 (2026) 1 page-13 page]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between cesarean anesthesia type and long-term neurodevelopmental outcomes in offspring: a nationwide retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this nationwide cohort, NA for cesarean delivery was associated with a modestly lower incidence and hazard of LNDDs compared with GA. These findings should be interpreted as exploratory and hypothesis-generating, rather than causal, and highlight the need for further research integrating detailed perinatal and anesthetic data.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging strategies for polysaccharide modification and functional enhancement in food systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polysaccharides, the most abundant natural biopolymers, exhibit outstanding biocompatibility and versatile functionality, making them valuable for applications in food, biomedicine and sustainable packaging. However, their native forms often suffer from limitations such as poor mechanical strength, thermal instability and rapid enzymatic degradation, which hinder broader industrial applications. This review critically examines recent advances in emerging modification techniques such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effective in vitro evaluation of biogenic amines in fermented food using mast cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Legal limits and toxic thresholds for histamine levels in food have been established by the Codex Alimentarius Commission as well as by national food safety authorities in various countries In this study, we found that mast cell degranulation was increased in a histamine concentration-dependent manner, and this degranulation was found to be associated with MRGPRX2, a receptor involved in non-IgE-mediated allergic reactions, as demonstrated by molecular docking analysis and mRNA expression. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Articular impaction of olecranon fracture is associated with poor postoperative clinical outcome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Articular impaction in olecranon fractures is associated with worse postoperative outcomes, with inadequate impaction reduction contributing to increased step-off and poorer function. Achieving optimal impaction reduction and minimizing residual step-off are critical to improving clinical and radiological outcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SLC16A3 as a novel therapeutic target for overcoming radioresistance and chemoresistance in lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiotherapy and chemotherapy are central components of lung cancer treatment. However, the development of therapeutic resistance significantly limits their efficacy. Here, we identified SLC16A3 as a potential biomarker associated with radioresistance and chemoresistance in lung cancer. Transcriptomic and protein analyses revealed significantly higher SLC16A3 expression in radioresistant R-H460 cells than in parental H460 cells, and immunohistochemistry further confirmed higher SLC16A3...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitigating suffusion-induced reactivity loss in sulfate-reducing barriers: Upscaling from multi-layered soil tank to pilot-scale demonstration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the effectiveness of permeable reactive barriers (PRBs) in stimulating sulfate-reducing bacteria (SRB) to remove both sulfate (SO(4)^(2-)) and metal ions (Me^(2+)) from groundwater. PRBs comprising a mixture of conventional reactive materials, including livestock compost, oak sawdust, calcite, and coarse gravel, were simulated in two-dimensional tanks, to which contaminated groundwater from a smelter site in Korea was introduced. The simple placement of the materials resulted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a long-term survival prediction model for patients undergoing invasive coronary angiography using ensemble-based machine learning in time-to-event analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Survival analysis-based ensemble ML models, such as Survival Quilts, improve survival prediction by capturing time-varying influences of key predictors, offering a foundation for more precise cardiovascular care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of APOBEC in early-stage epidermal growth factor receptor-mutant non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: APOBEC enrichment may present at initial diagnosis of early-stage EGFR mutant NSCLC and is associated with poor post-recurrence TKI PFS and PRS rather than RFS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lethal Heat and Humidity Events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change increasingly threatens global health as more frequent extreme heat events, combined with varying humidity levels, exacerbate both direct and indirect health risks, strain energy resources, and lead to economic loss. Vulnerable populations, including the elderly, young children, and those with preexisting health conditions, face greater risks due to lower physiological adaptive capacity. Those from socioeconomically disadvantaged communities are also vulnerable because of increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated with Glaucomatous Progression in Eyes Underwent Refractive Corneal Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with POAG and a history of RCS who present with longer axial length and thinner central corneal thickness, are at significantly higher risk of glaucomatous progression, highlighting the importance of vigilant long-term monitoring in these eyes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exposure to heavy metals, bisphenol A, and phthalates: Implications for precocious or delayed puberty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the associations between exposure to heavy metals, bisphenol A (BPA), and phthalates and precocious or delayed puberty. This study was a cross-sectional study using the data obtained from the Korea Environmental Exposure and Health Survey in Children and Adolescents. Blood samples were collected to measure lead, mercury, and cadmium levels, whereas spot urine samples were analyzed for BPA, phthalate metabolites, and creatinine levels. Sexual maturation status was assessed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Efficacy of Neoadjuvant Peptide Receptor Radionuclide Therapy in Neuroendocrine Tumors: A Meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Neoadjuvant PRRT appears to be an effective therapeutic strategy for patients with NETs, particularly by reducing tumor size and stage in borderline resectable or unresectable cases. These findings suggest that neoadjuvant PRRT represents a promising option to facilitate surgical resection and improve outcomes in NET patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of perioperative fentanyl analog exposure with risk of psychiatric disorder in non-cardiac surgery: A 10-year retrospective study in a Korean tertiary hospital]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative fentanyl use is linked to a higher risk of psychiatric disorders compared to other opioids. These findings emphasize the need for careful use and monitoring of fentanyl in surgical patients, considering both immediate and long-term mental health effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domain-specific physical activity and depressive symptoms in Korean adults: An isotemporal substitution study using KNHANES data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The observed associations between physical activity and depressive symptoms appear to vary by activity type and the social context. The potential mental health benefits of leisure-based activity may be weaker during periods of societal disruption, such as the COVID-19 pandemic. These findings highlight the need for physical activity guidelines that consider both domain-specific patterns and the psychosocial environment in which activity takes place.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drosophila Abi maintains blood cell homeostasis by promoting clathrin-mediated endocytosis of Notch]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Abl-interactor (Abi) proteins induce actin polymerization by activating Wiskott-Aldrich syndrome protein (WASp) or SCAR/WASP-family verprolin-homologous protein. Loss of mammalian Abi1 causes myeloproliferative neoplasm; however, little is known about how the Abi family of actin-regulatory proteins regulates blood cell homeostasis. Here, we demonstrate that Drosophila Abi promotes plasmatocyte-to-crystal cell transdifferentiation but represses plasmatocyte-to-lamellocyte transdifferentiation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison Between Anterior and Posterior Decompression for Degenerative Cervical Myelopathy With Multilevel Foraminal Stenosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Anterior and posterior decompressive surgeries are reliable for the surgical treatment of DCM with multilevel foraminal stenosis and showed similar outcomes for both myelopathy and upper extremity radicular symptoms. The major etiology compromising the clinical outcome was a higher incidence of CASP in the anterior group and persistent or recurrent upper extremity radicular symptoms in the posterior group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polynucleotide (DOT-PN) for Accelerated Healing of Lip Necrosis After Filler-Induced Vascular Compromise]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Further controlled studies are warranted to define optimal PN dosing intervals, timing of administration, and comparative effectiveness versus other adjunctive treatments for filler-induced ischemic complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus from the Asian conference on tumor ablation working group on image-guided thermal ablation for lung tumor: 10 key questions and answers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Percutaneous image-guided thermal ablation (IGTA) is increasingly utilized for the management of primary and metastatic lung tumors. Several academic societies across various countries have issued clinical practice guidelines, opinion statements, and recommendations for IGTA in the treatment of lung tumors. However, unresolved conceptual and practical challenges persist, underscoring the need for a more comprehensive consensus on the safe and effective application of IGTA, particularly in Asian...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative CT Measurements of Interstitial Lung Disease: Same-Day Variability Between Two Vendors-A Prospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Clinical application of quantitative CT (QCT) measurements of interstitial lung disease (ILD) for longitudinal monitoring of disease progression requires understanding of how such measurements vary across vendors. Objective: To evaluate same-day variability between vendors for QCT measurements of fibrosis extent in patients with ILD. Methods: This prospective study recruited participants with diagnosed ILD from January 2023 to August 2024. Participants underwent two serial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basal EMG Amplitude in REM and NREM Sleep as a Predictor of Disease Progression in Isolated REM Sleep Behavior Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Elevated basal EMG amplitude during both REM and NREM sleep in iRBD patients shows potential as a prognostic marker, indicating muscle tone dysregulation beyond REM atonia loss and underscoring the need to consider broader sleep stages in iRBD evaluation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soft Tissue Substitutes: Current Biomaterials and Indications at Teeth and Implant Sites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soft tissue augmentation around teeth and dental implants is a central aspect of periodontal and peri-implant plastic surgery. Autogenous soft tissue grafts are generally regarded as the gold standard for increasing keratinized mucosa, mucosal thickness, and soft tissue height, supported by extensive long-term evidence. However, limitations such as restricted tissue availability, increased surgical time, and donor-site morbidity have encouraged the development of soft tissue graft substitutes,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of long working hours with the use of combustible cigarettes, electronic cigarettes, and heated tobacco products among young adults: a population-based study of South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Long working hours is linked to the use of various forms of tobacco products among young adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploiting Mg-Interdiffusion-Driven Work-Function Reduction in Ti/Mg/Ti Multilayers to Achieve Low-Resistivity Ohmic Contacts to (001) β-Ga<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Low-resistivity Ohmic contact formation in β-gallium oxide (β-Ga(2)O(3)) is crucial for high-efficiency power electronics and deep-ultraviolet (DUV) optoelectronic devices. In this study, we successfully developed a Ti/Mg/Ti multilayered metal stack (20 nm/50 nm/20 nm) as an Ohmic contact to (001) β-Ga(2)O(3). The Mg interlayer, with its low work function relative to Ti and the electron affinity of β-Ga(2)O(3), effectively reduces the Schottky barrier, enabling low contact resistivity. The Ti...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applying the technology acceptance model to predict digital therapeutics use in South Korea: The roles of digital literacy, online information trust, and privacy concern]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings highlight the complex interplay among digital literacy, trust, and privacy in influencing DTx adoption. Emphasis on user-centered design, strong privacy protection, and digital literacy education will be essential for fostering broader acceptance of digital therapeutics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A deep learning-based early prediction framework for weight management using real-world lifelog data: GRU-ODE-Bayes model development and validation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed model predicted early outcomes in weight management and might contribute to developing effective intervention methods for participants at risk of failure and reducing the burden of frequent self-reporting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting the quality of cookies with oleogel as a shortening substitute using hyperspectral imaging and artificial intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A total of 36 oleogels, made from various waxes and vegetable oils, were utilized as shortening substitutes in cookies, and machine learning incorporating three boosting models (AdaBoost, GBM, and XGBoost) was applied to predict their effects on the quality attributes of the cookies. Carnauba wax oleogels exhibited the highest melting temperature and contributed to stronger cookie texture, while beeswax oleogels produced cookies with greater spreadability and lower hardness. Similar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Saccharomyces cerevisiae</em>-Fermented Salmon Placental Protein Inhibits Muscle Loss in a Mouse Model of Sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Addressing sarcopenia and frailty in aging populations is crucial for improving quality of life and reducing healthcare dependence among these patients. Although no specific drugs have been approved for treating sarcopenia, protein supplements rich in branched-chain amino acid (BCAA) have been reported to increase muscle mass and function in elderly individuals. Fermentation of salmon placenta protein is an effective approach to improve BCAA content compared to previous sarcopenia-related...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the safety and efficacy of a donepezil depot injection in dogs with canine cognitive dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canine cognitive dysfunction (CCD) is an age-related neurodegenerative disorder for which effective treatments remain limited, and objective diagnostic and therapeutic assessment tools using biomarkers or neuroimaging are still lacking compared with human Alzheimer's disease. This study evaluated the safety and efficacy of a long-acting donepezil depot injection in dogs with CCD, using behavioral scores and serum neurofilament light chain (NfL) as primary outcomes, with baseline MRI for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Athlete data sovereignty: addressing the legal and policy gaps in sports technology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative tadalafil for recovery of continence and voiding function after radical prostatectomy for prostate cancer: a single-center experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Postoperative tadalafil is associated with improved recovery of erectile and voiding function, as well as higher continence rates, without compromising oncologic outcomes. These findings support its consideration as part of routine postoperative management in selected RP patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<sup>18</sup>F-florastamin positron emission tomography/computed tomography in men with clinical suspicion of prostate cancer: A phase I prospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ^(18)F-Florastamin is a promising PET tracer that correctly identifies foci of cancer within the prostate with a higher accuracy than conventional imaging (MRI), and may be helpful in stratifying patients with low to intermediate PSA levels to better assess the need for an invasive biopsy. Our cohort study suggests triage with ^(18)F-Florastamin PET/CT has the potential to reduce unnecessary biopsies in 9/20 (45%) patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The dose-volume histogram-based evaluation of predictors for gross hematuria after postprostatectomy radiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results suggest that gross hematuria after PPRT occurs frequently, especially among patients on anticoagulant/antiplatelet therapy and those with an absolute bladder V40 Gy ≥median and relative bladder V65 Gy ≥median during PPRT. Although most cases of gross hematuria were self-resolved, up to 16.1% required invasive surgical intervention. Limiting PPRT dose exposure to the bladder may also reduce the incidence of gross hematuria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oncologic outcomes of salvage radiotherapy and lymphadenectomy for positron emission tomography-positive lymph nodes in biochemical recurrence: A systematic review to inform treatment decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite salvage LND or RT, about half of BCR patients with PET-positive nodal recurrence showed disease progression, suggesting limited effectiveness of focal therapies alone. RT appeared to provide better short-term disease control than LND, highlighting the importance of treatment selection. The study underscores the necessity for further investigation into optimal salvage management strategies for BCR using PET in prospective clinical studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical implication of peri-seminal vesicle soft-tissue invasion in patients with pT3b prostate cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In pT3b patients, peri-SV soft-tissue invasion and lymph node metastasis are common. These findings suggest that a more radical surgical approach is warranted in patients with suspected SVI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of 7-tesla <em>ex vivo</em> and conventional 3-tesla magnetic resonance imaging for prostate cancer staging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The 7T ex vivo MRI enhances the diagnostic accuracy, clarity, and reproducibility of EPE assessment and reduces tumor size underestimation compared to 3T MRI, supporting its potential role in optimizing preoperative prostate cancer staging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of pentosan polysulfate therapy in patients with interstitial cystitis for relief of lower urinary tract symptoms: 15-year single center experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PPS provides clinical benefits in urinary symptoms voiding symptoms and QoL over time, arriving plateau within 3 months. Such benefits based on the IPSS tend to be more evident in younger patients, suggesting that PPS mostly benefits early treatment if suspected for IC/BPS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence-driven digital pathology in urological cancers: current trends and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) in digital pathology has gained attention owing to its potential in urological cancer diagnosis and management. This review highlights AI's applications and challenges in three major urological cancers. Prostate cancer studies have demonstrated reliable diagnostic performance and promising prognosis prediction. Renal cancer study shows potential but faces challenges in generalizability and prognosis. Bladder cancer studies are limited by the lack of large-scale...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-dependent Increase in Cortisol after 1-mg Overnight Dexamethasone Suppression Test in Adrenal Incidentalomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cortisol levels after 1-mg ODST increased over time, suggesting an age-related effect and highlighting the need for age-tailored diagnostic and management strategies for MACS in older patients with AI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Job Crafting as the Missing Link: Understanding Its Role in Nurses' Work Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nurses with higher positive psychological capital and those working in a positive work environment are more likely to be involved in job crafting, which in turn enhances their work engagement. These findings suggest that both individual and organizational strategies are essential in promoting individual nurses' job crafting and work engagement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of Venoarterial Extracorporeal Membrane Oxygenation as a Procedural Support Tool in Cardiovascular Instability: A Case Series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The use of venoarterial extracorporeal membrane oxygenation (VA-ECMO) is increasing worldwide. Patients with cardiogenic shock were the first indication for VA-ECMO according to the Extracorporeal Life Support Organization (ELSO) guidelines. However, recent studies have shown that VA-ECMO is not beneficial in patients with cardiogenic shock. This report describes the case of three patients who presented with infarct-related cardiac arrest without cardiogenic shock and received VA-ECMO to support...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epitope-level analysis of cross-reactive human HLA antibodies against genetically modified swine leukocyte antigens in xenotransplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cross-reactive anti-SLA antibodies are common in highly sensitized human sera, driven by antibody specificity and epitope conservation. Despite glycan xenoantigen deletion, sensitized sera maintain IgG-mediated cross-reactivity and cytotoxicity against gene-edited pig cells. These findings highlight the need for detailed epitope-level analysis to refine immunologic risk assessment and recipient selection to reduce antibody-mediated rejection in clinical xenotransplantation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residue dynamics and metabolic pathways of sulfoxaflor in Cirsium japonicum var. maackii and Olea europaea L]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings contribute to our understanding of the residue and metabolic characteristics of sulfoxaflor and provide fundamental data for establishing safe pesticide use guidelines and MRLs for thistle and olive cultivation. © 2025 Society of Chemical Industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Super-Resolution Tracking of mtDNA Remodeling and Inflammatory Release with a Selective Fluorescent Probe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondrial DNA (mtDNA) is vital for mitochondrial function and cellular homeostasis, with its spatiotemporal dynamics are tightly linked to development, metabolism, and disease progression. However, super-resolution tracking of mtDNA in live cells remains limited by lack of selective, photostable small-molecule probes. Here, we present mtNARed, a rationally engineered, wash-free fluorescent probe featuring a large Stokes-shift, and high photostability that enables super-resolution tracking of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Autologous Blood-Derived Extracellular Vesicles on Skin Regeneration and Anti-Aging: A Clinical Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates the clinical efficacy and safety of autologous blood-derived EVs in facial rejuvenation, supporting their potential as a non-invasive cosmetic treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Challenges and Clinical Implications of Microsatellite Instability/Mismatch Repair Deficiency in Solid Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mismatch repair (MMR) system plays a crucial role in correcting replication errors; when the MMR system is deficient (dMMR), replication errors (particularly within microsatellites) accumulate throughout the genome, leading to microsatellite instability (MSI). The key MMR genes include MLH1, MSH2, MSH6, and PMS2. Germline mutations in these genes are associated with Lynch syndrome, whereas in sporadic solid tumors, dMMR is often caused by hypermethylation of the MLH1 promoter. As the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Features and Outcomes of Endoscopic Resection of Superficial Nonampullary Duodenal Tumors in South Korea: A 15-Year Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ER is effective and safe for SNADETs, achieving high curative resection rates, low recurrence, and acceptable complication risks. Selection of resection method should be individualized, with cold EMR and underwater EMR offering safe and efficient alternatives for the treatment of smaller lesions, while ESD may be reserved for the treatment of larger lesions or complex cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased Heart Failure Risk with Gastric Cancer Progression: A Nationwide Population-Based Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with gastric cancer, the risk of heart failure requiring hospitalization increased with worsening cancer stage. Even in young patients and those without metabolic risk factors, close monitoring for heart failure development following cancer treatment is essential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Dual Role of A20 (TNFAIP3) in Viral Infection: A Context-Dependent Regulator of Immunity and Pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A20 (TNFAIP3) is a ubiquitin-editing enzyme that plays a central role in the regulation of inflammation and cell death, primarily through modulation of NF-κB signaling. In the context of viral infection, A20 exhibits a dual nature: it can both suppress antiviral immune responses to facilitate viral replication and act as a host-protective factor to prevent immunopathology. This review synthesizes current findings on the context-dependent roles of A20, focusing on its capacity to switch between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful Surgical Excision of a Chronic Abscess in a Hawksbill Turtle (<em>Eretmochelys imbricata</em>): A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In sea turtles, soft tissue abscesses typically present with a solid, caseous consistency and respond poorly to pharmacological treatment. A hawksbill turtle (Eretmochelys imbricata) exhibited a chronic subcutaneous mass near the cloacal region that had persisted for three years. Histopathological examination confirmed the existence of an abscess composed of concentric necrotic layers and chronic inflammatory cell infiltration, with no detectable pathogens. The lesion was surgically excised...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr Virus Promotes Gastric Cancer Progression by Modulating m6A-Dependent YTHDF1-TSC22D1 Axis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr virus (EBV) infection is closely associated with gastric cancer, yet its role in m6A-dependent gene regulation remains poorly understood. In this study, we investigated how EBV infection alters the m6A methylation pattern in gastric cancer cells and examined its impact on TSC22D1 mRNA stability through interaction with the m6A reader protein YTHDF1. m6A RNA immunoprecipitation sequencing (MeRIP-seq) revealed a significant reduction in m6A methylation of TSC22D1 in EBV-infected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergence of Multidrug-Resistant and Biofilm-Producing <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em> from Raw Poultry in Algeria: Implications for Public Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Staphylococcus aureus is a common foodborne pathogen, posing significant concern due to the emergence of its multidrug-resistant (MDR) strains. The aim of this study was to assess the antibiotic resistance profiles in S. aureus isolated from raw poultry, the associated resistance genes, and their ability to form biofilms. S. aureus was isolated and identified using conventional microbiological methods. Antimicrobial susceptibility profiles were assessed using the disk diffusion method, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An <em>rpoB</em> Sequence Type Network as a Framework for the Evolutionary Investigation of <em>Clostridium perfringens</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clostridium perfringens is an opportunistic Gram-positive bacterium that causes necrotic enteritis and other severe infections in animals, as well as food poisoning in humans. In this study, we introduce a framework consisting of rpoB sequence typing (RSTing) and network analysis to investigate the evolutionary trajectories of C. perfringens. By analyzing 319 rpoB sequences-300 from public databases and 19 newly sequenced isolates from chicken and cattle sources-we identified 84 rpoB sequence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr Virus Silences GSDME and Pyroptosis in Gastric Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr virus (EBV)-associated gastric carcinoma (EBVaGC) represents a distinct molecular subtype characterized by extensive DNA methylation and altered cell death signaling. This study investigated the regulation and function of gasdermin E (GSDME), a key mediator of pyroptosis, in EBVaGC. Transcriptomic analysis of The Cancer Genome Atlas (TCGA) data revealed that GSDME expression was selectively suppressed in EBV-positive gastric cancer, while other gasdermin family members were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub>: An Oxide Semiconductor for Thin-Film Transistors, a Short Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the discovery of amorphous oxide semiconductors, a new era of electronics opened. Indium gallium zinc oxide (IGZO) overcame the problems of amorphous and poly-silicon by reaching mobilities of ~10 cm²/Vs and demonstrating thin-film transistors (TFTs) are easy to manufacture on transparent and flexible substrates. However, mobilities over 30 cm²/Vs have been difficult to reach and other materials have been introduced. Recently, polycrystalline In(2)O(3) has demonstrated breakthroughs in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Co-Reactant Engineering for Au Nanocluster Electrochemiluminescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Co-reactants are essential in co-reactant-based electrochemiluminescence (ECL) systems because they generate reactive intermediates that can oxidize or reduce ECL luminophores, thereby driving ECL emission. In the context of ECL, gold nanoclusters (Au NCs) have emerged as innovative luminophores, owing to their tunable electronic structures and excellent biocompatibility. However, their efficiency in ECL applications is often compromised by challenges such as limited excited-state generation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive Evaluation of a Passive Upper-Limb Exoskeleton in Agricultural Tasks: Integrating Physiological, Postural, and Cognitive Measures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the effects of a passive upper-limb exoskeleton in agricultural work using a repeated-measures design with 24 adult males across three exoskeleton conditions (No Exo, Prototype, and Airframe), three work directions (left, front, and right), and two work distances (near and far). Outcomes included muscle activity, center of pressure travel, task completion time, perceived exertion, body part discomfort, and usability. Airframe use significantly reduced shoulder and upper-arm...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does Coxsackievirus B3 Require Autophagosome Formation for Replication? Evidence for an Autophagosome-Independent Mechanism: Insights into Its Limited Potential as a Therapeutic Target]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Coxsackievirus B3 (CVB3), a neurotropic enterovirus, is a major causative agent of viral encephalitis and myocarditis, yet no protective vaccine or effective antiviral therapy is currently available. Autophagy plays a dual role in viral infections, acting as both an antiviral defense and a process that can be exploited by certain viruses. Although CVB3 has been proposed to utilize autophagosomes as replication platforms, the underlying mechanisms remain controversial....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Herbal Inhalation Therapy for Allergic Rhinitis: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Allergic rhinitis (AR) is a common immunological disorder characterized by nasal symptoms and impaired quality of life. Despite advances in pharmacotherapy, symptom control often remains inadequate. Herbal medicine atomized inhalation (HMAI), a modern adaptation of traditional East Asian fumigation, may offer an effective adjunct or alternative therapy. This systematic review and meta-analysis evaluated the clinical efficacy and safety of HMAI, emphasizing its role as a localized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rosuvastatin Versus Atorvastatin for Cardiovascular Disease Risk in Patients with Type 2 Diabetes: A Korean Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Rosuvastatin and atorvastatin are indicated for cardiovascular protection in patients with type 2 diabetes (T2D) but may differ in clinical effectiveness and safety. This study compared real-world cardiovascular and safety outcomes associated with rosuvastatin versus atorvastatin in patients with T2D, with an emphasis on older adults. Methods: This retrospective cohort study used electronic health records from 10 Korean hospitals standardized to the Common Data Model. Adults (≥18...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Potential of <em>Gynostemma pentaphyllum</em> (Thunb.) Makino Against COVID-19 Identified Through Network Pharmacology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The ongoing challenges posed by COVID-19 have highlighted the need for multi-target therapeutic strategies addressing both acute immune responses and systemic complications. Gynostemma pentaphyllum (Thunb.) Makino, a traditional herbal medicine rich in flavonoids and saponins, exhibits diverse pharmacological activities, including immunomodulatory and cardiovascular effects. In this study, we investigated the potential of G. pentaphyllum as a complementary treatment for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coixol and Sinigrin from <em>Coix lacryma-jobi</em> L. and <em>Raphanus sativus</em> L. Promote Fat Browning in 3T3-L1 Adipocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Obesity, a metabolic disorder resulting from an energy imbalance, often leads to excess fat and related diseases. Browning of white adipose tissue, which increases energy expenditure, is a promising anti-obesity strategy. Herbal medicines are considered safer than conventional drugs, but their fat browning mechanisms remain unclear. Therefore, this study aims to examine the effects of Coix lacryma-jobi L. and Raphanus sativus L., alongside their active compounds, coixol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing PROTAC Discovery Through Artificial Intelligence: Opportunities, Challenges, and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proteolysis Targeting Chimeras (PROTACs) represent a transformative modality in drug discovery, enabling the selective degradation of disease-relevant proteins through the ubiquitin proteasome system. Despite their therapeutic promise, the rational design of PROTACs remains a complex and resource-intensive process, involving multiple parameters such as target and ligase compatibility, ternary complex formation, linker optimization, and degradation efficiency. Recent advances in artificial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptome-Guided Drug Repurposing Identifies Homoharringtonine (HHT) as a Candidate for Radiation-Induced Pulmonary Fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Radiation-induced pulmonary fibrosis (RPF) remains a major burden of successful lung cancer radiotherapy. Clinically validated drugs targeting RPF remains scarce. Methods: We employed a transcriptome-based drug repurposing approach using REMEDY, a computational platform built on the Library of Integrated Network-Based Cellular Signatures (LINCS). Differentially expressed genes (DEGs) derived from radiation-induced lung injury (RILI) models were used as a query to identify compounds...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategic Combinations of Antibody-Drug Conjugates from 2023 to 2025: From Dual Therapies to Innovative ADC-Based Regimens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs) are a potent class of targeted cancer therapies that combine the specificity of monoclonal antibodies with the cytotoxic potency of chemotherapeutic agents. By targeting tumor cells with minimal impact on healthy tissues, ADCs achieve a favorable balance between efficacy and systemic toxicity. This therapeutic modality has demonstrated significant clinical success, as evidenced by the FDA approval of 15 ADCs by 2025, with one later withdrawn due to safety...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Senotherapeutic Potential of Araliadiol in Senescent Human Dermal Fibroblasts: An In Vitro Study Using Three Senescence Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: With the rapid aging of the global population, the interest in therapies for age-related diseases has increased substantially. The skin is particularly important, as aging-related changes are visible and negatively impact quality of life. Therefore, the identification of senotherapeutic candidates that are effective against skin aging is of considerable importance. Given the cost and reproducibility limitations of existing senescence models, this study established three...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valorization of Potato Peel Waste into Bioactive Compounds and Sustainable Bioplastics Production Through a Novel Biorefinery Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study deals with the successful exploitation of easily available and renewable potato peel waste (PPW) as an excellent feedstock in the production of PHA using Ralstonia eutropha. The process entailed the extraction of bioactive components from PPW by use of solvent-based procedures and screening of their antioxidant and antidiabetic activity. The extracted PPW biomass was subject to acid hydrolysis using different concentrations of sulfuric acid for hydrolysis and solubilization of sugar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical Behavior of Carbon-Fiber-Reinforced Polymer Composites (Towpreg) Under Various Temperature Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the hydrogen economy rapidly expands, carbon-fiber-reinforced polymer composites (Towpreg) have become key materials for next-generation hydrogen pressure vessels, offering superior processability, reproducibility, and storage stability compared to conventional wet-winding composites. Since hydrogen storage vessels are evaluated at three representative service temperatures (-40, 25, and 85 °C), Towpreg materials must maintain consistent mechanical performance across this range to meet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fish Consumption and the Risk of Depression: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis of Observational Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This systematic review and meta-analysis of observational studies aimed to assess the association between fish consumption and the risk of general and pregnancy-related depression, with implications for public health promotion. Methods: We retrieved 5074 articles from PubMed and Embase through November 2023 and included 35 observational studies in the analysis. We synthesized effect estimates as relative risks (RRs) with corresponding 95% confidence intervals (CIs) using a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioconversion-Based Postbiotics Enhance Muscle Strength and Modulate Gut Microbiota in Healthy Individuals: A Randomized, Double-Blind, Placebo-Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: KP supplementation produced a modest within-group improvement in grip strength, potentially through gut-muscle axis modulation involving irisin and anti-inflammation pathways. These preliminary findings suggest that kefir-derived postbiotics may have potential relevance for muscle health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iodine Intake and Risk of Mortality: Evidence from a Nationally Representative Korean Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Iodine intake influences thyroid-related and metabolic diseases that have important public health implications. However, longitudinal evidence of the association between iodine intake and mortality remains scarce and limited to Western populations. Given the markedly high iodine intake among Asians and possible ethnic or regional differences in iodine sensitivity, population-based data from Asian cohorts are needed. Methods: We analyzed 5497 adults from the Korean National...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Copper Oxide Nanoparticles on Adventitious Shoot Regeneration, Axillary Shoot Multiplication, Rooting, and Bioactive Compounds in <em>Ajuga multiflora</em> Bunge]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study investigated the effects of copper oxide nanoparticles (CuO NPs) at concentrations of 0, 5, 10, 20, and 40 mg/L on micropropagation and the accumulation of lipophilic metabolites in Ajuga multiflora, a medicinally valuable ornamental species. The highest number of adventitious shoots (29.4 shoots per explant) was obtained on the shoot induction medium with 5 mg/L CuO NPs. Shoot production gradually decreased at higher CuO NPs concentrations, falling to just 1.1 shoots per...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping Endangered Plant Distributions, Species Richness, and Climate Refugia Under SSP Climate Scenarios in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change significantly threatens the survival and distribution of endangered plants. This study quantified current and future patterns of habitat suitability and species richness for legally protected vascular plants in South Korea under two SSP climate scenarios. We modeled the distributions of 69 species designated as Class I or Class II endangered wild plants and evaluated in the Korean National Red List using IUCN criteria. Random Forest (RF) species distribution models were fitted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Channel-Free Micro-Well-Template-Assisted Magnetic Particle Trapping for Efficient Single-Particle Isolation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a channel-free, micro-well-template-assisted magnetic particle trapping method for efficient single-particle isolation without the need for microfluidic channels. Dual-surface silicon micro-well arrays were fabricated using photolithography, PE-CVD, and DRIE processes, featuring hydrophilic well interiors and hydrophobic outer surfaces to enhance trapping performance. The proposed method combines magnet-assisted sedimentation with rotational sweeping of a glass slide placed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Metal-Enhanced Fluorescence Nanorods on Micro Post Arrays for Portable Detection of Human Semen Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rapid and reliable on-site identification of body fluids is essential in forensic and field diagnostic applications. Commercial kits provide only single results and often suffer from cross-reactivity, while conventional microarrays offer multiplex capability but lack sufficient fluorescence intensity for field-deployable systems. In this study, we present a highly sensitive nanorods on micro post array (NMPA) substrate and a smartphone-based portable detection system. The NMPA substrate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simple Process for Flexible Light-Extracting QD Film and White OLED]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum dots (QDs) have tremendous potential for next-generation displays due to their high color purity, photoluminescence efficiency, and power efficiency. In this work, we present a simple and cost-effective method for fabricating flexible single- and multiple-layer films, and they can be detached and attached to the outside of OLEDs as a light-scattering and color-conversion layer. Light extraction efficiency is enhanced by forming low-density structures by using the reactive ion etching...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Process Optimization for Metal-Contact Etching in 3D Integration Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates a metal-contact etching process that differs from conventional device contact etching by focusing on the film-stack configuration and the associated super-contact etching characteristics. Because metal-contact etching is closely linked to both physical profiles and electrical performance, evaluating a single parameter provides limited insight; thus, the physical profile characteristics of metal-contact etching and 3D-integrated super-contacts were comprehensively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual Surfactant-Assisted Hydrothermal Engineering of Co<sub>3</sub>V<sub>2</sub>O<sub>8</sub> Nanostructures for High-Performance Asymmetric Supercapacitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a dual surfactant-assisted hydrothermal approach for the synthesis of Co(3)V(2)O(8) (CoVO) nanostructures and their surfactant-modified derivatives, PVP-assisted Co(3)V(2)O(8) (P-CoVO) and PVP-SDS co-assisted Co(3)V(2)O(8) (P/S-CoVO), which were directly grown on nickel foam. The use of PVP and SDS enabled controlled nucleation and growth, yielding a hierarchical nanoflower-like morphology in P/S-CoVO with increased porosity, a higher surface area, and uniform structural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication of Nanostructures on Surface of Micro-Lens Arrays Using Reactive Ion Etching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we fabricated a nanostructure on the surface of the micro-lens array (MLA), which is one of the light extraction technologies of organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs), by performing the Reactive Ion -Etching (RIE) process. The MLA consists of a lensed area and a lens-less bottom (flat film area). We performed a systematic analysis to find ways to improve the light extraction efficiency of the MLA surface and flat film area. By controlling the RIE process time and type of gas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selection of Base Materials for Repair Welding Using BWM-TOPSIS and BWM-RADAR Approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this paper, the selection of the optimal base material to be used in the repair welding process is presented. The aim of the study was to determine which of the available materials has the best characteristics, based on an analysis conducted in a company engaged in construction works. Three base materials were considered in the study: ABRADUR 58, E DUR 600, and CrWC 600 electrodes. Repair welding was performed on components for a construction machinery facility using the manual metal arc...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A handheld photoacoustic microscopic probe integrating a transparent ultrasound transducer and a fiber scanner]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoacoustic microscopy (PAM) has been widely used in biomedical studies to provide high-resolution 3D anatomical, functional, and molecular images of living subjects. While handheld PAM systems have been proposed to extend its applicability, it has proved challenging to achieve a compact device that combines fast imaging with high spatial resolution and signal to noise ratio. Here we demonstrate a handheld PAM probe integrating a fiber scanner and high-frequency transparent ultrasound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lessons from Failed Attempts of Computationally Guided Synthesis of Aluminosilicate STF and IFR Zeolites in Hydroxide Media]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although zeolites are primarily aluminosilicates in terms of chemical composition, not all zeotypes have been successfully synthesized as aluminosilicates to date. This study aims to contribute answering the long-standing question of why some zeotypes cannot, or have not yet been, synthesized as aluminosilicates, using a computational approach that combines big data, artificial intelligence, accurate descriptors, and an algorithm for designing quaternary ammonium organic structure-directing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Constructing High-Performance Solar Cells by Incorporating an A1-A2-Type Polymer Donor as a Guest Material]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Owing to the intramolecular push-pull electron effect between the electron donor (D) unit and electron acceptor (A) unit, the D-A type based polymer donors display outstanding device performance. However, the imperfect energy levels lead to the D-A-type-based polymer device exhibiting high voltage loss. In this study, an A1-A2-type copolymer M1 was developed with 1,3-bis(2-ethylhexyl)-5,7-di(thiophen-2-yl)benzo[1,2-c:4,5-c']dithiophene-4,8-dione (BDD) as the A1 unit and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MIRA: A Transformer-Based Framework for Idler Roller Anomaly Detection and Localization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monitoring the condition of belt conveyor idlers is critical for ensuring safe and efficient operation of industrial conveying systems. However, existing methods often suffer from limited scalability and delayed fault detection, particularly under variable environmental conditions. In this work, we propose MIRA, a transformer-based framework for monitoring idler roller anomalies, which detects and localizes faults using acoustic and vibration signals collected from low-cost sensors. MIRA employs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surface Passivation with Lattice-Matched Bidentate Ligand Enabling High-Performance Perovskite Quantum Dot Photodetectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface halide vacancies are prevalent on lead halide perovskite (LHP) quantum dots (QDs) due to their intrinsically low formation energy, and they serve as dominant non-radiative recombination centers that degrade optoelectronic performance. While ligand exchange has been commonly used to mitigate these surface defects, the influence of multidentate ligand geometry on binding interactions with QD surfaces remains largely unexplored. In this study, we demonstrate that controlling the spatial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Field Emission Control via Work Function Modulation in Semimetallic Graphene Edge Cathodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graphene, the bandgapless 2D crystal, uniquely combines metal-like conductivity with an electrostatically tunable Fermi level-an ability that conventional metals lack. Here, we exploit this semimetallic property to realize a vacuum edge emitter whose current can be directly modulated through work function control rather than relying on vacuum-channel field reshaping. We demonstrate a graphene edge-emitter nanoscale vacuum transistor with an off-channel gate, enabling spatial separation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discrepancy in perceived appropriate and desired resuscitation durations between physicians and laypersons in cardiac arrest patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined a discrepancy that exists between the duration of resuscitative efforts that physicians perceive as appropriate and the duration that laypersons desire. We conducted an online nationwide cross-sectional survey with 323 physicians and 2,667 laypersons. Physicians were significantly more likely than laypersons to consider a duration of ≥ 30 min as appropriate for resuscitation, especially in younger patients (age 0-6:85% vs. 27%; age 7-17:84% vs. 29%; both p < 0.001). Although...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coordinated regional association of cathepsins and dipeptidyl peptidases with N-truncated Abeta42, Abeta40, and tau in Alzheimer's brain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Regional distributions of amyloid-β (Aβ) and tau accumulation have provided important insights into the pathomechanisms of Alzheimer's disease (AD). While such analyses have typically been conducted through histochemical or clinical imaging studies, we previously reported unique regional associations among Aβ species, tau and other proteins by biochemically analyzing multiple postmortem brain regions. Here, using a new cohort and novel ELISAs, we investigated the regional relationships of Aβ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pluripotent epigenetic regulator OBP-801 attenuates fibrosis and maintains lower intraocular pressure in a rabbit PRESERFLO MicroShunt surgery model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The inhibition of fibrosis in filtering blebs is indispensable for lowering intraocular pressure (IOP) after PRESERFLO MicroShunt surgery (PMS). We previously reported the anti-fibrotic effect of OBP-801 (OBP) on a filtering bleb in a rabbit glaucoma filtration surgery model using a 22-gauge cannula. In this study, we investigated the effect of OBP after PMS in rabbit eyes for the development of a new practically applicable anti-fibrotic treatment. This study involved 19 Japanese white rabbits...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Position-independent emergence of neocortical neuron molecular identity, connectivity and function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brain architectures vary widely across species, yet how neuronal positioning constrains the type of circuits that can be made, and their function, remains poorly understood. Here we examine how neuronal position affects molecular identity, connectivity and function by studying Eml1 knockout mice, which exhibit abnormally located (heterotopic) neurons beneath the cortex. Heterotopic neurons maintained their molecular signatures, formed appropriate long-range connections and exhibited coherent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41476107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Whole-Body Pattern of Muscle Degeneration and Progression in Sarcoglycanopathies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: To characterize whole-body intramuscular fat distribution pattern in patients with sarcoglycanopathies and explore correlations with disease severity, duration and age at onset.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is the role of plant-based alternatives to animal foods in the Great Food Transformation? A narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several plant-based alternatives to animal foods (PBAFs) have been introduced in the market in the past decade to provide consumers with an easy substitution for animal protein. Despite the extensive literature on the nutritional composition of these plant-based products, these products must be assessed considering their impacts on diets, the environment and society. This critical review aims to evaluate the role of plant-based alternatives to animal foods in the Great Food Transformation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasound as a non-invasive diagnostic tool to detect deep endometriosis using the International Deep Endometriosis Analysis terminology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Non-invasive diagnosis of DE with TVS performed in accordance with the IDEA consensus statement has a high diagnostic accuracy. Implementation of the IDEA methodology in daily gynecological practice has the potential to shorten the diagnostic delay and expedite treatment strategies. Accurate DE mapping may improve triaging referral of patients, trigger a multidisciplinary team and potentially mitigates operative risks, resulting in a reduced financial burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of challenges in up-scaling in-situ biomethanation in wastewater treatment plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In-situ biomethanation is a promising technology for buffering fluctuations in renewable energy supply and renewable methane production. This study aimed to evaluate two key challenges in scaling up in-situ biomethanation: (1) struvite precipitation, which can cause blockages in sludge pipelines as a serious issue for digesters, and (2) hydrogen conversion behavior under varying hydrogen injection rates, water pressures, and digestate viscosities. Experiments were conducted using a 2-m³ pilot...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced graphene oxide enhances emerging contaminants removal in anaerobic wastewater treatment: Synergistic role of adsorption and microbial metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Certain persistent emerging contaminants (ECs) exhibit low removal efficiency during anaerobic digestion (AD), strategies to enhance the ECs removal have attracted widespread attention. We evaluated the removal efficiency of 14 typical ECs during the AD process, and investigated an enhancement strategy through the addition of reduced graphene oxide (rGO). The average removal efficiency of ECs was only 50.9 ± 1.1 % due to the poor removal efficiency of ECs containing amino, tertiary amide and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune profiling of human blood cells after indirect exposure to crystalline silica particles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Occupational exposure to respirable crystalline silica (RCS) is a significant health concern associated with pulmonary and systemic diseases, mediated in part through lung macrophage toxicity. In this study, we employed an ex vivo indirect exposure model, to explore potential links between silica-induced macrophage toxicity and changes in innate and adaptive immune cell phenotypes, that may contribute to systemic effects of RCS. THP-1 derived macrophages served as a macrophage model and were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Paradoxical worsening on olorofim in patients undergoing treatment for invasive fungal diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Paradoxical reactions to appropriate antimicrobial therapy are infrequently observed in systemic fungal diseases. Similar responses are seen in the treatment of both tuberculosis (TB) (worsening of lymphadenitis) and leprosy (reversal reactions) suggesting a similar pathophysiologic mechanism may be responsible given the overlapping immune response between mycobacterial and fungal pathogens. Awareness of this potential syndrome is essential during the treatment of patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can the <sup>13</sup>C-octanoic acid breath test accurately measure gastric emptying after sleeve gastrectomy and Roux-en-Y gastric bypass? A proof-of concept analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This proof-of-concept analysis suggests that the 13C-octanoic acid breath test has potential as a valid, non-invasive method for assessing gastric emptying in post-bariatric surgery patients. However, larger validation studies are warranted to confirm these preliminary findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An In Silico Platform for 3D Ultrasound and Collateral Ligament Mechanics to Validate 3D Speckle Tracking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed framework accurately quantifies ligament strains derived from three-dimensional ultrasound and provides a controlled environment for developing and benchmarking speckle-tracking methods. By linking realistic biomechanics to ultrasound image formation, it enables standardized evaluation before cadaveric and clinical studies and supports translation of three-dimensional ultrasound strain mapping to intra-operative and longitudinal assessments of soft-tissue balance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical safety of ultra-high-dose methylcobalamin in patients with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis: Open-label extension of a phase 2/3 randomized controlled study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: There were no particular safety issues as reported in the phase 2/3 study and no clear deterioration in survival rate or physical function when ultra-high-dose methylcobalamin was administered intramuscularly in patients with advanced ALS. This regimen could be a candidate for initial therapy with further add-on to overcome ALS in the future.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between electrographic seizures and better neurological functional outcomes in non-convulsive status epilepticus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: NCSE with ESz was associated with better functional outcomes than RPPs alone. Spared alpha-band background activity and larger amplitude of post-discharge slow shifts may indicate spared brain function in patients with PDs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term recurrence patterns in rectal cancer after neoadjuvant therapy: 25-years of real-world data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Histopathological features and tumor response to neoadjuvant therapy are strong predictors of recurrence risk in rectal cancer. Identifying reliable baseline biomarkers of treatment response is essential to refine patient risk stratification and personalize neoadjuvant treatment strategies in the TNT era.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41475046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-specific DNA methylation alterations in sperm at imprint control regions may contribute to the risk of autism spectrum disorder in offspring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Research findings suggest that advanced paternal age is associated with an increased risk of autism spectrum disorder (ASD) in children. The biological process behind this father-to-child inheritance of a disease may be driven by sperm epigenetic marks. This has been suggested earlier, but the identification of epigenomic regions responsible for these age-related responses have not been further elaborated. To identify sperm-specific marks, we conducted an epigenome-wide association study in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Initial experience with a novel device for supporting a debilitated patient during total skin electron beam therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Total skin electron beam therapy (TSET) is the specialized and effective therapy for mycosis fungoides and Sézary syndrome. The Stanford TSET technique, which is the one most often used, requires the patient to remain standing for an extended time. Here, we report on the invention of a device to assist in patient positioning for TSET and how the device is used in clinical care. Our novel device comprises supports for the patient's head and upper limbs plus a bicycle-style saddle seat. We used...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multicompartmental analysis of microbiome alterations under radiation stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual attachment of the buccinator muscle at the pterygoid hamulus: implications for pterygoid implant surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study revealed a dual attachment of the buccinator muscle to the pterygoid hamulus and emphasized its close proximity to the maxillary tuberosity. Additionally, low BV/TV values in some specimens highlight the anatomical variability of this region. Understanding individual differences in bone structure and the precise location of soft tissue attachments is essential for safer and more predictable pterygoid implant placement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunable Charge Transport Properties Through Precise π-Stacking Modulation in Isostructural Porous Molecular Conductors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the structure-property relationships in electrically conductive metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) is critical for their rational design toward practical applications. Since single crystals of MOFs with through-space conductive π-stacked columnar structures are relatively easy to obtain, their structures can be determined with high accuracy. However, elucidating those structure-property relationships without interference from carrier scattering and variations in carrier concentration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fast-Ion-Conductor Multiscale Nanoconfinement Overcomes Ion-Transport Limitations in All-Solid-State Sodium Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Composite polymer electrolytes (CPEs) hold significant potential for high-performance all-solid-state sodium batteries, yet their development remains hindered by compromised ionic transport kinetics arising from limited conduction pathways and strong Na^(+) coordination. Here, we report a fast-ion-conductor multiscale nanoconfinement strategy that enables continuous high-throughput Na^(+) migration in CPEs by embedding polyethylene glycol (PEG)-confined boron-rich covalent organic framework...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PEX14 powers OPTN (optineurin) to drive peroxisome turnover]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cells maintain organelle integrity and metabolic balance through tightly coordinated quality control systems. Autophagy plays a central role by recycling damaged and unnecessary cellular components, with selective pathways providing specificity through dedicated receptors. Although OPTN is well-established as a receptor for mitophagy, aggrephagy, and xenophagy, its role in pexophagy, the selective autophagic degradation of peroxisomes, has only recently been recognized. Our recent work...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asymmetric synthesis of (+)-gomadalactones A and (-)-B: contact sex pheromones of white-spotted longicorn beetle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The white-spotted longicorn beetle (Anoplophora malasiaca), a serious fruit tree pest, relies on contact sex pheromones for mating purposes. The asymmetric synthesis of the pheromonal components, (+)-gomadalactones A and (-)-B, was achieved using an improved enantioselective version of our previous racemic synthesis method. The key 3-oxabicyclo[3.3.0]octane framework was constructed using a combination of Vassilikogiannakis one-pot, photodriven cyclopentenone synthesis with DBU-mediated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of hemophilia B treatment via population PK modeling of rIX-FP, including a 3-week regimen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: rIX-FP supports individualized prophylaxis with extended intervals up to 3 weeks in patients ≥12 years while younger children typically require more frequent dosing due to higher weight-normalized clearance. These PK-based insights can guide shared decision-making to balance protection, treatment burden, and patient preference across pediatric and adolescent age groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moving the Fine Print to the Front Page: Transparent Communication of Facial Genetics Research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AI-enabled facial genetics research has transformative potential for biomedical and forensic applications, but raises serious ethical, legal, and social challenges. Candor and clarity promote the advancement of science and facilitate the development of evidence-informed and ethically sound policy guardrails for scientific applications. Expanding upon our recent Comment on Difface, here we examine some of the ethical dimensions of AI-enabled facial genetics research, illuminate a lack of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum human chorionic gonadotropin can predict live birth 7 days after frozen-thawed blastocyst transfer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We determined the hCG cutoff values for live births after frozen-thawed blastocyst transfer. We suggest that it is possible to predict pregnancy outcomes as early as the 7th or 8th day after frozen-thawed blastocyst transfer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diaphragmatic curvature analysis using dynamic digital radiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The value of ΔAUD was smaller according to the severity of COPD. ΔAUD can be helpful in distinguishing healthy subjects from COPD patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260101024209&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>