<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 07:36:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene editing in cancer therapy: overcoming drug resistance and enhancing precision medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The CRISPR system has revolutionized cancer gene therapy, offering unparalleled precision in genetic manipulation for targeted oncogene disruption, mutation correction, and immune system modulation. This breakthrough tool has demonstrated remarkable potential in overcoming drug resistance, enhancing chemotherapy sensitivity, and improving immunotherapy strategies such as CRISPR-engineered CAR-T cells. Additionally, oncolytic virus-mediated CRISPR delivery has emerged as a novel approach for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GPU-accelerated homology search with MMseqs2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rapidly growing protein databases demand faster sensitive search tools. Here the graphics processing unit (GPU)-accelerated MMseqs2 delivers 6× faster single-protein searches than CPU methods on 2 × 64 cores, speeds previously requiring large protein batches. For larger query batches, it is the most cost-effective solution, outperforming the fastest alternative method by 2.4-fold with eight GPUs. It accelerates protein structure prediction with ColabFold 31.8× over the standard AlphaFold2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disparities in Physical Function and Rehabilitation Utilization: A Cross-sectional Study of Patients Hospitalized for Acute Medical Illness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this study of patients hospitalized at a large urban academic medical center, Black patients had poorer functional outcomes yet nearly half the likelihood of discharging to a post-acute care facility compared to White patients. Race was a more consistent driver of disparities than neighborhood disadvantage. Hospital, healthcare system, and public policy changes are needed to improve discharge location appropriateness and recovery after hospitalization for vulnerable patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early experience with next-generation wireless technology for detecting cochlear implant electrode tip fold-over and placement without X-ray: nucleus SmartNav]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SmartNav offers a highly sensitive and reliable method for detecting TFO during CI at least in normal cochlear anatomy, dramatically reducing the need for intraoperative X-ray, thereby decreasing anesthesia time and eliminating radiation exposure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ret finger protein deficiency attenuates adipogenesis in male mice with high fat diet-induced obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ret finger protein (RFP, also known as TRIM27) is a multifunctional E3 ubiquitin ligase implicated in transcriptional regulation. While previously reported to repress myogenesis, its role in adipose tissue metabolism remains unclear. Here, using both global and adipocyte-specific RFP-knockout male mice subjected to high-fat diet feeding, we found that RFP deficiency markedly attenuated body weight gain, adipose tissue expansion and adipocyte hypertrophy, while improving glucose tolerance,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brazilein Impedes IKK Activation by Disrupting RIPK1 Polyubiquitination, Increasing Apoptotic Susceptibility in Cells with Constitutively Active NF-κ]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ubiquitination of RIPK1 serves as a critical regulatory switch in determining the outcome of prosurvival NF-κB signaling by linking the TNFR1 signaling complex to upstream IKK activation. Therefore, identifying bioactive compounds that modulate RIPK1 ubiquitination has emerged as a promising strategy to enhance the therapeutic efficacy of TNF, particularly in cancers with constitutively active NF-κB signaling. In our previous in vitro phytochemical study, we demonstrated that brazilin, isolated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Suboptimal Graft Function at 1 Month Post-Transplantation on Long-Term Outcomes in Living Donor Kidney Transplant Recipients: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Suboptimal graft function at 1-month post-transplantation is associated with increased acute rejection but does not independently predict inferior long-term graft or patient survival. These findings suggest that long-term outcomes can be preserved despite suboptimal functional recovery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated and Programmable Cell-Free Systems for Scalable Synthetic Biology with a Focus on Biofoundry Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell-free protein synthesis (CFPS) has been used as a transformative technology in synthetic biology, providing a programmable, scalable, and automation-compatible platform for biological engineering. Freed from the limitations of cell viability and growth, CFPS enables rapid design iteration, precise control of reaction conditions, and high-throughput experimentation. Recent integration of CFPS with biofoundries-automated, high-throughput biological engineering platforms-has dramatically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Production of Recombinant S1 Protein of Porcine Epidemic Diarrhea Virus in Recombinant CHO Cells for Application in Indirect ELISA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The N-terminal S1 subunit of the spike protein (S1 protein) of porcine epidemic diarrhea virus (PEDV) is recognized as a potential diagnostic antigen for detecting anti-PEDV immunoglobulin A (IgA) levels in colostrum, a key indicator for assessing passive immunity against PEDV infection. Given the advantages of producing Fc-fusion proteins in mammalian cells, it is important to investigate how the addition of the Fc region affects the diagnostic performance of the PEDV-S1 protein. In this study,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Film-forming system of optimized tacrolimus-loaded nanostructured lipid carriers for effective topical treatment of atopic dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tacrolimus (TAC), a calcineurin inhibitor used topically for T-cell-mediated skin diseases, faces challenges due to poor solubility and limited skin penetration. To address these limitations, a film-forming system (FFS) incorporating nanostructured lipid carriers (NLCs) was developed for enhanced topical delivery. TAC-loaded NLCs (TAC-NLC) were prepared via high-temperature and high-pressure homogenization and optimized using Box-Behnken design. The optimized TAC-NLC showed 102.7 nm particle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening developmental (neuro)toxicity of biocides in zebrafish embryos identifies synergistic and antagonistic neurotoxic effects of biocide mixtures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exposure to various biocides is a major concern due to their adverse effects on humans and other organisms. However, information on the developmental (neuro)toxicity effects of biocides, particularly that of biocide mixtures, remains elusive. In this study, we evaluated the developmental (neuro)toxicity of 74 individual biocides and 30 mixtures derived from them using a zebrafish embryonic model. Neurobehavioral analyses were conducted at sublethal concentrations, and behavioral disorders were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcutaneous Auricular Vagus Nerve Stimulation for Functional Dyspepsia: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Considering the certainty of the evidence, taVNS can improve dyspepsia symptoms, quality of life, anxiety, and depression in patients with FD without serious adverse events. Additional high-quality studies are needed to establish optimal treatment protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature-Induced Interfacial Intermixing and Trap Modulation in ONO-Based Flash Memory Capacitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigated the effects of hydrogen annealing on the electrical properties and reliability of NAND flash memory capacitors featuring an oxide-nitride-oxide charge-trap dielectric stack. A thin interfacial SiOxNy transition layer, inherently formed between SiO2 and Si3N4 during processing, was analyzed for compositional and structural changes across annealing temperatures from 300-500 °C. Key electrical characteristics-including capacitance-voltage behavior, programming speed, data retention,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying predictive markers of head and neck squamous cell carcinoma in an umbrella trial (KCSG HN 15-16 TRIUMPH trial)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Genomic profiling plays a significant role in the management of recurrent or metastatic HNSCC and may help identify potential targets for precision therapeutics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone morphogenetic protein-mediated Ventx3.2 regulates mesendoderm patterning and gut morphogenesis during Xenopus embryogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bone morphogenetic protein (BMP) signaling plays a pivotal role in germ layer specification and organogenesis during vertebrate development. In Xenopus laevis, BMP signaling activates the Ventx family of homeobox transcription factors, which are essential regulators of mesodermal and endodermal (mesendoderm) fate. Within the Ventx family members, the specific role of Ventx3.2 in mesendoderm development and organogenesis remains poorly defined. Here, we elucidate the role of Ventx3.2 using gain-...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photothermal Annealing-Enabled Millisecond Synthesis of Carbon Nanoonions and Simultaneous Single-Atom Functionalization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbon nanoonions (CNOs), known for their nanometer-scale surface curvature and potential for versatile functionalization, are widely used in energy and environmental applications. However, they face challenges from energy-intensive synthesis and time-consuming post-treatments, resulting in low yields and poor-quality sp² shells, which limit their commercial viability. In this study, we introduce a direct-contact annealing (DCA) platform reaching up to 3030 K within 1.4 ms (2.2 × 10⁶ K s^(-1)),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Balancing Cell Growth and Product Synthesis for Efficient Microbial Cell Factories]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The sustainable, bio-based production of industrially valuable chemicals and materials from renewable, non-edible biomass through biorefineries has emerged as a vital strategy for tackling urgent global challenges, including climate change, and for realizing the "net zero carbon" commitments recently pledged by nations worldwide. Metabolic engineering has played a central role in enabling the development of microbial strains capable of efficiently overproducing a diverse array of target...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stress-induced preference for antioxidants by <em>Drosophila</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In an ever-changing environment, animals make optimal decisions to ensure their well-being. Faced with limited food sources, they often seek foods that provide the nutrients they require to maintain homeostasis. Under extreme circumstances (e.g., infection), they may exhibit ingestive behaviors, such as seeking out substances (e.g., toxins) that suggest self-medication. Few studies, however, have investigated the mechanisms that ensue self-medication. Here, we report the selective intake of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tail-Group Modulated Covalent Functionalization of Solvent-Dispersible MXenes for Selectivity-Tunable Gas Sensing at Room Temperature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The advancement of highly selective and sensitive gas sensors is essential for various fields, and MXene has emerged as a strong candidate for chemiresistive gas sensing due to its high electrical conductivity, tunable surface chemistry, and ability to operate at room temperature. This study demonstrates a versatile strategy for covalently functionalizing Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXenes using diazonium salts with diverse tail groups, enabling tunable gas selectivity. By systematically modulating surface...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Force-Induced Selective Carbon-Carbon Bond Cleavage in Mechanoresponsive Topochemical Polymers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mechanoresponsive polymeric materials that respond to mechanical deformation are highly valued for their potential in sensors, degradation studies, and optoelectronics. However, direct visualization and detection of these responses remain significant obstacles. In this study, novel mechanoresponsive polybiidenedionediyl (PBIT) derivative topochemical polymers are developed that depolymerize under mechanical forces, exhibiting a distinct and irreversible color change in response to grinding,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-Synthetic Functionalization of Covalent Organic Frameworks for Highly Sensitive and Selective Detection of Plasticizers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here in, The nanoporous COF was synthesized by using 2-hydroxy-1,3,5-benzenetricarbaldehyde (BTC) and 2,5-diamino-1,4-benzenedithiol (2,5-DABT) under solvothermal conditions. The resulting COF features hydroxy groups from BTC selectively modified with longer octyl chains to impart hydrophobicity, while pendant thiol groups from 2,5-DABT anchor plasmonic silver (Ag) nanoparticles, yielding a superhydrophobic nanoporous material (denoted as Octyl-COF-SH@Ag). Indeed, the resultant Octyl-COF-SH@Ag...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ApoE deficiency protects from mRNA vaccine-induced mitochondrial dysfunction at the injection site under metabolic stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rationale: The local tissue effects of mRNA vaccination remain incompletely understood. We investigated how SARS-CoV-2 mRNA vaccination impacts injection site tissues in the context of different metabolic states and apolipoprotein E (ApoE) status. Methods: We administered intramuscular SARS-CoV-2 mRNA vaccination to wild-type and ApoE-deficient mice under regular and high-fat diets, as well as macaques. We performed transcriptomic analysis, ultrastructural examination, functional assessments...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250919033546&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-function robotic gripper for traction and closure in gastric endoscopic submucosal dissection: an in vivo porcine model study (with video)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The robotic dual-function gripper significantly enhanced technical performance and mucosal healing in gastric ESD within a porcine model, suggesting its potential as an effective adjunct for gastric therapeutic endoscopy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of minimally invasive distal pancreatectomy in patients with a history of major upper abdominal surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MIDP appears to be a safe and feasible option for selected patients with PUAS, including major procedures, without significantly increasing the risks of severe complications or conversion to open surgery. These findings support the broader use of MIDP in patients with complex surgical histories.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of One-Year auditory rehabilitation outcomes by etiology in pediatric patients with bilateral severe hearing loss (70-90 dB): enlarged vestibular aqueduct vs. Other causes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Children with EVA may achieve superior short-term language outcomes with hearing aids, potentially due to a third window-related hidden air-bone gap. However, given the progressive nature of EVA, long-term follow-up is required to assess articulation development and determine optimal timing for cochlear implantation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Birthweight, height, and body mass index in relation to the expression of stem cell markers among women with benign breast biopsies in the Nurses' Health Study II]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adiposity measures may be associated with stem cell marker expression among cancer-free women.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spine surgery for metastatic spine cancer in the era of advanced radiation therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metastatic spine cancer (MSC), a common complication of advanced malignancies, poses significant challenges due to pain, neurological deficits, and mechanical instability. While radiation therapy is a cornerstone of treatment, the role of spine surgery is evolving, fueled by advances in surgical techniques and radiation modalities such as stereotactic body radiation therapy (SBRT). This review examines the evolving role of spine surgery in MSC management, focusing on separation surgery, surgical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of circulating c-reactive protein levels with central Alzheimer's disease biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study revealed differential associations between circulating CRP levels and central AD biomarkers that varied according to the CRP concentration. Further studies are necessary to elucidate the mechanisms underlying the inverse relationship between circulating CRP and brain Aβ within the clinically normal range, as well as potential aggravating effects of elevated CRP on Aβ-independent neurodegeneration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carotenoid-Producing <em>Qipengyuania algicola</em> sp. nov. and <em>Qipengyuania rhodophyticola</em> sp. nov., Isolated from Marine Algae, and Emended Description of the Genus <em>Qipengyuania</em> Xu <em>et al</em>. 2020]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two Gram-stain-negative, facultatively aerobic, non-motile, catalase- and oxidase-positive, rod-shaped bacteria, designated strains DGS2-2^(T) (orange-pigmented) and DGS5-3^(T) (yellow-pigmented), were isolated from marine red algae collected in Korea. Strain DGS2-2^(T) grew at 20-40°C, pH 6.0-10.0, and in 1.0-6.0% (w/v) NaCl, while DGS5-3^(T) grew at 15-40°C, pH 6.0-10.0, and in 2.0-6.0% NaCl. Ubiquinone-10 was the sole respiratory quinone. The G+C contents were 62.5% for DGS2-2^(T) and 57.5%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Anaerobic Biodegradation and Biomethane Production from Bioplastics by the Addition of Aerobically Prepared Triacylglycerol Lipase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to overcome the limited biodegradability of bioplastics under anaerobic conditions. With polycaprolactone (PCL) as a model system, the effect of a bioplastic-degrading enzyme, triacylglycerol lipase (TGL), on its degradation and biomethane production was investigated. As the PCL film did not show evidence of any degradation over 14 days under anaerobic conditions in the sludge, TGL from Bacillus sp. JY35 was added to promote PCL breakdown into its monomeric form, which could be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suicide methods among adolescents and adults in Korea, 1997-2021: an issue of accessibility and awareness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The decline in pesticide-related suicides demonstrates the effectiveness of paraquat restrictions. In contrast, the dramatic rise in suicides involving gases and vapours suggests the influence of media reporting. The increase in drug-related suicides may be attributed to greater availability and access to psychiatric medications. The high rate of suicides by falls among adolescents likely reflects the higher impulsivity of this age group. In addition, the rise in adolescent suicides...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-based assessment of Clinical Activity Score and detection of active thyroid eye disease using facial images: validation of Glandy CAS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Glandy CAS, an ML-assisted system for detecting active TED using facial images, showed high accuracy and outperformed general ophthalmologists. This system can consistently and accurately assess disease activity, facilitating early detection and timely treatment of active TED. Based on this clinical trial, the SaMD received KMFDS approval (Product Licence No., 24-93).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in perceived neighborhood environments by COVID-19: A nationwide Korean survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacological Research - Perspective Natural Products, Artificial Intelligence, and the Future of Anti-Aging Pharmacology: A Human-Centered Call to Action]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging is increasingly recognized as a process driven by oxidative stress, chronic inflammation, mitochondrial decline, and impaired autophagy. Natural products provide a rich source of antioxidants and autophagy modulators that can counteract these hallmarks of aging, yet their translation into effective interventions has been slow. Recent advances in artificial intelligence (AI), omics and bioinformatic technologies now enable the systematic identification of active compounds, prediction of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ARABIDOPSIS NITRATE REGULATED 1 negatively regulates the tolerance of salt stress by controlling ion homeostasis and GA metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previous studies have linked nitrate uptake regulation in plants to salt stress tolerance. Building on this, our study aimed to investigate the role of the ANR1 gene, involved in nitrate sensing and signaling, in salt stress response using anr1 knock-down plants. Our results showed that anr1 plants exhibited improved tolerance to salt stress compared to Col-0, with better root length, biomass, and chlorophyll content. Under salt stress, anr1 plants accumulated less reactive oxygen species (ROS)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-driven pupillary-computer interface via binary-coded flickering stimuli]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pupillary-computer interface (PCI) refers to a novel interaction modality that leverages pupil size variations elicited by changes in visual stimulus brightness. The PCI based on the pupillary light reflex (PLR) induced by binary-coded visual stimuli was proposed. A novel PCI interface was devised to overcome the limitations of conventional electroencephalogram hardware, using artificial intelligence to model subtle pupil signal patterns induced by visual stimuli. The proposed PCI system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequence variability of the K1 gene in Kaposi's sarcoma-associated herpesvirus and its role in pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infectious pathogens account for approximately 13% of all human cancers globally, with oncogenic viruses constituting the majority. Among them, Kaposi's sarcoma-associated herpesvirus (KSHV), a gammaherpesvirus, remains a persistent public health concern. Although KSHV is endemic in sub-Saharan Africa, where it drives high rates of pediatric and endemic Kaposi's sarcoma (KS), AIDS-related KS remains a significant burden among immunocompromised individuals, especially in areas with limited access...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient degradation of Amoxicillin in contaminated water using a dielectric barrier discharge throughput reactor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amoxicillin (Amx) is an emerging pollutant that is inadequately degraded by conventional wastewater treatment systems, posing significant risks to microbial populations and the environment. This study employed a dielectric barrier discharge throughput reactor to enhance Amx degradation. Optimal degradation occurred at an airflow rate of 1 lpm and a solution flow rate of 0.2 lpm, achieving a degradation rate of 0.07302 min^(-1), as determined by ultraviolet-visible spectroscopy. Raman and Fourier...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of potential therapeutic targets for problematic alcohol use using multi-omics data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Problematic alcohol use (PAU) is a serious global health issue with limited treatment options. Although genetic studies have identified genomic regions associated with PAU, the specific causal genes and proteins remain unclear. This study aimed to identify these causal genes by integrating diverse genetic and molecular data to inform better treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triggering mitotic catastrophe by podophyllotoxin induces apoptosis in oral squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides compelling evidence supporting the potential therapeutic significance of inducing MC-mediated apoptosis in OSCC. The results underscore the role of PPT and its derivatives, such as etoposide and teniposide, in targeting rapidly dividing cancer cells through interference with mitotic progression, offering insights into novel therapeutic strategies for oral cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of Pharmacokinetics and Comparison Between One-point versus Two-point Sampling for Therapeutic Drug Monitoring of Vancomycin in Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AUC-based vancomycin dosing was associated with a reduced incidence of AKI in pediatric patients, without compromising efficacy. Further studies are warranted to refine the exposure targets for bacteremia resolution.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Antibiotic Use for Pediatric Patients With Pneumonia: A Nationwide Analysis in South Korea (2016-2023)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among children in South Korea diagnosed with bacterial pneumonia, macrolides were most frequently prescribed, and prescriptions for third-generation cephalosporins showed an increasing trend. These findings underscore challenges in antimicrobial stewardship and need for strengthened nationwide antimicrobial stewardship policies for pediatric pneumonia tailored to age, setting, and seasonal trends.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exposure to Radiation and Thyroid Cancer Risk Among Young Female Nurses: Longitudinal Analysis From the Korea Nurses' Health Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Younger age, night shift work, and duration of radiation exposure were significantly associated with an increased risk of thyroid cancer in young female nurses. These findings highlight the importance of early screening and occupational risk management, including regular radiation monitoring and support for circadian health, in health care settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioresponsive Nucleic Acid Base Pair-Inspired Nanogels for Codelivery of Chemo-/Protein Drugs in Targeted Cancer Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Codelivery of chemo- and protein drugs enhances efficacy but faces challenges from physicochemical differences and inefficient release. We fabricated dual-responsive and tumor-targeting nucleic acid base-inspired nanogels (DTNANGs) for the in vivo codelivery of gemcitabine (Gem) and cytochrome C (CC). The nanogels were engineered through pH-sensitive base-pairing cross-linking between guanine- and cytosine-modified hyaluronic acid derivatives. DTNANGs achieved high drug-loading efficiency (96.3%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Promoter-proximal transcription-translation coupling controls early transcription in Escherichia coli]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The functional coupling of transcription and translation contributes significantly to maintaining messenger RNA (mRNA) expression in bacterial cells. Premature transcription termination and fast mRNA decay are known to limit the expression of mRNAs when transcription is decoupled from translation. Here, we report that inhibiting the generation of untranslatable mRNAs from the promoter-proximal region is a newly identified but essential pathway of mRNA quality control by transcription-translation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The contrast between monovalent and multivalent metal battery anodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monovalent (lithium, sodium, potassium) and multivalent (magnesium, calcium, aluminum) metal anodes are promising alternatives to graphite anodes for overcoming the performance limitations of lithium-ion batteries. In this Review, we compare and contrast their electrochemical behaviors in nonaqueous electrolytes by discussing their common challenges of irregular metal deposition and unstable solid electrolyte interphases (SEIs), as well as their differences, which are due to dissimilar surface...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary Inflammatory Potential and Chronic Kidney Disease Risk: Exploring the Mediation Effects of Circulating Proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The association between the DII and incident CKD risk may be partly mediated by alterations in circulating protein profiles involving TNF receptor superfamily-related pathways and plasma omega-3 fatty acids. Dietary counseling aimed at lowering the consumption of sugar-rich and high-fat dairy products may be beneficial.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Neutropenia on Clinical Outcomes in Critically Ill Patients with Acute Respiratory Failure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Neutropenia at ICU admission is independently associated with increased mortality in patients with ARF, particularly among those without cancer. SOFA score is a strong prognostic indicator among patients with neutropenia. These findings highlight the need for improved risk stratification, and suggest that patients with neutropenia may benefit from specific management strategies, which should be investigated in future studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Father's Parenting and Child Self-Control: A Comparison Between the Netherlands and South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parents from different cultures may employ different parenting behaviors to support children's development. It remains unclear whether the associations of parental warmth and control with self-control abilities vary across cultures. Moreover, little is known about how these associations may differ for father' parenting behaviors. We investigated the associations of paternal warmth and control with children's self-control problems using data from the Netherlands and South Korea. Data came from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prefrontal cortex hypoactivation in response to sleep-related pictures in shift workers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shift work can lead to mental health issues such as sleep disturbances and cognitive impairment. Neural activation in response to external sleep-related stimuli may vary according to shift work patterns. In this study, we investigated the differences in brain activity in response to sleep-related stimuli between shift-worker (SW) nurses and healthy controls (HCs), and we also assessed the relationships between sleep-related problems and brain activity. The hypothesis was that shift workers would...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Middle Ear Neuroendocrine Tumor With Transient Facial Paralysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroendocrine tumors originating in the middle ear are rare, and presentation with facial paralysis is extremely uncommon. A 19-year-old woman with a history of transient facial paralysis presented with a right-sided middle ear mass. Surgical exploration of the tympanic cavity was performed using a transcanal endoscopic approach. Histopathologic examination confirmed the diagnosis of a middle ear neuroendocrine tumor. After surgical excision of the tumor, no recurrence or facial paralysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional Rehabilitation With Anatomic Reconstruction of Oroantral Fistula With Lateral Approach of Sinus Elevation Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oroantral fistula (OAF), defined as an epithelized pathologic communication between the oral cavity and the maxillary sinus, develops when an oroantral communication (OAC) has remained unclosed for 48 to 72 hours or longer. To close an OAF, infections within the maxillary sinus, such as sinusitis, must be treated through sinus irrigation, medication, or sinus surgery. In addition, physical closure using a local flap is required, so various techniques have been proposed for this purpose. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Periventricular diffusivity reflects APOE ε4-modulated amyloid accumulation and cognitive impairment in the Alzheimer's disease continuum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Altered glymphatic-related fluid dynamics are increasingly recognized as a feature of Alzheimer's disease (AD). We generalized an established diffusion imaging framework to quantify periventricular diffusivity (PVeD), hypothesizing that fast diffusion signals in the periventricular region can reflect amyloid beta (Aβ) deposition across the AD continuum.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facile Decellularization of Stem Cell Spheroids by Integrating Bioactive Nanofibers for Enhanced Wound Healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decellularized 3D spheroids of stem cells may address challenges associated with the direct transplantation of cellular components; however, decellularization is inefficient in large spheroids due to the dense cellular architecture, which restricts detergent infiltration and the preservation of biomolecules. In this study, a strategy incorporating anti-oxidative polydopamine (PD)-coated nanofibers into human adipose-derived stem cell (hADSC) spheroids is developed to facilitate solution...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feline Renal Cortical Thickness-Aortic Diameter Ratio in Healthy Versus Diseased Kidneys: Comparative Ultrasonographic Evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this retrospective multicenter study, we aimed to establish the renal cortical thickness-aortic diameter (RCT:Ao) ratio as a diagnostic parameter for detecting feline acute kidney injury or chronic kidney disease (AKI or CKD). This study included bilateral kidneys of 152 normal, 171 CKD, 19 AKI, and 15 acute-on-chronic kidney disease (ACKD) cats. Ultrasonographic measurements were obtained in the midsagittal plane of the kidneys and aorta. Multiple linear regression analysis of RCT, body...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scavenging Meets Reinforcement: A Dual-Functional Electrolyte Additive Approach to Dendrite-Free Lithium-Metal All-Solid-State Batteries Under Low-Pressure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Among the challenges facing Li-metal all-solid-state-batteries (ASSBs), achieving stable low-pressure operation remains a formidable task owing to limited interfacial contact and Li-dendrite growth. In this study, a simple yet scalable approach is presented to address these issues via a dual-functional additive strategy. Sulfide-based solid electrolytes (SEs) are reformulated by incorporating mechanically robust and lithium-scavenging Li(4)Ti(5)O(12) (LTO) particles through powder mixing and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Clinical Benefits of Age-Adjusted Sagittal Correction in Adult Spinal Deformity Surgery: Results From Patient Grouping Using a Hierarchical Cluster Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Hierarchical cluster analysis effectively stratified ASD patients based on postoperative sagittal parameter offsets and identified a balanced alignment (cluster B) that optimizes clinical outcomes and minimizes mechanical complications. These results suggest a practical and nuanced approach to sagittal alignment correction in ASD surgery, emphasizing the integration of multiple parameters for improved outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Cholesterol associated with TB in people living with HIV in an Asia-Pacific cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this Asia-Pacific cohort of adults living with HIV, low CD4+ cell count and low total serum cholesterol were associated with increased TB odds. Cholesterol may represent a low-cost adjunct marker to support TB risk stratification in PLHIV in endemic settings, but requires validation and evaluation of feasibility and cost-effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Live Zoster Vaccination and the Reduced Risk of Chronic Respiratory Diseases: An Emulated Target Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Live zoster vaccination significantly reduced the incidence of chronic respiratory disease and related hospitalizations. These findings suggest that live zoster vaccination may provide public health benefits beyond preventing herpes zoster in adults aged ≥ 50 years.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A First-In-Human Dose-Escalation Phase 1 Study of Basroparib (STP1002), a Tankyrase Inhibitor, in Patients with Advanced-Stage Solid Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Basroparib (STP1002) was shown to be a safe and well-tolerated tankyrase-selective inhibitor with preliminary anti-tumor activity warranting further investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Cell RNA Analysis Reveals Reduced Frequency and Activity of CXCR5<sup>+</sup> Atypical Memory B Cells in Islet Xenotransplantation Treated With Clinically Applicable Immunosuppressants Including Belimumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study elucidates the mechanism of action of Belimumab in non-human primate models, serving as preclinical subjects for B-cell-targeted therapy research in a xenotransplantation context. Significantly, our data indicate that Belimumab not only reduces the proportion of antibody-secreting atypical memory B cells but also induces functional impairment across all B cell subsets. Given the potential pathogenic roles of atypical memory B cells in autoimmunity and other related...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHO preferred product characteristics for bivalent Salmonella Typhi/Paratyphi A vaccine for comprehensive protection against enteric fever- key considerations and research gaps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In 2021, Salmonella Paratyphi A caused >2 million illnesses, resulting in >14,000 deaths, most of which occurred among children under 5 years of age in socioeconomically deprived populations. Both typhoid fever and paratyphoid fever occur in such areas, but paratyphoid fever is currently concentrated in South Asia. Typhoid conjugate vaccines are recommended for the control of enteric fever in typhoid-endemic settings; however, there are increasing demands for the development of vaccines that can...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential effects of nesfatin-1 on proliferation and migration in normal and cancerous human lung cells via the PI3K/AKT pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nesfatin-1, initially identified as an appetite-regulating hormone, has also been detected in various cancer tissues and implicated in tumorigenesis. However, its role in the proliferation and migration of lung cancer cells remains unclear. This study aims to investigate the effects of nesfatin-1 on the proliferation and migration of human lung cancer cells and elucidate the underlying molecular mechanisms. The expression of nesfatin-1 protein and NUCB2 mRNA was detected in the immortalized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: The Application of Virtual Reality in Shoulder Surgery Rehabilitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.7759/cureus.58280.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning model using cross-sequence learning to identify orbital fractures in radiographs of patients under 20 Years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orbit fractures under 20 years are a medical emergency requiring urgent surgery with the gold standard modality being high-resolution CT. If radiography could be used to identify patients without fractures, the number of unnecessary CT scans could be reduced. The purpose of this study was to develop and validate a deep learning-based multi-input model with a novel cross-sequence learning method, which outperforms the conventional single-input models, to detect orbital fractures on radiographs of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Methylphenidate in Patients With Brain Disease: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This systematic review and meta-analysis evaluated the efficacy and safety of methylphenidate in patients with brain disease. A comprehensive search up to November 4, 2024 identified 33 randomized controlled trials involving 1,369 participants with traumatic brain injury (TBI), stroke, Parkinson's disease (PD), Alzheimer's disease (AD), other dementias, and multiple sclerosis. Methylphenidate was administered at 10-80 mg/day or 0.1-1 mg/kg/day for durations ranging from a single dose to 6...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeted autophagic clearance of Tau protects against Alzheimer's disease through amelioration of Tau-mediated lysosomal stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Lysosomal dysfunction could be an underlying cause of Alzheimer's disease, with Tau oligomer being an important inducer or amplifier of lysosomal stress associated with the disease. Tau oligomer is a well-known substrate of autophagy, and selective degradation of Tau with Tau-specific autophagy degrader might be feasible. Methods: Tau-specific autophagic degraders were synthesized by combining leucomethylene blue, linkers and a lysosomal degradation tag (Autac). Tau clearance and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Environmental and genetic effects on phytochemical and nutritional composition of onion (<em>Allium cepa</em> L.) varieties in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fpls.2025.1649912.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determinants of orphan drug health technology assessment in South Korea: an empirical analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The pricing of orphan drugs in South Korea is predominantly influenced by external reference pricing. Drugs targeting smaller patient populations tend to be priced higher. This finding can guide policymakers, pharmaceutical companies, and healthcare providers in their efforts to balance patient accessibility with the sustainable development of orphan drugs and the financial sustainability of public health insurance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of the Needle Tip Position for the Proper Contrast Spread Pattern and Clinical Outcomes During Cervical Transforaminal Epidural Injections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Positioning the needle at the medial one-third of the articular pillar during CTFESI promoted improved access to the optimal target area with more spread into the epidural space, as well as providing improved pain reduction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of oxygen content and structure on graphene derivative-based hydroelectric nanogenerators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydroelectric nanogenerators (HENGs) produce clean energy from water as a sustainable source, gaining attention. The performance of HENGs is influenced by the morphology, chemical composition, and structural changes in carbon nanomaterials, which limits electrode design. We explored various graphene nanomaterial structures and oxygen contents, finding that graphene oxide with optimal oxygen content yields the best performance with water and artificial sweat sources.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unmanaged 'Managed Heart': Associations between Emotional Labour and Cardiovascular Disease Risk Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study suggests emotional labour as a critical occupational stressor contributing to various CVD risk factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progression of the estimated glomerular filtration rate in asphyxiated neonates undergoing therapeutic hypothermia during the first 10 days of life]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Based on a pooled dataset in TH cases, we converted Scr centiles to eGFR centiles. Based on median values, this resulted in a polynomial function in TH cases, compared to healthy term neonates. This eGFR function enables precision pharmacotherapy for GFR-cleared drugs in this vulnerable population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and efficacy of robot-assisted bile ductoplasty and intrapancreatic bile duct resection in congenital biliary dilatation: a single-center retrospective cohort (2013-2024)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Robot-assisted surgery is increasingly being utilized for congenital biliary dilatation (CBD); however, limited data exist on its feasibility across age groups, particularly for bile ductoplasty and intrapancreatic bile duct (IPBD) resection. This was a retrospective cohort study that compared the outcomes of robot-assisted versus laparoscopic CBD surgery in 159 patients (Rob group: 57; Lap group: 102) treated between 2013 and 2024. In the Rob group, hospital stay was significantly shorter,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HPV Education and Its Impact on Vaccination Willingness and Recommendation Intentions Among Unvaccinated Japanese University Students: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although Japan resumed proactive HPV vaccination in 2022 and introduced catch-up initiatives, vaccination rates remain low, partly due to insufficient cancer education during school years. Moreover, male vaccination remains underrecognized despite its cancer prevention benefits. This study evaluated the effect of a planned educational intervention on HPV-related knowledge, willingness to receive vaccination, and recommendation intent among unvaccinated male and female university students. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of Heart Rate on Hemodynamics in Fontan Circulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The standard value of heart rate (HR) and the effect of HR on Fontan circulation remain unclear. HRs and hemodynamic parameters were evaluated in 59 adults with Fontan circulation without pacemaker (PM) and then compared with those of 15 patients with PM. The minimum HR in Holter monitoring, HR in resting electrogram, resting HR in cardiopulmonary exercise (CPX), maximum HR in Holter, and peak HR in CPX were observed during sleep, supine, sitting, maximum daily activity, and exercise,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: JNK2-MMP-9 axis facilitates the progression of intracranial aneurysms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of obesity with musculoskeletal health and functional mobility in females-a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity is a prevalent global health challenge with a significant yet unclear impact on musculoskeletal health, particularly among females. This systematic review aimed to unravel the association between obesity and musculoskeletal health, as well as functional mobility in women. A comprehensive literature search was conducted across PubMed, Scopus, Web of Science, and the Cochrane Library for articles published between January 2001 and December 2023. Studies were selected based on their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoinduced non-reciprocal magnetism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Out of equilibrium, the action-reaction symmetry of interactions is often broken, leading to the emergence of various collective phenomena with no equilibrium counterparts. Although ubiquitous in classical active systems, implementing such non-reciprocal interactions in solid-state systems has remained challenging, as known quantum schemes require precise single-site control. Here, we propose a dissipation-engineering protocol that induces non-reciprocal interactions in solid-state platforms...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Rational Selection for Solubilized Formulation Technologies Utilizing Physicochemical Properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enhancing the solubility of poorly water-soluble oral small-molecule drugs remains a critical challenge in the pharmaceutical industry, particularly during the early stages of drug development when selecting solubilized formulation technologies. This difficulty largely stems from the absence of objective indicators for comparing formulations. This study aimed to establish the selection indicators for solubilized formulation technologies based on applicable formulation preparation among amorphous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the Film-Forming Ability for Heparinoid Cream Formulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We compared the film-forming ability of a heparinoid cream (HP-C) formulation, an oil-in-water-type emulsion used as a moisturizer, and found that the original HP-C (HP-C(O)) formulation formed a thick and robust film that floated easily on an acrylic plate. It is suggested that the thickness and robustness of HP-C(O) contributed to the retention of its high keratin water content, while its floatability helped prevent adhesion to clothing after application. Among the generic HP-C formulations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Novel TLC Identification Test for "Rosemary Oil" and "Rosemary Water" Listed in the Japanese Standards of Quasi-Drug Ingredients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rosemary oil (RO) and rosemary water (RW) are widely used ingredients in cosmetics. According to the Japanese Standards of Quasi-Drug Ingredients (JSQDI), RO is defined as an essential oil obtained by the steam distillation of fresh rosemary (Rosmarinus officinalis L.) leaves, branches, and flowers, whereas RW is the water layer obtained from the steam distillation of the leaves. Although the JSQDI outlines a specific TLC identification test for RW, this test is time-consuming (15-cm development...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Drug Monitoring Using Two-Dimensional Chromatography System Composed of Two Types of Temperature-Responsive Chromatography Columns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Therapeutic drug monitoring (TDM) is crucial for enhancing the effectiveness of pharmacological treatments. This study developed two types of two-dimensional (2D) chromatography systems. The primary column used a poly(N-isopropylacrylamide) (PNIPAAm) hydrogel-modified bead-packed column, while the secondary column employed either an octadecyl silyl (ODS) column or a PNIPAAm-terminally-modified column. The primary PNIPAAm-hydrogel-modified column effectively separated serum proteins and drugs,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraocular vasculature formation precedes extraocular vasculature penetration of mouse eyes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The posterior ocular circulatory system comprises choroidal vasculature and central retinal and posterior ciliary arteries (PCAs) that are fundamental for ocular tissue maintenance. Much is known about the development of the retinal vascular system, but that of the posterior ocular circulation system remain obscure. Therefore, we aimed to clarify the development of the intraocular vasculature involved in the posterior ocular circulation system. Choriocapillaris and hyaloid capillaries are formed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive and executive functions of top level para-karate athletes with intellectual disability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Karate is one of the most popular martial arts. This study investigates the cognitive profiles of top-level Para Karate athletes with intellectual disability (ID), aiming to assess the extent to which cognitive abilities are related to athletic performance. Cognitive and executive functions, including decision-making, processing speed, working memory, cognitive flexibility, and inhibitory control, are critical in high-level sports but are often understudied in athletes with ID. We conducted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An amino acid transporter in the small intestine mediates basolateral efflux of plant-derived nicotianamine iron complexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nicotianamine (NA), a plant-derived metal chelator abundant in vegetables, is a bioavailable iron-chelating compound in mammals. We recently reported that NA-iron (NA-Fe) complexes are absorbed in the small intestine via a proton-conjugated amino acid transporter (PAT1). However, the subsequent process remains unknown. In this study, using radioactive iron tracers and NA export quantification in Xenopus laevis oocytes, we identified the heterodimeric amino acid transporter as being responsible...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-physiological <sup>18</sup>F-fluorodeoxyglucose uptake in the myocardium as an early sign of silent myocardial ischemia: a onco-cardiology perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct circuit motifs evaluate opposing innate values of odors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the innate value of objects is critical for expressing adaptive behaviors. However, where and how this computation takes place in the brain remain elusive. By recording from virtually every neuron in Drosophila higher olfactory areas, we show that the lateral horn is a site of innate odor value computation, where distinct neurons represent opposing innate values. A connectome-based spiking network model recapitulating the neural activity indicates that representations of aversive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic and DNA methylomic factors associated with the efficacy of oral medroxyprogesterone acetate on endometrial neoplastic disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings not only provide a foundation for identifying effective biomarkers for MPA efficacy, but also reveal deeper insights into the mechanism of action of progestins.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterizing resting-state EEG oscillatory and aperiodic activity in neurodegenerative diseases: A multicentric study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Batch effects in the rsEEG power spectrum can be mitigated with harmonization. Oscillatory alpha power reduction may better reflect AD abnormalities, whereas pronounced oscillatory frequency slowing and greater aperiodic activity characterize LBD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Classification of peripheral pulmonary lesions in Endobronchial ultrasonography image using a multi-branch framework and voting ensemble]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The utilization of a multi-branch framework and ensemble learning proves to be more effective in addressing data imbalance issues. Furthermore, image transformation based on coordinate systems contributes to optimizing the model's understanding of image structures, which can further enhance performance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why boys cry and don't cry: The Contextual-Statistical (ConStat) approach to the perceived validity of generics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[People judge the validity of bare plural generic generalizations ('generics' for short, e.g., 'Women are empathic') in a notoriously fickle way. We present the Contextual-Statistical (ConStat) framework to explain these judgments, showing that they follow consistent principles and are therefore logical and predictable. ConStat rests upon the assumption that generics transmit information of relevance for action. It consists of five tenets. (1) People may understand generics as being meant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of rapid nucleic acid amplification tests and rapid antigen tests for influenza in the emergency department]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with suspected influenza in the emergency department, although rapid NAAT and RAT demonstrated good agreement, the cases that tested positive by the rapid NAAT but negative by the RAT were significantly more frequent. This suggests that rapid NAAT may be a more suitable diagnostic tool in the emergency department, as rapid NAAT can help avoid false negatives, enable timely antiviral treatment, and improve clinical decision-making within the critical treatment window.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic insights into RAD51-mediated nucleosome binding and remodeling in homologous recombination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eukaryotic cells organize their genomic DNA into chromatin to achieve both compact packaging and precise regulation of essential processes, including DNA repair. Depending on the type of damage, distinct repair pathways are activated through the targeted recruitment of repair factors to chromatin. RAD51 is the central recombinase in homologous recombination (HR) and forms nucleoprotein filaments, but its mode of chromatin engagement has remained elusive. In this review, we summarize recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40967099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a selective and sensitive measurement method for permanganate and its first quantification under actual ozonation conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Environmental water typically contains manganese, and when treated with ozone (O(3)), MnO(4)^(-) is produced, sometimes turning the water pink. However, there has been no measurement method that could specifically detect only MnO(4)^(-) with sufficient sensitivity. Furthermore, the MnO(4)^(-) concentration during ozonation has never been reported. Therefore, as an initial step in this study, we developed a selective and sensitive method for quantifying MnO(4)^(-), which is unaffected by other...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exceptional high number of IPD cases in winter season 2024-2025 in Belgium in concomitance with rise in vaccine serotypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Following lifting of containment measures post-COVID, the number of invasive pneumococcal disease (IPD) infections continued to increase, reaching a record number last winter season 2024-2025 in Belgium. This exceptional increase is largely due to high numbers in (older) adults, and mainly an increase of vaccine serotype IPD. Over 95 % of IPD cases last winter could theoretically be prevented by vaccination. Cases of serotypes 12F, 14 and 4 were three or more times higher compared to pre-COVID...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Long-term antibody responses to the Ebola virus and the vaccine vector after rVSV-ZEBOV vaccination in DRC" [Vaccine 62 (2025) 127537]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Problematic gambling and alcohol misuse among adults in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Problematic gambling is associated with alcohol misuse among Japanese adults, and there are no sex- or age-related differences in these associations. Efforts to inform the general public about the potentially detrimental effects of problematic gambling in relation to alcohol misuse may have important public health benefits.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A grammar of movements: Acquisition and retrieval of biased probability distributions in a finite-state grammar-based serial reaction time task]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Motor sequence learning research has been primarily concerned with simple frequentist patterns, thereby neglecting the motor system's ability to handle uncertainty and non-deterministic environments. In this study, we combine methods from motor neuroscience and neurolinguistics to study how probabilistic systems are acquired during motor learning. Two groups of young adults practiced a probabilistic serial reaction time task (pSRTT) for three consecutive days. The pSRTT was generated from a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protein hydrolysis for amino acid analysis revisited]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several protein hydrolysis methods exist for amino acid composition analysis, yet their suitability for accurately quantifying individual amino acids in foods remains unclear. We compared six different hydrolysis methods for chromatography-based amino acid analysis of plant-based food matrices, including oat, pea, and pea aquafaba, using milk, bovine serum albumin, and β-lactoglobulin as animal protein references. Enzymatic hydrolysis resulted in superior amino acid recoveries compared to other...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-scale investigation of PQ3-quinoxaline derivatives as selective COX-2 inhibitors: synthesis, structural analysis, DFT, MD simulations, and in silico/in vitro evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quinoxaline has emerged as a promising scaffold in drug discovery, particularly in the development of anti-inflammatory agents, due to its structural versatility and broad pharmacological potential. Its flexible chemical framework permits diverse modifications, enabling the design of derivatives that can target critical molecular pathways implicated in cancer progression. The title compounds of 3-phenylquinoxalin-2(1H)-one (PQ3a-f), were synthesized in good yields from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging Invasive Haemophilus influenzae Type C Infection in a Hib-vaccinated Child: Implications for Surveillance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic errors in older patients: a secondary analysis of case reports]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Diagnostic errors involving failure to consider the correct diagnosis, recognize urgency, and identify complications were more common in older patients. Understanding these mechanisms is essential to develop diagnostic strategies specific to older patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-capacity, reversible hydrogen storage using H<sup>-</sup>-conducting solid electrolytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen absorption and desorption in solids are pivotal reactions involved in batteries and hydrogen storage devices. However, conventional thermodynamic and electrochemical hydrogen storage using high-capacity materials suffers from high hydrogen-desorption temperatures and instability of electrolytes. In this work, we explored electrochemical hydride ion (H^(-))-driven hydrogen storage and developed a solid electrolyte, anti-α-AgI-type Ba(0.5)Ca(0.35)Na(0.15)H(1.85), which exhibits excellent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable entanglement of nuclear spins mediated by electron exchange]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The use of nuclear spins for quantum computation is limited by the difficulty in creating genuine quantum entanglement between distant nuclei. Current demonstrations of nuclear entanglement in semiconductors rely on coupling the nuclei to a common electron, which is not a scalable strategy. In this work, we demonstrated a two-qubit controlled-Z logic operation between the nuclei of two phosphorus atoms in a silicon device, separated by up to 20 nanometers. Each atom binds separate electrons,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aberrant Expression of Gonadotropin-Releasing Hormone Receptor in Human Mast Cells Enhances the Recruitments of Trophoblasts and NK Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that GnRHR expression in mast cells promotes their supportive role in pregnancy establishment by increasing the LIF, MMP-9, and CXCL16 productions, recruiting trophoblasts and NK cells.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BFAR promotes neutrophil infiltration and immunosuppressive reprogramming through the PRP19-YBX1 axis to induce immune evasion in gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The immunosuppressive tumor microenvironment (TME) remains a major barrier to effective immunotherapy in gastric cancer (GC). Here, we identified the E3 ubiquitin ligase BFAR as a critical regulator of neutrophil-mediated immune evasion through the S100A8/A9-BFAR-PRP19-YBX1 signaling axis. Multi-omics analyses revealed that BFAR is overexpressed in GC and correlates with poor prognosis. Functional studies demonstrated that BFAR knockdown suppressed tumor growth by reducing neutrophil...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EFLM checklist for the assessment of AI/ML studies in laboratory medicine: enhancing general medical AI frameworks for laboratory-specific applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) into laboratory medicine shows promise for advancing diagnostic, prognostic, and decision-support tools; however, routine clinical implementation remains limited and heterogeneous. Laboratory data presents unique methodological and semantic complexities - method dependency, analyte-specific variation, and contextual sensitivity-not adequately addressed by general-purpose AI reporting guidelines. To bridge this gap, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol for quantifying amino acids in small volumes of human sweat samples]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sweat, a biofluid rich in water, ions, and amino acids, is emerging as a valuable, non-invasive source for continuous health monitoring and disease diagnostics. Here, we present a protocol for amino acid analysis in small volumes of sweat samples. We describe steps for sweat collection, fluorescence derivatization of amino acids, and liquid chromatography analysis, which can be applied to the analysis of very small volumes of sweat samples. For complete details on the use and execution of this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Properties of Hydrogen Fluoride in Aqueous Solution Using Reactive Force Field]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The dynamics of hydrogen fluoride in aqueous solutions at the atomic scale cannot easily be analyzed experimentally and computationally because of the high reactivity of hydrogen fluoride (HF). To elucidate the behavior and growth process of HF aqueous solutions, this study investigated geometric and energetic properties using molecular dynamics simulations with a reactive force field. First, we examined that the previously proposed reactive force field operates properly in bulk HF aqueous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40966064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proposal for a new staging system of Sjögren's syndrome using salivary gland SPECT/CT: comparison with Saxon test, MR sialography, and histopathological examination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SPECT/CT is a highly suitable modality for quantitatively evaluating the stage of Sjögren's syndrome. Especially, the pre-stimulation SUVmax of the parotid glands serves as a valuable indicator for assessing Sjögren's syndrome stage and predicting prognosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intra- and intermuscular shear wave speed distributions in the human hamstrings during isometric and eccentric contractions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Hamstring muscles exhibit region-specific SWS profiles, largely influenced by passive mechanical properties. This heterogeneity may contribute to localised strain concentrations and injury risk, highlighting a potential target for prevention strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of dapagliflozin on uric acid in patients with moderate-to-severe chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dapagliflozin can decrease UA concentrations in patients with moderate CKD. This finding suggests that dapagliflozin has a beneficial effect on UA metabolism in patients with moderate CKD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of erythrodermic pemphigus foliaceus and bullous pemphigoid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parental illness intrusiveness in parents of children with neuromuscular disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared to parents of a child with T1D, parents in the NMD population may experience more impact of their child's disease in their personal life. Parents of youth with higher physical impairment may be particularly at risk for experiencing difficulties among a wide array of personal life domains.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International Validation of Echocardiographic Artificial Intelligence Amyloid Detection Algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: EchoNet-LVH can assist with earlier and accurate diagnosis of CA. EchoNet-LVH achieved development goals to be highly specific to maximize positive predictive value of downstream confirmatory testing since CA is a rare disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Type of Primary Surgery and Postoperative Velopharyngeal Function in Patients With Submucous Cleft Palate at 3 years and Older]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Palatoplasty and pharyngeal flap are indicated for submucous cleft palate (SMCP) as primary surgical techniques, but there are no rigid criteria regarding the choice of surgical techniques, and appropriate timing of performing surgery is still controversial. In the present study, 37 patients with SMCP who underwent palatoplasty or pharyngeal flap at our hospital were retrospectively reviewed to evaluate the validity of our criteria to choose between palatoplasty or pharyngeal flap for patients...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilizing an elemental sulfur and molecular hydrogen combination: cobalt silicate-catalyzed thiol synthesis from carbonyls]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We describe a cobalt silicate-catalyzed thiol synthesis from carbonyl and nitrile compounds using elemental sulfur and hydrogen. The system yields various thiols efficiently, with high catalyst recyclability. Mechanistic studies suggest the formation of sulfonium cations and polysulfanes as reaction intermediates, and sodium cations significantly influence the yield.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Room-temperature X-ray data collection enabled the structural determination of statin-bound CYP105A1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Streptomyces griseolus CYP105A1 exhibits monooxygenase activity towards a wide variety of structurally diverse substrates with regiospecificity and stereospecificity, making it suitable for broad applications. Our previous studies have demonstrated that both wild-type CYP105A1 and its mutants metabolize vitamin D(3) and its derivatives, as well as 12 types of nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs) and statins. Notably, the R84A mutant displayed high activity against vitamin D(3), numerous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infrared Attenuated Total Reflection Spectroscopy for a Layered Structure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For the analysis of a structural distribution in a range of thicknesses comparable with the wavelengths in the visible region of light, infrared attenuated total reflection (ATR) was derived on the basis of the wave vector and Poynting vector, paying attention to the phase of transmitted light. The absorption was ascribed to the energy flow into the rarer medium by the component of the Poynting vector in the z direction and further embodied for the layered structure. This derivation was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40965082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Individual-Level Effects of a Digital Behavioural Treatment for Chronic Pain: Proof-of-Concept of a Single-Case Experimental Design Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The digital behavioural treatment showed promise in addressing diverse pain profiles and associated functioning. The variability in responses highlights the benefit of using SCED to explore individual-level effects, thus offering a methodological proof-of-concept. Findings support further development, including tailoring to match individual needs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Settling and Along-Isopycnal Subduction of Small Microplastics Into Subsurface Layers of the Western North Pacific Ocean]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The vertical distribution of small microplastics (SMPs; 10-300 μm in size) and its relation to water masses were investigated through seawater sampling and hydrographic surveys from the sea surface to 1000 m in the North Pacific Ocean. The average ± standard deviation of SMP concentrations in 12 layers at four stations was 6910 ± 2620 particles m^(-3). Concentrations were high in isopycnal layers between potential densities of 23 and 25σ(θ) (100-300 m depths). Elevated concentrations were also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial: Computer vision mechanisms for resource-constrained robotics applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insomnia Improved by Intravenous Mesenchymal Stem Cell Transplant: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While several therapeutic options for insomnia are currently available, they often require long-term use and come with certain disadvantages. Given insomnia's significant impact on health overall, more effective treatments are warranted. Here, we report two patients with moderate to severe insomnia whose symptoms significantly improved following the intravenous administration of ex vivo -expanded bone marrow-derived mesenchymal stem cells (MSC). The cases were 50-year-old and 38-year-old men...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40964225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Newly developed evaluation for intestinal permeability using <em>Caenorhabditis elegans</em>: protective effects of agaro-oligosaccharides on intestinal permeability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The intestinal barrier represents the first line of host defense. Its dysfunction, defined as increased intestinal permeability, is widely recognized as an important factor in the clinical manifestation of various diseases. Consequently, maintenance of the intestinal barrier is necessary for human health. Caenorhabditis elegans has recently been used frequently as a model organism in studies of gut bacteria-host interactions and in screening for probiotics and prebiotics that promote gut health....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capturing systemic inflammation in a nonhuman primate using a new leukocyte activity assessment system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We developed an optical system that simultaneously monitors leukocytes producing the reactive oxygen species (ROS) superoxide and hypochlorite ions using only a few microliters of whole blood. Here, we report the first use of this system to measure circulating blood from a nonhuman primate. This observational pilot study involved rhesus monkeys recruited for a different purpose, brain positron emission tomography in the conscious state. The results indicated that (1) surgical inflammation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced phase angle as a potential indicator of mild cognitive impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigated the relationship between phase angle (PhA), measured using bioelectrical impedance analysis (BIA), and mild cognitive impairment (MCI). A cross-sectional analysis was conducted on 290 community residents (83.7% female, average age 74.9 years). Cognitive function was assessed using the Japanese version of the Montreal Cognitive Assessment (MoCA-J), with MCI defined as a score of ≤25. Body composition, including PhA, was measured using BIA. Multiple regression...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adiponectin inhibits chemokine-induced cell migration via direct interaction with platelet factor 4]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite adiponectin's recognized anti-inflammatory properties, its impact on cardiovascular homeostasis involves poorly defined mechanisms. We investigated the effect of adiponectin on chemokine-induced cell migration and their potential intermolecular interactions. Our findings revealed that cell migration induced by recombinant PF4, MCP-1, or RANTES in HL-60 cells was significantly inhibited by pre-treating cells with adiponectin. Surface plasmon resonance analysis and molecular docking...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomic diffusion barriers and inter-element miscibility guide the development of unexplored crystal phases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Z3-Fe(Pd,In)(3) ordered alloy nanoparticles containing alternating layers of an L1(0) (CuAu-type)-like PdFePd trilayer and a Pd-In ordered alloy monolayer are formed by following the inter-element miscibility of In, which is miscible with Pd but immiscible with Fe. An understanding of the atomic diffusion processes based on inter-element miscibility is required to effectively synthesize such unknown crystal phases. In this study, we demonstrated that the temperature required for the formation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preventing Multimorbidity: Moving Beyond the Single Disease Lens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The protective role of chloroplast NADH dehydrogenase-like complex (NDH) against PSI photoinhibition under chilling stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chilling stress induces photosystem I (PSI) photoinhibition in various plants, severely impairing their growth. However, the mechanisms suppressing chilling-induced PSI photoinhibition remain unclear. To identify factors preventing PSI photoinhibition, we compared two cucumber cultivars with different susceptibilities to PSI photoinhibition and chilling stress tolerance. Chilling stress caused uncoupling of thylakoid membrane in both cultivars, as previously reported. However, in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Hydroxy-Functionalized Polyethylene via Radical Copolymerization of Ethylene with Alkenyl Boronate and Post-Polymerization Oxidation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radical copolymerization of ethylene was performed with alkenyl boronate, and post-polymerization oxidation was conducted to synthesize hydroxy-functionalized polyethylene (PE). The copolymerization behavior was dependent on the molecular structure of the boron monomer: the copolymerization with α-methyl substituted monomer carrying boronic acid pinacol ester [isopropenylboronic acid pinacol ester (IPBpin)] afforded copolymers with higher molar masses than the vinyl-type monomer [i.e.,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sterically Congested LLX-Type PNSi Tridentate Ligands for Iridium-Catalyzed C(sp<sup>3</sup>)-H Borylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Iridium catalysts bearing LLX-type PNSi tridentate ligands (Ir/PNSi catalysts) were developed as new effective catalysts for the C(sp³)-H borylation of alkanes and alkyl groups that do not have directing groups. The Ir/PNSi catalysts were prepared in situ from [Ir(OMe)(cod)](2) and 8-diarylphosphino-2-[(di-tert-butylhydrosilyl)methyl]quinolines, which are readily synthesized from commercially available 8-bromo-2-methylquinoline. The Ir/PNSi catalyst exhibited higher chemoselectivity than a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multi-component density functional study on quantum effects of hydrogen nuclei on ground-state and excited-state proton transfer reactions in 7-hydroxyquinoline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The proton transfer (PT) reaction in 7-hydroxyquinoline (7-HQ), mediated by three methanol molecules, has been investigated using time-dependent density functional theory (TD-DFT) and multi-component DFT (MC_TD-DFT) calculations, which can incorporate nuclear quantum effects (NQEs) of protons and deuterons. The NQEs were found to induce the geometrical changes in both the ground-state and excited-state, and alter orbital energies, affecting the HOMO-LUMO energy gap and absorption and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40963396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250919033544&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and evidence of CO<sub>2</sub> as a vascular contrast agent as an alternative to iodine-based contrast media in vascular procedures: a systematic review by the ESUR Contrast Medium Safety Committee]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CO(2) is a safe alternative to ICM in vascular procedures, potentially reducing the risk of CA-AKI, especially in PAD procedures. However, more large-scale RCTs are needed to confirm these findings and further investigate other risk factors contributing to CA-AKI in both EVAR and PAD procedures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing RNA base editing on mammalian transcripts with small nuclear RNAs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endogenous uridine-rich small nuclear RNAs (U snRNAs) form RNA-protein complexes to process eukaryotic pre-mRNA into mRNA. Previous studies have demonstrated programmable U snRNA guide-targeted exon inclusion and exclusion. Here we investigated whether snRNAs can also enhance RNA base editing over state-of-the-art RNA-targeting technologies in human cells. Compared with adenosine deaminase acting on RNA (ADAR)-recruiting circular RNAs, we find that guided A>I snRNAs consistently increase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pan-UK Biobank genome-wide association analyses enhance discovery and resolution of ancestry-enriched effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Large biobanks, such as the UK Biobank (UKB), enable massive phenome by genome-wide association studies that elucidate genetic etiology of complex traits. However, people from diverse genetic ancestry groups are often excluded from association analyses due to concerns about population structure introducing false positive associations. Here we generate mixed model associations and meta-analyses across genetic ancestry groups, inclusive of a larger fraction of the UK Biobank than previous efforts,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic and epigenetic screens in primary human T cells link candidate causal autoimmune variants to T cell networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genetic variants associated with autoimmune diseases are highly enriched within putative cis-regulatory regions of CD4^(+) T cells, suggesting that they could alter disease risk through changes in gene regulation. However, very few genetic variants have been shown to affect T cell gene expression or function. Here we tested >18,000 autoimmune disease-associated variants for allele-specific effects on expression using massively parallel reporter assays in primary human CD4^(+) T cells. We find...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trophic dynamics and metabolic pathways in host parasite interactions revealed by nitrogen isotope analysis of amino acids in multiple tissues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trophic interactions are crucial for understanding food web complexity and energy flow in ecosystems. Including parasites in these analyses can alter dynamics and challenge ecological assumptions. Compound-specific isotope analysis offers greater precision than bulk stable isotope analysis by analyzing individual amino acids, providing deeper insights into nutrient exchange and metabolism in host-parasite systems. In this study, we conducted a 120-day controlled feeding experiment to investigate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redox-dependent liver gluconeogenesis impacts different intensity exercise in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatic gluconeogenesis produces glucose from various substrates to meet energy demands. However, how these substrates are preferentially used under different conditions remains unclear. Here, we show that preferential supplies of lactate and glycerol modulate hepatic gluconeogenesis, thereby impacting high-intensity and low-intensity exercise capacities, respectively. We find that liver-specific knockout of phosphoenolpyruvate carboxykinase 1 (L-Pck1KO), which blocks gluconeogenesis from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The arts for disease prevention and health promotion: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Differences in risk factor exposure and access to prevention resources have led to unequal health outcomes for noncommunicable diseases (NCDs) globally. Recent studies elucidate the health benefits of arts participation, but no systematic reviews have focused on NCD prevention and health promotion. Here we share results of a mixed-methods systematic review that included 95 studies of arts programs, practices and activities, addressing NCD risk factors across 27 countries. We found that most...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical implementation of an AI-based prediction model for decision support for patients undergoing colorectal cancer surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adverse outcomes after elective cancer surgery are a main contributor to decreased survival, poorer oncological outcomes and increased healthcare costs. Identifying high-risk patients and selecting interventions according to individual risk profiles in the perioperative period in cancer surgery is a challenge. Using real-world data on 18,403 patients with colorectal cancer from Danish national registries and consecutive patients from a single center, we developed, validated and implemented an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stabilizing a mammalian RNA thermometer confers neuroprotection in subarachnoid hemorrhage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mammals tightly regulate their core body temperature, yet how cells sense and respond to small temperature changes remains incompletely understood. Here, we discover RNA G-quadruplexes (rG4s) as key thermosensors enriched near splice sites of cold-repressed exons. These thermosensing RNA structures, when stabilized, mask splice sites, reducing exon inclusion. Specifically, rG4s near splice sites of a cold-repressed poison exon in the neuroprotective RBM3 are stabilized at low temperatures,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-depth switching by triple wavefront modulation of quarter-waveplate geometric phase lenses for vergence-accommodation-matching extended reality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a novel approach to resolving the vergence-accommodation conflict (VAC) in extended reality (XR) optics by introducing a quarter-waveplate (QWP) geometric phase lens (GPL) capable of triple wavefront modulation-focusing, defocusing, and non-modulating at infinity. This polarization-driven behavior is interpreted using contour trajectories on the Poincaré sphere and compared against conventional half-waveplate (HWP) GPLs. Leveraging this property, we propose a bi-stacked QWP GPL module...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A low frequency damaging SORCS2 variant identified in a family with ADHD compromises receptor stability and quenches activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) is a common neurodevelopmental disorder affecting 5% of children and 2.5% of adults worldwide. ADHD is considered a polygenic disorder caused by a combination of both common and rare risk variants, each with low individual effect size. The Vps10p domain receptor SorCS2 is involved in neuronal development and synaptic plasticity by modulating brain-derived neurotrophic factor (BDNF) signaling. We here describe the identification and characterization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of acute anorexia nervosa and of short-/long-term recovery after refeeding on the hormonal profiles of activin A, GDF-15 and follistatins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anorexia Nervosa (AN) is a severe eating disorder characterized by endocrine and metabolic abnormalities. In this study, we evaluated how the concentrations of proteins recently linked with energy homeostasis might be altered in acute AN (acAN), whether their levels are associated with reproductive hormones and whether they are restored after weight recovery. Our results show that activin A, follistatin, LH and estradiol concentrations are decreased while growth/differentiation factor-15...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Role of PRMT5 in Embryonic Developmental Arrest: Insights from IVF-ET Discarded Human Embryos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Embryonic developmental arrest is a critical factor affecting the success rate of in vitro fertilization and embryo transfer (IVF-ET), and protein arginine methyltransferase 5 (PRMT5) plays a crucial role in early embryonic development. However, the mechanisms by which PRMT5 regulates embryonic development remain largely unexplored. Following the acquisition of informed consent from the patients, human embryos discarded from the IVF process were collected as experimental material. Real-time...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Visual Abstract: The Trajectory of Reflux and its Associating Factors in Patients After Esophagectomy Based on Salivary Pepsin Testing: A Prospective Longitudinal Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Benefits and risks of therapeutic hypothermia for hypoxic-ischemic encephalopathy in late preterm infants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Therapeutic hypothermia (TH) is standard care for term neonates with moderate to severe hypoxic-ischemic encephalopathy (HIE), but its use in preterm infants 33-35 weeks' gestational age (GA) remains controversial. This review article summarizes the biological rationale, clinical evidence, and real-world experience supporting or challenging TH in this population. Preclinical models show neuroprotective effects of TH at developmental stages equivalent to late preterm infants. Retrospective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using glucagon receptor antagonism to evaluate the physiological effects of extrapancreatic glucagon in totally pancreatectomised individuals: a randomised controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS/INTERPRETATION: We conclude that inhibition of the glucagon receptor using LY2409021 during OGTT in totally pancreatectomised individuals does not produce detectable effects on glucose, lipid or amino acid metabolism, ruling out metabolic effects of extrapancreatic glucagon.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40968190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250919033545&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>