<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:20:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of trivalent Sb<sup>3+</sup>-ion doping on charge carrier recombination dynamics of cesium lead bromide perovskite quantum dots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-ion doping of perovskites has proven to enhance their photoluminescence (PL) properties and stability; however, the underlying charge carrier dynamics remain unclear. We synthesized a cesium lead bromide (CsPbBr(3)) perovskite quantum dot (PQD) incorporating a heterovalent Sb^(3+) ion dopant and its pristine counterpart and performed time-resolved single-particle PL spectroscopy. The PL intensity and lifetime of the Sb-CsPbBr(3) PQD were remarkably enhanced compared to those of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catastrophic Degradation in Solid Oxide Fuel Cells Caused by Air Supply Interruption in Real-World Operations: Fundamental Mechanisms and Mitigation Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the rapid market expansion of solid oxide fuel cells (SOFCs), real-world operational incidents have unveiled various critical challenges. Malfunction of the gas supply system is among the most frequent and critical issues, severely damaging cells and stacks. However, the actual cause of this degradation remains completely unknown; existing explanations have been mostly speculative, and simple engineering-based solutions have proven ineffective. The study reveals that air supply interruption...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anticooperative self-assembly of perylene diimide dyes in water unveiled by advanced molecular dynamics simulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The self-assembly mechanism and the dynamics in water of π-stacked columnar aggregates of N,N-bis(2-(trimethylammonium)ethylene)perylene-3,4,9,10-tetracarboxylic acid bis-imide (PDI) have been investigated using classical molecular dynamics (MD) simulations based on an accurate quantum mechanically derived force field. Nano-scale aggregates composed of up to twelve monomers were studied through a combination of bottom-up and top-down approaches, complemented by enhanced sampling MD techniques....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fully Aqueous and Printable Photonic Inks with Tunable Pitch and Optical Memory via Hydrogen-Bonded HPC-PVA Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rewritable and structurally colored biopolymer coatings demand fully aqueous processing, optical tunability, and dry-state color retention, yet these requirements remain difficult to reconcile without chemical crosslinking. Competitive hydrogen bonding between hydroxypropyl cellulose (HPC) and poly(vinyl alcohol) (PVA) is leveraged to achieve dynamic pitch modulation and kinetic trapping of cholesteric order, thereby overcoming the intrinsic limitations of HPC-based inks. In this study, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving the Performance of Vacuum-Deposited Perovskite Light-Emitting Diodes via a Tailored Sequential Deposition Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vacuum-deposited perovskite light-emitting diodes (PeLEDs) are attracting increased attention owing to their precise thickness control and absence of solvent-orthogonality constraints, offering significant potential for optimizing device performance. Here, we systematically compare how varying the deposition sequence of a single additive, triphenylphosphine oxide (TPPO)─known for its effective defect passivation─critically affects the crystallization dynamics, film morphology, and optoelectronic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LC-MS-Guided Isolation of Triterpene Glycosides from <em>Holothuria atra</em>: Structural Features Governing TRPA1 Inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The LC-MS-guided separation of the extract from the sea cucumber Holothuria atra led to the isolation of 16 triterpene glycosides (1-16), including seven previously unreported derivatives consisting of three sulfated (1, 3, 5) and four nonsulfated congeners (12, 13, 15, and 16). Notably, compounds 15 and 16 feature a new aglycone structure bearing an 8(9),11(12)-diene scaffold. All isolates were evaluated for their inhibitory activity toward transient receptor potential ankyrin 1 (TRPA1). In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Position statement: Evidence-Based Exercise Guidelines for Sarcopenia in Older Adults: Insights from the Korean Working Group on Sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first Korean evidence-based exercise guideline developed within the KWGS algorithm, offering clinical and community practitioners specific, actionable strategies for preventing and managing sarcopenia. It supports tailored interventions using FITT principles aligned with individual goals and sarcopenia classification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol for efficient recovery of high-quality DNA from microbiome of marine invertebrates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Marine organisms often form symbiotic relationships with various microorganisms to adapt and thrive in harsh environments. These symbiotic microbes contribute to host survival by providing nutrition, modulating the hosts' immune system, and supporting overall physiological stability. Advances in high-throughput sequencing technologies have enabled a deeper understanding of the structure and function of symbiotic microbial communities, as well as host-microbe interactions. Notably, symbiotic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the biosynthetic potential of Korean Actinobacteria for antibacterial metabolite discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Actinobacteria, a phylum of Gram-positive bacteria, are renowned for their remarkable ability to produce antibacterial natural products. The National Institute of Biological Resources (NIBR) of Korea maintains a collection of Korean native actinobacteria. In this study, we explored the phylogenetic and biosynthetic diversity of the NIBR actinobacteria collection to assess its potential as a source of new antibacterial natural products. A 16S rDNA-based phylogenetic analysis revealed a high level...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving the Conductivity and Stability of Silver Nanowires Through Spontaneous Ligand Exchange for Joule Heating]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silver nanowires (AgNWs) are promising materials for optoelectronic devices, owing to their high transparency and conductivity. However, their performance is limited by polyvinylpyrrolidone (PVP) as an insulating capping agent that is essential for the synthesis of AgNWs but increases their intrinsic resistance. Herein, we introduce a facile spin-coating ligand exchange strategy that considers the physicochemical properties of ligands, including PVP solubility, viscosity, volatility, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and immunogenicity of adenoviral Fc-fused FMDV virus-like particle vaccine in swine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Foot-and-mouth disease (FMD) remains a major threat to global livestock health, and current inactivated vaccines face limitations in biosafety and cross-protection. Virus-like particle (VLP) -based vaccines offer a safer alternative, however, their production is often hindered by the cytotoxicity of the viral 3C protease. In this study, we developed a modified 3C protease with reduced cytotoxicity, enabling efficient expression of FMDV VLPs via an internal ribosome entry site (IRES)-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lactose-functionalized photosensitizer nanoparticles derived from thiophene-fused BODIPY for NIR-imaging-guided photodynamic treatment of hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Four near-infrared (NIR) photosensitizers (PSs) (PHTB, PBrTB, THTB, and TBrTB) based on thiophene-fused, BODIPY-conjugated, and liver-tumor-targeting lactose were synthesized and characterized. Brominating the BODIPY core of PHTB and the terminal thiophene rings of THTB yielded PBrTB and TBrTB, respectively. All derivatives exhibited strong NIR absorption (λ(ab) = 640-674 nm) as well as moderate fluorescence quantum yields (Φ(F) = 0.21-0.35) and self-assembled into stable, uniform nanoparticles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of preoperative immunonutrition in malnourished patients undergoing colorectal cancer surgery: a study protocol for a multicenter randomized clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Malnutrition is a significant risk factor for postoperative complications in patients undergoing colorectal cancer surgery. Although current guidelines recommend preoperative immunonutrition for malnourished patients, its clinical benefit remains controversial. Our previous randomized clinical trial assessing immunonutrition in unselected colon cancer patients showed no reduction in infectious complications. This study aims to evaluate the efficacy of preoperative immunonutrition in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteome mining of Yersinia Enterocolitica for drug targets and computational inhibitor identification with ADMET, anti-inflammation potential and formulation characteristics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Yersinia enterocolitica infection can manifest as self-limiting gastroenteritis and may lead to more severe conditions, such as mesenteric lymphadenitis, reactive arthritis, or rare systemic infections. Fluoroquinolones and third-generation cephalosporins are the most effective treatment options but tetracyclines and co-trimoxazole effectiveness may vary based on resistance patterns. To explore new therapeutic options in case of antibiotic resistance, we initially mined drug targets from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Author Reflections: OPSCC Survivorship-Patient Determinants and Treatment‑Specific Quality‑of‑Life Trade‑offs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Publisher Correction: Psilocybin's lasting action requires pyramidal cell types and 5-HT2A receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Selenium-alloyed tellurium oxide for amorphous p-channel transistors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wind speed interannual variability with measured data validations and its impact on energy yield in the Southwest Sea of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Republic of Korea (ROK) has set an ambitious goal of 40.7 GW of onshore and offshore wind farms by 2038, as outlined in the "11th Basic Plan for Electricity Supply and Demand" in May 2024. To achieve this target, both wind farm developers and the government are crafting policies for "Project Site Planning" and "Offshore Wind Farm Clusters". A major concern for stakeholders is the variability in annual wind resources driven by climate phenomena and climate change, which can lead to increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiographic Assessment of Successful Lumbar Spinal Fusion: A Systematic Review of Fusion Criteria in Randomized Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study TypeSystematic Scoping Review.IntroductionRadiographic assessment is crucial for diagnosing symptomatic pseudarthrosis and evaluating spinal fusion outcomes, yet no consensus exists on defining successful lumbar fusion. This scoping review presents criteria for imaging-based assessment after posterolateral and interbody lumbar fusion, aiming to guide consistent evaluation methods.MethodsFollowing PRISMA guidelines, a comprehensive search of Medline, Embase, and Scopus identified eligible...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel agents and evolving strategies for anemia management in lower-risk myelodysplastic syndromes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent developments in the treatment of lower-risk myelodysplastic syndromes have focused on improving anemia management, which remains a major clinical challenge. Erythropoiesis-stimulating agents (ESAs) and lenalidomide are the standard therapies; however, their effectiveness is limited by resistance and patient selection criteria. Luspatercept, a transforming growth factor-beta superfamily ligand trap, has shown improved transfusion independence and is now considered a frontline option for a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Importance of Lysosomal Trapping and Plasmodium Parasite Infection on the Pharmacokinetics of Pyronaridine: A Physiologically Based Pharmacokinetic Model-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates the value of PBPK modeling in elucidating key pharmacokinetic mechanisms, revealing the critical roles of lysosomal sequestration, Hb level, and parasitemia in pyronaridine disposition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Type 2 diabetes in patients undergoing gastric cancer surgery: areas requiring disease-specific glycemic management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review provides a comprehensive analysis of phase-specific management strategies for type 2 diabetes (T2D) in patients undergoing gastric cancer (GC) surgery, encompassing the preoperative, intraoperative and postoperative phases within the context of oncodiabetology. In the preoperative phase, predicting T2D remission and evaluating antidiabetic medications while considering their adverse event profiles are important. These medications include metformin and sodium-glucose cotransporter 2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of dioxin exposure on diabetes and potential dietary modification in the Korean population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic pass bias control for temperature-resilient neural networks using vertical NAND flash memory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vertical NAND (V-NAND) flash memory has emerged as a promising candidate for neuromorphic computing platforms due to its high density, scalability, and reliability. However, synaptic weights stored in V-NAND cells are highly sensitive to ambient temperature variations, resulting in significant conductance shifts that degrade the inference accuracy of neural networks. To address this challenge, we propose a dynamic pass bias (DPB) control scheme that compensates for temperature-induced weight...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letters to the Editor: rebuttal to OSIN-D-25-01417R1 "Letter to the editor concerning "Association between osteoporosis and risk of dementia: a Korean women nationwide population-based cohort study""]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Use of Late Gadolinium Enhancement and Left Ventricular Global Longitudinal Strain in Hypertrophic Cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LGE and LV-GLS provide complementary prognostic information in HCM. Patients with both increased LGE and decreased LV-GLS are at particularly high risk, highlighting the value of integrating both biomarkers for risk stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using a Vision-Language Model to Generate Visual Abstracts for Radiology Journals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between exposure to VOCs mixture and impaired renal function in Korean adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Evidence suggests that volatile organic compounds (VOCs) is linked to negative health outcomes. This study investigated the association of exposure to VOC mixtures with renal function parameters. Our study included a nationwide sample of Korean adults (n = 1758). The following nine urinary VOC metabolites were measured: SPMA, BMA, 3,4-MHA, 2-MHA, MA, 3-HPMA, BPMA, DHBMA, and PGA. Estimated glomerular filtration rate (eGFR) was calculated based on the serum creatinine levels. Urine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lace Index: Predict the High-Risk of 30-Days Readmission of Patients With Acute Myocardial Infarction: National Health Insurance Claims Data 2011-2020]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Study findings suggest the LACE index is a useful tool for predicting 30-day readmissions among AMI patients in Korea. Its simplicity and moderate accuracy support its application in clinical and policy-level risk stratification strategies. Future prospective studies should refine prediction models by incorporating additional clinical variables.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term Risk of Hydrocephalus Following Traumatic Brain Injury and Hemorrhagic Stroke: A Nationwide Cohort Study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TBI and HS are associated with a substantially increased long-term risk of hydrocephalus, especially in the early years following diagnosis. HS confers a greater risk than TBI. These findings underscore the need for prolonged surveillance in high-risk individuals and appropriate management of hydrocephalus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Managing Venous Pulsatile Tinnitus Using Intraoperative Doppler Ultrasound: How I Do It]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intraoperative Doppler ultrasound (IDU) can determine the exact location of sigmoid sinus dehiscence (SS-deh), diverticulum (SS-div) and large emissary vein (LEV). Furthermore, real-time measurement of the sufficiency during surgical SS-deh resurfacing procedures, periosteal flap insertion into the SS-div or LEV compression is possible with IDU.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expansion Pattern of Miniscrew Assisted Rapid Maxillary Expansion (MARPE) After Midpalatal Suture Separation: Clustering-Based Classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study introduces a concrete classification system for MARPE outcomes, emphasising the role of expansion efficiency and parallelism in optimising clinical results. These four identified phenotypes provide a data-driven validation of the existing concepts of expansion patterns and their implications for treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary valve-in-valve implantation using a Pulsta valve in repaired Tetralogy of Fallot]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the first case in Vietnam of transcatheter pulmonary valve-in-valve implantation using the self-expanding Pulsta valve in a young adult with repaired Tetralogy of Fallot. This case demonstrates the feasibility, safety, and early effectiveness of self-expanding valves in complex right ventricular outflow tract anatomies and highlights the importance of multimodal imaging in procedural planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of Boolean 2.0 criteria for remission and quality of life prediction in Korean patients with rheumatoid arthritis receiving targeted therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although Boolean 2.0 improves concordance with DAS28-ESR, it does not enhance the prediction of long-term functional or QoL outcomes. Its broader definition of remission warrants cautious interpretation in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Prognostic Value of the Prognostic Nutritional Index in Patients Undergoing Coronary Artery Bypass Grafting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative PNI was significantly associated with long-term mortality after coronary artery bypass grafting, and addition of PNI improved risk discrimination beyond conventional clinical models. Further prospective studies are warranted to validate these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Assessment of Condylar Bone Changes in Osteoarthritis Patients Using Single-photon emission computed tomography/computed tomography and Magnetic resonance imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study can provide the basis that SIR can be helpful in diagnosis in patients clinically suspected of having OA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure and Cardiovascular Outcomes in Adults With Diabetes and Chronic Kidney Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with diabetes and chronic kidney disease, SBP <130 mm Hg and diastolic BP <80 mm Hg were associated with reduced risk of CVD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perianal Disease Modifiers Are Associated With Less Severe Luminal Disease Activity in Children With Crohn's Disease at Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perianal fistulizing disease was more common in boys who exhibited milder disease activity, indicating the importance of recognizing perianal fistulizing disease as a clinical clue to the early diagnosis of underlying luminal CD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative Cosmetic Outcomes and Quality of Life After Thyroidectomy: A Systematic Review and Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Remote-access approaches and MIVAT offer superior cosmesis over CTA. TOA and BABA generally rank highest in both cosmesis and QOL, although evidence on QOL remains limited. These approaches may be considered for patients prioritizing aesthetic and psychosocial outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences of healthcare providers and patients with diabetes mellitus regarding continuous glucose monitoring use in South Korea: a multicenter, cross-sectional survey study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CGM provides significant clinical benefits but is limited by discomfort, costs, and educational burden. Sustained adoption requires device improvements, insurance support, and workforce expansion.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Injection-Based Therapies for Migraine in Older Adults: A Narrative Review of OnabotulinumtoxinA, Greater Occipital Nerve Block, and Anti-Calcitonin Gene-Related Peptide Monoclonal Antibodies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As global populations age, the clinical approach to managing migraine must evolve. Migraine in older adults presents unique treatment challenges due to comorbidities, poor adherence to treatment, altered pharmacokinetics, and polypharmacy. Injection -based preventive treatments such as onabotulinumtoxinA (BoNT-A), greater occipital nerve blocks (GONB), and anti-calcitonin gene-related peptide monoclonal antibodies (CGRP mAbs) offer promising alternatives. This narrative review highlights the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drawing Guideline for <em>JKMS</em> Manuscript (07) Baseline Table and Plots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The appropriate plot effectively conveys the author's conclusions to the readers. Journal of Korean Medical Science will provide a series of special articles to show you how to make consistent and excellent results easier. In this article, we will cover baseline table and plots. The baseline table is a very popular and essential table introduced in almost all medical papers, but it takes a lot of time and effort to create it. We introduce a simple yet effective tool to make this easy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary Fibrosis in Critically Ill Patients With COVID-19: A Multi-Center Retrospective Cohort Study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study demonstrated that in patients with severe COVID-19 pneumonia requiring MV, chest CT revealed fibrotic-like changes in approximately three-quarters of patients. In addition, our results suggest that higher daily doses of steroids may be associated with a reduced risk of pulmonary fibrosis. Further research is needed to determine the appropriate steroid dose that may reduce the progression of pulmonary fibrosis and improve clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Cutaneous and Genital Warts in Organ and Hematopoietic Stem Cell Transplant Patients: A Nationwide Population-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that transplantation is associated with an increased risk of both cutaneous and genital warts, with variations in risk based on age. These findings highlight the need for targeted surveillance and management strategies for wart prevention in transplant recipients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential Peripheral NLRP3 Inflammasome Expression in Parkinson's Disease and Multiple System Atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings challenge the prevailing hypothesis that NLRP3 inflammasome activation directly contributes to PD pathogenesis. Instead, the observed increase in ASC and caspase-1 expression suggests the potential involvement of alternative inflammasome pathways during disease progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiotherapy omission in low-risk, early-stage breast cancer: a single-center, real-world comparative analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Low-risk, early-stage breast cancer patients exhibited comparable disease recurrence and survival rates regardless of the RT status. Our study underscores the necessity for further investigation into RT omission in carefully selected patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility study of dose de-escalation in postoperative intensity-modulated radiation therapy for locally advanced thymoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Radiation dose de-escalation in locally advanced thymoma patients undergoing PORT showed comparable survival outcomes with reduced toxicity and shorter treatment duration, but requires longer follow-up to confirm efficacy and safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of radiotherapy in patients with intermediate- and high-risk meningiomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: RT with adjuvant or salvage intent showed favorable treatment outcomes in patients with intermediate- to high-risk meningioma. WHO grade 3 histology and recurrent tumors were identified as adverse prognostic factors for PFS in high-risk patients. LF was the dominant failure pattern after CFRT, accounting for 86.7% of all recurrences. These findings underscore the need for further studies on dose-escalated RT to enhance local control in patients with these adverse features.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is there a role of radiotherapy for steroid-resistant thyroid eye disease?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Community Care in Korea: Implementation and Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent progress in nickel oxide-based chemiresistive toxic-gas sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous advancements in technology and industry have resulted in the discharge of toxic and hazardous gases that pose a threat to human health and the environment. Consequently, developing gas-sensing devices with high sensitivities and selectivities toward these gases is crucial. In recent years, interest in sensors for gases based on p-type nickel oxide (NiO) materials has increased owing to their good catalytic activity, outstanding repeatability, high availability, excellent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum: Staphylococcus parequorum sp. nov. and Staphylococcus halotolerans sp. nov., isolated from traditional Korean soybean foods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bak and Bax are crucial for Gbp2-mediated pyroptosis during Vibrio and Salmonella infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pyroptosis a lytic form of programmed cell death, is a crucial host defense mechanism against bacterial pathogens. While caspase-mediated pathways are central to pyroptosis, the involvement of apoptotic regulators such as Bak, Bax, and MCL-1 in bacterial infection-induced pyroptosis remains unclear. Here, we investigated how these BCL-2 family proteins modulate pyroptosis induced by Vibrio vulnificus and Salmonella enterica serovar Typhimurium in murine cells. In mouse embryonic fibroblasts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PhoU interaction with the PhoR PAS domain is required for repression of the pho regulon and Salmonella virulence, but not for polyphosphate accumulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pho regulon plays a critical role in maintaining phosphate homeostasis in bacteria, with the PhoU protein functioning as a regulator that bridges the PhoB/PhoR two-component system and the PstSCAB2 phosphate transporter. While PhoU is known to suppress PhoR autophosphorylation under high phosphate conditions via interaction with its PAS domain, its broader regulatory functions remain elusive. Here, we investigated the role of the PhoU Ala147 residue in Salmonella enterica serovar Typhimurium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Additive manufacturing of MXene electrodes: from rheology-tunable nanoinks to size-scalable integrated electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Additive manufacturing (AM) has emerged as a transformative strategy for translating nanoscale materials into wafer-scale functional architectures, empowering the scalable fabrication of advanced electronics and energy systems. MXenes-a class of two-dimensional transition metal carbides and nitrides-exhibit exceptional electrical conductivity, tunable surface terminations, and mechanical compliance, positioning them as ideal candidates for AM-driven printed electronics. This review uniquely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of umbilical cord-derived mesenchymal stem cell-conditioned media for preventing and treating skin aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: UCMSC-CM is effective and safe for preventing and treating skin aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes of endoscopic resection of 1-1.5 cm sized grade 1 rectal neuroendocrine tumor: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Endoscopic resection of 1-1.5 cm grade 1 rectal NETs yielded comparable outcomes to those < 1 cm in size, suggesting its feasibility as a treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying Priority Habitats for Dung Beetle Conservation: Taxonomic and Functional Responses Across a Land-Use Disturbance Gradient]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anthropogenic activities are causing a decline in dung beetles due to land-use change and overexploitation. This underscores the need for their conservation, for which identification of high-priority habitats and associated species is necessary. To achieve this, this study evaluated taxonomic and functional diversity across various land-use types and dung types. Field experiments were conducted using dung-baited pitfall traps set up in different land-use types along a disturbance gradient: built...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative evaluation of three traditional herbal formulas on gastrointestinal motility in a mouse model of cold stress-induced dyspepsia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PS more effectively alleviated CS-induced GI dysfunction than both YT and ST. These comparative findings offer valuable insights for clinical applications in the treatment of cold-related digestive disorders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraoperative and postoperative suprachoroidal hemorrhage in pediatric patients undergoing penetrating keratoplasty or Ahmed valve implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The risk of intraoperative and delayed SCH should be considered in eyes with Peters anomaly, CG, and aniridia during intraocular surgeries that involve significant intraocular pressure fluctuations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of Birdshot Chorioretinopathy successfully treated with Adalimumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clonal Burden, Immunoglobulin Heavy Chain Variable Gene Somatic Hypermutations, and Immunoglobulin Gene Repertoire in Korean Patients with Chronic Lymphocytic Leukemia Assessed by Next-generation Sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: NGS may underestimate CLL clonal size, particularly when using the IGH leader primer set. IGHV SHMs were inversely associated with negative prognostic factors. Our data suggest ethnic differences in CLL pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex Disparities in Obesity: A Comprehensive Review of Hormonal and Genetic Influences on Obesity-Related Phenotypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Worldwide Incidence of Obesity, which tripled in 2016 from 1975, is a leading risk factor for chronic diseases. The presence of sex-dependent disparities in obesity has spurred increased interest in understanding the diverse environmental and genetic factors influencing this condition. Typically, men tend to have more visceral adipose tissue (VAT), while women generally have higher amounts of subcutaneous adipose tissue (SAT). These differences have been largely attributed to the effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genesis of Bolus Pressure During Primary Peristalsis: Key to Understanding "Functional Dysphagia"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS & INFERENCES: In patients with FD, bolus pressure is partly related to the compression of the manometry catheter by the esophageal wall. The proportion of BP-positive, bolus-negative areas in the BD distinguishes FD patients and controls.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-Transplant Outcomes in Patients with Previously Treated Extrahepatic Malignancies Undergoing Living Donor Liver Transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND Post-transplant outcomes were analyzed in adult patients with primary extrahepatic malignancies (EHM) who underwent living donor liver transplantation (LDLT). Few studies to date have analyzed post-transplant outcomes in adult patients with primary extrahepatic malignancies (EHM) who underwent LDLT. MATERIAL AND METHODS The study cohort included 109 patients who were treated for EHM more than 6 months before LDLT between January 2000 and December 2022. The clinicopathological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative red blood cell transfusion in gallbladder cancer surgery: Trends and determinants from nationwide data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative RBC transfusion rates in patients with GBC have declined over the past decade. Nevertheless, women, patients with lower income, and those managed at non-tertiary hospitals continue to receive transfusions at higher rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor-priming CD8<sup>+</sup> natural killer T-like cells as an efficient novel cell therapy for relapsed/refractory multiple myeloma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TPNC represents a novel cytotoxic lymphocyte product generated through tumor-driven priming. Their dual recognition capacity, functional versatility, and favorable safety profile highlight their potential as a scalable and personalized immunotherapy platform for hematologic malignancies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of core temperature monitoring methods during cytoreductive surgery with hyperthermic intraperitoneal chemotherapy: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: All three monitoring methods correlated strongly overall, but Teso exhibited phase-dependent discrepancies, particularly after HIPEC. These findings support tailoring core temperature measurement site selection with attention to the target organ, especially in laparotomy-based HIPEC procedures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helicobacter pylori infection is associated with an increased risk of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease and asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: H. pylori infection is associated with an increased risk of COPD and asthma. The risk of asthma was consistent across age groups and smoking statuses; in contrast, the risk of COPD varied. The findings of the present study underscore the pathophysiological interactions between chronic inflammation in the stomach and the lungs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between prescription patterns and primary care clinic closures in South Korea: A longitudinal retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Steroid and benzodiazepine prescriptions were linked to lower clinic closure risk, while antibiotic and injectable prescriptions were not. These findings suggest that evidence-based prescribing may not compromise clinic viability and that appropriate care and sustainability can be achieved together through informed policy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploration of Likert scale in terms of continuous variable with parametric statistical methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complete genome sequence of Streptococcus hominis isolated from subgingival biofilm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Streptococcus hominis is a recently described species within the genus Streptococcus, yet its genomic characteristics remain poorly understood, particularly in the context of the oral microbiome. Previously, only two complete genomes from non-oral sources were available. To address this gap, we sequenced and analyzed S. hominis strain KHUD_010, isolated from the subgingival biofilm of a healthy Korean adult.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STALARD: Selective Target Amplification for Low-Abundance RNA Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: STALARD provides a sensitive, simple, and accessible method for isoform-level quantification of low-abundance transcripts that share a known 5'-end sequence. Its compatibility with both qPCR and long-read sequencing makes it a versatile tool for analyzing transcript variants and identifying previously uncharacterized 3'-end structures, provided that isoform-specific 5'-end sequences are known in advance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of liver stereotactic body radiotherapy plans based on free breathing and averaged CTs after trans-arterial chemoembolization using lipiodol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: For liver SBRT with lipiodol retention, 3D plans based on FB and AVG images were virtually equivalent in producing the 4D cumulative doses under the accuracy of the XVMC algorithm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of adenovirus-based oncolytic virus to induce EBV lytic reactivation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ad-TBZ demonstrates potent and selective antitumor activity against EBVaGC through hTERTp-mediated selective replication and BZLF1-induced EBV lytic reactivation. These findings support Ad-TBZ as a promising novel monotherapeutic strategy for EBVaGC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Context-Aware Prompting Techniques for Classification of Tumor Response Categories in Radiology Reports Using Large Language Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiology reports are essential for medical decision-making, providing crucial data for diagnosing diseases, devising treatment plans, and monitoring disease progression. While large language models (LLMs) have shown promise in processing free-text reports, research on effective prompting techniques for radiologic applications remains limited. To evaluate the effectiveness of LLM-driven classification based on radiology reports in terms of tumor response category (TRC), and to optimize the model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward new clinical evaluation models for skin longevity: the need for predictive and accelerated approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Readability versus accuracy in LLM-transformed radiology reports: stakeholder preferences across reading grade levels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher-grade levels were generally preferred due to better accuracy, with a range of 12-17. Further increasing grade levels reduced readability sharply, limiting preference. These findings highlight the limitations of unsupervised LLM transformations and suggest the need for hybrid approaches that maintain original reports while incorporating explanatory content to balance accuracy and readability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychophysical dissection of temporal error monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The recent line of research robustly demonstrated that humans and rodents can keep track of the magnitude and direction of timing errors, composing a temporal error monitoring ability (TEM). However, the degree of dissociation between these two measures of TEM has not been investigated at the level of the underlying mental magnitude metrics. Specifically, we do not know whether the two behavioral manifestations of TEM differentially rely on subjective vs. objective time, whether the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comment on: "Anatomical distribution and prognostic heterogeneity in glioma: unique clinical features of occipital glioblastoma"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Strategy for occipital isolation by disconnecting convergent white matter fibers. A region of interest (ROI, yellow sphere) was placed in the occipital lobe, and tractography shows streamlines from the ROI. Two major bundles course along the bottom of the parietooccipital fissure (POF) and the trigone of the lateral ventricle. The anterior resection border (light-blue line) is defined by a line connecting the bottom of the POF to the trigone; the lateral resection border (green line) corresponds...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postmastectomy radiation therapy for implant-based breast reconstruction: a systematic review and meta-analysis for the 2022 Japanese Breast Cancer Society Clinical Practice Guideline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This meta-analysis demonstrated that PMRT in implant-based breast reconstruction is associated with a significantly increased risk of adverse outcomes. Given these risks, treatment decisions should involve through discussions with patients to ensure that they are fully informed of the potential benefits and complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a machine learning model for early prediction of intensive care unit acquired weakness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Machine learning models, especially random forests, can be used to predict if patients are at risk of developing ICU-AW, using data available within 24 h of admission. This tool allows prognostication early in an adult general critically ill patient population, with the potential to detect high cost and high need patients who benefit from different levels of care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>In situ</em> observation of polyurea formation by rapid-scan time-resolved infrared spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyurea and its derivatives exhibit excellent physical and chemical properties originating from intermolecular hydrogen bonding. Consequently, they have been used as coating materials that are resistant to heat, water, and chemicals, and in recent years, as materials for 3D printers. Their properties depend on their formation and hydrogen bonding mechanisms; however, these processes are very fast, making them challenging to study experimentally. In this study, polyurea formation via the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transperineal Ultrasound Immediately After Birth to Predict Postpartum Anorectal Dysfunction: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The presence of levator avulsion immediately after vaginal delivery predicts postpartum AI. Ultrasound appearance of the anal sphincter, genital hiatus and rectovaginal septum was not informative.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential modulation of adipose tissue insulin resistance by modified traditional Japanese diet and SGLT-2 inhibitor canagliflozin in type 2 diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This prospective observational study investigated the differential modulation of metabolic parameters by modified traditional Japanese dietary therapy for diabetes (MJDD) and SGLT-2 inhibitor canagliflozin in treatment-naïve patients with T2DM. Particular emphasis was placed on adipose tissue insulin resistance (adipo-IR). Newly diagnosed, drug-naïve T2DM patients were treated with either MJDD (n = 53) or canagliflozin (n = 55) for 3 months. Key metabolic indices-including BMI, FBG, HbA1c,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor response and thyroglobulin change in differentiated thyroid carcinoma treated with dabrafenib plus trametinib]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tg changes during dabrafenib plus trametinib treatment may not be associated with clinical response to dabrafenib plus trametinib treatment. Further study is needed to clarify the association between Tg level or inflammatory biomarkers change and clinical response to dabrafenib plus trametinib treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis and Structure-Activity Relationship Studies of Truncated Artificial Analogues of Amphidinol 3]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structure-activity relationship studies of artificial analogues of amphidinol 3 (AM3) were conducted. Based on the truncated molecule corresponding to the C21-C67 section of AM3, which elicited comparable antifungal activity to the parent compound, its stereoisomers were synthesized from polyol, bis-THP, and polyene units via Suzuki-Miyaura coupling and Julia-Kocienski olefination. Variants at both polyol and polyene termini were also synthesized. Evaluation of the antifungal activity of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRISPR/Cas9-directed disruption of wc-2 leads to absence of fruiting body development in Pleurotus ostreatus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Light, particularly blue light, is a key environmental factor that induces fruiting in certain agaricomycetes. In this study, we characterised mutant strains of Pleurotus ostreatus with disrupted wc-2, which encodes one of the white-collar proteins, Wc-2, to investigate the role of light in fruiting in P. ostreatus. We introduced two different plasmids containing expression cassettes for Cas9 and two different gRNAs targeting wc-2 separately into the dikaryotic P. ostreatus strain PC9×#64. Among...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variation in sperm motility and seminal protein expression is shaped by pre- and post-mating sexual selection in the mouthbrooding cichlid (Ophthalmotilapia ventralis)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sexual selection is a key driver of reproductive strategy evolution; however, its molecular mechanisms remain poorly understood. In the mouthbrooding Tanganyikan cichlid (Ophthalmotilapia ventralis), fertilization occurs in the female mouth cavity, where sperm competition and post-mating female choice arise because females collect sperm from multiple territorial males. Seminal plasma glycoprotein 120 (SPP120) is involved in sperm immobilization and aggregation, which may contribute to prolonged...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thymic Stromal Lymphopoietin Promotes Ozone-induced Inflammation in the Airway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ozone is associated with induction of airway hyperresponsiveness (AHR) and neutrophilic airway inflammation which is the characteristic of type 2 low inflammatory phenotype. Recently, epithelial cell-derived cytokines such as thymic stromal lymphopoietin (TSLP) have been recognized as therapeutic targets for asthma with type 2 low inflammation, but the mechanisms remain unknown. In the present study, BALB/c mice and TSLP receptor-deficient mice were exposed to ozone at 2 ppm for 3 hours. AHR,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FRET-based biosensor moxCRONOS enables quantitative monitoring of macromolecular crowding in organelles and protein aggregates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macromolecular crowding is a fundamental property of the intracellular environment that influences protein folding, enzymatic activity, and phase behavior. Disruptions to the homeostasis of macromolecular crowding can drive pathological processes, such as aberrant liquid-liquid phase separation and protein aggregation, which are central features of several neurodegenerative diseases. However, tools for quantifying crowding and aggregation remain limited. Here, we describe moxCRONOS, a Förster...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of viral activators of the HSV-2 UL13 protein kinase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although previous studies reported that the herpes simplex virus 2 (HSV-2) UL13 protein kinase mediates the phosphorylation of elongation factor 1δ (EF-1δ) in infected cells, we found here that individual expression of UL13 was insufficient to induce phosphorylation of EF-1δ in mammalian cells. This led us to hypothesize that HSV-2 UL13 requires viral cofactors for full kinase activity and prompted us to identify such cofactors. Our results were as follows. (i) Co-expression of UL13 with UL55 or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ampere-Level Electrosynthesis of CO via Well-Defined Pyridinic-N Incorporated Cobalt Phthalocyanine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-rate CO electrosynthesis from CO(2) is vital for efficient CO(2)-CO-C(2+) tandem conversion. Cobalt phthalocyanine (CoPc), featuring a Co-N(4) site naturally favorable for CO production, suffers from low conductivity. Herein, a molecular engineering strategy is reported to construct cobalt tetra-aza-phthalocyanine (CoTAP) by incorporating four pyridinic-N atoms at the β-positions of the CoPc macrocyclic backbone, effectively enhancing both conductivity and intrinsic activity. The resulting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of starting dose of tyrosine kinase inhibitors on outcomes following combination therapy of immune checkpoint inhibitors with tyrosine kinase inhibitors for previously untreated advanced renal cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The starting dose of TKIs did not significantly impact clinical outcomes following IO-TKI for RCC. These findings suggest a potential for the optimization of the starting dose of TKIs; however, prospective studies are warranted to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hygromycin B Is a Highly Versatile Inducer of Secondary Metabolite Production Applicable Across Diverse Fungal Taxa]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hygromycin B, a well-known antibiotic agent, was recently reported as an inducer of secondary metabolites for a fungal strain of Fusarium sp. In this study, we verified the versatility and usefulness of hygromycin B as an inducer of fungal secondary metabolite production. We demonstrate that hygromycin B induces the production of various fungal secondary metabolites, including polyketides, peptides, and terpenes, in 71% of 28 fungal strains belonging to the Ascomycota phylum, specifically within...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clonal hematopoiesis of indeterminate potential and the risk of cognitive impairment in the Women's Health Initiative Memory Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Clonal hematopoiesis of indeterminate potential (CHIP) confers an increased risk of several chronic aging-related diseases. Paradoxically, CHIP was associated with lower risk of dementia in recent studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlating Urinary Tract Infection Risks With Sodium-Glucose Cotransporter-2 Inhibitors: Insights From the National Health Insurance Data of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this large population-based cohort study, the use of SGLT2is was not associated with a statistically significant increase in the risk of UTIs. Although SGLT2i use is linked to increased glucose excretion in urine, this study indicates that the clinical impact on UTI risk is minimal. Overall, continuous monitoring and patient education regarding UTI symptoms remain to be important in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning-Integrated Electrochemical Sensors for Accurate and Continuous Free Chlorine Monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate and continuous monitoring of free chlorine concentrations is essential for ensuring water safety in applications such as drinking water disinfection and food sanitation. Traditional methods for free chlorine detection, including colorimetry and photometry, often involve complex sample preparation and lack real-time monitoring capabilities. Electrochemical sensors provide a promising alternative; however, their long-term accuracy is affected by pH variations, electrode surface...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ufisonitriles A and B, Antimalarial Isonitriles with Mitochondrial Function Inhibitory Activity Produced by <em>Amycolatopsis</em> sp. OK19-0009]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two novel antimalarials, named ufisonitriles A (1) and B (2), were isolated by bioassay-guided fractionation on mitochondrial function inhibitory activity using multidrug-sensitive budding yeast from the cultured broth of the Okinawan rare actinomycete Amycolatopsis sp. OK19-0009 strain. Their structures were comprehensively elucidated using HR-ESI-MS and 1D/2D NMR analyses and the modified Mosher's method. Structurally, 1 and 2 possess a novel skeleton with an isocyano group. In vitro...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proton Conduction, Dielectric Relaxation, Photoluminescence, and Photochromism Governed by Humidity and Alcohol Vapors in a Uranyl-Cobalt Framework with Labile Coordination Sites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stimuli-responsive coordination polymers serve as an efficient platform for the generation of functional systems, showing tunable magnetic, electrical, optical, and mechanical features, as well as their rich combinations. We report a truly multifunctional material based on a coordination framework employing photoluminescent uranyl(VI) cations bonded through cyanido bridges to cobalt(III) centers and between themselves by hydroxido and 1,4-diazabicyclo[2.2.2]octane-N,N'-dioxide linkers. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the Symposium "Concept of Integrated Approaches to Testing and Assessment (IATA) Using New Approach Methods (NAMs) -Learning from the Study of Thyroid Hormone System and Developmental Neurotoxicity-"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Food Safety Commission of Japan (FSCJ) hosted a symposium entitled "Concept of Integrated Approaches to Testing and Assessment (IATA) Using New Approach Methods (NAMs) -Learning from the Study of Thyroid Hormone System and Developmental Neurotoxicity-" to deepen our understanding on the application of NAMs through practical examples. The symposium took place at FSCJ meeting room (Akasaka, Minato-ku, Tokyo) on December 5th, 2024, attracting a total of 21 on-site attendees as well as 153 online...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Anisakis</em> Contamination in Fillets of Chub Mackerel and Blue Mackerel Sold in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the risk of anisakiasis, we investigated their prevalence in fillets of chub mackerel and blue mackerel in 2022 and 2023. The results indicated that the prevalence (percent of larvae-positive fillet samples) and abundance (number of larvae per 100 g fillet) of Anisakis larvae in fillets of chub mackerel were not significantly different between the Sea of Japan and the Pacific Ocean. The prevalence and abundance of Anisakis larvae in blue mackerel were markedly lower than those in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of Outbreaks Caused by <em>Clostridium Perfringens</em> in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clostridium perfringens is one of most problematic foodborne bacteria in Japan. The number of outbreaks caused by C. perfringens has not decreased. To clarify the characteristics of outbreaks in Japan, data in Annual Statistics of Food Poisoning Japan from 2000 to 2022 published by Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare, Japan was analyzed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling the gut-liver axis in autoimmune liver disease overlap syndrome: A multi-omics perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autoimmune liver disease overlap syndrome (OS) is a rare and clinically significant condition that has received limited attention in microbiome research. In their recent study, Wang et al combined 16S rRNA sequencing with untargeted metabolomics to characterize the gut-liver axis in OS, identifying shared features of dysbiosis in autoimmune hepatitis (AIH) and primary biliary cholangitis (PBC), and unique signatures, including enrichment of Klebsiella and Escherichia and depletion of aromatic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Explainable artificial intelligence for personalized management of inflammatory bowel disease: A minireview of recent advances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Personalized management of inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) is crucial due to the heterogeneity in disease presentation, variable therapeutic response, and the unpredictable nature of disease progression. Although artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning algorithms offer promising solutions by analyzing complex, multidimensional patient data, the "black-box" nature of many AI models limits their clinical adoption. Explainable AI (XAI) addresses this challenge by making data-driven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laeverin is Cell-Surface Target for Liquid-Phase Metastasizing Cancer Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Laeverin (LVRN) is a cell-surface immunoregulatory factor that is specifically expressed in embryo-derived extravillous trophoblast, which invades maternal spiral arteries without immune rejection during human placentation. Here, it is found that various epithelial cancer cell lines upregulated LVRN expression in association with the expression of POU5F1 after spheroid formation under floating conditions. Immunohistochemically, LVRN expression is detected in the lesions of vascular, lymphatic,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simultaneous measurement of apalutamide and N-desmethylapalutamide in human plasma using high-performance liquid chromatography with ultraviolet detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The combination of apalutamide, a nonsteroidal androgen receptor inhibitor, with androgen deprivation therapy enhances survival in patients with metastatic castration-sensitive prostate cancer. However, apalutamide exhibits complex pharmacokinetics and dose-dependent adverse effects, necessitating dose adjustments to optimize its therapeutic outcomes. To facilitate effective monitoring, a high-performance liquid chromatography (HPLC) system coupled with an ultraviolet (UV) detector...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A link to the past: classical phage ISP infects the recently described Staphylococcus borealis species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: here we expand the known host range of the traditional phage ISP by showing that it also infects S. borealis and can be adapted to the new host by serial passages, showcasing the flexibility of phages as an antimicrobial strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical effect of radical debris evacuation with a flexible neuroendoscope on patients with ventriculitis: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Neuroendoscopic radical debris evacuation in patients with ventriculitis may shorten the duration between the initial treatment and shunt surgery and potentially reduce the proportion of patients requiring shunt surgery. This effect is likely due to the attenuation of ventricular inflammation, contributing to improved clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hsa-miR-155-5p expression in primary breast tissue may have the potential for prediction of breast cancer brain recurrence: results from the multi-institutional exploratory cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Hsa-miR-155-5p expression in untreated primary breast tissue may be a valuable biomarker for predicting BCBR. A personalized escalation strategy is expected to be helpful in conquering brain metastases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The safety and efficacy of finasteride for transgender men with androgenetic alopecia: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Finasteride appears to be a safe and effective treatment for androgenetic alopecia in transgender men undergoing testosterone replacement therapy. However, its potential for reducing some of the effects of testosterone replacement therapy warrants further investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication of lingual fixed retainers on 2D prints: testing A novel workflow]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Calibrated 2D prints can be successfully used to fabricate LFRs. All 2D and 3D LFRs were deliverable. Conventional casts produced superior LFR fit than 2D prints.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive survival analysis of breast cancer patients: a bayesian network approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Through the integration of validated parametric survival models with a data-driven BBN, this study delivers a comprehensive framework for estimating individualized survival probabilities and visualizing the complex probabilistic relationships that characterize high-risk cancer patient profiles. This approach supports evidence-based, personalized breast cancer management and demonstrates the potential for guiding clinical decision-making and adapting to diverse external patient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Specialty and age-based differences in awareness and attitudes towards antibiotic stewardship: a cross-sectional online survey on Japanese clinic physicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights significant variability in AMR awareness and adherence across specialties and age groups. Internal medicine physicians showed the highest adherence, while pediatricians were the most familiar with AMR manuals. Otorhinolaryngologists demonstrated strong awareness but lower adherence. Targeted educational interventions, particularly focusing on older physicians and specific specialties, are needed to improve antimicrobial use and combat the growing threat of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abemaciclib-associated acute interstitial nephritis successfully treated with glucocorticoids: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We report a case of biopsy-proven AIN that developed shortly after the initiation of abemaciclib, leading to severe renal dysfunction with nephromegaly. While prolonged use of CDK4/6 inhibitors can cause both AIN and ATN, AIN can also occur after short-term use, highlighting the importance of a renal biopsy to determine the need for glucocorticoid therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of high-risk age groups for cisplatin-induced nausea and vomiting in young patients with sarcoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variable efficiency of nonsense-mediated mRNA decay across human tissues, tumors and individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Nonsense-mediated mRNA decay (NMD) is a quality-control pathway that degrades mRNA bearing premature termination codons (PTCs) resulting from mutation or mis-splicing, and that additionally participates in gene regulation of unmutated transcripts. While NMD activity is known to differ between examples of PTCs, it is less well studied if human tissues differ in NMD activity, or if individuals differ.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrocardiogram characteristics and possible associated factors in healthy Japanese children: the Tohoku Medical Megabank Project Birth and Three-Generation Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study described the ECG characteristics of Japanese children and found a relation between parents and children. ECG parameters in children aged 4-9 correlate with those in their parents, but not with sex or BMI. In particular, mother's ECG was strongly associated with that of children than father's ECG. The relation might be reflected by both genetic background and uterine environment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative effectiveness of antiviral treatment on household transmission of SARS-CoV-2: a retrospective cohort study using administrative data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Household transmission rates were not statistically different among three different outpatient oral antiviral agents. Hospitalization was associated with a trend toward lower transmission rates, possibly due to physical isolation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neoadjuvant chemotherapy strategies for optimizing safety and efficacy in elderly patients with locally advanced gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: NAC can be safely administered to elderly patients by increasing cycles while reducing per-cycle dosage. It may also serve as a viable alternative to upfront surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revisiting Religion and BMI: Recent Evidence from Australia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the association between religion and body mass index (BMI) for a representative sample of the Australian population. We used data from five waves of the Household Income Labour Dynamics Australia (HILDA) Survey to analyse responses from 58,694 adults aged 18+. Our OLS regression analysis reveals that religious affiliation significantly influences BMI for both men and women, even after controlling for sociodemographic factors, health behaviour and psychological variables....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and predictors of postoperative atrial fibrillation in patients with preoperative sinus rhythm undergoing cardiac or aortic surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Postoperative atrial fibrillation (POAF) is frequent after cardiac or aortic surgery and is linked to adverse outcomes. We evaluated the incidence and independent predictors of POAF in patients with preoperative sinus rhythm. We conducted a single-center retrospective cohort study of 78 patients undergoing cardiac or aortic surgery (May 2022-December 2024). POAF during the index hospitalization was modeled using multivariable logistic regression with three prespecified predictors: transmitral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Evaluation of Nemolizumab Pharmacokinetics and Efficacy in Prurigo Nodularis: A Population Pharmacokinetics and Model-Based Meta-analysis Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The PopPK and PopPD models well described the PK and PD profiles of nemolizumab in patients with PN. MBMA demonstrated that nemolizumab was superior to dupilumab in improving response rates in patients with PN. These findings, derived from pharmacometrics modeling and indirect comparison, may help inform future clinical studies and support the ongoing evaluation of nemolizumab in PN.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Doctrine of the Mean and Doctor-Patient Relationship: Proposal for the Doctor-Seeking-the-Mean Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Our experience in day-to-day medical practice suggests that the nature of the doctor-patient relationship (DPR) is considerably influenced by the attitudes of the individual patient and doctor. The DPR will also be significantly influenced by the social environment, including the healthcare system in which it develops. In addition, cultural influences on the DPR and its overriding ethical principles cannot be ignored. Moreover, the DPR cannot escape the influence of various coincidences. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The outcome of extracardiac lateral tunnel total cavopulmonary connection with growing conduit using expanded polytetrafluoroethylene graft]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Long-term results of the Fontan operation with extracardiac lateral tunnel using half cut expanded polytetrafluoroethylene graft and outside of the right atrium were favorable. Proportional increase of conduit size was demonstrated, suggesting a potential of the conduit to grow and that the growth might correlate with somatic growth.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient knowledge-based planning model construction in institutions with limited cases using plan quality metrics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prostate cancer volumetric modulated arc therapy (VMAT) planning often faces challenges in the construction of high-quality RapidPlan models when the number of cases is limited. In the present study, we retrospectively scored 90 VMAT plans using Plan Quality Metrics (PQM) and Adjusted PQM (APQM) and constructed 12 RapidPlan models from various combinations of cases with high and low PQM or APQM scores, each trained on 30 cases. Six representative models were selected for a detailed evaluation,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multidisciplinary surgical management with chemotherapy and transcatheter arterial embolization for a giant hypervascular pancreatic neuroendocrine tumor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic neuroendocrine tumors (pNETs) are rare and heterogeneous neoplasms occasionally presenting as giant, hypervascular, and anatomically complex tumors. In such cases, curative resection is often challenging, and multidisciplinary treatment is required. However, the clinical utility and optimal sequencing for these approaches remain unclear. We report a 39-year-old woman with a 130 mm hypervascular pNET occupying nearly the entire pancreas, complicated by portal vein tumor thrombus (PVTT)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differentiation of acute-phase AQP4-IgG+ optic neuritis from CNS inflammatory diseases using optic nerve head blood flow analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis of optic neuritis (ON) associated with aquaporin-4 immunoglobulin-G (AQP4-IgG), myelin oligodendrocyte glycoprotein immunoglobulin-G (MOG-IgG), or multiple sclerosis (MS) is challenging due to invasive and time-consuming tests. We investigated whether ophthalmologic assessments, including laser speckle flowgraphy (LSFG) and optical coherence tomography (OCT), are useful for distinguishing among these diseases at ON onset. This retrospective study included 10 AQP4-IgG+ON patients,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling corium pool stratification and focusing effect in APR1400 using a multiphase CFD framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurately predicting molten corium behavior is critical for assessing severe accident scenarios in nuclear reactors, particularly under In-Vessel Corium Retention with Reactor Vessel External Cooling (IVCR-RVEC) strategies. This study presents a high-fidelity computational framework developed in OpenFOAM to simulate multiphase heat transfer and vessel ablation during corium pool formation. Two approaches are evaluated: the traditional Enthalpy-Porosity (EP) method and a newly implemented...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design, Synthesis, and Biological Activity Evaluation of Flavonol Derivatives Containing Piperazine and Piperidine Thiourea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A series of flavonol derivatives incorporating piperazine and piperidine thiourea moieties were designed and synthesized. The compounds were evaluated for their activity against 8 plant pathogenic fungi and 6 plant pathogenic bacteria in vitro. Among them, Q23 had better inhibitory activity against Phytophthora capsici (P. c.) with an EC(50) of 6.68 μg/mL, outperforming the positive control azoxystrobin (Az, EC(50)= 72.60 μg/mL). Mechanistic studies indicated that Q23 inhibits fungal growth by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Integrated Nucleic Acid Sequence-Based Amplification (NASBA) and CRISPR-Cas13a-Based Platform for Accurate and Sensitive Detection of Cucumber Mosaic Virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cucumber mosaic virus (CMV) is a highly prevalent ssRNA viral crop pathogen that contributes to substantial losses in agricultural productivity worldwide. The first step in managing the impact of this pathogen is an accurate and timely diagnosis. However, current sensing strategies are hampered by several limitations, including insufficient sensitivity, off-target effects, and the need for complex instrumentation. To address these challenges, we refined a highly specific and sensitive system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Self-Efficacy Through Robotic Safety Support in Balance-Challenging Reach Tasks: Feasibility Study in Young Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The fall impact mitigation robot significantly improved self-efficacy during challenging balance tasks, despite providing no active physical support. These findings underscore the role of psychological reassurance in modulating balance-related behavior and suggest that robotic safety systems may influence motor performance through psychological mechanisms. Integrating psychological support into robotic fall prevention strategies may enhance their effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Barriers to Discharge for Nursing Home Residents With Serious Mental Illness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This qualitative study found that multiple intersecting barriers are associated with discharging nursing home residents with serious mental illness back to the community, which may lead to clinically inappropriate long-term stays for those who could theoretically have been in a lower level of care setting. These findings suggest that enabling successful discharge to the community for nursing home residents with serious mental illness may require collaborative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Home-Delivered Nutrition Services for Older Adults Under the Older Americans Act]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The findings of this qualitative study of home-delivered nutrition services for older adults suggest that home-delivered meals programs achieved their intended outcomes and yielded meaningful benefits beyond their stated purpose that remain to be quantified. The findings also support funding the Older Americans Act Nutrition Program.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbon dots endow glucose oxidase with autocatalytic features and anti-poisoning ability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glucose oxidase (GOx), an essential biocatalyst widely employed in food processing, pharmaceutical manufacturing, and bioenergy systems, faces persistent challenges in activity enhancement, stability improvement, and inhibitor resistance. Here, we demonstrate that hybrids of GOx and carbon dots (GOx-CDs) fundamentally transform GOx functionality through critical advancements. The hybrids exhibit a 387% greater catalytic activity compared with native GOx, accompanied by significantly enhanced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metacognitive Awareness of Lipreading Gains in Young and Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: While younger and older adults share similar awareness of lipreading benefits in speech perception, reduced sensitivity to effort reduction may impact older adults' motivation to use lipreading in everyday communication. Given the role of perceived effort in strategy adoption, these findings highlight the importance of addressing effort perceptions in interventions aimed at improving communication in aging populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Intravenous Racemic Ketamine on Global Severity and Individual Symptoms of Depression: An Exploratory Retrospective Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Maintenance intravenous racemic ketamine therapy demonstrated significant, persistent, and broad efficacy for treatment-resistant depression as demonstrated by reductions in Montgomery-Åsberg Depression Rating Scale and Patient-Health Questionnaire-9 total scores and equivocal changes in every item on both rating scales. The magnitude of change in individual items was similar to that of previous randomized trials, with suicidal ideation and depression demonstrating the largest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging trends and clinical challenges in AI-enhanced emotion diagnosis using physiological data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review explores the relationships between physiological parameters and emotions, as well as the potential value and applications of the use of machine learning to facilitate emotion recognition. First, the relationships between physiological parameters (such as heart rate, respiration, blood pressure, galvanic skin response, electroencephalography, and heart rate variability [HRV]) and emotions are discussed. The impacts of emotional states on these physiological parameters represent a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perspective on strengthening dementia prevention and control system: a comprehensive framework for national health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging ChatGPT for Report Error Audit: An Accuracy-Driven and Cost-Efficient Solution for Ophthalmic Imaging Reports]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GPT-4o effectively enhances the accuracy of ophthalmic imaging reports by identifying and correcting common errors. Its implementation can potentially alleviate the workload of ophthalmologists, streamline the reporting process, and reduce associated costs, thereby improving overall clinical workflow and patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From modeling to therapy: the efficient and precise tools for mitochondrial base editing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pre-incubation with levocarnitine alleviates vitrification and thawing damage in mouse oocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Supplementation of LC to mouse oocytes before vitrification can improve their warming outcomes, which is related to the changes in lipid droplet distribution in oocytes caused by LC by improving lipid metabolism.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic analysis and immunotherapy prediction based on key receptor-ligand pairs of bladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our risk prediction model significantly improves the evaluation of prognosis and the prediction of immunotherapy responsiveness in bladder cancer patients. This advancement promotes the development of precise, individualized treatment strategies for bladder cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation between a healthy lifestyle index, quality of life, and depression in Iranian individuals with cardiovascular disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results highlight the importance of promoting physical activity, reducing alcohol consumption, and encouraging social engagement as key components of healthy lifestyle interventions for patients with CVD. These strategies may effectively improve QoL and reduce depressive symptoms, underscoring the need for holistic and behaviorally focused approaches in the routine care of cardiovascular patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vulvodynia: still a dramatically neglected condition. A position statement on pathogenetic mechanisms from the Italian Society of Andrology and Sexual Medicine (SIAMS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The crucial role of explainable artificial intelligence (XAI) in improving health care management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This current opinion explores the transformative potential of explainable artificial intelligence (XAI) for health care management systems. While AI has already demonstrated substantial benefits in clinical decision-making, operational efficiency and patient outcomes, its adoption is often hindered by the lack of transparency in AI-driven decision-making. XAI bridges this gap by providing interpretability, thereby increasing trust between policy-makers, clinicians, administrators and patients....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Granulopoietic Dysregulation in a Patient-Tailored Mouse Model of Barth Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Voxel-wise analysis of brain metastasis predilection sites in breast cancer by clinical features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The preferred locations of breast cancer with brain metastases could be observed based on different clinical and biological characteristics, which could be clues for further study and helpful for clinical strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a health-related social need screener for adults soon to be, and recently released, from incarceration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incisor position objective for favorable profile in orthodontic camouflage treatment of skeletal class II cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In skeletal Class II orthodontic camouflage treatment, the relatively favorable post-treatment profiles are associated with the U1 position anterior to the ANS-Pog line. U1-ANPo of around 4.7 mm could be tentatively proposed as a practical IPO reference in treatment planning for such cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930152006&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>