<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 07:44:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term safety and treatment discontinuation patterns of OnabotulinumtoxinA for post-stroke spasticity: a retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Repeated onabotulinumtoxinA injections were not associated with unexpected safety concerns over long-term follow-up. Approximately 25% of patients discontinued treatment during the observation period, including cases documented as treatment completion due to clinical improvement. Stroke type was associated with treatment discontinuation patterns, supporting the importance of individualized long-term treatment planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to "Conclusions about a link between SAPHO syndrome, IgA nephropathy and dental amalgams can only be drawn after extensive analysis" by Delrieu et al]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reply to "Matters arising: Conclusions about a link between SAPHO syndrome, IgA nephropathy and dental amalgams can only be drawn after extensive analysis" by Delrieu et al. (2025).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PpZAT12 from a native Kentucky bluegrass (Poa pratensis L.) confers drought tolerance through regulating antioxidant defense system and multiple metabolic pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimized library preparation, sequencing, and data analysis protocols for the generation of orbivirus consensus sequences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Whole genome sequencing (WGS) via next-generation sequencing (NGS) platforms offers a powerful approach for investigating viral genetic diversity. Orbiviruses are an economically important group of arboviruses with a double-stranded RNA (dsRNA) genome consisting of 10 segments. Traditional approaches to virus sequencing relied primarily on processing with various treatments such as lithium chloride to enrich dsRNAs and then sequencing on Illumina platforms due to its lower error rate. To reduce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alternative malonyl-CoA pathways for microbial production of diverse products]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Malonyl-CoA serves as a central precursor for the biosynthesis of diverse high-value compounds, including lipids, organic acids, and polyketides, in engineered microbial fermentation systems. However, insufficient malonyl-CoA supply often limits the production of these products. Intracellular malonyl-CoA levels are tightly regulated by the activities of acetyl-CoA carboxylase (ACC) and fatty acid synthesis pathway enzymes. Although strategies have been developed to redirect malonyl-CoA flux from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Water- and Light-Stable Red-Emitting Perovskite Quantum Dots by Silane-Siloxane Dual Encapsulation for Full-Color Displays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Red-emitting perovskite quantum dots (Red-PQDs) are highly crucial components for achieving full-color PQD-based color-converters. However, red-PQDs are particularly prone to degradation due to their highly ionic bonding nature, phase instability, and insufficient surface passivation. Developing highly stable red-PQDs in diverse environments remains a critical barrier to their practical implementation as light emitters in displays. Here, we report a long-term stable red-PQD through a dual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating deep learning-based surrogate modeling into urban forest allocation optimization for maximizing carbon sequestration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Urban afforestation has emerged as a key strategy for enhancing carbon sequestration to mitigate climate change. However, afforestation strategies driven by area-expansion targets can overlook the spatial heterogeneity of carbon uptake and the synergistic effects of ecological connectivity. This study presents an integrated optimization framework that incorporates a deep learning-based surrogate model, combining an Artificial Neural Network (ANN) with a Genetic Algorithm (GA), to optimize...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Additive manufacturing of metastructures at the micro- and nano-scale]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of additive manufacturing techniques offers more opportunities for fabricating complex structures with designed properties that are challenging to achieve using traditional manufacturing methods. Micro-/nano-scale metastructures are among the most promising applications of additive manufacturing and are composed of meta-atoms at the subwavelength scale with artificial design, which enables the creation of materials and structures with tailored and programmable properties that go...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protein synthesis blockade prevents fear memory reactivation via inhibition of engram synapse strengthening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memory relies on ensembles of engram cells in the brain. While previous studies have established the existence of these cells, the relationship between cellular and synaptic activity remains unclear. To address this, we applied the dual-enhanced green fluorescent protein reconstitution across synaptic partners (dual-eGRASP) technique in mice to examine synaptic connectivity between the ventral CA1 and the basal amygdala during memory formation. We found that contextual fear conditioning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Access to Hindered Alkyl Aryl Ethers via Radical-Polar Crossover C(sp<sup>3</sup>)-O Coupling Enabled by Dual Organosulfur/Photoredox Catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A dual organosulfur/photoredox catalytic method for radical-polar crossover (RPC) C(sp³)-O coupling between phenols and alkyl radical precursors is reported. While prototypical photocatalytic systems are incompatible with phenols due to their redox non-innocent behavior and low nucleophilicity, we show that incorporation of an organosulfur electron-shuttle catalyst enables the phenols to serve as competent O-nucleophiles in RPC chemistry. This system operates efficiently at sterically demanding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electronic coupling in a synthetic model of the Cu-cofactor unit of the P<sub>M</sub> state in cytochrome <em>c</em> oxidase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A hydroquinone-imidazole-Cu(II) complex reproduces the Tyr-His-Cu unit of cytochrome c oxidase. Laser-induced EPR and DFT reveal a semiquinone radical electronically isolated from Cu(II) by orthogonal orbital alignment. The weak magnetic exchange underscores how geometry governs coupling, providing insight into transient states of metalloenzymes and their synthetic analogues.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FAST-CRISPR: Fusogenic Association and Secured Transfection of CRISPR/Cas9 Ribonucleoproteins Using Lipid-Silica Hybrid Nanoparticles for Therapeutic Genome Editing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clinical translation of CRISPR/Cas9 therapeutics is challenged by inefficient cytosolic delivery and toxicity issues associated with viral vectors and nanoparticle-based carriers. To overcome these concerns, herein we report a lipid-silica hybrid nanoparticle platform for fusogenic association and secured transfection of CRISPR/Cas9 (FAST-CRISPR), designed for rapid cytosolic delivery of CRISPR/Cas9 ribonucleoproteins, followed by efficient gene editing. Through direct fusion with the plasma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of MAO-B Inhibitors on Cognition in Patients with Parkinson's Disease: A Systematic Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Rasagiline may provide global cognitive benefits in PD, but MAO-B inhibitors, including rasagiline, generally did not demonstrate significant effects on individual cognitive domains. These findings suggest limited cognitive impacts of MAO-B inhibitors beyond managing the motor symptoms. Further large-scale, long-term studies using domain-specific cognitive assessments are warranted to clarify their roles in cognitive performance in patients with PD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of <em>Ecklonia cava</em> Kjellman Extract Complex in Respiratory Health: A Randomized, Double-Blind, Placebo-Controlled, Multicenter Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrialization, air pollution, and respiratory infections have highlighted the importance of maintaining respiratory health. Ecklonia cava Kjellman (EC) has anti-inflammatory, antioxidative, and anti-allergic effects and therapeutic potential for respiratory symptoms. We evaluated the efficacy and safety of Ecklonia cava Kjellman extract complex (EEC), composed of EC and Chrysanthemum indicum Linnaeus (C. indicum) extract, in respiratory health. A randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Adolescent Non-Suicidal Self-Injury: A Narrative Review of Theoretical Models and Evidence-Based Psychotherapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DBT is currently the first-line treatment for NSSIs in adolescents. However, the field must move toward personalized care. Future research should focus on validating alternative therapies through head-to-head randomized controlled trials, identifying the core change mechanisms across treatments, and implementing stepwise care models to improve accessibility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virtual lab of artificial intelligence agents accelerating nanobody design against SARS-CoV-2 variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI)-driven research frameworks are reshaping the boundaries of biomedical discovery. The Virtual Lab exemplifies this transformation, assembling large language model (LLM) agents into coordinated scientific teams functioning as investigators, specialists, and critics. The system autonomously designed, scored, and refined nanobody candidates against emerging SARS-CoV-2 variants, and subsequently validated them experimentally. These findings demonstrate how AI can move...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A developmental stage-aware graph transformer framework for automated bone-age assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: By leveraging a skeletal graph structure based on anatomical relationships and incorporating a developmental stage-aware processing mechanism, the DSGTF framework provides an accurate and efficient automated solution for clinical bone-age assessment. The proposed approach exhibits strong stability and consistency across different age groups and sexes, making it a reliable tool for real-world medical applications. This model effectively simulates the clinical assessment process by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between vitamin D status and insulin resistance in Korean adolescents: differential effects of obesity using non-insulin-based indices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Vitamin D deficiency is significantly associated with higher IR in adolescents, as measured by non-insulin-based indices. This association appears to be strong in overweight/obese individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent trends of pericardiocentesis in pediatric population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide analysis of the pleiotropic drug resistance (PDR) gene family and putative PDR specific mirnas: deciphering their functions in development processes and varied stresses in Triticum aestivum L]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Thus, the results of this study establish a strong basis for further investigation of the functions of TaPDR genes across different tissues, developmental stages, phytohormone responses, and diverse stress in wheat.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation on physical and physiological properties of extracellular vesicles derived from Enterococcus faecalis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular membrane vesicles (EVs) are nanosized particles that contain various molecules originating from their parental cells and are produced by all three domains of life, including bacteria. Bacterial EVs are known to contribute to bacterial infections and immune responses in various human diseases. Enterococcus faecalis is an opportunistic pathogen. In this study, we examined the physical and physiological properties of EVs generated by E. faecalis, including particle size, protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyaluronic Acid Fillers for Vaginal Augmentation: Efficacy and Safety]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates the potential of vaginal filler treatment to positively impact female sexual well-being. Both subjective reports of satisfaction and objective physiological measures indicate improvements following the procedure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prenatal exposure to oral glucocorticoids and risk of long-term neurodevelopmental disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strain-dependent modeling of a mechano-electrochemical energy harvester based on carbon nanotube yarn]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the electrochemical equivalent circuit model for a carbon nanotube (CNT) coiled yarn subjected to external mechanical deformation. The mechanically coiled CNT yarn electrode, with average coil diameters of 83 μm and 112 μm, operates in an electrode-electrolyte configuration in which applied strain induces mechano-electrochemical energy conversion. Electrochemical impedance spectroscopy (EIS) was employed to characterize the impedance behavior of the coiled CNT electrode...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automatic diagnosis of age-related macular degeneration using machine learning and image processing techniques]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The efficacy and safety of 5% lidocaine patch for postoperative pain in unilateral inguinal herniorrhaphy: prospective randomized controlled pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Binary mineral nanoparticles enable intravascular delivery of metal ions to tumors for metalloimmunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although disruptions in metal ion homeostasis leading to severe cellular damage and regulated cell death are a promising strategy for cancer immunotherapy, challenges in overloading these ions to tumor cells without premature release have limited their therapeutic applications. In this study, we develop binary mineral nanoparticles incorporating both Ca^(2+) and Na^(+) ions to enhance the cytotoxic effects of ion interference in cancer immunotherapy. Engineered using a microfluidic system for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The interconnected wirings between medial prefrontal cortex and claustrum and their governing roles in the methamphetamine reward memory in male mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bidirectional communication between medial prefrontal cortex (mPFC) and claustrum (CL) plays a critical role in drug reward memory, particularly for conditioned drug-associated cues. However, their precise circuitry remains unclear. Here, using viral tracing, chemo-&opto-genetics and patch-clamp, alongside methamphetamine (METH) conditioned place preference (CPP) model, we dissected the connectivity pattern between mPFC and CL in male mice. Two relatively independent pathways of top-down mPFC-CL...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in Sero-Immunological Status for Infectious Diseases in Solid Organ Transplantation: A 20-year Single-Center Study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The sero-immunological landscape of SOT candidates has changed over time, reflecting generational shifts in Korean society. These changes highlight the importance of targeted screening and tailored management, particularly for high-risk donor-seropositive/recipient-seronegative transplantations, as well as the critical need for timely immunization in transplant candidates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular and Microbiological Characteristics of Uropathogenic <em>Escherichia coli</em> Harboring CTX-M-55]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The extended-spectrum β-lactamase (ESBL) CTX-M-55, a CTX-M-15 variant distinguished by an amino-acid substitution (Ala77Val), has enhanced enzymatic activity due to higher structural stability. In Korea, CTX-M-55 remains insufficiently characterized, particularly in the context of urinary tract infections (UTIs). We identified CTX-M-55 among uropathogenic Escherichia coli isolates and compared its microbiological characteristics with those of CTX-M-15. In total, 247 E. coli isolates were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Chrysanthemum zawadskii</em> flower Extract Rescues Inflammatory Cognitive Impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chrysanthemum zawadskii flower ethanol extract (CZ-F) was evaluated for its neuroprotective potential against inflammation-associated cognitive impairment. To assess its anti-inflammatory properties, we first conducted in vitro studies using LPS-stimulated BV2 microglial cells. CZ-F demonstrated strong antioxidant activity with IC₅₀ values of 186.04 μg/ml (DPPH) and 94.56 μg/ml (ABTS), suppressed the production of reactive oxygen species and nitric oxide, and downregulated the expression of iNOS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Miniaturized volatile organic compound sensor platform for the real-time monitoring of bacterial growth and antibiotic susceptibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Rapid and accurate determination of bacterial antibiotic susceptibility is essential for effective therapy and prevention of antimicrobial resistance. However, conventional culture-based assays are time-consuming (≥24 h) and labor-intensive, requiring centralized infrastructure. While rapid approaches such as microfluidics and mass spectrometry have been developed, they are often limited by high cost, complex instrumentation, or poor portability, underscoring the need for simple,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of the efficacy of Endo-TLIF and OLIF-360 assisted by optical navigation in the treatment of degenerative lumbar spondylolisthesis lesions, a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates that both Endo-TLIF and OLIF-360 achieve favorable outcomes in the treatment of degenerative lumbar spondylolisthesis. Compared with OLIF-360, Endo-TLIF offers advantages in earlier postoperative ambulation, shorter incision length, reduced intraoperative blood loss, and more direct spinal canal decompression.Conversely, OLIF-360 provides distinct benefits in restoring disc height, improving lumbar sagittal alignment, and promoting interbody fusion. Regarding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic gases as emerging treatments for oral diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oral delivery of gas-based therapies provides a targeted, minimally invasive approach to treating oral diseases. Conventional strategies, such as mechanical debridement, antibiotics, and surgical intervention, are limited by the inaccessibility of oral biofilms, the development of antimicrobial resistance, and challenges in promoting tissue regeneration. Therapeutic gases, including oxygen (O(2)), ozone (O(3)), nitrous oxide (N(2)O), nitric oxide (NO), carbon monoxide (CO), carbon dioxide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of RALY as a novel regulator of DSCR1 transcription]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Down syndrome critical region 1 (DSCR1) is located on chromosome 21, whose N-terminal coding sequence lacks recognizable motifs, and its precise transcriptional and translational regulation remains incompletely understood. Utilizing a bicistronic reporter system, we identified the core promoter region of DSCR1, which enables investigation of its gene regulatory mechanisms. Proteomic analyses via LC-MS/MS revealed that RALY directly binds to the DSCR1 promoter, influencing its transcriptional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anomalous Hall, Nernst, and Spin Hall effects in CoMnCrGa: A first-principles study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The quaternary Heusler compound CoMnCrGa emerges as a highly promising candidate for spintronic and transverse thermoelectric applications, as revealed by comprehensive first-principles calculations. CoMnCrGa stabilizes in the Type-I cubic structure ($F\bar{4}3m$) with a ferromagnetic ground state. The total magnetic moment of $\sim 1.09\,\mu_B$ obeys the Slater-Pauling rule, indicating a nearly half-metallic character corroborated by high electronic spin polarization. Prominent Berry curvature...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redefining molecular design and exciton dynamics in single-component organic photocatalysts for efficient solar-to-hydrogen conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A major challenge in organic single-component photocatalysts (SCPCs) for hydrogen (H(2)) generation is their intrinsically inefficient exciton separation and charge generation. To address this, we designed two thienopyridine-fused benzodithiophene (TPBDT) molecules, TPBDT-2FIC and TPBDT-INCNO1, featuring wide bandgaps, extended coplanar π-conjugated backbones, and small Stokes shifts to improve molecular packing and exciton diffusion. TPBDT-INCNO1 incorporates a cyclic imine group that enables...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Prognostic Model for Poststroke Dementia Using Multiple International Cohorts: A STROKOG Collaboration Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Dementia risk prediction models developed for the general population perform poorly in stroke cohorts. Existing stroke-specific models are few and limited by short prediction horizons or reliance on neuroimaging. The aim of this study was to develop a clinically practical model for predicting 5-year dementia risk after stroke using commonly available variables and individual participant data from the Stroke and Cognition Consortium (STROKOG).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeted Supramolecular Senolytics by Enzyme-Responsive Disassembly and Intracellular Polymerization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent evidence indicates that elimination of senescent cells from tissue can be a therapeutic approach to treat age-related disease, but selective targeting of senescent cells remains a challenge. Here, we report a dual-responsive self-assembly system selectively targeting senescent cells by responding to two hallmark features: elevated reactive oxygen species levels and increased alkaline phosphatase (ALP) activity. The engineered monomer (p-Mito-1), bearing phosphate-protected thiol groups...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic and Epigenomic Landscapes of Sarcopenia: From Molecular Etiology to Precision Interventions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenia-the age-related loss of skeletal muscle mass and strength-is a major contributor to frailty, disability, and mortality in the elderly. Once considered a physiological consequence of aging, sarcopenia is now recognized as a complex multifactorial syndrome driven by intricate interactions between genetic predispositions, epigenetic regulation, environmental exposures, and lifestyle factors. Recent advances in high-throughput genomics and epigenomics have transformed our understanding of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A unified framework integrating local effect and DNA damage for the derivation of cell survival model parameters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: When the same energy is delivered to a cellular target, DNA damage and the resulting cellular response may vary depending on the density and distribution pattern of the energy delivered to the critical volume of each cell. DNA damage can be quantitated based on the pattern of dose distribution over the sub-micrometer volumes in nucleus. DNA double-strand breaks (DSBs) are considered the most critical events for cellular effects. Local effect model (LEM), DNA damage model (DDM), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of the synergistic effect of co-gasification of rice husk and cashew nut shell in a dynamic environment of nitrogen and steam in a fixed-bed reactor system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the depletion of energy resources like coal, dependence on cleaner energy carriers like biomass is growing in the present century. Gasification is the most renowned and more energetically efficient technology for extracting this energy via the generation of syngas than other thermochemical conversion processes. It can produce power, liquid fuel, and valuable chemicals like methanol, upon which the present civilization relies. In contrast, other thermochemical processes can produce products...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Versatile applications of LIG-based biosensors: from environmental monitoring to biomedical innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graphene-based biosensors are recognized as one of the most innovative tools in the fields of biological and medical diagnostics. This paper investigates the laser-induced graphene process and its impact on the electrical and chemical properties of biosensors. By employing advanced laser methods, researchers can finely tune both the architecture and functional characteristics of graphene, thereby improving the sensor's ability to detect specific substances with greater accuracy and selectivity....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erythropoietin-derived Non-erythropoietic Peptides Conferring Oxidative Stress Resistance to Keratinocytes and Fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Concentration Type I Atelocollagen Enhances Early Cartilage Regeneration: An In Vivo Comparative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High-concentration atelocollagen-based scaffolds significantly enhanced both the efficiency and quality of cartilage regeneration by providing mechanical support and a favorable microenvironment for chondrogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporary mechanical support in fulminant myocarditis: prognostic factors and clinical implications from the FULLMOON study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite a relatively young cohort, FM requiring t-MCS is associated with a high 1-year mortality rate. Timely recognition and early referral to specialized ECMO centers before cardiac arrest are critical.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reactive oxygen species-mediated inactivation of Listeria monocytogenes and Staphylococcus aureus induced by pulsed plasma treatment: influence of duty ratio and unit time]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reactive oxygen species (ROS) are key mediators of plasma-induced microbial inactivation. This study investigated the influence of pulsed plasma parameters, specifically duty ratio and unit time, on the inactivation of Listeria monocytogenes and Staphylococcus aureus. Pulsed plasma-activated water PAW was generated under controlled discharge conditions, where the unit time, defined as the duration of a single plasma discharge cycle, and the duty ratio, the fraction of the unit time during which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Periungual Bowen Disease Mimicking a Melanocytic Nevus: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Periungual Bowen disease is an uncommon form of squamous cell carcinoma in situ that may mimic benign pigmented lesions, such as melanocytic nevi. We report a case of a 36-year-old man who presented with an irregularly shaped brown macule on the periungual area of the right third finger, with a history of gradual enlargement over 8 years. The patient reported occasional periungual trauma because of nail picking but had no significant medical history. A punch biopsy was performed, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shear-driven finite-velocity diffusion and its generalization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We consider shear-driven finite-velocity diffusion, both normal and anomalous. In the macroscopic description, this leads to a telegrapher's or Cattaneo-like equation. We analyze the probability density function, and the corresponding moments are obtained analytically. We show that the system exhibits a characteristic crossover of the anomalous dynamics. We also explore corresponding processes under stochastic resetting and find that the systems reach non-equilibrium stationary states in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacterial sensing and response for neutralization and detoxification of environmental ammonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ammonia present in the environment is a major source of nitrogen, but it can be toxic to bacteria. While the biochemical mechanisms involved in the metabolic detoxification of cellular ammonia are well understood, little is known about how bacteria manage toxic external ammonia to survive, especially when ammonia is present as a waste product at high concentrations. Here, we demonstrate that a two-component system consisting of the sensor kinase GrtK and the response regulator GrtR is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-effectiveness of female-only and gender-neutral HPV vaccination strategies in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both female-only 4vHPV and 9vHPV strategies are cost-effective under Japan's economic standards. Furthermore, GNV with 9vHPV provides greater health benefits and cost-effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide insights on early childhood neurodevelopment during a global health crisis: evidence from COVID-19 in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The COVID-19 pandemic led to significant developmental declines among young children, particularly in language and social domains and among toddlers. Boys were more adversely affected than girls, especially in language and socioemotional skills, highlighting sex-related vulnerabilities. Prioritising early screening and interventions targeting these key domains, alongside sex-sensitive strategies and caregiver support, will be essential to mitigate developmental disruptions during...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of metal-assisted chemical etching for microscale Si structures using Arrhenius method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-assisted chemical etching (MACE) has emerged as a promising method for fabricating high-aspect-ratio Si microstructures without the damage or complexity associated with plasma-based etching. However, its thermal activation behavior and the role of catalyst morphology remain poorly understood, especially at the microscale. This study systematically investigated the effects of etchant temperature, metal thickness, and pattern geometry on the etching kinetics of MACE. By constructing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between the Duration of Elevated Perfusion Pressure and Neurological Outcomes in Out-of-Hospital Cardiac Arrest Survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The duration of a MAP >80 mmHg during the 0-48 and 25-48 hour periods after ROSC was associated with good neurological outcomes at six months in OHCA survivors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic effects of <em>Angelica gigas</em> Nakai in experimental rat model of polycystic ovary syndrome with network pharmacology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) is a prevalent endocrine disorder in reproductive-aged women, characterized by disrupted ovarian function due to multiple factors. Angelica gigas Nakai (AG), known for its multi-compound and multi-target properties, was investigated as a potential therapy using an integrated approach combining network pharmacology and experimental validation. Active compounds of AG were matched with PCOS-related genes, and 45 overlapping targets were identified. Network analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lariciresinol and secoisolariciresinol enhance myogenic differentiation and mitochondrial biogenesis in C2C12 myotubes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lariciresinol (LR) and secoisolariciresinol (SLR), phytochemicals found in pine bark and flaxseed, are known for their anticancer effects, risk reduction of cardiovascular disease, hormone regulation, and antioxidant activities. However, researches on their effects on skeletal muscle function are scarce. Therefore, this study aimed to investigate the efficacy of LR and SLR in promoting muscle hypertrophy and mitochondrial function in C2C12 mouse-derived myoblasts. LR and SLR were found to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bi-dimensional health space mapping: machine learning analysis of population health dynamics in Korean and Dutch cohorts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Health spans a broad spectrum, encompassing various biological and lifestyle factors. The complexity of biological systems necessitates for integrating diverse factors into a unified biomarker. We constructed a health space model that highlights metabolism and oxidative stress as key indicators for tracking healthy aging and mapping health trajectories. To ensure cross-ethnic relevance, we used data from the Dutch Nutrition Questionnaires plus and Korean National Health and Nutrition Examination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of <em>Lactobacillus</em>-fermented garlic extract on hangover relief: a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled crossover study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hangovers are a set of unpleasant symptoms following excessive alcohol intake. This study evaluated the effects of Lactobacillus-fermented garlic extract (LFGE) on hangover symptoms in a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled, crossover trial involving 25 participants. Hangover severity was assessed using the Acute Hangover Scale (AHS) at 1, 2, 4, and 15 h post-consumption, while blood alcohol and acetaldehyde levels were measured at multiple time points up to 15 h. LFGE significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of temperature distribution and heat penetration during retort sterilization on the quality characteristics of canned whelk (<em>Buccinum striatissimum</em>)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study analyzed the temperature distribution and heat penetration characteristics during canned whelk production using two retort sterilizers. The quality characteristics of the products were also analyzed. The structural characteristics of the retorts, product loading methods, and product quantity affected various characteristics of the thermal profiles, including the range of secondary sterilization temperatures, the cold and hot locations in the two retorts, and the heat penetration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-obesity effect of <em>Bifidobacterium adolescentis</em> SPM2022, isolated from Korean adult]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to evaluate the anti-obesity effect of Bifidobacterium adolescentis SPM2022 (SPM2022). Culture supernatant of SPM2022 reduced lipid accumulation (p < 0.01) and expression of adipogenic genes (p < 0.001) during 3T3-L1 differentiation. The effects on anti-obesity and lipid metabolism were assessed in the high fat diet (HFD)-induced obese C57BL6 mouse after 4 weeks of obese induction. Experimental groups (n = 6/group): normal diet, HFD, and HFD fed with 10⁹ CFU/day of SPM2022....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of flavonoid, carotenoid, and organic acid profiles in various commercial dried citrus chips]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study analyzes the flavonoid, carotenoid, and organic acid profiles of 18 commercial dried citrus chips, including 6 Korean and 12 imported cultivars, which are categorized into citron, pomelo, and mandarin groups based on their origin. Hesperidin and narirutin predominate in citron and mandarin groups, whereas naringin is prevalent in pomelo group. Green tangerine chip showed the highest contents of hesperidin (3180.24 ± 296.55 mg/100 g) and narirutin (424.98 ± 9.23 mg/100 g), while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking the potential of Contract Research Organizations in Africa's clinical trials ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite representing 18% of the world's population and 20% of the disease burden, only an estimated 2% of global clinical trials include at least one study site in Africa. This underscores the critical need for continued research on how to overcome clinical trial challenges on the continent. In countries with established reputations for clinical trials, Contract Research Organizations (CROs) play a vital role, accounting for half of the research workforce and effectively managing clinical trials...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction Model for Low Bone Mineral Density in Cancer Survivors and Age-Matched Controls Using a Causal Bayesian Network: A Nationwide Population-Based Study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Causal Bayesian network modeling identified muscle mass as a key modifiable factor influencing BMD among cancer survivors. These findings highlight the importance of muscle-preserving lifestyle interventions, including resistance exercise and adequate protein intake, in survivorship care. The CBN approach provides a framework for identifying individualized risk pathways and can support personalized bone-health management strategies in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Exploratory Pilot Study of Brain Functional Connectivity and Heart Rate Variability in Male Children With Autism Spectrum Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Resting-state EEG coherence may be associated with the clinical characteristics of ASD, and vmHRV may exert a moderating effect on this relationship. These preliminary findings suggest that the concurrent evaluation of brain and autonomic functions can be useful for elucidating the pathophysiology of ASD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation-Focused Psychotherapy for Children With Emotion Dysregulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emotion dysregulation is a transdiagnostic risk factor in childhood psychopathology that contributes to externalizing behaviors. To address this, regulation-focused psychotherapy for children (RFP-C) has been developed as a manualized, short-term psychodynamic intervention for 5- to 12-year-olds with externalizing behaviors rooted in underlying emotion dysregulation and affective conflict. The therapy follows a structured protocol comprising 16 child play therapy sessions and 4 parent sessions....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evidence-Based Psychotherapy for Disruptive Behavior Disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Disruptive behavior disorder (DBD), which includes oppositional defiant disorder and conduct disorder, is among the most common externalizing disorders in childhood and adolescence. This review aimed to identify evidence-based psychotherapies for DBD and summarize their empirical foundations and characteristics. We searched for randomized controlled trials and systematic reviews using PubMed, PsycINFO, and Google Scholar, focusing on major evidence-based guidelines from the National Institute...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerebellar subregional structural changes across the Alzheimer's disease continuum: a longitudinal analysis of cognitive and behavioural correlates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although traditionally viewed as relatively spared in Alzheimer's disease (Ad), the cerebellum is increasingly recognized for its contribution to cognitive and behavioural dysfunction. However, longitudinal data delineating subregional cerebellar involvement across the Ad continuum remain limited. In this study, we investigated longitudinal cerebellar atrophy and its clinical correlates in 259 older adults classified via amyloid PET into four biomarker-defined groups: cognitively normal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cortical asymmetry in autosomal dominant Alzheimer's disease progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The cortical asymmetry index evaluates the cortical thickness asymmetry between hemispheres. We investigated cortical asymmetry index in asymptomatic and symptomatic mutation carriers of autosomal dominant Alzheimer's disease to explore the brain asymmetry within the Alzheimer's disease continuum. Sixty baseline T1-weighted MRI scans were obtained from the Clinic Barcelona cohort. Baseline and longitudinal MRI data from 564 participants within the dominantly inherited Alzheimer network...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Marked Reversibility of Functional Small Airway Disease Following Reduction of Hazardous Inhalational Exposure: A PRM CT Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a case illustrating the role of parametric response mapping (PRM) in detecting and monitoring small airway disease (SAD) related to occupational inhalational exposure. A 52-year-old woman, a lifelong never-smoker with chronic occupational exposure to metal cutting-fluid fumes and metal particles, presented with exertional dyspnea and moderate airflow obstruction. PRM CT revealed PRM-functional small airway disease (PRM-fSAD) of 15.7% and PRM-emphysema of 0.2%. After 1.5 years of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tissue-Resident ILC2s Across Organs: Heterogeneity, Niche Crosstalk, and Shared Regulatory Circuits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Type 2 innate lymphoid cells (ILC2s) are an important source of innate cytokines that contribute to allergic inflammation. Recent studies have also suggested that ILC2s play a biological role in peripheral tissues such as lung, fat, intestine and skin, controlled by alarmins, neuropeptides and environmental factors. Furthermore, emerging studies have shown that tissues including the pancreas, uterus and meninges contain ILC2s that contribute to normal biological function. Here, we review recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aging Mediates Inflammatory Transformation of Kidney-Resident Macrophages via Thrombospondin-1 Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kidney-resident macrophages (KRMs) are long-lived immune cells crucial for maintaining kidney homeostasis, with roles that vary depending on kidney condition. Their phenotypes can exert different effects on kidney status, but how the phenotypes of KRMs evolve in aged kidneys and the resulting impacts on kidney homeostasis remain poorly understood. Through single-cell RNA sequencing, we identified a phenotypic shift in KRMs within aged kidneys characterized by increased oxidative phosphorylation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondria Derived From iPSCs Control by Reciprocal Regulation of Th17/Treg and Anti-Fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several studies have reported the immunoregulatory effects of transplanting mitochondria from mesenchymal stem cells. However, whether similar effects can be achieved using mitochondria derived from human induced pluripotent stem cells (iPSCs; iMito) has not yet been investigated. Here, we examined the protective effects of iMito in a dextran sodium sulfate (DSS)-induced colitis mouse model. To address this, we investigated the effects both in vitro and in vivo. First, iMitos were transferred...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cytokine Engineering in CAR-T Cell Therapy: Next-Generation Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimeric Ag receptor (CAR)-T cell therapy has demonstrated success primarily in B-cell malignancies, but efficacy in solid tumors remains limited by Ag heterogeneity, immunosuppressive tumor microenvironments, and restricted infiltration. Cytokine engineering has emerged as a promising strategy to overcome these barriers. Fourth-generation CAR-T cells, known as T cells redirected for universal cytokine-mediated killing, demonstrated the feasibility of localized immune modulation through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IL7-TBRII, a Dual Cytokine Modulator Targeting IL-7 and TGF-β Pathways, Inhibits Tumor Progression and Metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor-infiltrating CD8^(+) T cells are a key determinant of anti-tumor efficacy in immunotherapy. IL-7 has been explored as a cytokine therapy to expand CD8^(+) T cells, showing promising anti-tumor effects in preclinical models. However, clinical outcomes remain limited, likely due to the immunosuppressive tumor microenvironment. To enhance the efficacy of IL-7 therapy, we reanalyzed publicly available single-cell RNA-sequencing (scRNA-seq) data of tumors treated with IL-7, identifying elevated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current practices and considerations in intense pulsed light therapy for meibomian gland dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intense pulsed light (IPL) therapy has emerged as a promising modality for the treatment of meibomian gland dysfunction (MGD), a leading cause of evaporative dry eye disease. However, its clinical application varies significantly across studies, with notable procedural heterogeneity in device selection, treatment intervals, anatomical coverage, and adjunctive strategies. This comprehensive review synthesizes 110 clinical studies to delineate prevailing procedural trends and identify...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current therapeutic landscape of dry eye and meibomian gland disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic outcomes of oral cefcapene in meibomitis-related keratoconjunctivitis: A Propensity-matched cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adjunctive use of short-term oral cefcapene therapy alongside standard eyelid hygiene measures resulted in a significant reduction in CSSs in patients with MRKC. However, this reduction was not accompanied by a statistically significant improvement in subjective symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conjunctival microvascular alterations in dry eye disease: A comparative study of Sjögren's and non-Sjögren's subtypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings reveal distinct conjunctival microvascular signatures in patients with SSDE, and support vessel diameter as a discriminator. The association between hemodynamic changes and MGD parameters in the NSDE group underscores the interplay between MGD and conjunctival microcirculation in NSDE. The differences in microvasculature identified in this study may serve as valuable biomarkers for DED subtype classification and the development of personalized treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the cost-effectiveness of artificial intelligence-enhanced osteoporosis screening in men and women using routine chest radiographs in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[South Korea, now a "super-aged" society, faces a rising burden of fragility fractures, yet underdiagnosis remains a major barrier, with limited DXA access restricting early detection. Artificial intelligence (AI) applied to routine chest radiographs enables opportunistic screening. In March 2025, Osteo Signal, a deep learning model developed in the South Korean population, received regulatory approval for use in both men and women. Unlike prior evaluations in women only, this study assessed its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Korean Colorectal Cancer Reveals Novel Driver Gene and Clinically Relevant Mutations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colorectal cancer (CRC) ranks as the third leading cause of cancer-related deaths worldwide, characterized by genomic heterogeneity arising from ethnic and interindividual differences. Producing region-specific data to characterize ethnic-specific somatic mutations is essential for advancing CRC research. Additionally, accurate somatic mutation detection requires paired tissue analyses to account for interindividual diversity. This study aims to highlight the importance of ethnic diversity in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma GFAP as a mediator and moderator of Aβ, tau, and neurodegeneration in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astrogliosis is increasingly recognized as a critical component of Alzheimer's disease (AD) pathology, but its precise mechanistic contribution to the interplay among amyloid-β (Aβ), tau, and neurodegeneration remains unclear. Glial fibrillary acidic protein (GFAP), a widely used biomarker of astrocytic activation, shows strong associations with both Aβ and tau pathologies; however, its causal and modulatory involvement in disease progression has yet to be fully delineated. In this study, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combination of Atelocollagen Gel With Induced Pluripotent Stem Cell-Derived Tenocyte for Rotator Cuff Tendon Regeneration in a Rat Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study demonstrates that an injection of atelocollagen containing iPSC-TCs into the lesion after rotator cuff repair produced excellent residual effects. The addition of iPSC-TCs embedded in atelocollagen to a surgically repaired rotator cuff could improve tendon quality by increasing type I collagen production.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoptotic Cancer Cell-Primed Cancer-Associated Fibroblasts Suppress Immunosuppressive Macrophages via WISP-1-Integrin α5β3-STAT1 Signaling in Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell death within the tumor microenvironment (TME) plays a pivotal role in shaping tumor-specific immunity. The dynamic interplay between cancer-associated fibroblasts (CAFs) and tumor-associated macrophages (TAMs) is central to tumor progression and immune regulation. Here, we show that conditioned medium (CM) from lung CAFs exposed to apoptotic cancer cells selectively impairs the survival of M2-like macrophages, induces apoptosis, and promotes their reprogramming toward an M1-like phenotype....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AVN944 Elicits Apoptotic Responses and Impedes Tumorigenic Potential in Ewing's Sarcoma Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inosine monophosphate dehydrogenase 2 (IMPDH2) is implicated in survival and proliferation of cancer cells because of its role in guanine nucleotide biosynthesis. This study evaluates the efficacy of AVN944, an IMPDH2 inhibitor, as a treatment for Ewing's sarcoma, a challenging malignancy in pediatric and young adult patients. Gene expression data, as well as clinical outcomes for sarcoma patients, from The Cancer Genome Atlas (TCGA) were analyzed to determine the association between IMPDH2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circulating Branched-Chain Amino Acids are Associated with Higher Odds of Obesity: Findings from the FiLWHEL Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher circulating BCAA profiles, independent of dietary BCAA intake levels, were associated with a higher prevalence of obesity, with no evidence of interaction in the divergent independent associations between dietary and circulating BCAAs and obesity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling scalable ferroelectric-based future generation vertical NAND flash with bonding-friendly architecture: strategies for erase and disturb optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel ferroelectric VNAND (Fe-VNAND) architecture based on a TCAT (Terabit Cell Array Transistor) structure, integrating an amorphous IGZO channel and a band-engineered filler insulator for enhanced erase and disturbance characteristics. To overcome the limitations of poor hole transport in IGZO, a tailored erase (ERS) scheme employing stepped dummy word-line biasing is introduced, which effectively mitigates over-erasure at the bottom of the NAND string and enables reliable bitline...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Timed up and go test as a screening tool for exercise capacity after lung cancer resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TUGT demonstrates significant correlations with both CPET and 6MWT and may serve as a simple, feasible, and clinically valuable screening tool for identifying patients with reduced postoperative exercise capacity. Incorporating TUGT into routine postoperative evaluations may facilitate early detection of reduced functional capacity and guide timely referral for pulmonary rehabilitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors governing tumor penetration of nanomedicines: intrinsic and extrinsic determinants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanomedicine-based drug delivery has shown considerable promise for cancer therapy; however, the efficient transport and deep penetration of nanoparticles within solid tumors remain major challenges for clinical translation. These limitations arise from the combined effects of nanoparticle physicochemical properties and biological transport barriers acting across multiple biological scales, rather than being governed by any single isolated parameter. Accordingly, nanoparticle transport and tumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SABRE Acethydrazide as a Co-Substrate Agent for Quantitative Analysis of Submicromolar N-Heterocyclic Compounds Using Parahydrogen Hyperpolarization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Signal amplification by reversible exchange (SABRE) hyperpolarization is a well-known method for enhancing nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) signals by transferring para-hydrogen-derived polarization to the analyte of interest. However, due to inherent sensitivity limitations, detecting analyte signals at micromolar (μM) or lower concentrations remains challenging. This study proposes acethydrazide (ACH) as a novel co-substrate, which significantly improves SABRE hyperpolarization efficiency and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multicenter Analysis of the Learning Curve for Endoscopic Ultrasound-Guided Gallbladder Drainage: A Cumulative Sum Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Based on CUSUM analysis, approximately 23 procedures may be required to achieve technical proficiency in EUS-GBD with regard to minimizing adverse events, while 27 procedures are necessary to reach proficiency in terms of procedure time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Energy-Based Devices for the Treatment of Cutaneous Lesions in Patients With Lupus Erythematosus and Dermatomyositis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: EBD treatments may provide cosmetic improvement in selected LE and DM patients and are generally safe. Larger controlled studies are needed to confirm efficacy and establish optimal protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fractional Exhaled Nitric Oxide for Diagnosing Eosinophilic Chronic Rhinosinusitis: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FeNO levels are significantly elevated in ECRS patients compared to non-ECRS patients. The high diagnostic odds ratio suggests that FeNO has potential as a noninvasive diagnostic tool for ECRS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nerve Stimulator-Guided Epidural Anesthesia in a Rhesus Macaque (Macaca mulatta)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A male rhesus macaque underwent inguinal hernia repair under general anesthesia, with epidural anesthesia administered at the fourth lumbar vertebral level using a nerve stimulator-guided technique. This method provided effective analgesia and stable hemodynamics, supporting its potential as an objective alternative to landmark-based approaches in nonhuman primates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The intersection of health inequalities and COVID-19: Evidence from National Health Insurance Big Data in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Health inequalities persist along lines of income and wealth, shaped by unequal access to healthcare, differences in health behaviors, and pre-existing chronic conditions. The COVID-19 pandemic further put families in Korea under health strain and worsened their health outcomes. This study investigates how pre-existing socioeconomic disparities intersect with health outcomes. Using the national administrative health big data provided by the Korean National Health Insurance Service, we employ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Super-Resolution" Deep Learning Image Reconstruction in Dynamic Myocardial Perfusion: A Prospective Evaluation of Image Quality and Hemodynamic Parameters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SR-DLR and NR-DLR significantly enhanced image quality by reducing noise and improving SNR and CNR while maintaining hemodynamic quantification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoscopic predictors of iron deficiency in Helicobacter pylori gastritis: a Kyoto classification-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Younger age, female sex, and larger hyperplastic polyps (≥5 mm) are associated with iron deficiency in patients with H. pylori gastritis. These features may help identify patients at higher risk of iron deficiency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomechanical Assessment of IOL Stability and Position Based on Suture and Inlet Variations in the Canabrava Double-flanged Technique]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Caution is advised in patients with a predisposition to iris chafing as the risk may persist regardless of fixation parameters.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Versatile Microfluidic Cryogel Microbead Platform for Modular Biofabrication and Tissue Regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbead-based modular systems offer significant potential for biofabrication strategies in tissue regeneration. In this study, we present a tunable microfluidic cryogel microbead (MCB) platform that enables injectable, modular assembly of cells and tissue-specific regeneration. The MCBs are designed to incorporate diverse ECM compositions, porosities, and bioceramic components tailored to specific tissue types. They support cell viability and function, and when loaded with endothelial cells,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strong Base-Promoted Pd-Catalyzed Asymmetric Hydroalkoxylation of Alkoxyallene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new protocol for the Pd-catalyzed hydroalkoxylation of alkoxyallene is presented that proceeds under strongly basic conditions. Notably, this method accommodates sterically hindered tertiary alcohols and carbohydrate-derived alcohols, which proved unreactive under the previous base-free conditions. This result was rationalized by the outer-sphere addition of alkoxide nucleophile to the syn π-allyl complex. Synthetic utility of the reaction was demonstrated by convergent synthesis of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case reports that high-dose-rate brachytherapy using custom-designed mouthpiece mold for early-stage squamous cell carcinoma of the hard palate is useful]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study might show that HDR-customized MBT is useful for early-stage SCCHP and might be an alternative curative treatment option for them to preserve oral function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[End-of-life emergency medical service transport among patients with terminal cancer by cardiopulmonary arrest status: A nationwide mortality follow-back survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients transported in CPA experienced fewer EOL discussions, showed socioeconomic disparities, and had distinct perceptions of the quality of death. These findings emphasize the need to enhance advanced care planning communication and emergency preparedness in EOL cancer care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes of Balloon-Only Venous Arterialization for Chronic Limb-Threatening Ischemia After Failed or Unfeasible Revascularization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: BOVA appears to be a feasible limb salvage strategy for patients with CLTI without conventional revascularization options.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a global screening system for detecting protein-protein interactions by luminescence complementation in fission yeast]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deciphering protein-protein interactions (PPIs) is crucial for a comprehensive understanding of biological processes, yet current methodologies often provide incomplete interactome maps. Here, we present a sensitive bimolecular NanoBiT-based protein complementation assay platform for robust PPI detection in the fission yeast Schizosaccharomyces pombe. Our platform utilizes two NanoLuc moieties, SmBiT and LgBiT, fused to interacting protein partners, generating a quantifiable luminescent signal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early-life colonization by aromatic-lactate-producing bifidobacteria lowers the risk of allergic sensitization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early-life microbial exposures shape immune development and allergy risk. Food allergen sensitization, reflected by the presence of food allergen-specific immunoglobulin E (IgE), is an early indication of impaired immune tolerance. Here we show that early-life transmission of aromatic lactate-producing bifidobacteria strains in 147 children followed from birth to 5 years of age, facilitated by vaginal delivery, exposure to older siblings and exclusive breastfeeding for the first 2 months, led to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility study of a newly developed solid gel pad containing tamarind seed gum for diagnostic ultrasonography in human subjects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526518/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526518/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neonatal hyperoxia exposure causes cerebellar lesions and behavioral abnormalities in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimally invasive surgery for right-sided colon cancer with superior mesenteric artery rotation: clinical features and short-term outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The vascular course in patients with SMAR differs from the usual pattern and this may increase the risk of unexpected vascular injury, potentially leading to intraoperative bleeding and prolonged operative time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linking molecular tension and cellular tractions: a multiscale approach to focal adhesion mechanics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Focal adhesions (FAs) are mechanosensitive structures that mediate force transmission between cells and the extracellular matrix. While Traction Force Microscopy (TFM) quantifies cellular tractions exerted on deformable substrates, Förster Resonance Energy Transfer (FRET)-based tension probes, such as vinculin tension sensors, measure molecular-scale forces within FA proteins. Despite their potential synergy, these methods have rarely been combined to explore the interplay between molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell and spatial transcriptomic profiling of cardiac fibroblasts following myocardial infarction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardiac fibroblasts (CFs) are key mediators of heart repair following myocardial infarction (MI). A specific CF subpopulation, termed Reparative Cardiac Fibroblasts (RCFs), has been shown to orchestrate scar formation and prevent ventricular rupture after MI. However, the timing of RCF appearance and the molecular events underlying this transition remain largely undefined. Here, we present a multi-modal dataset capturing the transcriptional dynamics of CFs during the early phase post-MI. Our...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Living sensor display implanted on skin for long-term biomarker monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study introduces an approach to biomarker monitoring through the development of a "Living Sensor Display" implanted on the skin, designed for long-term, continuous tracking of biomarkers, such as inflammatory cytokines. By leveraging the natural high selectivity and sensitivity of keratinocyte stem cells (KSCs) to environmental stimuli, we genetically engineered these cells to express fluorescent proteins in response to specific biomarker signals, specifically TNF-α signalling. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cultural diversity of religion across 117 countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Humans show marked diversity in cultural values, beliefs, and preferences. Here, we analyze survey responses from 640,110 individuals in 117 countries (representing 89% of the World's population), and 2,333 sub-national districts, surveyed in the World Values Survey and the European Values Study. Across multiple sets of comparable cultural traits, we find that religion consistently emerges as the cultural trait that exhibits the largest cross-country divergence (measured by the Cultural Fixation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Use of Proton Pump Inhibitors Affects Blood Levels of Indoxyl Sulfate in Japanese Patients with Chronic Kidney Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proton pump inhibitors (PPIs) are implicated in the progression of chronic kidney disease (CKD), but the mechanism behind this is unclear. PPIs are known to inhibit organic anion transporters (OATs) and affect intestinal microbiota. PPI use may influence serum concentrations of indoxyl sulfate (IS), a uremic toxin that contributes to CKD. This study compares serum IS concentrations between Japanese patients receiving long-term PPI prescriptions and those receiving non-PPIs, evaluating the effect...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SMTP-44D Improves High Glucose-Induced Vascular Endothelial Dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic diabetic complications are mostly caused by vascular disorders, with only a few effective treatments or preventive measures currently available. In this study, we investigated the effects of Stachybotrys microspora triprenyl phenol-44D (SMTP-44D), a fungus-derived compound that inhibits both the epoxide hydrolase and phosphatase activities of soluble epoxide hydrolase (sEH), using human umbilical vein endothelial cells (HUVECs) in a high glucose treatment model. When HUVECs were treated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41526227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Variability of the Electromechanical Window in Long-QT Syndrome and Drug-Induced QT Prolongation: Value for Enhanced Arrhythmia-Risk Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Temporary accentuation of EMW negativity is a marker of impending VT in LQTS and diQTP patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Faecal colonisation with extended-spectrum β-lactamase-producing Escherichia coli and Klebsiella pneumoniae in rural Burkina Faso]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ESBL-E prevalence was high and associated with poor hygiene and seasonal variation. Higher rainy season prevalence was not explained by reported antibiotic use and may reflect increased environmental exposure risks, which requires further exploration. Improving hygiene-standards and establishing community-level AMR surveillance can provide effective steps forward in mitigating AMR burden in rural sSA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a sandwich ELISA for serum leptin measurement in chub mackerel across reproductive stages and feeding and nutritional statuses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leptin is an adipocyte-derived hormone that links nutritional status with endocrine and reproductive functions. However, only a limited number of teleost species allow reliable measurement of circulating leptin. In this study, we aimed to develop a specific and sensitive sandwich enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay (ELISA) for measuring serum leptin A in chub mackerel (Scomber japonicus) using two polyclonal antibodies. Validation assays confirmed high specificity, sensitivity, recovery,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A C. elegans model of familial Alzheimer's disease shows age-dependent synaptic degeneration independent of amyloid β-peptide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The membrane-embedded γ-secretase complex is involved in the intramembrane cleavage of ~150 substrates. Cleavage of amyloid precursor protein (APP)-derived substrate C99 generates 38-43-residue secreted amyloid β-peptides (Aβ), with the aggregation-prone 42-residue form (Aβ42) particularly implicated in the pathogenesis of Alzheimer's Disease (AD). However, whether Aβ42 is the primary driver of neurodegeneration in AD remains unclear. Dominant mutations in APP or presenilin-the catalytic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles from microalgae Pavlova in non-heated condition potently enhance innate immune response as a novel cell-derived immunostimulatory adjuvant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In vaccine therapy, there is a growing interest in novel immunostimulatory adjuvants derived from food products or dietary supplements with safe profiles. Pavlova is a microalga commonly used as a dietary supplement. Owing to its immune-activating potency and safety profiles, Pavlova offers novel possibilities as an immunostimulatory adjuvant. However, precise control of their proliferation profile and subsequent immune activation when administered to the host is difficult, limiting their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aerobic Threshold Evaluation Using a Sweat Lactate Sensor in Healthy Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The use of a sweat lactate sensor to evaluate the aerobic threshold has not been fully validated in women with low sweat rates. This study aimed to validate aerobic threshold assessment using a sweat lactate sensor in healthy women. Sixteen healthy women who underwent exercise tests using respiratory gas analysis were included. Sweat lactate levels were monitored using a wearable lactate sensor, and the sweat rate was measured using a ventilated capsule perspiration meter. A correlation analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental validation of a Fisher information-based predictive framework for dose and time optimization in PET-guided online adaptive proton therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[&#xD;The range determination uncertainty (σ(est)) based on positron emission tomography (PET) imaging, which stems from the Poisson statistics of the detected signal, can be theoretically predicted using Fisher information. This study aims to experimentally validate a Fisher information-based predictive framework that optimizes the irradiation dose and measurement time required for reliable range verification in PET-guided online adaptive proton therapy.&#xD;Approach:&#xD;First, we defined a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantifying biological effects of spatially heterogeneous carbon ion dose distributions using EUD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to experimentally investigate the cell survival responses of tumor and normal cell lines to spatially heterogeneous carbon ion dose distributions with varying peak-to-valley dose ratios (PVDRs) and linear energy transfer (LET) conditions, and to assess the utility of equivalent uniform dose (EUD) as a quantitative metric for analyzing these responses. HSGc-C5 (tumor) and Nuli-1 (normal tissue) cell lines were irradiated using carbon ion beams with different spatial dose patterns...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to: Focal Boosting in Localized Prostate Cancer in the Era of Systemic Therapy and Prostate-Specific Membrane Antigen Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carotenoids identified from slipper-shaped oyster Magallana bilineata powder residue exhibit potent biological activities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carotenoids are a diverse class of biologically active compounds that contribute significantly to human health, serving vital functions in nutrition and overall well-being. Magallana bilineata, a commercially important oyster species, yields a shelf-stable powder residue possessing bioactivities with unknown specific compounds. Carotenoids are key marine bioactive compounds, but their presence in oysters remains underexplored. The present study aimed to identify the bioactive compounds from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Adverse Event Reports of Dipeptidyl Peptidase-4 Inhibitor-Associated Pemphigoid in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The number of reported DPP-4 inhibitor-associated pemphigoid events increased after the revised precautions of package inserts for DPP-4 inhibitors were released.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SOD1 deficiency drives ferroptosis-linked oxidative and reproductive aging, mitigated by ginseng root extract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging is accompanied by cumulative oxidative stress that promotes tissue degeneration and reproductive decline. Here, we show that deficiency of superoxide dismutase 1 (SOD1) accelerates oxidative injury and reproductive aging through a ferroptosis-linked redox imbalance, and that ginseng root extract (GR) confers protection across species. Aged hairless Sod1⁻^(/)⁻ mice exhibited markedly elevated skin and plasma oxidative stress markers-including 8-isoprostane, malondialdehyde (MDA), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Exploring Predictive Risk Factors for Myocardial Injury in Children Treated with Anthracyclines: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of Symptoms and Evaluation of Surgical Indications After Birth Based on Tracheal Morphology of Double Aortic Arch]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To establish objective criteria for predicting postnatal respiratory symptoms and determine surgical indications in fetuses with double aortic arch (DAA). This single-center, retrospective cohort study included fetuses diagnosed with DAA using fetal echocardiography and managed perinatally at Kanagawa Children's Medical Center from January 2013-December 2024. Clinical data, fetal echocardiography, postnatal contrast-enhanced computed tomography (CT) findings, surgical intervention, and outcomes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative performance of a 3D CZT and conventional SPECT/CT for Tb-161 imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Quantitative Tb-161 SPECT imaging can be performed using both a conventional and a 3D CZT SPECT/CT. Given its higher sensitivity, the 3D CZT system is preferred, as it achieved better image quality with an 8-min acquisition compared to a conventional system with a 16-min acquisition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Disc-FX versus L'DISQ for percutaneous disc decompression: pilot comparative study using the minimal clinically important difference]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this pilot study, Disc-FX and L'DISQ had comparable short-term pain outcomes. Any apparent QOL advantage with Disc-FX should be interpreted cautiously as exploratory and potentially confounded, and requires confirmation in adequately powered prospective comparative studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customized Face Guards as Protective Devices for Ocular Trauma in Futsal Players: A Case Report and Clinical Efficacy Evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a case involving a futsal player with brain concussions and commotio retinae to protect the affected area and support a safe, prompt return to play custom face guard instead of a commercial face guard and sports goggles. For a better fit, we fabricated a custom face guard, for which a facial impression was taken using dental alginate material and plaster in July 2019. The following month, the custom face guard was set on the player's face so that its outline provided minimal coverage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative functional analysis of papaya leaves at different developmental stages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Papaya (Carica papaya L.), a tropical plant belonging to the Caricaceae family, is widely cultivated in tropical and subtropical countries. Young leaves grow from the stem tips, petioles elongate, and leaf color changes from light green to dark green during development. Papaya leaves are used as therapeutic agents in folk medicine and potential functional food materials; however, the specific associations between the leaf development stage and functional components of papaya remain unknown....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of bZIP60 function through C-terminal region translated after splicing in <em>Arabidopsis</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The unfolded protein response (UPR) is a central regulatory pathway that ensures the proper function of the endoplasmic reticulum (ER) through efficient protein folding and quality control. In Arabidopsis, bZIP60 mRNA is activated by an IRE1-mediated unconventional splicing that excises a 23-nucleotide intron, resulting in the spliced form (bZIP60s mRNA) that encodes the active bZIP60 transcription factor lacking a transmembrane domain. In this study, we investigated the functional role of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A start codon-targeted genome editing strategy for generating hypomorphic mutants of lethal plant genes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In plants, the functional characterization of essential genes is often hindered by the lethality associated with complete loss-of-function alleles. Here, we present a genome editing-based strategy to generate viable hypomorphic alleles through selective removal of the translation start codon. Using Arabidopsis thaliana NON-SMC ELEMENT 1, which encodes a conserved component of the Structural Maintenance of Chromosomes (SMC) 5/6 complex involved in DNA repair and genome stability, as a model, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rye sprout as a host for the rapid transient production of a recombinant protein using a geminivirus DNA-containing expression vector]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The agroinfiltration technique using sprouts as a host is one of the most cost-effective, efficient, and rapid methods for producing recombinant proteins. We previously reported that radish sprouts were the best host for this purpose. To find suitable alternative sprouts comparable to radish sprouts, we investigated rye sprouts using a wheat dwarf virus (a geminivirus) DNA-containing expression vector. Various rye cultivars were tested, and Raitaro and Ryokuhiyo sprouts exhibited the highest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cohort study of sustainable cultivation methods in mandarin orange orchards across Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Variability in environmental conditions and farming practices often leads to discrepancies between experimental results and outcomes in farmers' fields. This gap poses a challenge for understanding the effects of agricultural inputs and methods under real-world conditions, particularly in fruit cultivation systems, where large-scale experimental data are limited. In this study, we applied a cohort study approach leveraging data from farmers' fields to investigate the effects of pesticide and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient expression of human interleukin-15 in <em>Nicotiana benthamiana</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A plant-based expression system provides a cost-effective, scalable, and safe alternative to traditional cell culture platforms. In this study, recombinant human interleukin-15 (IL-15) was transiently expressed in Nicotiana benthamiana plants using agroinfiltration. IL-15 is a cytokine with significant potential in cell engineering, immunotherapy, and cancer therapy. A codon-optimized IL-15 gene was cloned into a binary vector designed for plant expression and introduced into Rhizobium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phenotypic Spectrum of Gastric Adenocarcinoma and Proximal Polyposis of the Stomach (GAPPS) in Denmark: A Case Series Characterizing the First Danish Families With the <em>APC</em> Promotor 1B Variant c.-191T &gt; C]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric adenocarcinoma and proximal polyposis of the stomach (GAPPS) is a rare autosomal dominantly inherited gastric cancer syndrome that is characterized by fundic gland polyposis of the stomach (> 100) and an increased risk of gastric cancer. The genetic cause is recognized as a pathogenic variant in the promotor 1B of the APC gene. Presently, there are no established clinical criteria, and current guidelines are based on limited evidence. In this report, we identified two families with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extraintestinal Manifestations and Cytomegalovirus Reactivation Are Predictors of Difficult-To-Treat in Ulcerative Colitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with UC, the presence of EIM and CMV reactivation was significantly associated with steroid dependence, steroid refractoriness, and resistance to biologic and molecular-targeted therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Miyake Revisited: Validating the Factor Structure of an Open-Source Cognitive Control Test Battery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cognitive control is a prerequisite for achieving goals in daily life. Miyake et al. (2000) distinguished three separable but correlated cognitive control functions in young adults: inhibition, shifting, and updating. This three-factor model was later adapted to a bi-factor model with a common factor and separate updating and shifting factors. Over the years, these models have been replicated in various young adult samples. However, other studies have failed to confirm these models. Furthermore,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improvement in coronary microvascular dysfunction after transcatheter aortic valve implantation leading to positive fractional flow reserve and percutaneous coronary intervention: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The management of coronary artery disease in patients with severe aortic stenosis is controversial, with no consensus on optimal revascularization strategies. The validity of using fractional flow reserve to assess ischaemia in this population is debated. Conflicting results have arisen regarding the impact of transcatheter aortic valve implantation on fractional flow reserve values. We present the case of a patient with severe aortic stenosis and intermediate left anterior...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of unilateral neck muscle vibration on tilt direction and variability of subjective postural vertical in the frontal plane during seated posture in healthy adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Unilateral neck muscle vibration (NMV) activates the primary endings of muscle spindles and modulates both subjective visual vertical and subjective straight-ahead perception. However, its effects on subjective postural vertical (SPV), crucial for postural balance, remain poorly understood. We aimed to investigate the effects of unilateral NMV-induced proprioceptive stimulation on SPV tilt direction and intraindividual variability in the frontal plane in healthy participants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-sectional comparative shotgun metagenomic analysis of the subgingival resistome in healthy subjects and patients with periodontitis from four countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Subgingival resistome profiles vary significantly by periodontal status and geography, underscoring the influence of clinical and regional factors on antimicrobial resistance in the oral microbiome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No Alterations in ACL Injury Risk Factors in Preadolescent Elite Female Handball Players Following an Eight-Week Targeted Training Intervention: A Randomised Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adolescent female handball players are at elevated risk of anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) injury. Early interventions during preadolescence seem crucial for improving motor strategies and potentially preventing injuries. This randomised controlled trial on preadolescent female handball players investigated the effects of an 8-week ACL injury prevention program (ACL-IPP) targeting modifiable neuromuscular and biomechanical risk factors and assessed retention effects 8 weeks post-intervention....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel Dual-Task Paradigm for Return-to-Sport Screening After ACL Injury: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This pilot study demonstrates the feasibility and preliminary reliability of the dual-task paradigm, particularly within the ACLR group. Poorer cognitive, hop, and upper-body test performances and smaller test-retest improvements for the ACLR group suggest persistent dual-task deficits following injury, supporting the paradigm's utility for ecologically valid ACL rehabilitation and return-to-sport assessment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemotherapy resistance due to epithelial-to-mesenchymal transition is caused by abnormal lipid metabolic balance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Invasive cancer is defined by the loss of epithelial cell traits resulting from the ectopic expression of epithelial-mesenchymal transition (EMT)-related transcription factors such as Snail. Although EMT is known to impart chemoresistance to cancer cells, the precise molecular mechanisms remain elusive. We found that Snail expression confers chemoresistance by upregulating the cholesterol efflux pump ABCA1 as a countermeasure to the excess of cytotoxic free cholesterol relative to its major...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turn-off fluorescence sensing of benzenediols <em>via</em> guest-induced π-conjugation switching in bisimidazole-based hydrindacene allosteric receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluorescent bisimidazole-based hydrindacene allosteric receptors 1a-c and 2 were synthesized for nonlinear ON/OFF sensing of benzenediols. By tuning their D-π-D conjugation through substituent modification, these receptors were designed to function as turn-off fluorescent sensors based on the cleavage of their π-conjugation accompanied by binding with benzenediols. The cooperative allosteric binding demonstrated selective and efficient nonlinear quenching toward orcinol.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut microbiota mediates the beneficial effects of exercise on autism-like behaviors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight exercise and FMT as promising strategies for alleviating ASD-related symptoms through gut-brain axis modulation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome sequencing uncovers the history of the Russian desman's gradual population decline and contributes to the evolutionary history of Talpidae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although anthropogenic factors have undoubtedly contributed to recent declines, our data reveal that the reduction in the desman population is primarily an ancient process driven by natural causes. This has resulted in persistent declines in both effective population size and geographic range and then subsequent evolutionary extinction of ancient taxa with limited adaptive capabilities. These findings lay the groundwork for future genomic conservation studies, incorporating expanded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of biomedical entities from multiple repositories using a specialized metadata schema and search-augmented large language models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking the power of extracellular vesicles: multi-omics integration for cancer biomarker discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41527006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260113024354&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>