<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:17:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural investigation of human U6 snRNA recognition by spliceosomal recycling factor SART3 RNA recognition motifs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human spliceosome-associated factor 3, SART3, is a key factor in spliceosome recycling and engages with U6 small nuclear RNA (snRNA) to promote the formation of the U4/U6 small nuclear ribonucleoprotein complex. Unlike its counterpart U4/U6 snRNA-associated-splicing factor PRP24 (Prp24) from Saccharomyces cerevisiae, which uses four RNA recognition motifs (RRMs) for the U6 snRNA interaction, SART3 has two RRMs at its C terminus. Here, we demonstrate that SART3 binds U6 snRNA as a dimer, and four...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glycosylated LGALS3BP is highly secreted by bladder cancer cells and represents a novel urinary disease biomarker]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bladder cancer incidence has recently risen, making it the ninth most diagnosed cancer, highlighting an urgent need for novel and effective diagnostic and therapeutic strategies to improve patient outcomes. Here, we report on a secreted glycoprotein, Galectin-3-binding protein (LGALS3BP), as a potential biomarker and therapeutic target for bladder cancer. We found a significantly elevated LGALS3BP expression in bladder cancer tissues, correlating with disease progression. Moreover, urinary and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterizing epithelial-mesenchymal transition-linked heterogeneity in breast cancer circulating tumor cells at a single-cell level]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epithelial-mesenchymal transition (EMT) generates heterogeneity in circulating tumor cells (CTCs), affecting their biological properties and hampering their detection. This limits our understanding of the mechanisms underlying hematogenous dissemination, especially in early breast cancer (BC), where CTCs are rare. Here, we aimed to detect CTCs with different EMT statuses from BC patients. CTCs in blood samples from 107 BC patients were evaluated using immunomagnetic depletion and multi-marker...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preclinical Evaluation of a Novel Molecule Targeting Nucleoside Homeostasis to Restore Energy Metabolism and Cognitive Function in Alzheimer's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is the most prevalent cause of dementia, characterized by progressive cognitive decline and cerebral metabolic impairment. Yet, the therapeutic options for addressing the disease pathogenesis are limited. Here, we report an approach by targeting brain nucleoside homeostasis and energy metabolism to alleviate AD-associated cognitive deficits. A compound, J4, was designed to modulate nucleoside homeostasis by interacting with the equilibrative nucleoside transporter-1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting early progression to atezolizumab-bevacizumab in hepatocellular carcinoma: a clinical and imaging-based scoring system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We developed an early progression score that integrates clinical and imaging factors with high specificity to accurately predict early progression in patients with advanced HCC undergoing Atezo-Bev therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-Transplant Outcomes by Bridging Strategy: A Nationwide Multicenter Study of Heart Transplant Recipients in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Direct ECMO bridging is associated with worse early post-transplant outcomes, primarily driven by severe PGD and early mortality, underscoring the need for careful candidate selection. LVAD bridging provided outcomes comparable to non-MCS and may offer a bridge-to-candidacy strategy for selected ECMO patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Particulate matter 2.5 promotes pulmonary fibrosis in allergic asthma through macrophage reprogramming toward the M2 phenotype]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inhaled particulate matter 2.5 (PM2.5, ≤ 2.5 μm) exacerbates airway inflammation and promotes fibrosis in allergic asthma. However, most studies have focused on airway inflammation, and direct evidence linking PM2.5 to fibrosis in allergic asthma remains limited. Here, we investigated how PM2.5 promotes fibrotic progress in allergic asthma, focusing on macrophage plasticity. PM2.5 induced neutrophil-dominant acute inflammation, whereas house dust mite (HDM) induced T helper 2- and immunoglobulin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acidity-Mediated Metal Oxide Heterointerfaces: Roles of Substrates and Surface Modification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although strong modulation of interfacial electron concentrations by the relative acidity of surface additives is suggested, direct observation of corresponding changes in surface conductivity, crucial for understanding the role of local space charge, is lacking. Here, a model platform comprising well-aligned mixed ionic-electronic conducting Pr(0.2)Ce(0.8)O(2-δ) nanowire arrays (PCO(NA)) is introduced to show that acidity-modulated heterointerfaces predict electron depletion or accumulation,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revealing How Acid Sites Enhance the Electrocatalytic Glycerol Oxidation Performance on Pt Loaded Zeolite-Carbon Composite Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The catalytic role and function of acid sites in solid acid catalysts, such as zeolites, are well understood in the context of heterogeneous catalytic reactions. But although many studies have highlighted the importance of acid sites, their catalytic effects in electrocatalytic reactions have rarely been investigated. In this work, a novel catalyst synthesis strategy is developed, integrating metal sites with acid sites for application in the electrocatalytic glycerol oxidation reaction (EGOR)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simplified and Accurate Approach to Sleep Disorder Prediction Using Body Composition Metrics: A Development and Validation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Predicting the risk of sleep disorders such as insomnia, obstructive sleep apnea (OSA), and comorbid insomnia and sleep apnea (COMISA) typically requires costly and time-consuming assessments. The SLEEPS algorithm simplifies this process using only nine questions, including body mass index (BMI). However, BMI alone cannot capture differences in body composition, as individuals with the same BMI may have different muscle and fat distribution. This study aims to improve sleep disorder prediction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Backbone Tailoring Enables High-Performance and Stable n-Type Organic Mixed Ionic-Electronic Conductors for Synaptic Simulation and Biosensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-performance and stable n-type organic mixed ionic-electronic conductors (OMIECs) are crucial for advancing organic electrochemical transistors (OECTs)-based low-power complementary circuits and biosensors, yet their development remains a great challenge. Herein, the study presents a series of donor-acceptor polymers incorporating bithiophene (BTI) and fused BTI derivatives with varying conjugation backbone lengths as acceptors. The mid-size fused BTI dimer enables polymer PBTI2g-DTCN with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photocatalytic Radical Umpolung for Strain-Release Difunctionalization of (Aza)bicyclo[1.1.0]butanes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Azetidines and cyclobutanes are increasingly valued as potent bioisosteres of pyridines and benzenes in medicinal chemistry. Herein, we report a radical umpolung strategy for the regioselective difunctionalization of azabicyclo[1.1.0]butanes (ABBs) and bicyclo[1.1.0]butanes (BCBs) that exhibits complementary regioselectivity to conventional polar strain-release methods. This approach uses photocatalytically generated electrophilic sulfonyl radicals from readily available sulfinates to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Efficacy and Safety of Baricitinib in Patients With Alopecia Areata in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Baricitinib was well tolerated and resulted in clinical improvement among patients with AA in a real-world clinical setting. Baricitinib is a potential treatment option for patients with treatment-resistant AA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential Modulation of Skin Barrier Proteins and Lipid Synthesis by <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em>, <em>Staphylococcus hominis</em>, and <em>Cutibacterium acnes</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Collectively, these findings suggest that S. aureus compromises the skin barrier function by downregulating the expression of barrier-associated proteins and lipid synthesis enzymes, whereas S. hominis and C. acnes enhance barrier integrity by upregulating these components. These differential microbial effects elucidate potential mechanisms by which the skin microbiome contributes to barrier homeostasis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High Plasma Renin and Aldosterone Levels Are Associated With a Unique Phenotype in Primary Hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the importance of stratifying hypertensive phenotypes to enable personalized treatment for primary hypertensives with elevated renin and aldosterone levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship Between Food Insecurity and Poor Cardiovascular Health in Korean Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Food insecurity is associated with poor CVH in Korean adults. Specifically, it is associated with current smoking and high blood pressure. Improving food insecurity may help prevent poor CVH in Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current Therapeutic Patterns of Pulmonary Arterial Hypertension in Korea: A Five-Year Follow-up of the PHOENIKS Longitudinal Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The current Korean PAH treatment strategy must be improved to align with the revised guidelines and optimize patient outcomes. Further efforts are needed to change health insurance coverage criteria to enhance guideline adherence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct prognostic and molecular profiles of fat versus vein invasion in T3a renal cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In T3a RCC, site of invasion was an independent prognosticator of survival regardless of tumor size. SFI and RVI tumors exhibited distinct genomic and pathway profiles suggesting an intrinsically disparate competencies directing the tumors to adopt different invasion mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determining lymph node metastasis and dissection and following prognosis in pancreatic neuroendocrine tumors: risk prediction using preoperative factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Risk stratification using preoperative factors can inform surgical decisions in pNETs. LN dissection may be omitted in low-risk patients, while high-risk cases require accurate staging and postoperative planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic impact of serum triglycerides in acute pancreatitis: Evidence from multi-center cohort study using a common data model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HTG is associated with a higher risk of developing severe AP. Younger patients (<60 years) with HTG may be vulnerable to a more severe disease course.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbiome of Dipteran vectors associated with integron and antibiotic resistance genes in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The spread of antibiotic resistance genes (ARGs) across the environment and the role that organisms that interact with humans play as reservoirs of resistant bacteria pose important threats to public health. Flies are two-winged insects composing the order Diptera, which includes synanthropic species with significant ecological roles as pollinators, vectors, and decomposers. Here, we used iSeq100 metabarcoding to characterize the microbiome of six dipteran species in South Korea: Lucilia...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[4-1BB<sup>+</sup> Tregs and inhibitory progenitor exhausted T cells confer resistance to anti-PD-L1 and anti-CTLA-4 combination therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Predictors of immune checkpoint inhibitor response in cancer remain elusive. From a previous phase 2 neoadjuvant immunotherapy window-of-opportunity study, we present the single-cell RNA and T cell receptor (TCR) sequencing analysis of 57 pre- and post-treatment tumor biopsies from head and neck cancer patients treated with durvalumab (anti-PD-L1) alone or with tremelimumab (anti-CTLA-4), identifying key cellular and molecular predictors of immune checkpoint inhibitor (ICI) response. Malignant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of cinnamaldehyde on rheological, physicochemical, and structural properties of mung bean protein/low methoxyl pectin-based emulsion gels as a delivery system of vitamin D3 for dysphagia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study aimed to develop mung bean protein/low methoxyl pectin-based emulsion gels with different concentrations (0 %, 10 %, 30 %, and 50 %) of cinnamaldehyde as a delivery system of vitamin D3 for dysphagia. In the frequency sweep test, the storage modulus (G'), loss modulus (G"), and complex viscosity (η*) of the emulsion gels increased with increasing concentration of cinnamaldehyde due to hydrogen bond and Schiff base reaction in the gel network, as proved by FT-IR and XRD. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical feasibility of fully automated three-dimensional liver segmentation in low-dose chest computed tomography (CT) for assessing hepatic steatosis: an alternative to abdominal CT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The LDCT-derived volumetric liver HU and HS grading based on these measurements strongly aligned with AbCT-based evaluation, indicating the potential of LDCT as an AbCT alternative in HS screening.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inactivation of Vaccinia Virus via Nitric Oxide-Plasma Activated Water: A Potential Way to Inactivate Mpox Virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mpox virus (Poxviridae family) an emerging environmental bio-contaminant caused a non-zoonotic human infection in 2022. The recent surge mirrors early COVID-19 trends, highlighting the need for effective viral inactivation to prevent outbreaks and reduce environmental risks. Our study explores an eco-friendly and non-toxic antiviral approach using nitric oxide (NO(x))-plasma activated water (PAW) for environmental decontamination. Vaccinia virus (VACV) chosen as a surrogate model due to their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A biomimetic folding paper co-culture system for analyzing cellular crosstalk in bone healing: Interactions of bone morphogenetic protein-2, Wnt family member 1, periostin, and platelet-derived growth factor subunit A between periosteum-derived progenitor cells and adipose-derived stem cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bone defects, commonly associated with osteoporosis, result in fragile bones prone to fractures in both men and women. Osteoporotic fractures often lead to prolonged healing due to impaired cell differentiation. Understanding cellular crosstalk during bone regeneration is crucial for developing effective treatments. Periosteum-derived progenitor cells (PDPCs) and adipose-derived stem cells (ADSCs) play essential roles in bone formation because ADSCs secret key growth factors, such as bone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of intradermal Danish- vs. transcutaneous Tokyo-strain BCG vaccination in Korean children: A nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this large real-world cohort, intradermal BCG (Danish-1331) and transcutaneous BCG (Tokyo-172) provided equivalent protection against pediatric tuberculosis. Intradermal vaccination was associated with only a very small increase in lymphadenitis, while serious adverse events were uncommon with both methods. These findings support programmatic flexibility in BCG vaccination policy: both methods are safe and effective, so selection can be guided by vaccine supply, delivery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dupilumab improves quality of life assessed by the Quality of Life in Hand Eczema Questionnaire]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative efficacy and safety of tislelizumab and other programmed cell death protein 1 inhibitors in first-line treatment of advanced gastroesophageal cancers: a systematic review and network meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Overall, these analyses suggest that tislelizumab + chemotherapy is similarly efficacious to pembrolizumab + chemotherapy and nivolumab + chemotherapy, and is associated with a similar or lower incidence of grade ≥ 3 treatment-related adverse events in the first-line treatment of gastric/gastroesophageal junction cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PSM-SMOTE: propensity score matching and synthetic minority oversampling for handling unbalanced microbiome data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PSM-SMOTE effectively addresses dual imbalance in microbiome data and consistently enhances performance, providing a practical solution for imbalanced data analyses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vestibulo-sympathetic interaction and otolith function in postural orthostatic tachycardia syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Otolithic function may play a role in accentuating BPV and HRV in POTS by contributing to enhanced sympathetic outflow.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogeochemical conceptualization of granitic-urban area for sustainable water resource management: a case study of Daejeon, Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Groundwater is increasingly vital under growing demand and climate pressures, making its effective management essential for sustainable use. A thorough understanding of hydrogeochemical processes is therefore critical to secure water quality and guide resource development. This study develops a conceptual model of a granitic aquifer in Daejeon, Korea, representing a typical weathered-fractured system under mixed urban and green land-use conditions. An integrated approach was applied, combining...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation between the Electrical Properties and Formation Temperature of Self-assembled Monolayer-Based Molecular Junctions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Self-assembled monolayers (SAMs) of molecules have been reported to exhibit improved structural quality when formed at elevated temperatures; however, this effect has long been ignored in the field of molecular electronics. In this study, electrical measurements such as current-voltage characteristics were combined with scanning tunneling microscopy (STM) images to analyze the correlation between the SAM formation temperature and the resulting electrical properties of SAM junctions using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Testosterone-mediated regulation of renal GSTA1/2 expression in male mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These suggest that testosterone suppresses renal GSTA isoform expression in male mice, with GSTA1/2 being more sensitive to testosterone-mediated inhibition than GSTA3 or GSTA4.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integration of locking screw fixation into 3D-printed patient-specific porous titanium implants enhances osseointegration: an <em>in vivo</em> study in a rabbit bone defect model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This study demonstrates that integrating locking screw fixation into 3D-printed porous titanium PSIs enhances osseointegration by improving primary stability. These findings suggest that locking fixation in PSI designs may improve outcomes for load-bearing bone defect reconstructions in veterinary and potentially human applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences of Women With Diabetes Using Wearable Continuous Glucose Monitors During Pregnancy: A Qualitative Descriptive Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PurposeThe purpose of this study was to describe the experiences of women with diabetes using continuous glucose monitoring (CGM) during pregnancy.MethodsA qualitative descriptive design was used. Fourteen perinatal women participated in this study, and data were collected through in-depth interviews conducted between November 2024 and May 2025. Qualitative content analysis was performed using NVivo software.ResultsThe participants were ages 31 to 42 years. One participant had pregestational...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aggregation-Enhanced-Emission Polymer Donor Improves the Efficiency of Organic Solar Cells by Suppressing Nonradiative Recombination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonradiative voltage loss (ΔV(nr)) is a critical factor that limits the efficiency of organic solar cells (OSCs). Introducing highly luminescent materials is a promising approach to reduce ΔV(nr). The majority of prior works have focused on enhancing luminescence of low-bandgap nonfullerene acceptors, whereas highly luminescent donors have received far less attention. Herein, we designed and synthesized a highly luminescent polymer donor with aggregation-enhanced emission property, namely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virus Enhanced Microrobots for Biofilm Eradication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biofilms pose significant challenges in biomedical, industrial, and environmental applications due to their inherent resistance to antimicrobial agents. This study introduced an innovative and effective strategy for biofilm eradication by employing virus-conjugated microrobots (virus@microbots). These biofunctionalized microrobots are synthesized via the hydrothermal method, followed by the functionalization of the viruses. The synergy of microrobots' active movement and the virus's specificity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LDI, A Lipid Droplet Inhibitor, Disrupts Lipid Accumulation and Modulates Hepatic Lipid Profiles in Fatty Liver]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Excessive lipid droplet accumulation in hepatocytes drives the progression of metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD), often leading to inflammation and fibrosis. As obesity and metabolic syndrome rise, MASLD has become a global concern, spurring research into effective treatments. Here, the design of a Lipid droplet inhibitor (LDI) is presented, incorporating porous silica nanostructures along with PKCα C1A and Candida Rugosa lipase, aimed at directly degrading lipid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal Eustachian Tube Plugging Method for Patulous Eustachian Tube Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sitting-position surgery may improve CR outcomes due to real-time symptom feedback. Angiocatheters are effective but prone to extrusion. Plugging is a promising procedure for PET with a favourable safety profile.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-voltage stability of sulfide-based all-solid-state batteries: benefit of the parasitic reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe interfacial degradation occurs in sulfide-based all-solid-state batteries (ASSBs) at high voltages, due to the parasitic reaction between the solid electrolyte (SE) and Ni-rich layered oxide. Herein, we show that a conformal nanoscale coating of Li(6)PS(5)Cl (LPSCl) on LiNi(0.8)Co(0.1)Mn(0.1)O(2) (NCM) promotes the homogeneous parasitic reaction and improves the high-voltage stability, enabling durable cell operation, even after extended storage at 4.25 V vs. Li/Li^(+).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stabilizing Pt-Fe dual-metal single atoms in ZIFs: a pathway to form heterogeneous catalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dual-atom catalysts (DACs) show promise for enhanced catalytic performance through synergistic metal interactions, yet their formation and stability during high-temperature pyrolysis remain poorly understood. In this study, we report the atomic-scale structural evolution and stabilization of Pt-Fe hetero-pairs anchored on N-doped carbon derived from zeolitic imidazolate framework-8 (ZIF-8) using in situ high-resolution high-angle annular dark-field scanning transmission electron microscopy (HR...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defect-induced subgap state engineering in neuromorphic metal-oxide phototransistors for in-sensor color processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the rapid development of autonomous vehicles, intelligent robots, and mobile electronics, retina-inspired neuromorphic photosensors have attracted growing interest as color image processors for machine vision systems. These devices typically mimic essential functions of the human retina, such as multicolor detection and the processing of raw visual information. However, most neuromorphic photosensors have been implemented with heterojunction channel structures or complex circuit...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cervical cancer screening rates in Korean women of childbearing age with systemic lupus erythematosus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectiveCervical cancer remains a leading cause of death among women of childbearing age despite the proven efficacy of screening in reducing mortality rates. Women with systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) are at a higher risk for cervical cancer but tend to have lower screening rates. This study aimed to assess cervical cancer screening (CCS) rates and identify factors influencing screening uptake among Korean women of childbearing age with SLE.MethodsWomen aged 20-49 with SLE and age matched...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Cell Transcriptomic Profiling Reveals a Distinct Monocyte MIF/ANXA1 Signature Associated With Poor Responsiveness to ICS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inhaled corticosteroids (ICSs) are the foundation of asthma management, yet a subset of patients exhibits poor clinical response despite adequate treatment. Understanding the cellular and molecular mechanisms underlying this heterogeneity is essential for developing targeted therapies. We performed single-cell RNA sequencing on peripheral blood mononuclear cells from 6 healthy controls, 6 ICS responders, and 4 ICS poor responders with asthma. We analyzed transcriptional profiles of immune cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transdermal Allergen-Specific Immunotherapy Using a Biodegradable Microneedle Array Patch in a Murine Model of Peanut Anaphylaxis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PE-MAP TDIT demonstrated therapeutic effects in peanut anaphylaxis, suggesting its potential for developing a novel TDIT for patients with peanut anaphylaxis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma Metabolomic Biomarkers of Middle-Adulthood to Late-Adulthood Atopic Dermatitis: A Prospective Cohort Study From the UK Biobank]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings from this prospective study suggest that the identified plasma metabolites could better clarify the underlying metabolic vulnerabilities and improve risk prediction associated with the development of middle-adulthood to late-adulthood AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct Clinical and Cytokine Features of Moderate-Severe Persistent AR Phenotype by ARIA Classification: COCOA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that 4.4% of Korean children had a moderate-to-severe persistent AR phenotype, as defined by ARIA. Early sensitization to Der p, Der f, birch, and Japanese hop at age 3 and prenatal antibiotic use are risk factors. Furthermore, this phenotype may involve both T helper 2 and T helper 17-related immune responses, reflecting a potential shift toward more complex or mixed patterns of inflammation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunotherapy in Peanut Allergy: The Present and the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnification-Invariant Retinal Distance Estimation for Vitreoretinal Surgery Using a Laser Aiming Beam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Using the area of laser aiming beam attached to the surgical tool, our method can predict the distance of the surgical tool to the retina with errors that are acceptable for implementing virtual fixtures during robot-assisted retinal surgery. The predicted distance is also independent of microscope magnification and can work when initial parameters are not precisely known. Future work will involve adapting this method to in vivo environments and further reduction in prediction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Validation of the Updated Korean Atopic Dermatitis Diagnostic Criteria in a Hospital Setting in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The updated KADA criteria provide a practical and intuitive diagnostic tool, effectively addressing the limitations of previous criteria and improving the efficient and comprehensive diagnosis of AD, especially in those with diverse presentations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of a PTPD-12-Containing Cream on Improvement in Hyperpigmentation: A Randomized, Split-Face Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PTPD-12 cream significantly reduced melanin levels in facial hyperpigmentation, supporting its potential as a novel, safe, and effective therapeutic option for pigmentary disorders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Para-Phenylenediamine Sensitization and Polysensitization: TNF-α, CXCL11, and Immune-Regulatory Gene Polymorphisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PPD sensitization identifies patients at increased risk for PS and reactivity to mercury compounds and fragrance-related substances. Preliminary genetic observations require validation in larger studies to determine potential immunogenetic contributions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbiome-Based Interventions for Skin Aging and Barrier Function: A Comprehensive Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The skin microbiome, a dynamic ecosystem of microorganisms, is essential for maintaining skin health by protecting against pathogens, modulating immunity, and enhancing barrier function. External factors such as pollutants, harsh skincare products, and aging disrupt microbial balance, leading to compromised skin health and accelerated aging. Aging-related changes, including reduced microbial diversity, loss of beneficial metabolites, and increased oxidative stress, contribute to inflammaging....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and Safety of CENTUM™, an Everolimus-Eluting Stent, in Patients With Coronary Artery Disease: A Prospective Multi-Center Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CENTUM was effective and safe at 12 months in all patients who underwent percutaneous coronary intervention. Our findings support the broader application of CENTUM in patients with coronary artery disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanding Global DES Horizons With the Korean-Made CENTUM™ Stent]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary Hypertension Redefined: From Historical Thresholds to Prognostic Relevance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De-escalating Medical Therapy in Heart Failure With Improved Left Ventricular Ejection Fraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnosis and Management of Statin-Associated Muscle Symptoms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Statin-associated muscle symptoms (SAMS) are a common clinical challenge that often lead to poor adherence or discontinuation of statin therapy, thereby undermining its well-established cardiovascular benefits. This review explores the current understanding of the epidemiology, pathophysiology, clinical presentation, and diagnostic considerations of SAMS, with a particular focus on distinguishing true statin intolerance from nonspecific muscle complaints. We discuss evidence-based management...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Short-term and Standard Duration Dual Antiplatelet Therapy in Elderly Patients: A Pooled Analysis of Five Korean Randomized Clinical Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Standard DAPT strategy may increase bleeding risk in elderly patients without reducing ischemic events, despite no significant age-treatment interaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of Coronary Artery Disease in Patients With Severe Aortic Stenosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The coexistence of severe aortic stenosis (AS) and coronary artery disease (CAD) presents complex diagnostic and therapeutic challenges, particularly as transcatheter aortic valve replacement (TAVR) expands to younger, lower-risk populations. CAD prevalence in AS patients ranges from 27.7% in low-risk cohorts to 74.9% in high-risk populations, synergistically worsening ventricular function and prognosis. Diagnostic evaluation remains challenging due to overlapping symptomatology and altered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Value of Angiotensin Receptor-Neprilysin Inhibitors (ARNIs) in Korea: Moving From Cost-Effectiveness to Implementation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncovering a Distinct Hormonal Phenotype in Primary Hypertension: Rethinking the Role of Renin and Aldosterone Measurement for Hypertension Management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and Safety of COVID-19 Vaccination in Patients With Heart Failure: A Nationwide Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: COVID-19 vaccination in patients with HF was associated with a reduced risk of hospitalization for HF, all-cause mortality, and other cardiovascular events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single versus Multiple Inflow Source for Coronary Artery Bypass Surgery in Ischemic Cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In ICMP patients, CABG using multiple inflow sources was associated with improved outcomes, particularly in those without recent or profound myocardial injury.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Performance of Angiography-Derived FFR According to the Analysis Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The diagnostic accuracy of QFR decreases with increasing lesion complexity, system factors, lower angiographic image quality, and analysis difficulty. These findings suggest that specific lesion, system, and imaging-related factors can significantly impact the reliability of QFR in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Proteome Features in Patients With Aortic Stenosis Using Data-Independent Acquisition-Based Proteomic Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This proteomic analysis identified potential molecular targets associated with AS pathogenesis, providing a foundation for further research on disease mechanism and therapeutic development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251005151749&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular-switch-embedded organic Schottky barrier transistors for a high switching ratio]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Research on organic semiconductors has increasingly focused on developing multifunctional devices, leveraging their inherent advantages such as lightweight properties, low-cost fabrication, and tunable optoelectronic characteristics. Within this context, the exploration of molecular switches, particularly diarylethenes (DAEs), for precise current modulation in transistors has garnered significant interest. While the optimal molecular switch design has been extensively studied, advancements in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asian dust exacerbates cedar pollen-induced allergic conjunctivitis in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Asian sand dust (ASD), a type of fine particulate matter originating from arid regions of East Asia, is known to exacerbate respiratory diseases, but its impact on the ocular surface remains poorly understood. Given the increasing prevalence of allergic conjunctivitis in Japan, particularly during the Japanese cedar pollen (JCP) season, we investigated whether ASD exposure aggravates ocular allergic inflammation. Using a mouse model sensitized with JCP, we found that conjunctival instillation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular insights into HER2/ERBB2 amplification and carcinogenesis in gallbladder cancer associated with pancreaticobiliary maljunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first evaluation of HER2/ERBB2 expression in GBC with PBM based on WES, HercepTest, and FISH. The significant increase in ERBB2 expression, driven by the synergistic interplay between GBC and PBM, underscores a critical molecular interaction that may inform the development of targeted therapeutic strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GPAM upregulation enhances hepatic fat deposition and reduces visceral adipose tissue in response to trans-fatty acids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A TFA-rich HFD increased hepatic GPAM expression, exacerbated steatosis, and decreased VAT. Therefore, GPAM may regulate systemic fat accumulation in the body.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photodegradation of methylene blue using carbonized bagasse doped with cerium oxide nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing need for sustainable and effective materials for environmental remediation drives the development of new catalytic supports for photocatalytic processes. Despite numerous advances, a gap remains in utilizing biomass-based materials for efficient photocatalysis, particularly in degrading organic pollutants. This research explored the potential of agave bagasse, a waste product from tequila production in Mexico, as a sustainable catalytic support doped with cerium oxide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Features of Pediatric Invasive Escherichia coli Disease: A Study at Seven Facilities in Chiba Prefecture in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pediatric IEDs are more frequent in children with comorbidities, and they vary in clinical features according to the age group. ESBL-producing strains should be considered in empiric therapy, particularly in infants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chelation-Driven Dissolution and Single-Crystal Growth of Hybrid Metal Organochalcogenide Semiconductors by Polydentate Amines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ability to grow single crystals is critical to modern society, particularly forming the foundation of the semiconductor industry that drives transformative innovations. While inorganic semiconductors are typically grown using melt-based methods, and organic semiconductors via solution processing, these approaches are often unsuitable for hybrid organic-inorganic semiconductors, which tend to exhibit low thermal stability and high solvent resistance. Here, we report a general solution-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Doppler-inclusive reclassification of fetal growth restriction based on Japanese criterion: a single-center study on perinatal outcomes of pathological and normal small fetuses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: FGR with Doppler-inclusive criteria can be better for practical use providing high relevance to perinatal outcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of ibrutinib and diagnostic liver biopsy for idiopathic refractory ascites after allogeneic stem cell transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Idiopathic portal hypertension-related refractory ascites (IRA) is a rare but potentially life-threatening complication following allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplantation (allo-HCT). Its pathogenesis remains unclear, and optimal diagnostic and therapeutic strategies have yet to be established. Here, we report a case of a 58-year-old man who developed progressive ascites after allo-HCT. Although the clinical findings met diagnostic criteria for hepatic veno-occlusive disease/sinusoidal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical predictors of underlying severe obstructive sleep apnea in patients undergoing gastrointestinal endoscopy under conscious sedation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Not only the presence of UAO, but also minimum SpO(2) < 90% during GE-CS was identified as an independent predictor of severe OSA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phagophores originate from endoplasmic reticulum membranes in vasopressin neurons in a mouse model of familial neurohypophysial diabetes insipidus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Familial neurohypophysial diabetes insipidus (FNDI) is an autosomal dominant disorder caused by mutations in the arginine vasopressin (AVP) gene. In AVP neurons in a mouse model of FNDI, aggregates of mutant AVP precursors accumulate within a specific compartment of the endoplasmic reticulum (ER). However, as FNDI mice aged, or were exposed to repeated water deprivation, the ER lumen dilated and mutant aggregates dispersed throughout the ER. Meanwhile, autophagic isolation membranes, known as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Patients' Needs and Preferences for Cardiac Pacemaker Implantation: A Qualitative Study on Disease and Medical Device Characteristics to Inform a Quantitative Preference Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural and Energetic Analysis of the CmABCB1 Substrate Transport]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[P-Glycoprotein, a member of the ATP-binding cassette (ABC) transporter family (ABCB1), actively exports various hydrophobic compounds from the cell. Crystal structures of the eukaryotic Cyanidioschyzon merolae homologue (CmABCB1) in both inward-facing (IF) and outward-facing (OF) conformations have suggested a transport mechanism involving conformational changes in the transmembrane helices (TMHs) and nucleotide-binding domain (NBD) dimerization. In this study, we employed the string method to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reactivity of Structural Oxygens in Platinum Group Metal-Free Co-Doped ATiO<sub>3</sub> (A = Ca, Sr, and Ba) Perovskite Catalysts for CO Oxidation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platinum group metal-free catalysts can be designed by maximizing the reactivity of structural oxygen in metal oxide catalysts. This study indicates that the symmetry of the perovskite oxide affects the CO oxidation activity and the release behavior of oxygen in the perovskite lattice. Specifically, cubic-type SrTi(0.8)Co(0.2)O(3) and hexagonal-type BaTi(0.8)Co(0.2)O(3) showed much higher CO oxidation activities than orthorhombic-type CaTi(0.8)Co(0.2)O(3). The oxygen-release properties evaluated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Albumin Continues to Engender Debate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between short-term exposure to ambient ozone concentration and influenza incidence in Kawasaki City, Japan: a time-stratified case-crossover analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overall, non-optimal photochemical O(x) levels are associated with a substantial burden of influenza morbidity. These findings may inform local public health initiatives by aiding the development of targeted preparedness and prevention strategies to mitigate short-term effects of air pollution.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accurate detections of the heterozygous SNPs with rice genomic data and prediction of de novo spontaneous mutation rate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We have developed a methodology for the detection of true positive HVs within Illumina sequencing techniques. This system removed false positive HVs, allowing for the estimation of true positive HVs and, consequently, the estimation of the mutation rate. The study outlines a clear, step-by-step procedure that can be employed to detect true HVs in different organisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Granulomonocytapheresis for chronic inflammatory diseases and sepsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Granulomonocytapheresis (GMA) has long been used to treat refractory chronic inflammatory diseases. Recently, an exploratory clinical study showed that GMA was effective for sepsis, and its use has been approved in Japan. The purpose of this review is to spread the knowledge about GMA in chronic and acute inflammation. GMA is a selective extracorporeal therapy designed to remove activated granulocytes and monocytes, key drivers of inflammation in various immune-mediated diseases. Initially...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploratory high-throughput screening of repurposed drugs for canine lymphoid malignancies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This exploratory screening study identified clinically approved drugs with available pharmacokinetic data as candidate therapeutic agents for the treatment of canine lymphoid malignancies. Based on this study, further studies are warranted to validate the in vivo efficacy and elucidate the underlying mechanisms of candidate drugs in canine lymphoid malignancies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41044621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of single-unit umbilical cord blood transplantation and haploidentical transplantation using posttransplant cyclophosphamide during first complete remission of acute myeloid leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Choosing an optimal alternative donor is an important clinical concern in allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplantation (HCT). In Japan, single-unit umbilical cord blood transplantation (UCBT) has been widely used in the last two decades, whereas HCT from HLA-haploidentical related donors (haplo-HCT) has been increasingly used following the advent of posttransplant cyclophosphamide (PTCY) for graft-versus-host disease (GVHD) prophylaxis. This registry-based study aimed to compare outcomes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Review of Trials for Unsuccessful Pediatric Drug Development Programs Submitted to the US Food and Drug Administration 2015-2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings from this review suggest that, although this represents an improvement from pre-2012 pediatric drug development programs, that basic problems are still encountered in pediatric trial designs and dose selection. The 15% failure rate may represent close to a best-case scenario for pediatric drug development presently, but an increased use of pediatric extrapolation could change that.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GmAP2 enhances plant tolerance to aluminum toxicity and phosphorus deficiency in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overexpression of the GmAP2 gene regulates several aspects of gene expression in Arabidopsis, including acid-aluminum stress, low-phosphorus stress, ERF family transcription factors, ABA signaling, and genes related to lateral root development. The overexpression of GmAP2 can help plants mitigate the effects of aluminum toxicity and increase their tolerance to low-phosphorus stress. Ethylene response factors (ERFs) represent one of the largest transcription factor families in plants and are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STRIPE partners in precision medicine: regulatory perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ophthalmic complications associated with COVID-19: a large US national database analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: To assess ophthalmic complications following COVID-19 infection and the impact of mRNA vaccination.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creeping fat is associated with transmural healing in patients with Crohn's disease receiving ustekinumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among all the body composition parameters, MCFI and fibrofatty proliferation score assessed on baseline CTE were independently associated with TH, and they demonstrated greater predictive efficacy compared to sarcopenia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond PSMA: theranostic cell surface targets in metastatic prostate cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Numerous prostate cancer cell surface markers are emerging as theranostic targets. For patients ineligible for or developing progression following PSMA-targeting therapies, extending cell surface targeting therapeutics, whether they are ADCs, cellular therapies, or RPTs, is increasingly vital.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First therapeutic drug monitoring of experimental favipiravir in Borna disease virus 1 (BoDV-1) encephalitis patients reveals significant gaps in antiviral treatment: a pilot investigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In conclusion, monitoring experimental FPV therapy in BoDV-1 encephalitis is feasible and should be performed continuously. Future prospective in-depth (multicenter) studies should include more patients and focus on dose-finding, dose-response relationships, and define a therapeutic index to improve outcomes of this so far nearly uniformly fatal disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of childhood maltreatment on treatment outcomes for posttraumatic stress symptoms and aggression in male former combatants using narrative exposure therapy [NET] - results from a RCT in Eastern democratic Republic of Congo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CSA among former soldiers was significantly associated with a higher prevalence of PTSD and increased risk of both sexual revictimization and the perpetration of sexual and other violent acts. FORNET demonstrates effectiveness in reducing appetitive aggression, PTSD symptoms, and violent behavior even in the subgroup highly affected by CSA - showing an even greater impact on current violent behavior. The ability of NET to address trauma and perpetration in a chronological sequence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of hypertension in the cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic syndrome among black adults: The Jackson Heart Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic (CKM) syndrome consists of four progressive stages and is characterized by the interaction of metabolic risk factors, chronic kidney disease (CKD), and cardiovascular disease (CVD). We assessed the prevalence of hypertension in CKM and its role in progression to more advanced stages. We included 2118 Black adults from the Jackson Heart Study without a history of coronary heart disease, heart failure, stroke or stage 0 CKM (normal weight, no metabolic risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scrotal reconstruction using anterolateral thigh flap in a pediatric patient: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Avulsion injury of genitalia is rare, particularly in pediatric patients. The reconstruction of necrotic scrotal tissue presents a significant challenge. This case report describes a pediatric patient who experienced complete avulsion of the left inguinal, scrotal, and penile regions, accompanied by multiple pelvic fractures, and the scrotal tissue subsequently became necrotic. We performed scrotal reconstruction using a pedicled anterolateral thigh flap and fixed both testes. Postoperatively,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of two chemiluminescent assays in determining rubella IgG in sera with low levels of specific IgG]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The evaluated CLIA showed discrepancies in determining rubella immunity, highlight inadequate standardisation in the quantification of specific IgG, which could lead to errors in patient management, incorrect classification of immune status, and unnecessary revaccinations in this patient population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of Idarubicin loaded Equalspheres in the TACE procedure for Rabbit Liver Tumor Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that ES can rapidly load IDA and achieve sustained release. The shrinkage of ES needs to be a concern in clinical applications. The IDA-TACE is an effective procedure for achieving hepatic tumor locoregional treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world Experience of Angiotensin II and Renin Usage in Patients With Distributive Shock:A Single-center Descriptive Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Angiotensin II can be used to decrease the doses of non-angiotensin II vasopressors, and renin concentration may potentially aid in the prognostication of patients with distributive shock.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innate immune cell subsets are enriched in synovial fluid of ACPA-negative rheumatoid arthritis and characterized by distinct type I IFN gene signatures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identifies a distinct innate cell composition and type I IFN gene response in synovial joints, but not in peripheral blood, of patients with ACPA- RA. Similar IFN levels across groups suggest the IFN signature may have been primed before the cells entered the joints. These findings provide a foundation for future research on type I IFN responses in ACPA- RA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observational Health Data Analysis of the Cardiovascular Adverse Events of Systemic Treatment in Patients with Metastatic Hormone-sensitive Prostate Cancer: Big Data Analytics Using the PIONEER Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND CLINICAL IMPLICATIONS: Our study highlights important heterogeneity in real-world, observational mHSPC data. The included patients demonstrated a substantial comorbidity burden, often exceeding that reported in clinical trials, alongside a high rate of cardiovascular AEs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pembrolizumab in Combination With Platinum-Based Chemotherapy in Patients With Recurrent EGFR and ALK Gene Altered Non-Small-Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Pembrolizumab in combination with chemotherapy demonstrated encouraging RR of 42% and OS of 22 months among patients with recurrent EGFR+ NSCLC. The efficacy in ALK+ patients was not encouraging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When did "I don't know" become a diagnosis? A conceptual review on diagnoses of exclusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diagnosis of exclusion (DOE) is a term used when a conclusive diagnosis of a condition cannot be reached after exhausting a list of differential diagnoses. A comprehensive search across multiple electronic databases and AI-assisted search platforms was conducted to identify published literature related to DOE. The search identified 29 conditions with a DOE and several articles discussing the concept of DOE. However, no publication reported specific criteria or frameworks to help clinicians reach...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of autologous platelet-rich plasma therapy in the management of oral submucous fibrosis: an exploratory case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Based on this exploratory evidence, we propose intralesional PRP therapy as a safe and clinically effective treatment for mild to moderate OSF. (Oral Surg Oral Med Oral Pathol Oral Radiol YEAR;VOL:page range).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mindfulness Skills: Impact on Surgical Well-being and Performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cognitive training is essential for optimal performance in high-stakes fields like surgery. Research shows that mindfulness-based interventions can help surgeons achieve cognitive clarity, emotional regulation, and technical excellence, benefiting patients, teams, and health care systems. For these interventions to be effective, they must be culturally accepted, integrated at multiple levels, and tailored to specific specialties. Despite challenges, context-sensitive strategies and consistent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unexplained early deaths in EMERALD-1: is liver failure the reason? - Authors' reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MPAC: a computational framework for inferring pathway activities from multi-omic data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MOTIVATION: Fully capturing cellular state requires examining genomic, epigenomic, transcriptomic, proteomic, and other assays for a biological sample and comprehensive computational modeling to reason with the complex and sometimes conflicting measurements. Modeling these so-called multi-omic data is especially beneficial in disease analysis, where observations across omic data types may reveal unexpected patient groupings and inform clinical outcomes and treatments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tiotropium in Patients With Airflow Limitation According to the Fixed Ratio But Not the Lower Limit of Normal: A Secondary Analysis of the Tiotropium in Early-COPD Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated tiotropium treatment improved lung function, ameliorated lung function decline, and reduced exacerbations compared with placebo in patients with FR+LLN-, providing evidence-based medicine evidence for the treatment in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Mucus Plugging and Body Mass Index in Patients With Advanced COPD GOLD 3/4 With Emphysema]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: COPD is classified by its clinical phenotypes-chronic bronchitis and emphysema. A CT-based mucus plug score (MPS) was recently identified as a biomarker to subgroup COPD patients with increased airway mucus plugs. While not necessarily linked to more pronounced symptoms or structural lung changes, mucus plugs are associated with increased mortality. Interestingly, a higher MPS seems to be associated with a lower body mass index (BMI), likewise associated with increased mortality....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Body Mass Index and Bronchodilator Responsiveness in Adults: Analysis of 2 Population-Based Studies in 4 South American Countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: There was a differential relationship between BMI and types of BDR: higher BMI was associated with FVC-specific responsiveness, whereas lower BMI was linked to FEV₁-specific BDR in individuals with asthma and chronic bronchitis and to overall BDR in those with chronic bronchitis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gain-of-function variants in IRF6 cause hidradenitis suppurativa, ectodermal dysplasia, and deafness syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BNST-projecting histaminergic circuits mediate state-dependent anxiety behavior through post-synaptic histamine H3 receptors on GABAergic neurons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the precise mechanisms underlying anxiety and anxiety disorders is crucial for identifying novel interventions. In this study, we report a histaminergic circuit targeting the bed nucleus of the stria terminalis (BNST) that mediates anxiety-like behavior in mice. First, we observed a significant decrease in both histamine signaling and histaminergic fiber activity in the BNST when mice entered an anxious environment. Selective modulation of the BNST-projecting histaminergic circuit...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decadal Decline in Heat-Attributed Excess Mortality and Evolving Population Vulnerability: Evidence from a Neighborhood-Scale Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While prior research has established the mortality risk of heat waves, limited evidence exists on the temporal dynamics of excess mortality and premature death burden, particularly at fine spatial scales. Here, we assessed decadal changes in heat-attributed excess mortality and years of life lost (YLL) with rapid aging. We analyzed daily mortality and meteorological data from 211 neighborhoods in Shanghai, China, during two warm-season periods (June-September, 2009-2011 and 2019-2021). A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three-dimensional cell spheroid technology: Recent advances and emerging strategies in cartilage regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Three-dimensional (3D) cell spheroid technology has led to significant advances in cartilage injury repair, the construction of osteoarthritis (OA) models, and the development of platforms for screening therapeutics targeting cartilage diseases. Compared with conventional two-dimensional (2D) cell culture, this technology better mimics the in vivo microenvironment, thus providing stronger support for cell growth and viability. Furthermore, it effectively stimulates chondrocytes proliferation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for long-term sickness absence in patients with high-impact chronic pain - a scoping review and Swedish register-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-impact chronic pain (HICP) affects 8% of individuals worldwide. Beyond its direct consequences, HICP increases the risk of long-term sickness absence (LTSA), leading to income loss and increased societal costs. Prevention is essential and understanding risk factors for LTSA is a critical first step. We conducted a joint scoping review and Swedish register-based cohort study, to first identify and subsequently analyze potential risk factors. A multivariable logistic regression model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of neuron-derived extracellular vesicles miRNA profile between patients with behavioural variant frontotemporal dementia and primary psychiatric disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The behavioural variant of frontotemporal dementia (bvFTD) often overlaps clinically with primary psychiatric disorders (PPD), leading to frequent misdiagnosis and delayed intervention. The "Diagnostic and Prognostic Precision Algorithm for behavioural variant Frontotemporal Dementia" (DIPPA-FTD) study aims to enhance bvFTD diagnosis by integrating clinical and molecular biomarkers. Among these, neuron-derived extracellular vesicles (NDEVs) isolated from plasma offer a minimally invasive means...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cannabidiol releases CB<sub>1</sub>R from A<sub>2A</sub>R repression in ischemic stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cannabidiol (CBD) is a phytocannabinoid with potential in one of the most prevalent syndromes occurring at birth, the hypoxia of the neonate. CBD targets a variety of proteins, adenosine A(2A)R and cannabinoid CB(1)R receptors included. These two receptors may interact to form heteromers (A(2A)R-CB(1)R Hets) that are also a target of CBD. Thus, we aimed to assess whether the expression and function of A(2A)R-CB(1)R-Hets is affected by CBD in animal models of hypoxia of the neonate and in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationship between physical activity domains by level and illness intrusiveness in people with multiple sclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings further elucidate the connections between physical activity and illness intrusiveness, which may help inform future interventional approaches.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular subtyping and therapeutic prediction of hepatocellular carcinoma based on exosome proteomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precision medicine increasingly relies on molecular subtyping to guide individualized therapy for hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC), yet conventional tissue biopsies have limited capacity to capture tumor heterogeneity and temporal changes. This study utilized patient-derived xenograft (PDX) models to isolate authentic tumor-derived exosomal proteins, which were profiled to classify HCC patients into molecular subtypes. Differential expression analysis combined with survival association screening...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cystic fibrosis mutant DNA analysis by interfacial electrochemical reactions with gold nanorods as catalysts on interdigitated tautochrone-curve electrodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis and intervention are crucial for improving clinical outcomes in patients with cystic fibrosis (CF), a life-shortening genetic disorder, making the development of cost-effective and reliable analytical systems for detecting the mutant gene essential. In this research, an innovative approach leveraging the synergistic use of gold nanorods (GNRs) as catalysts and fabricated aluminium interdigitated tautochrone-curve electrodes (ITE) is proposed for recognising CF-associated mutated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Melting-freezing pretreatment as an effective strategy to enhance enzymatic hydrolysis for porous starch preparation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to provide a sustainable and efficient method for producing structure stabilized porous starch by combining critical melting and freeze-thaw pretreatment (CMFT) with enzymatic hydrolysis (EN). Compared with EN alone, CMFT+EN synergistically facilitates porous structure formation while maintaining structural integrity, achieving 80 % and 60 % improvements in oil/water absorption capacities, respectively. The CMFT pre-generated surface grooves enhanced enzyme molecules attachment,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthetic genomics-based generation of the tick-borne encephalitis virus Siberian subtype prototype strain and E51K-attenuated variant for vaccine development and antiviral screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tick-borne encephalitis virus (TBEV) is a re-emerging pathogen in Kazakhstan, where the increasing risk of its spread underscores the need for improved healthcare preparedness, including the development of local vaccines. However, the absence of reference TBEV strains in the country presented a major challenge. To address this, we generated a prototype strain (Vasilchenko) of the Siberian TBEV genotype, predominant in Kazakhstan, using synthetic genome and molecular infectious clone technology....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERP markers of basic and higher order cognitive and affective Theory of Mind processing in young adulthood]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Basic and higher order attribution of mental states to others (ToM) based on visual social cues was recently associated with different early and late occurring event-related potential (ERP) components. As cognitive and affective ToM in everyday life occur in unspecific order, this study included three experiments in which they were presented in different sequences to investigate possible mutual influences of these types. ERPs of first, second, and third order cognitive and affective ToM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multinational survey of physician knowledge about management of chronic hepatitis C]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The surveyed physicians demonstrated a strong awareness of the current HCV guidelines but indicated potential gaps in knowledge and inconsistencies. Continuous education and support are essential to enhance adherence to HCV management protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Umbilical Cord Blood Transplantation Provides an Alternative for Patients with Chronic Granulomatous Disease Lacking HLA-Matched Donors: a PIDTC Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplantation corrects the phagocytic defect in patients with chronic granulomatous disease (CGD) and resolve infection risk and immune dysregulation. Umbilical cord blood transplantation (UCBT) is an option for patients lacking suitable HLA-matched bone marrow or peripheral blood stem cell donors. However, information related to UCBT for CGD is limited to a few small case series and limited subsets of larger cohorts where detailed information is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Characteristics, Treatment Response and Outcomes of Bronchiolitis Obliterans Syndrome in Children with Hematologic Malignancies Undergoing Haploidentical Hematopoietic Cell Transplantation with G-CSF/ATG-Based Protocol: A Single-Center Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight the importance of early diagnosis of BOS and initiating treatment for patients with early stages of the disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the impact of membrane fluidity in shaping lipid-based drug delivery systems development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Membrane fluidity is a fundamental property extensively studied in biological membranes and biophysical research, where it is critical to understanding membrane structure and function. However, its application in the development and manufacturing of lipid-based drug delivery systems, such as liposomes and lipid nanoparticles, remains underexplored. This mini-review shifts the focus toward the practical implications of membrane fluidity in pharmaceutical formulation and manufacturing. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput characterization of 5886 HER2 variants identifies 112 new in cellulo gain-of-function mutations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ERBB2 (HER2) is a well-studied oncogene with several driver mutations apart from the well-known amplification defect in some breast cancers. We used the GigaAssay to test the functional effect of HER2 missense mutations on its receptor tyrosine kinase function. The GigaAssay is a modular high-throughput one-pot assay system for simultaneously measuring molecular function of thousands of genetic variants at very high accuracy. The activities of 5886 mutations were classified, significantly more...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41046000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrolyte-free electrochemical ammonia stripping integrated with flocculation for efficient nitrogen recovery from swine manure biogas slurry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel electrochemical ammonia stripping (EAS) technology integrated with flocculation was developed to effectively remove and recover ammonia nitrogen from swine manure biogas slurry (SMBS) without alkali addition or heating. The optimal operational conditions were established by the suspended solids (SS) removal rate, the ammonia nitrogen removal rate (ANRR), and recovery content. The maximum SS removal rate (66 %) was achieved by adding 4 g/L of cationic polyacrylamide at pH 7 with stirring...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of the global regulatory factor VeA in Cordyceps militaris and its overexpression combined with tea polyphenols to enhance cordycepin production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cordyceps militaris has recently been regarded as a promising chassis for high-value compound production owing to its advantage in liquid fermentation, while further exploration of genetic targets and exogenous effectors is needed to enhance its productivity. This study presents the first demonstration of the global regulatory factor VeA as a key modulator of morphological development, conidiogenesis, and cordycepin biosynthesis in C. militaris. Furthermore, screening of exogenous effectors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Motivating increases in physical activity to prevent recurrence of weight gain after metabolic bariatric surgery: The Exercise Values of Life and Vitality Everyday (EVOLVE) trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first study to examine whether an ACT-based intervention can foster autonomous motivation for sustained MVPA to prevent weight recurrence after MBS. The results may inform more robust guidelines for PA in MBS and support integration of these strategies into clinical practice to prevent significant weight recurrence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting the FBXO5-DOK6 Axis to Overcome Temozolomide Resistance in Glioblastoma via Proteasome-Cytomechanics Regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of resistance to temozolomide (TMZ) represents a critical challenge in the management of glioblastoma (GBM), yet the molecular basis for this resistance is still not fully elucidated. In this study, we utilized a custom-designed CRISPR/Cas9 sgRNA library that targets 1,117 genes associated with ubiquitination, combined with a positive-negative dual screening strategy, to identify pivotal factors in TMZ resistance. This approach revealed F-Box Protein 5 (FBXO5), an E3 ligase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Irreversible electroporation with intratumoral plant virus immunotherapy induces systemic immunity in a metastatic model of pancreatic cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic cancer remains highly resistant to immunotherapy, necessitating innovative strategies. This study explores a novel combination of irreversible electroporation (IRE) and plant virus-based nanoparticles to enhance immune responses in pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC). IRE is a non-thermal tumor ablation technique already in clinical use, but it often fails to prevent metastasis. Plant viral nanoparticles, such as cowpea mosaic virus (CPMV), have shown potent immune-stimulating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using Explainable Machine Learning to Better Understand the Environmental and Socioeconomic Contributions to Preterm Birth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preterm birth (PTB) remains a leading cause of child mortality, yet the role of ambient air pollution remains disputed. In a cohort of 52,642 singleton births in Southwest China (2020-2023), we combined an automated machine-learning (AutoML) method with SHapley Additive exPlanations (SHAP) to rank and quantify 12 environmental, clinical, and sociodemographic predictors of PTB. Environmental factors collectively explained 48.5% of the importance of the model features, with residential ambient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polystyrene nanoplastics induce ovarian injury by PI3K-Akt pathway-driven macrophage extracellular trap formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanoplastics (NPs), an emerging and increasingly prevalent environmental pollutant, pose a significant threat to organisms. Although recent research has begun to elucidate the mechanisms underlying ovarian toxicity induced by NPs, the involvement of cellular interactions, particularly those involving immune cells, in ovarian injury remains poorly understood. Here, we established a murine model exposed to polystyrene nanoplastics over an 8-week period to explore the role of macrophages in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic Diversity and Evolution of Antibiotic Resistance in Yersinia enterocolitica across Multiple Hosts in Eastern China: A 19-Year Surveillance Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Yersinia enterocolitica is a pathogenic Yersinia species whose public health significance in China is frequently underestimated. Y. enterocolitica poses significant health risks through gastrointestinal infection and extra-intestinal complications. This study conducted systematic, whole-genome sequencing (WGS)-based surveillance of Y. enterocolitica in Jiangsu Province, China (2005-2023), to elucidate epidemiological trends, genomics and antimicrobial resistance (AMR) characteristics, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to Letter to the Editor Regarding "Predictive Accuracy of the 3-m Backward Walk Test for Fall Risk in Q2 Older Adults"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strengthening community protection: a call for localised preparedness, response, and resilience for public health emergencies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive dissection of rectal cancer organoids in responses to chemoradiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The responses of cancer organoids to treatments in vitro can predict the clinical outcomes of corresponding patients. Here, we further uncover that the responses of cancer organoids to combined treatments predict the clinical outcomes of locally advanced rectal cancer (LARC) patients more faithfully than monotherapy with 92.50% and 93.75% accuracy in the discovery and validation cohorts, respectively, which is partly due to the synergistic (3.91%, 5/128) and antagonistic (4.69%, 6/128) treatment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Updated efficacy and predictive biomarkers of QL1706, a bifunctional PD-1/CTLA-4 dual blocker in advanced solid tumors-A phase 1/1b study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[QL1706 has shown promising efficacy in solid tumors in a phase 1/1b study. Here, we report updated long-term survival outcomes and biomarker analyses. Among 468 patients treated with QL1706 (5 mg/kg), median progression-free survival (mPFS) and overall survival (mOS) are 1.5 and 14.2 months for non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC), 1.9 and 20.2 months for nasopharyngeal carcinoma (NPC), and 4.2 and 18.6 months for cervical cancer (CC), respectively. Liver metastasis is correlated with poor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Segregated supramammillary-dentate gyrus circuits modulate cognitive and affective function in healthy and Alzheimer's disease model mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While progressive cognitive decline is the defining feature of Alzheimer's disease (AD), many patients also develop prominent neuropsychiatric symptoms, including anxiety and depression. The circuit-level mechanisms underlying these distinct symptom domains remain poorly understood, and treatments that address both cognitive and noncognitive aspects of AD are limited. Here, we identify anatomically, molecularly, and functionally distinct subpopulations of supramammillary (SuM) neurons that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of the peptide Vulnusin, a wound signal that mediates mechanical-injury-induced nociception in Drosophila]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Animals can acutely sense a puncture or cut in their skin through nociceptors. However, the molecular identity of such "wound signals" and their receptors on nociceptors remains unknown. In Drosophila larvae, class IV dendritic arborization neurons are multimodal nociceptors that detect harsh touch, heat, and UV light to initiate nociceptive behavior. Here, we identify Vulnusin (from vulnus, a Latin word for wound), an endogenous peptide likely serving as a wound signal. Vulnusin, derived from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A spinal circuit for skilled locomotion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neural circuits in the spinal cord have a critical role in integrating sensory information and descending commands to coordinate body movements. Defining the functional diversity of spinal neurons is therefore essential for understanding the mechanisms underlying motor control. In this study, by combining anatomical, molecular, and functional analyses in mice, we identified and characterized a subtype of spinal ascending neurons belonging to the V0 family. We found that V0g ascending neurons are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preemptive gain control in primary visual cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neurons continuously adapt their response properties to their environment. In the visual cortex, this includes gain control processes such as contrast normalization, which matches neurons' limited dynamic response range to the prevailing contrasts. Contrast normalization converges to a state that is optimal for processing the current visual input but not for the new, unknown input that impinges on the retina after each eye movement. We hypothesized that this conflict between current...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How human infrastructure threatens biodiversity by squeezing sandy coasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coastal dunes form valuable ecosystems that provide flood protection, drinking water, and high biodiversity worldwide. Although their functioning hinges on habitat zonation along >km-scale sea-to-land gradients, infrastructure development progressively squeezes natural dune ecosystems into a narrow strip. Yet it remains unknown how much undisturbed coastal width is required to support the diverse suites of habitats and species assemblages found in natural dune systems. Here, we investigate plant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inflammation in atherosclerosis: Lessons and therapeutic implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory pathways operate at all stages of atherosclerosis. These processes are driven by risk factors and other stimuli that can spark inflammation by eliciting misdirected responses of intrinsic vascular cells and leukocytes, culminating in lesion initiation, progression, and complication. Continuing dissection of the key underlying inflammatory mechanisms with increasingly sophisticated tools has inspired successful clinical trials and enabled translation to the clinic. Here, we review...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iron Deficiency Definitions in Heart Failure Across Ejection Fraction Phenotypes: Prevalence, Symptoms, and Cause-Specific Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Irrespective of definition, ID was highly prevalent (highest in HFpEF) and independently associated with worse symptoms or HR-QoL. ID defined as TSAT <20% showed the strongest associations with outcomes, including mortality and HF or cardiovascular/noncardiovascular hospitalizations, likely representing the preferred definition with which to enroll a higher-risk group in trials.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicted Risk, Preclinical Heart Failure Measures, and Incident Heart Failure: The ARIC Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preclinical HF measures indicate higher absolute HF risk within PREVENT-HF categories and enhance HF risk prediction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "PbARP1 enhances salt tolerance of 'Duli' pear (Pyrus betulifolia Bunge) through abscisic acid signalling pathway" [Plant Physiology and Biochemistry 227 (2025) 110075]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41045894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251005151747&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>