<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 19:22:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacial Curvature, not Simply Size, Controls Spontaneous Hydrogen Peroxide Formation in Water Microdroplets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Micron-sized water droplets promote redox reactions that are absent in bulk water, yet the kinetics of these interfacial processes remain poorly understood. Here we use real-time fluorescence imaging to monitor spontaneous hydrogen peroxide (H(2)O(2)) generation in individual microdroplets. Both the apparent production rate and equilibrium concentration of H(2)O(2) increase with decreasing droplet size, even after normalizing for surface area, revealing an intrinsic curvature-dependent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping QTLs for PHS resistance and development of a deep learning model to measure PHS rate in japonica rice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rice (Oryza sativa L.) is a staple food for more than half of the global population. Preharvest sprouting (PHS), which reduces yield and grain quality, presents a major challenge for rice production. The development of PHS-resistant varieties is a major goal in japonica rice breeding. A deep learning model to automate PHS rate measurement was developed using the YOLOv8 algorithm. The model had high mean average precision (0.974). PHS rate measurements made using the model correlated strongly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Olefin Ligand Metathesis for Colloidal Emissive Nanocrystals with Enhanced Stability and Photosensitivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-resolution patterning of colloidal perovskite nanocrystals (PNCs) is essential for next-generation display technologies, yet conventional approaches relying on exogenous photosensitive ligands or additives often compromise optical properties and colloidal stability. Here, we present a nondestructive ligand modification strategy based on olefin metathesis, in which original oleic acid and oleylamine ligands are converted into metathesized ligands featuring dual anchoring groups and shortened...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of pyrogallol nanocomposite on miRNA and its associated pathways during radiation-induced toxicity in small intestine of irradiated Balb/C mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer is the abnormal and uncontrolled growth of cells that changes the structure of nearby cells or tissues. Cancer treatment strategies include surgery, chemotherapy, immunotherapy, and radiotherapy. Radiation therapy is one of the most frequently used cancer treatment modalities. Ionizing radiation not only kills cancer cells but also affects surrounding normal cells, causing extensive damage to all organs including the liver, kidneys, and intestines. Thus, identifying radioprotective agents...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microscopic positive surgical margins in robotic thyroidectomy: does robotic approach make a difference?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microscopic positive surgical margin (mPSM) is a known risk factor of recurrence in patients with differentiated thyroid cancer. While robotic thyroidectomy has gained acceptance as an alternative to open surgery, its impact on margin status remains unclear. This retrospective cohort study analyzed 2587 cases with differentiated thyroid cancer who underwent thyroid surgery between 2009 and 2023. Of these, 206 underwent robotic and 2381 underwent open thyroidectomy. The mPSM rate was comparable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of heated humidified circuits on arterial oxygenation during one-lung ventilation in thoracic surgery: a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Using heated humidified circuits significantly improves PaO(2) during OLV in patients undergoing thoracic surgery compared to conventional circuits. These findings suggest that heated humidified circuits can be considered as an option when hypoxemia persists despite other interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Asia Pacific Cardiovascular Research (ASPIRE) Network: Facilitating and Advancing Regional Cardiovascular Clinical Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[POST-TRAUMATIC STRESS DISORDER AMONG EMERGENCY RESPONDERS AND VICTIMS OF DISASTERS IN KAZAKHSTAN: PREVALENCE, RISK FACTORS, AND REHABILITATION NEEDS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Both victims and emergency response personnel show a significant need for medical and psychological rehabilitation. Early diagnosis and targeted rehabilitation programs are essential to reduce long-term psychological consequences in high-risk groups. The Mississippi PTSD Scale can be used as an effective screening tool in post-disaster rehabilitation practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-density lipoprotein cholesterol and clinical outcomes in patients with liver cirrhosis: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This large-scale nationwide study demonstrated that elevated LDL-C levels are significantly associated with an increased risk of cardiovascular events in patients with LC, while both low and high LDL-C levels are associated with a higher risk of all-cause death. These findings highlight the need for individualised lipid management strategies in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of 4D Flow MRI-Derived Aortic Hemodynamics and Their Relationships With Left Ventricular Remodeling in Patients With Moderate Aortic Stenosis: A Preliminary Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with moderate AS, 4D flow MRI revealed heterogeneous aortic hemodynamic profiles and peak TKE was a significant hemodynamic parameter related to early LV remodeling. However, these findings need to be confirmed in further studies with larger sample sizes and a long-term serial follow-up data.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alkali Metalation Enables Natural Anthraquinone Derivatives as Sustainable Cathode Materials for Lithium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic electrode materials (OEMs) derived from natural quinones can enable sustainable lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) if their dissolution-induced capacity fading in organic electrolytes and their conductivity issues are addressed. It is demonstrated that converting natural anthraquinones (AQs) into organic alkali-metalated salts effectively inhibits their dissolution in aprotic electrolytes. For this purpose, a solubility indicator (ΔMPI) is developed, which reliably guides the selection of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of Amorphous Phases in Mixed Conduction of Conjugated Regioblock Copolymers for Organic Electrochemical Synaptic Transistors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Growing interest in organic electrochemical synaptic transistors (OECT-STrs) based on conjugated polymer mixed ionic-electronic conductors (CP-MIECs) has intensified, leading to the need to establish clear design rules and fundamentally understand the distinct roles of crystalline and amorphous domains in the electrochemical doping behavior of CP-MIEC films. Here, OECT-STrs based on regioregular-block-regiorandom (regioblock) conjugated copolymers with precisely controlled crystallinity are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adversity is Differentially Related to Anger and Sadness Regulation in Newcomer Refugee Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study employed developmental niche frameworks to examine how adversity at the child- and parent-levels, as well as at the relational level through parental discipline strategies, was associated with refugee newcomer children's emotion regulation. Participants were 128 Syrian newcomer children (52% girls; ages 5-15 years) and their mothers who have been resettling in Canada. Mothers and children reported adverse life experiences in an interview, and mothers reported parental discipline...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Association betweend Rheumatoid Arthritis and Stroke Risk by Serologic Status and Stroke Subtypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with RA are at significantly greater risk for both IS and HS compared to those without RA and that SPRA patients showed higher risk than SNRA patients. Further studies are required to determine the potential of tsDMARDs in the prevention of stroke in RA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptional intermediary factor 1 gamma prevents lung inflammation and fibrosis via alveolar type 2 cells, fibroblasts, and macrophages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transcriptional intermediary factor 1 gamma (TIF1γ) inhibits transforming growth factor-beta (TGFβ) signaling, the main pathway involved in fibrosis. We previously showed that TIF1γ regulated anti fibrotic processes in the liver. Herein, we aimed to evaluate the therapeutic potential of TIF1γ in pulmonary fibrosis (PF). TIF1γ inhibited the TGFβ-induced epithelial-mesenchymal transition in alveolar type 2 cells and activation of fibroblasts in vitro. In activated macrophages, TIF1γ reduced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychiatric Morbidity Following Intestinal Infectious Diseases: A Nationwide Cohort Study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intestinal infectious diseases (IIDs), typically considered self-limiting, may exert lasting effects on mental health. This nationwide retrospective cohort study investigated the association between recurrent IID and the subsequent development of psychiatric disorders in South Korea. Using data from the National Health Insurance Service-National Sample Cohort (2002-2013), adults with three or more IID diagnoses were matched to controls without IID by age, sex, and health screening year. Eight...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[External radiation dose reconstruction for settlements near the Semipalatinsk nuclear test site, Kazakhstan, in the international multicenter study: a detailed review and comparative analysis of the initial data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Studies on health effects of radiation exposure to residents around the Semipalatinsk nuclear test site (SNTS), Kazakhstan, are necessary for epidemiological assessment of radiation-related health risks after low-dose irradiation. Radiation dose estimates are the principal point for radiation epidemiological studies. These estimates should be based on the most reliable initial data, used for dose estimations. The comparative critical analysis of various available archival and published initial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vivo responses of β-tricalcium phosphate-based paste-like artificial bone with antibacterial properties under potentially infectious conditions using a rabbit model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Calcium-phosphate cement (CPC), a paste-like artificial bone, is a material form that allows minimally invasive treatment. However, CPC is not infection resistant, which may lead to surgical site infections. We recently developed a paste-like organic/inorganic hybrid artificial bone that is compatible with the bone remodeling cycle. In this study, we added silver-loaded tricalcium phosphate, which has antibacterial properties, to the hybrid CPC and fabricated a prototype "antibacterial CPC"....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful repeated endoscopic balloon dilatation for esophageal stricture as chronic graft-versus-host disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial heterogeneity of FGFR2b in gastric cancer: a comparative analysis of primary tumors and peritoneal dissemination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric cancer with peritoneal dissemination (PD) confers poor prognosis and limited treatment options. FGFR2b-targeted therapy has emerged as a potential approach for FGFR2b-positive tumors. However, the expression and amplification status of FGFR2b in PD remains poorly characterized. This study aimed to investigate FGFR2b expression and gene amplification in matched primary tumors and PD tissues from gastric cancer patients, and to evaluate their association with established biomarkers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clonal Hematopoiesis and Risk of New-Onset Myocarditis and Pericarditis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, CHIP was a strong risk factor for myocarditis and pericarditis among middle-aged adults. Targeting CHIP and its downstream pathways may represent a strategy for preventing or treating pericarditis and myocarditis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current perspectives on proton and electron transfer pathways in photosystem II water oxidation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photosystem II (PSII) catalyzes the light-driven oxidation of water, progressing via sequential oxidation states (S-states) of the Mn4CaO5 cluster. Among structural snapshots of intermediate S-states obtained using X-ray free-electron laser (XFEL) crystallography, two-flash XFEL structures assigned to the S3 state reveal an additional oxygen atom (O6) near the O5 site of the cluster, leading to proposals that O6 is incorporated as a new substrate water molecule during the S2 to S3 transition....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Role of IL-4+ Memory T Cells in SARS-CoV-2 Booster Vaccination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vaccines effectively stimulate protective immune responses in healthy individuals, but the precise roles of germinal center (GC) and follicular helper T (TFH) cells in SARS-CoV-2 vaccine responses are not fully understood. This study used a conditional loss-of-function mouse model to investigate antibody responses to the Wuhan spike protein, specifically eliminating newly developed TFH cells during either the primary or memory phase. Our findings demonstrated that TFH-mediated GC responses are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sulfur-Mediated Microenvironment Modulation of High-Density Fe-N<sub>4</sub> Sites for High-Efficiency Oxygen Reduction and Cryotolerant Quasi-Solid-State Zinc-Air Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-atom catalysts (SACs) featuring Fe-N(4) active sites hold significant potential for the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR). However, achieving high-density Fe-N(4) active sites while precisely modulating their microenvironment to enhance ORR activity remains a formidable challenge. Here, an S-mediated strategy is presented for the preparation of Fe single-atom-loaded S,N-doped carbon (FeNSC). This strategy leverages the interactions between S and N during pyrolysis to significantly suppress...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Dyadic Experience of a New Breast Cancer Diagnosis Into the Shared Decision-Making Process: A Qualitative Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The study underscores the emotional complexity and interdependence of the patient-caregiver dynamic following a breast cancer diagnosis. Being the patient-caregiver relationship central to cancer care, it is important to encourage coordinated involvement of both parties in the clinical process may reduce psychological distress, alleviate decisional conflict, and enhance overall quality of life. These findings support the adoption of a person-centered, relational model of care that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ivabradine in Patients Undergoing Noncardiac Surgery: a Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients undergoing noncardiac surgery, ivabradine did not reduce the occurrence of MINS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physical Activity Levels in Individuals with Asthma: A Comparison Between Wearable Device Users and Non-Users: 2017 BRFSS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the health benefits of physical activity (PA), many individuals with asthma are not sufficiently active. Wearable devices (WD) are increasingly popular tools for promoting PA, but limited research has examined their effectiveness among individuals with asthma. This study aims to compare PA levels between WD users and non-users with asthma. Data were drawn from the 2017 Behavioral Risk Factor Surveillance System. Participants who self-reported a diagnosis of asthma were included in this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Piperonal-derived Schiff base molecules as potential multi-target therapeutic agents against Alzheimer's and diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These complementary studies highlight several hit candidates for further development as therapeutic agents against DM and AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A "Council of Caregivers" and Dementia Friends Geriatrics Person-Centered Session for First-Year Medical Students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aspirin dosing after acute coronary syndrome with suspected aspirin resistance: the ANDAMAN trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with ACS and DM or HRAR, twice-daily aspirin did not significantly reduce the risk of MACE compared to once-daily dosing. No significant difference was observed in major bleeding between groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare Leadership Perspectives on Priority-Setting, Geriatrics and Rural Care, and Effective Advocacy Strategies: Lessons From the Veterans Health Administration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study provides a deepened understanding of how and why healthcare leaders make decisions about resource allocation, as well as six actionable strategies that can help advocates of geriatrics, including those in rural settings, make the most effective business case for bolstering care for older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry updates from the field of stem cell research and regenerative medicine in July 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Latest developments in the field of Advanced Therapy Medicinal Products and regenerative medicine compiled from publicly available information and press releases from non-academic institutions in July 2025.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multicenter study on the comparability of myocardial strain values acquired with different CMR scanners and analyzed with different post-processing software: insights into the "Traveling Volunteers" study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Inter-scanner reproducibility for CMR FT measurements was high for GLS and GCS, suggesting potential use in routine CMR examinations. However, strain values between the two software vendors (CVI and Medis) were significantly different, indicating the need for standardization and implementation of software-specific cutoff values.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrinsic Motivation Moderates the Effect of Family Conflict on Disordered Eating Behaviors in Adolescents with Type 1 Diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Few studies have examined effects of intrinsic motivation (IM) on adaptive behaviors among adolescents with type 1 diabetes (T1D), although greater IM has been associated with less diabetes-related family conflict (FC) and increased regimen adherence. Greater FC has also been associated with disordered eating behaviors (DEBs). We examined the moderating role of IM between FC and DEBs in a culturally diverse sample of youth with T1D. 226 adolescents (Mage = 15.03, 59.3% female, 65.8% Hispanic,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor Necrosis Factor Alpha-Mediated Interaction Between Microglia and Müller Cells Exacerbates Retinal Ganglion Cell Damage in Experimental Glaucoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Interaction between Müller cells and microglia aggravates neuroinflammation, resulting in retinal ganglion cell (RGC) death in glaucoma. Here, we investigated how tumor necrosis factor-alpha (TNF-α) produced by activated microglia mediates the crosstalk between Müller cells and microglia and impacts RGC injury in a chronic ocular hypertension (COH) glaucoma model. In COH retinas, elevated TNF-α induced the activation of Müller cells and microglia, and recruited microglia to the ganglion cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitophagy Activation by N-Acetylcysteine Protects against Mic60 Deficiency-Induced Auditory Neuropathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Auditory neuropathy (AN) is a sensorineural hearing loss that impairs speech perception, but its mechanisms and treatments remain limited. Mic60, essential for the mitochondrial contact site and cristae organizing system, is linked to neurological disorders, yet its role in the auditory system remains unclear. We demonstrate that Mic60^(+/-) mice develop progressive hearing loss from 6 months of age, with reduced auditory brainstem response amplitudes despite preserved outer hair cell function,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of Monoclonal Antibodies in Alzheimer's Disease: Successes, Failures, and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD), referred to as a type of dementia, is a progressive neurodegenerative disease with cognitive decline and key features comprising extracellular amyloid-β(Aβ) and intracellular neurofibrillary tangles. Monoclonal antibodies (mAbs) are a new therapeutic approach targeting the specific biochemical abnormalities associated with AD. This review summarizes several mAbs designed for AD, which helps to describe their mechanisms, including amyloid clearance from the brain as well...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of age and treatment-related adverse events on financial toxicity among patients with breast cancer: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: No study identified the multidimensional domain of FT as a primary outcome among YA versus non-YA women with non-metastatic invasive breast cancer. Two studies showed younger age was associated with greater FT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Eliminating Waiting Periods for the Children's Health Insurance Program with Children's Enrollment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Waiting period elimination under the ACA led to modest but significant increases in CHIP enrollment among children. Our results suggest potential CHIP enrollment benefits from the elimination of waiting periods that were maintained in 9 states.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of Unhealthy Lifestyle Behaviours in Children and Adolescents with Mental Disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unhealthy lifestyle behaviours, such as sleep problems, low physical activity, poor diet, and excessive screen time, are common among children and adolescents. Lifestyle has a significant impact on children's physical and mental health. This study examined the prevalence of unhealthy lifestyle habits in children and adolescents in psychiatric care, and how they vary by age, gender, and diagnosis. Parent-reported data on sleep, physical activity, diet (i.e., vegetables and fruit), and screen time...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An MRI-based model for preoperative prediction of tertiary lymphoid structures in patients with gallbladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The MRI-based combined model developed in this study can preoperatively predict intratumoural TLS status. It accurately stratified the RFS of patients after surgery and the OS of patients with immunotherapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chromosomal Instability and Chromoanagenesis as Forces for Genomic Evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advances in sequencing techniques have revealed extreme chromosomal diversity and underscored the importance of chromoanagenesis in macroevolution, speciation, and the context of cancer and tumor progression. Evolution is essential for adapting to the environment, preparing for future pressures, ensuring survival, and generating diversity. Here, we discuss some events like chromothripsis and other chromosomal rearrangements, emphasizing their roles as driving forces in genomic evolution from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recql5-Deficient Mice as a Model for Studying Chromoanagenesis Phenomena]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Complex chromosomal rearrangements (CCRs) present significant challenges and opportunities in cancer and congenital disease research. Reproducing these rearrangements experimentally in animal models has been challenging, limiting our insights into their mechanisms and impacts. Recql5 is a critical DNA helicase that participates in replication, transcription, and repair processes. We recently succeeded in facilitating CRISPR/Cas9-mediated induction of CCRs in mice, harboring Recql5 deletion. Some...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Chromatin Configuration Promotes Constitutional Chromosomal Rearrangements in Post-Meiotic Sperm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The complex nuclear packaging of sperm DNA, known as sperm chromatin organization, is essential for protecting the paternal genome during fertilization. Recent studies suggest that changes in the post-meiotic chromatin structure, a specific arrangement that forms after meiosis is completed, may be associated with an increased risk of constitutional chromosomal rearrangements (CCRs) in offspring. This review examines the potential mechanisms by which abnormal post-meiotic organization may impair...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Molecule Studies with AFM and High-Speed AFM: From Nucleosomes to Chromosomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atomic force microscopy (AFM) is a single-molecule imaging technique invented in 1985. Development of high-speed AFM (HS-AFM) in 2001 now allows for the direct visualization of the dynamics and kinetics of biological molecules. In this chapter, we describe methods to both reconstitute in vitro and extract in vivo chromatin for air mode AFM and HS-AFM studies. With these methods, sub-nanometer static and time-resolved topographical measurements of nucleosome and chromatin conformations and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oligopaint FISH to Study Chromosomal Architecture and Structural Variations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Three-dimensional DNA fluorescent in situ hybridization (3D-FISH) has been extensively used for the study of chromosome organization, from large-scale chromosome territories to finer sub-megabase structures, such as topologically associating domains (TADs) or internal TAD features such as chromatin loops. The development of oligo-based technology has rendered this technique highly versatile and allowed to study chromosomal structures at different scale levels, as well as structural variations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visual Inspection of Sequencing Data for Diagnosis: Practical Guide to Structural Variant Analysis Using Integrative Genomics Viewer (IGV)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Next-generation sequencing (NGS) has revolutionized clinical genomics, enhancing structural variant (SV) analysis, especially found in chromothripsis. This guide focuses on key steps of SV interpretation using IGV, detailing methods for assessing SV veracity and distinguishing true SVs from artifacts. This resource aims to aid clinicians and researchers in effectively interpreting NGS-derived SV calling data to improve diagnostic accuracy and patient care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application and Prospects of Long-Read Sequencers for Preimplantation Genetic Testing for Structural Rearrangements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Long-read sequencers are known for their effectiveness in detecting genomic structural variations (SV) and are becoming a standard approach for comprehensive genetic analysis. In preimplantation genetic testing (PGT) for SV carriers, information on breakpoint junctions is required to determine the carrier status in embryo selection. Long-read sequencers are employed for SV cases that are difficult to analyze with conventional cytogenetical methods and the detailed SV junction information they...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification and Characterization of Chromothripsis by Optical Genome Mapping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Optical genome mapping (OGM) is a robust method for identifying and characterizing chromothripsis. While conventional short-read sequencing techniques encounter challenges in detecting chromothripsis due to limitations in read length and difficulties in analyzing repetitive sequences, OGM leverages the visualization of long DNA molecules to overcome these obstacles. OGM involves a multi-step process, starting with the extraction of ultra-high molecular weight DNA, followed by fluorescent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid Sequencing Characterization of Complex Chromosomal Rearrangements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Complex chromosomal rearrangements (CCRs), defined as structural variants involving more than two chromosomes or multiple breakpoint junctions, are challenging to resolve, and causal mutations often go unnoticed in genome studies. Short-read whole-genome sequencing enables the characterization of rearrangement junctions in unique sequences. However, issues persist within repetitive regions of the genome, which are prone to rearrangements. Therefore, complementary genome sequencing technologies...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EEG neurofeedback for the treatment of neuropathic pain in the elderly-a mechanistic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuropathic pain (NP) is a complex pain disorder that constitutes a significant problem in the aging population, impacting quality of life and everyday functioning. In the quest to develop effective treatments, much research effort has been made to understand brain activity in people with NP, revealing a number of disordered electroencephalogram (EEG) patterns. This information can then be used to inform neurofeedback therapy, a novel approach that involves volitionally training brain activity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ameliorating effect of veratric acid against mercury-induced neurologic deficit and reproductive toxicity in female rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of this investigation was to explore the potential effects of veratric acid on central nervous and reproductive toxicity caused by mercuric chloride in female rats. Six mercury-exposed female rats in each group were separately treated with 12.5, 25, and 50 mg/kg of veratric acid. The brain and ovaries were then evaluated for biochemical and histopathological analysis. Based on the results obtained through this study's assessment methods, mercuric chloride (HgCl(2)) administration may...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sharp increase in Chlamydia pneumoniae infections in 2024 in Germany]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chlamydia pneumoniae (C. pneumoniae) is a recognized cause of respiratory infections in children and adolescents, while it is often considered a negligible pathogen in adults outside of outbreaks. We performed a retrospective analysis from a nationwide surveillance network in Germany that collected data from 2018 to 2024. A multivariate analysis (binomial model) was performed to assess the influence of year, hospitalization status, gender and age on C. pneumoniae detection rate. Our analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of the value of novel inflammatory indicators derived from complete blood count in predicting for pertussis in children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CBC-derived inflammatory indicators, particularly NLR and NMLR, may serve as valuable tools for early predicting for pertussis in children under 2 years old in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The German Center for Child and Adolescent Health - A new structure for translational research in pediatrics shaping the health of children today and future generations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The new German Center for Child and Adolescent Health (DZKJ) founded as part of the German Centers for Health Research provides an unprecedented and unique opportunity for internationally outstanding research that contributes to the health and well-being of children and adolescents by creating a sustainable, multidisciplinary translational research center with a wide spectrum of clinical and scientific disciplines. The DZKJ attracts and motivates some of the best basic and clinical scientists in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling the Effects of Temperature and Resource Quality on the Outcome of Competition Between Aedes aegypti and Aedes albopictus and the Resulting Risk of Vector-Borne Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The community composition of vectors and hosts plays a critical role in determining risk of vector-borne disease transmission. Aedes aegypti and Aedes albopictus, two mosquito species that both transmit the viruses that cause dengue, chikungunya, and Zika, share habitat requirements and compete for resources at the larval stage. Ae. albopictus is generally considered a better competitor under many conditions, while Ae. aegypti is able to tolerate higher temperatures and is generally a more...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes of vitrectomy for proliferative diabetic retinopathy: a real world study in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study reported a comprehensive post-vitrectomy incidence and predictive factors in Chinese PDR patients in a long-term follow up. This would aid in the clinical understanding of this lifelong disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimal invasive open tibial fracture model in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The presented tibial fracture model with open osteotomy and retrograde pin insertion revealed minimal operative intervention and anesthesia, quick recovery and fracture healing with big callus formation. It is an easy to address fracture model for musculoskeletal research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inclisiran-based treatment strategy in hypercholesterolaemia: the VICTORION-Difference trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: An inclisiran-based treatment strategy was superior to ioLLT in LDL-C goal achievement, delivering early and sustained LDL-C reduction, with fewer MRAEs in individuals with hypercholesterolaemia. cholesterol, muscle-related adverse events, quality of life, statins.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing caloric and self-experienced dizziness symptoms: diagnostic value and implications in functional dizziness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights the potential diagnostic value of comparing symptoms with caloric stimulation and provides further support for motion perception overestimation in functional dizziness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterogeneity of diabetes and disease progression with a tree-like representation: findings from the China Cardiometabolic Disease and Cancer Cohort (4C) study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS/INTERPRETATION: These findings characterise the heterogeneity of diabetes phenotypes and complication risks in the Chinese population, suggesting potential implications for personalised diabetes care. Given the observed phenotypic differences, management strategies should consider population-specific characteristics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex-Specific Cardiac Magnetic Resonance Phenotypes in Danon Disease: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Danon disease (DD), an X-linked disorder due to lysosome-associated membrane protein 2 (LAMP2) mutations, features life-threatening cardiomyopathy. Sex-based cardiac magnetic resonance (cardiac MR) differences are recognized but lack quantitative analysis despite their critical importance in establishing sex-specific diagnostic thresholds and personalized treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathogenic breaches: how viruses compromise blood-tissue barriers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Blood-tissue barriers (BTBs) are highly specialized, selectively permeable surfaces that separate the circulatory system from delicate tissues and organs. Critical examples include the blood-brain barrier (BBB), blood-retinal barrier (BRB), blood-testis barrier (BTB), and other organ-specific barriers, including the alveolar-capillary interface in the lungs and the glomerular filtration barrier in the kidneys. These barriers regulate the bidirectional transport of nutrients, gases, and waste...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transjugular Transcatheter Tricuspid Valve Replacement in Patients With Cardiac Implantable Electronic Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Transjugular TTVR is safe and effective for managing TR and heart failure in patients with CIEDs. Due to the small sample size, these findings highlight the need for larger, prospective studies to validate these outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of RSV Vaccine on Heart Failure Hospitalizations: A Prespecified Analysis of the DAN-RSV Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Best of endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography articles 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of Myocardial T1 Mapping and Extracellular Volume Fraction in Heart Failure: A Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ECV has consistent prognostic implications across HF spectrum, regardless of HF types, clinical characteristics, and various etiology. Native T1 is less predictive than ECV, particularly in HF with preserved ejection fraction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HIV and syphilis coinfection in pregnancy and adverse birth outcomes in Uganda]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We report high TPPA seroprevalence, low syphilis testing rates in antenatal care, and significant associations with adverse birth outcomes among WHIV in Uganda, emphasizing the need to improve prenatal syphilis testing and treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[c-Myc inhibits macrophage antimycobacterial response in Mycobacterium tuberculosis infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mycobacterium tuberculosis (MTB) remains a major cause of global mortality, yet natural immunity prevents disease in more than 90% of exposed individuals. Interferon gamma (IFN-γ) is a critical regulator of innate immunity and enhances macrophage antimicrobial responses. In this study, we investigated how IFN-γ timing influences macrophage control of MTB. We found that pre-infection IFN-γ exposure primes macrophages for enhanced bacterial control by activating key antimicrobial pathways, whereas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of symptoms associated with Long COVID among adolescents in the United States, Summer 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Limited information is known about Long COVID among adolescents. This study will compare the risks associated with symptoms among adolescents who tested positive, were tested but never tested positive, and who were never tested for SARS-CoV-2 infection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bivalent RSV Prefusion F Protein-Based Vaccine for Preventing Cardiovascular Hospitalizations in Older Adults: A Prespecified Analysis of the DAN-RSV Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In adults aged 60 years or older, all-cause cardiorespiratory hospitalization was significantly lower with RSVpreF than with no vaccine. The findings suggest potential downstream cardiorespiratory benefits of RSV immunization, although the effect on all-cause cardiovascular hospitalization was not statistically significant.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RSV Vaccine Effectiveness Against Hospitalization Among US Adults Aged 60 Years or Older During 2 Seasons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Respiratory syncytial virus vaccines prevented RSV-associated hospitalization during 2 seasons, although effectiveness was lower in patients with immunocompromise and cardiovascular disease than in those without these conditions. Ongoing monitoring is needed to determine the optimal RSV revaccination interval.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measles transmission risk during commercial air travel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Measles transmission on aircraft has been well-documented, and many countries perform contact investigations after exposure events during air travel. This review summarized and updated available evidence for measles transmission risk during commercial air travel to inform best practices for public health response after such exposures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trauma-Informed Care as Structural Disruption: Social Work at the Frontlines of Systems Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A paradigm shift is needed-from models of integrated care toward liberatory health systems rooted in justice, equity, and structural transformation. By reframing TIC as a disruption strategy, health and social work can move beyond symptom management to advance structural change.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultralow Content of Chromium Species in Zeolite for Efficient Catalytic Propane Dehydrogenation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Supported chromia catalysts have been commercially used in propane dehydrogenation, which relies on Cr loading at weight fractions of up to 20 wt %. This leads to problems in managing spent catalysts with a high content of toxic chromium species. These catalysts also rapidly deactivate within 10-15 min, requiring frequent regeneration in each cycle. To overcome these problems, we developed a siliceous MFI zeolite with an ultralow Cr content (e.g., 0.09 wt %) that exhibits high activity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mt1 Expression Artifacts: A Caution to Cre Users]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Pressure and Temperature on the Thermodynamics of α-Helices: Implications for Piezophilic Adaptation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In light of the recent realization that a significant fraction of microbial biomass lives under high hydrostatic pressure, there is a renewed interest in understanding the molecular details by which proteins in these organisms modulate their functional native state. The effects of pressure on protein stability are defined by the volume changes between the native and denatured states. The conformational ensemble of the denatured state can depend on several extrinsic variables, such as pH and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional/dissociative seizures: Proposal for a new diagnostic label and definition by the ILAE task force]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The acceptability and validity of the term "psychogenic nonepileptic seizures" (PNES) have been questioned. Currently, numerous alternative terms, such as "conversion," "dissociative," "functional," "attacks," and "events," are used in both medical literature and clinical practice, leading to confusion among professionals and patients. The lack of a uniform diagnostic label is likely to impede research funding and service development. The International League Against Epilepsy (ILAE) Psychiatry...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Myocarditis or Pericarditis With High-Dose vs Standard-Dose Influenza Vaccine: A Prespecified Secondary Analysis of the Randomized DANFLU-2 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Dose vs Standard-Dose Influenza Vaccine and Cardiovascular Outcomes in Older Adults: A Prespecified Secondary Analysis of the DANFLU-2 Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This study found reduced incidence of cardiorespiratory hospitalization among those who received HD-IIV vs SD-IIV, driven by a lower incidence of CV hospitalizations, and particularly heart failure hospitalizations. These differences should be interpreted as exploratory findings in the setting of a large RCT with a neutral primary outcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of bivalent respiratory syncytial virus prefusion F protein-based vaccine in individuals with or without atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease: the DAN-RSV trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The VE of an RSVpreF vaccine vs no vaccine against respiratory and cardiovascular outcomes was similar among individuals ≥ 60 years of age with pre-existing ASCVD as compared with those without.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac Troponin T in Tofersen-Treated SOD1 ALS Patients: Beginning to Resolve the Catch-22 of Identifying Treatment Responsive Biomarkers in ALS Drug Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D-Printed Precision Porous Scaffolds Promote Healing In Vivo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precision porous scaffolds hold promise for tissue engineering and regenerative medicine due to their ability to support cell ingrowth and vascularization and mitigate the foreign body reaction (FBR). In previous work, we demonstrated that vat photopolymerization 3D printing enables the fabrication of porous scaffolds with 40 μm interconnected cubical pores. This study aims to do a preliminary evaluation of cellular responses and the FBR to 3D-printed scaffolds with 40 μm cubical pores, in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compound Heterozygous Structural Variants in Cases with Unsolved PRKN-Associated Parkinson's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this article we describe a rare configuration of compound heterozygous structural variations involving partially overlapping chromosomal regions at the PRKN locus, which are difficult to detect through standard diagnostic genetic technologies. This study highlights the importance of integrating WGS into clinical practice. © 2025 The Author(s). Movement Disorders published by Wiley Periodicals LLC on behalf of International Parkinson and Movement Disorder Society.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Epitope-based matching for platelet transfusion overview: Is it time?"-Insights and future directions from the 2024 American Red Cross symposium on platelet component selection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Respiratory Viruses, Vaccines, and the Heart: Lessons from DANFLU-2, DAN-RSV, and Beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preanalytical variables and analytes in liquid biopsy approach for brain tumors: A comprehensive review and recommendations from the RANO Group and the Brain Liquid Biopsy Consortium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review explores the pivotal role of preanalytical variables in bringing liquid biopsy approaches into the clinic for brain tumors. Preanalytical variables encompass a range of critical issues, from blood sample collection and handling to the impact of tumor heterogeneity and patient-specific factors. These variables introduce challenges such as false positives, false negatives, and variability in the analysis of tumor signals, which can hinder the diagnostic and prognostic utility of liquid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-dose vs. standard-dose inactivated influenza vaccine and cardiovascular outcomes in persons with or without pre-existing atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease: the DANFLU-2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among individuals ≥65 years, the rVE of HD-IIV vs. SD-IIV against respiratory and cardiovascular outcomes was similar among those with vs. without pre-existing ASCVD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Dose vs. Standard-Dose Influenza Vaccine in Heart Failure: A Prespecified Analysis of the DANFLU-2 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Influenza contributes substantially to disease burden in individuals with heart failure (HF) and is an established trigger of cardiovascular (CV) and HF events. Standard-dose inactivated influenza vaccine (SD-IIV) is recommended for HF, though immune responses may be attenuated. High-dose IIV (HD-IIV) was developed to enhance immunogenicity, but its effectiveness compared with SD-IIV against hospitalization for influenza and CV disease by HF status remains uncertain. Methods: This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular-Focused Messaging to Improve Influenza Vaccination Rates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In a large individually randomized trial embedded in routine care across a national U.S. health system, a cardiovascular-focused nudge intervention did not increase influenza vaccination rates on a background of low uptake. Nevertheless, this trial illustrates the feasibility of conducting large care-embedded trials of nudges in U.S. health systems. (Funded by Kaiser Permanente's Garfield Memorial Fund; trial registration, ClinicalTrials.gov NCT06571747.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cryo-EM structures of the MnmE-MnmG complex reveal large conformational changes and provide new insights into the mechanism of tRNA modification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MnmE and MnmG form a conserved protein complex responsible for the addition of a 5-carboxymethylaminomethyl (cmnm5) group onto the wobble uridine of several transfer RNAs (tRNAs). Within this complex, both proteins collaborate intensively to catalyze a tRNA modification reaction that involves glycine as a substrate in addition to three different cofactors, with FAD and NADH binding to MnmG and methylenetetrahydrofolate (5,10-CH2-THF) to MnmE. Without structures of the MnmEG complex, it remained...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HIV-2 evades restriction by ZAP through adaptations in the U3 LTR region despite increased CpG levels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Simian immunodeficiency viruses infecting sooty mangabeys (SIVsmm) gave rise to nine groups of human immunodeficiency virus type 2 (HIV-2). Two of these (A and B) spread substantially with an estimated 1-2 million individuals affected. The evolutionary adaptations that facilitated HIV-2's spread in humans are still poorly understood. Here, we report that diverse SIVsmm strains efficiently infect primary human T cells. However, they are more sensitive to interferon than HIV-2, indicating that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of artificial intelligence-generated vs human-authored abstracts in a real-world setting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MOLECULAR MECHANISMS OF OBSTETRIC ANTIPHOSPHOLIPID SYNDROME]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This review focuses on the effects of the antiphospholipid syndrome on the endometrial receptivity and pregnancy outcomes, paying special attention to how early diagnosis and treatment can enhance the chances of a successful pregnancy and reduce complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GENETIC ASPECTS OF WARFARIN DOSING ALGORITHMS IN CARDIAC SURGERY PATIENTS WHO HAVE UNDERGONE HEART SURGERY: SYSTEMATIC REVIEW]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings reinforce the clinical importance of the use of genotype data for more precise warfarin dosing in improving TTR, INR control, and bleeding risk. Further studies are needed to optimize the algorithms, extend the gene panels, and tailor the approaches more for patients after cardiac surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adjunctive Pulsed Dye Laser Therapy for Paronychia Induced by Anticancer Agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PDL adjuvant therapy significantly improves both clinical signs and patient-reported outcomes in anticancer drug-induced paronychia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalised treatment of patients with immune thrombotic thrombocytopenic purpura]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The duration of therapy with caplacizumab, rituximab and glucocorticoids in patients with iTTP should be determined by the achievement of target ADAMTS13 activity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Features of the phenotypic manifestations of GERD in its comorbidity with obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A comprehensive analysis of the characteristics of refluxate allows us to assess the course of the disease in more details, make assumptions about a unique combination of aggression factors for each patient, determine the severity of damage to the mucous membrane of the esophagus and, thanks to this, optimize approaches to therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Natural variation in CHELATASE SUBUNIT I-A increases grain weight and enhances wheat yield]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Grain weight is a major determinant of wheat (Triticum aestivum L.) yield and is controlled by quantitative trait loci (QTLs) derived from natural variations. Here, we report the cloning of a major yield QTL in bread wheat that functions in the chlorophyll biosynthesis pathway. We found that the natural variation of CHELATASE SUBUNIT I-A (CHLI-A), encoding a magnesium chelatase subunit, enhances chlorophyll content and photosynthesis rate, leading to increased leaf area and grain weight....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aseptic non-touch technique training for ultrasound guided difficult peripheral vascular access: A prospective randomized study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates the successful implementation of aseptic non-touch technique for USPVA training for physicians using a mixed reality simulator.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechano-Bactericidal Surfaces Achieved by Epitaxial Growth of Metal-Organic Frameworks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mechano-bactericidal (MB) surfaces have been proposed as an emerging strategy for preventing biofilm formation. Unlike antibiotics and metal ions that chemically interfere with cellular processes, MB nanostructures cause physical damage to the bacteria. The antibacterial performance of artificial MB surfaces relies on rational control of surface features, which is difficult to achieve for large surfaces in real-life applications. Herein, a facile and scalable method is reported for fabricating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-Pot Isothermal Nucleic Acid Amplification Assisted CRISPR/Cas Detection Technology: Challenges, Strategies, and Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884263/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The cutting-edge CRISPR (Clustered Regularly Interspaced Short Palindromic Repeat)/Cas (CRISPR-associated proteins) system, as an emerging molecular diagnostic technique, is driving revolutionary developments in the detection field due to its high specificity and efficiency. However, the CRISPR-based assays typically require the combination with an additional pre-amplification step based on isothermal nucleic acid amplification to meet the requirements of clinical diagnosis, which brings issues...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884263/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Randomised Controlled Trial Testing a Behavioural Intervention Program for the Prevention of Type 2 Diabetes Among American Indian Youth: The Tribal Turning Point Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this trial among American Indian youth spanning the COVID-19 pandemic, the TTP intervention yielded short-term improvements on obesity measures but only in the subset who participated before the pandemic.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrinsic Photo-Crosslinkable Semiconductive Small-Molecule Crystals (i-PSSCs) for Patterning Electronic Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precise patterning of small-molecule semiconductive crystals without external chemical additives remains a significant challenge. Herein, intrinsic photo-crosslinkable semiconductive small-molecule crystals (i-PSSCs) are designed and synthesized by associating [1]benzothieno[3,2-b]benzothiophene core with diacetylene-ended groups. The i-PSSCs undergo self-crosslinking directly upon UV light irradiation to yield micron-scale patterned crystalline films through a combination of photo-crosslinking...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[K29-Linked Ubiquitination of Transcription Regulators Controls Cell Proliferation in the Unfolded Protein Response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ubiquitin chains perform diverse biological functions through different linkages. However, the understanding of non-canonical K29-linked ubiquitin chains is relatively limited. Exploring the physiological functions of K29-linked ubiquitin chains beyond degradation is crucial for deciphering the ubiquitin chain code, which is essential for understanding cellular physiology. The unfolded protein response (UPR) serves as a crucial mechanism for cells to cope with endoplasmic reticulum stress...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brain Atrophy Does Not Predict Clinical Progression in Progressive Supranuclear Palsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Baseline clinical severity and brain atrophy could not predict individual clinical progression, suggesting no need for MRI-based stratification of patients in future PSP trials. © 2025 The Author(s). Movement Disorders published by Wiley Periodicals LLC on behalf of International Parkinson and Movement Disorder Society.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of a real-time prescription benefit on adherence and utilization of low-cost prescription alternatives for members new to diabetes treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Access to RTPB tools provides prescribers with formulary benefit and therapeutic options that allow them to provide the lowest-cost clinical treatment, thus improving adherence, increasing use of generic medications, and lowering plan and patient OOP costs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current landscape of US Food and Drug Administration use of expedited regulatory approvals for colorectal cancer care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ERPs have expedited approvals for new and increasingly targeted CRC treatments. All CRC treatments approved through Accelerated Approval or Breakthrough Therapy Designation after 2018 still await confirmatory trial results. These findings highlight the complexity of available drugs and diagnostic tests and the challenges facing managed care pharmacists in formulary management, diagnostic test coordination, and the development of utilization criteria given limited long-term clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world costs, treatment patterns, and clinical outcomes associated with treatments for advanced anaplastic lymphoma kinase-positive non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights the economic burden and variable clinical outcomes among patients with advanced ALK+ NSCLC. These real-world estimates inform cost-effectiveness analyses and clinical decision-making regarding treatment sequencing, particularly given uncertainty surrounding multiple preferred 1L options in clinical guidelines.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compound heterozygous <em>ROBO1</em> gene variants in a neonate with congenital hypopituitarism, dysmorphic features and midline abnormalities: a case report and review of the literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This case, together with accumulating evidence, supports ROBO1 as a potential causative gene for CH. ROBO1 should be considered during genetic evaluation of patients with CH and midline abnormalities. The co-occurrence of NOTCH3 and GPR161 variants raises the possibility of an oligogenic or multigenic etiology. The cross-talk between ROBO/SLIT and NOTCH signaling pathways may contribute to the complex phenotype observed and warrants further functional investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interplay Between Mental Health, Greenness, and Environmental Factors in Cardiovascular Mortality: Insights from AIR-MIND]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings indicate multidimensional interactions between AP exposure, mental health, and SES conditions in shaping mortality risk. Greater access to mental health services modified the effects of environmental exposures, attenuating the associated risk. SES and greenness exposure might be associated with heterogeneous modifying effects, but seem predominantly to reduce risk. Our study highlights the necessity for context-specific urban planning strategies that consider local...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental Pain Model Based on Short-Wave Diathermy Replicates the Intensity, Quality and Spatial Distribution of Chronic Shoulder Pain: A Parallel Group Validation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Experimental pain induced by SWD accurately reproduces many relevant characteristics of chronic shoulder pain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular IgE Sensitization Profiling With Micro-Arrayed Allergen Molecules in Adult Patients With Asthma From the LEAD Cohort: A Precision Medicine Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Molecular allergy diagnosis allowed the detection of genuine IgE sensitizations in adult patients with asthma; enabling stratification for precision medicine-based forms of personalized treatments such as allergen-based immunotherapy (AIT) and/or administration of biological treatments in asthma.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solar-Mechano Symbiosis Dual-Mode Janus Bioaerogel for Context-Adaptive Atmospheric Water Harvesting Beyond Solar Reliance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solar-driven sorption-based atmospheric water harvesting (SS-AWH) offers promise for addressing global freshwater scarcity. However, the SS-AWH heavily relies on favorable and sustained solar irradiation; yet real-world solar irradiation exhibits significant spatiotemporal fluctuations, limiting its sustainable application, as non/low-light conditions sharply reduce water productivity. This constraint is fundamentally due to the singleness of the water release pathway via photothermal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beneficial Properties of Enterococcus faecium Strains Isolated From Bats' Fecal Samples]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The principal objective of current study was to isolate and characterize Enterococcus faecium (E. faecium) strains from the fecal samples of Nyctalus noctula bats and to evaluate their probiotic potential and antimicrobial properties. Fecal samples were collected from bats in a rehabilitation center, and bacterial isolates were screened for antimicrobial activity against Listeria monocytogenes. Two bacteriocin-producing strains, E. faecium ST01TL and ST76TL, were selected based on rep-PCR...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rutin Enhances Intestinal Barrier Function and Protects Against X-Ray Radiation-Induced Barrier Dysfunction in Human Epithelial Caco-2 Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The small intestinal epithelium plays a critical role in nutrient absorption but is highly sensitive to radiation-induced injury. Despite this vulnerability, therapeutic strategies to prevent or restore radiation-induced intestinal barrier dysfunction remain limited. Polyphenols are known to protect the intestinal barrier by mitigating and repairing damage. Rutin, a quercetin-3-O-rhamnosylglucoside with antioxidant, anticancer, antidiabetic, and antihypertensive activities, may help preserve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40884154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid simulation for real-time flood depth prediction using support vector machine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Local Intensive Precipitation (LIP), intensified by climate change, has increasingly caused severe urban flooding. Although traditional hydrodynamic models such as SWMM and FLO-2D offer high accuracy in flood prediction, their computational demands hinder real-time application. This study introduces a rapid flood depth prediction model based on a Support Vector Machine (SVM), trained with data generated from a physically-based 1D-2D coupled simulation. The target area is the Jinheung Apartment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthetic data generation method improves risk prediction model for early tumor recurrence after surgery in patients with pancreatic cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic cancer is aggressive with high recurrence rates, necessitating accurate prediction models for effective treatment planning, particularly for neoadjuvant chemotherapy or upfront surgery. This study explores the use of variational autoencoder (VAE)-generated synthetic data to predict early tumor recurrence (within six months) in pancreatic cancer patients who underwent upfront surgery. Preoperative data of 158 patients between January 2021 and December 2022 was analyzed, and machine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxiracetam and physical activity in preventing cognitive decline after stroke: A multicenter, randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This multicenter, double-blind, placebo-controlled trial, commissioned by South Korea's Ministry of Food and Drug Safety, evaluated the effect of oxiracetam for preventing post-stroke cognitive impairment (PSCI) and explored potential interaction with physical activity using neuroimaging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural and functional characteristics of local immune memory formation in SARS-CoV-2-infected cynomolgus macaques]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the primary interface with the environment, the lungs require a robust local immune defense against pathogens. In a non-human primate model of SARS-CoV-2 Omicron infection, we used scRNA-seq, spatial transcriptomics, and immunoassays to investigate localized immune memory. Our results demonstrated established adaptive responses in lung tissue and medLNs, with significant activation of tissue-resident T cells and GC (germinal center) B cells. Inducible bronchus-associated lymphoid tissue...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating the neurophysiological effects of active noise cancellation on concentration in noisy environments using functional near-infrared spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we used functional near-infrared spectroscopy to examine the neurophysiological effects of active noise cancellation (ANC) technology on cognitive performance in noisy environments. Forty-one normal-hearing adults performed an auditory decision-making task in ANC ON and ANC OFF conditions. During the task, concentration changes in oxyhemoglobin (Δoxy-Hb) in the prefrontal cortex were measured, subjective listening effort was assessed using a visual analog scale (VAS), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SKKU, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BIDpred: unraveling B cell Immunodominance hierarchical pattern using statistical feature discovery and deep learning prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40881689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Knowledge of B cell immunodominance is important for designing vaccines that may elicit effective immune responses. However, the prevalence and characteristics of B cell immunodominance remain poorly understood. In this study, we introduced an immunodominance score through novel data processing methods and identified statistically significant characteristics of B cell immunodominance at the residue and patch levels. Based on these findings, we developed BIDpred, a B cell ImmunoDominance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40881689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Extraluminal silicone tracheal stent: Development and evaluation in a rabbit model of tracheomalacia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40880060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tracheal collapse (TC), defined by excessive tracheal collapsibility, often results in severe respiratory distress in small-breed dogs. Surgical intervention, including the placement of extraluminal stents, has been employed as a treatment option. Owing to the anatomical and physiological similarities between rabbit and canine tracheas, a rabbit model was utilized to develop a novel extraluminal silicone tracheal stent and evaluate its feasibility in treating tracheomalacia. The stent was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40880060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Evolution and Zoonotic Potential of Muju Virus (Orthohantavirus puumalaense) in Craseomys regulus, Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40879634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orthohantavirus puumalaense causes hemorrhagic fever with renal syndrome in Europe, with Puumala virus (PUUV) as its primary representative. Muju virus (MUJV), harbored by Craseomys regulus, an Arvicolinae rodent species endemic to the Republic of Korea (ROK), is also a genotype of O. puumalaense. However, their genomic diversity and zoonotic potential remain largely unknown. To investigate their prevalence, 185 voles were collected from 23 regions of the ROK between 2012 and 2023. Serological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40879634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in nanoporous NO<sub><em>x</em></sub> gas sensors: synergizing Raman spectroscopy, IoT, and machine learning for high-performance detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Among various pollutants, nitrogen oxides (NO(x)) stand out as particularly harmful irritant gases, known to cause airway inflammation at elevated concentrations. Chemiresistive gas sensing (CGS) has revolutionized gas detection with its low power consumption, cost-effectiveness, high sensitivity, fast response, and long-term stability. Traditional materials such as metal oxides, conducting polymers, and carbon-based materials used for NO(x) detection often suffer from poor selectivity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystal structures of the μ2 subunit of clathrin-adaptor protein 2 in complex with peptides derived from human papillomavirus 16 E7]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human papillomaviruses (HPVs) cause abnormal cellular proliferation, leading to malignant or benign lesions, such as cervical cancer and warts. The genome of HPV16, the most prevalent high-risk oncogenic genotype within the Alphapapillomavirus genus, encodes two oncoproteins. One of these proteins, E7, interacts with multiple host proteins and modulates their functions through distinct pathways. The CR2 domain of HPV16 E7 was recently reported to interact with the μ2 subunit of clathrin-adaptor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-Pot Monomer-Level Fabrication of Anion Exchange Membranes for High-Performance Water Electrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anion exchange membrane (AEM) water electrolysis (AEMWE) is considered an economical technology for producing green hydrogen energy. However, conventional AEMs comprising polymer backbones with anisotropically aligned cationic pendant groups exhibit unsatisfactory AEMWE performance and durability, limiting their practical implementation. Herein, a facile method for fabricating a durable high-performance AEM via a one-pot monomer-level Menshutkin (m-Men) reaction in a porous mechanical support is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep-Learning-Based Automated REM Sleep Detection in Patients With REM Sleep Behavior Disorder: Is It Reliable?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our U-Sleep-based REM sleep detector based on only EEG and EOG data showed good performance in detecting REM sleep. However, it performed considerably worse in RBD, especially in PD with RBD. Using transfer learning with fine-tuning by expert review, a high-performance REM sleep-detecting system will be realized.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potentially Inappropriate Medication Use in Patients With Parkinson's Disease: Analysis of Korean National Health Insurance Claims Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The prevalence and usage of PIMs were high in Korean PD patients during 2014-2019, and the utilization of PIM^(PD)s persisted throughout this period. These findings can be used to develop evidence-based guidelines for robust polypharmacy management strategies to ensure the safety of medications used by PD patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update of the Korean Clinical Practice Guidelines for Stroke: Blood Pressure Management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hypertension is a major risk factor for stroke, and appropriate management of blood pressure (BP) is crucial for both prevention and treatment. Since the 2009 publication of the Clinical Practice Guideline (CPG) by the Korean Stroke Society (KSS), significant advances have been made in BP management for stroke patients, particularly in cases involving intracerebral hemorrhage and in the context of endovascular reperfusion therapy for ischemic stroke. In light of recent evidence, the CPG...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40878301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered MSC-EVs loaded with BDNF-enhancing neuropeptides via a non-disruptive method enhance post-stroke neuroregeneration via intranasal delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mesenchymal stem cell-derived extracellular vesicles (MSC-EVs) show potential as neuroregenerative therapies. Incorporating bioactive compounds such as neuropeptides that enhance brain-derived neurotrophic factor (BDNF) expression may amplify their therapeutic potential. We developed a clinical-scale method for loading neuropeptides into MSC-EVs, while preserving their structural integrity and therapeutic functionality. Through scalable 3D bioprocessing, we produced high-purity MSC-EVs and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physical correlation between stochasticity and process-induced damage in ferroelectric memory devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the influence of sputtering plasma-induced damage on stochastic characteristics in HfZrO₂ (HZO)-based ferroelectric tunnel junctions (FTJs), with an emphasis on memory and neuromorphic device optimization. Variation of the sputtering plasma power during top electrode deposition introduces distinct levels of trap within the HZO layer. Low-frequency noise (LFN) spectroscopy and temperature-dependent electrical measurements confirm that higher plasma power generates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence as an independent reader of risk-dominant lung nodules: influence of CT reconstruction parameters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Variations in reconstruction kernels significantly affected AI's performance in risk-dominant nodule type classification, but not nodule detection. Ensuring consistency with radiologist-preferred kernels significantly improved agreement in nodule type classification and may help integrate AI more smoothly into clinical workflows.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inguinal intranodal CT lymphangiography for thoracic duct injury: feasibility with rapid scanning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CTL successfully depicted central lymphatics and thoracic duct injury with short examination times and an acceptable radiation dose.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DCNN models with post-hoc interpretability for the automated detection of glossitis and OSCC on the tongue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to develop and evaluate deep convolutional neural network (DCNN) models with Grad-CAM visualization for the automated classification with interpretability of tongue conditions-specifically glossitis and oral squamous cell carcinoma (OSCC)-using clinical tongue photographs, with a focus on their potential for early detection and telemedicine-based diagnostics. A total of 652 tongue images were categorized into normal control (n = 294), glossitis (n = 340), and OSCC (n = 17). Four...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Besifovir dipivoxil maleate versus other antivirals in reducing hepatocellular carcinoma in chronic hepatitis B]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Besifovir dipivoxil maleate (BSV) has potent antiviral efficacy against chronic hepatitis B (CHB). This study investigated the efficacy of BSV in reducing hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) development compared to other antiviral therapy (AVT) agents. We conducted a retrospective cohort study on treatment-naïve patients with CHB who initiated an AVT between 2017 and 2022 with BSV (n = 486), entecavir (ETV) (n = 852), tenofovir alafenamide (TAF) (n = 801), or tenofovir disoproxyl fumarate (TDF) (n =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[All-optically controlled phased-array for ultrasonics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ability to dynamically shape ultrasound fields is critical for emerging applications in therapeutic ultrasound, particle manipulation and tissue engineering. While existing phased arrays provide beam steering for imaging, these newer applications require higher intensities. This complicates the electrical driving and ultimately limits the array size and spatial complexity of the field. Here, we introduce a scalable architecture for driving phased arrays using a single power source and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduction of lymphotoxin beta receptor induces cellular senescence via the MDMX-p53 pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The lymphotoxin β receptor (LTβR), a key activator of non-canonical NF-κB signaling, is expressed in various cells, including cancer cells. Although high expression of LTβR has been associated with poor patient prognosis and drug resistance, conflicting evidence suggested that LTβR induces apoptosis. To investigate the functional role of LTβR in tumors, we performed LTβR knockdown in cancer cells. We found that LTβR knockdown induced senescence phenomena such as reduced cell number; increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk stratification of pT1b urothelial carcinoma based on spatial relationships between invasive tumour and muscularis propria on TURB specimens for predicting muscle-invasive urothelial carcinoma in radical cystectomy: A new proposal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This new risk stratification method presents promise in guiding early aggressive treatment decisions, though larger prospective studies are essential for further validation and clinical integration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pomalidomide, Cyclophosphamide, and Dexamethasone for Relapsed/Refractory Multiple Myeloma: A Single-Center Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The addition of cyclophosphamide to Pd in moderately to heavily pretreated RRMM patients showed promising efficacy, supporting PCd as a potential therapeutic option in real-world clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between traumatic brain injury and the prevalence of Alzheimer's disease dementia and behavioral and psychological symptoms of dementia: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our results underscore the importance of traumatic brain injury prevention in patients with mild cognitive impairment for mitigating the progression and neuropsychiatric complications of Alzheimer's disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of estimated glucose disposal rate in predicting myosteatosis: Insights from abdominal CT analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated a significant association between decreased eGDR levels and increased myosteatosis, as defined by sex-specific cutoffs of CT-based myosteatosis indices.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nursing Leadership in Times of Doctor's Strike: Korea's Path to Research Excellence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use of Double Cages for Biportal Endoscopic Transforaminal Lumbar Interbody Fusion: A Comparison of 3-Dimensional-Printed Titanium and Polyetheretherketone Cages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both double 3D-printed titanium and PEEK cages demonstrated high fusion rates with no significant differences in overall success. However, double 3D-printed titanium cages showed better early fusion grades and comparable subsidence to that of PEEK cages. Although long-term follow-up is necessary to ascertain efficacy, these findings suggest that 3D-printed titanium cages offer advantages in early fusion quality in BETLIF. Further research is needed to optimize cage arrangement, cage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40883011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences of Individuals With Visual Impairments in Adapted and Nonadapted Group Exercise Programs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Physical activity is vital for health, yet individuals with visual impairments face barriers in conventional fitness settings. This study aimed to understand the perceptions and lived experiences of exercisers with visual impairments (EVI) who participated in an adapted group exercise program (AGEP) and to identify the perceived barriers and facilitators to exercise participation among EVI in both AGEP and non-AGEP settings. Thematic analysis of focus-group interviews with nine EVI identified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Personalized Antibiotic Treatment for Methicillin-Resistant Staphylococcus aureus Bloodstream Infections in ICU Patients Using a Deep Learning-Based Causal Inference Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights linezolid and daptomycin treatment in select subgroups, while a deep learning-based model enables personalized antibiotic recommendations for ICU treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Same-day versus Multiday Planning/Treatment Radioembolization with Yttrium-90 Resin Microspheres in Patients with Liver Cancer ≥ 5 cm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Same-day planning/treatment radioembolization with resin microspheres is as effective and safe as multiday radioembolization for large liver tumors ≥ 5 cm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Layered Double Hydroxides and Layered Double Oxides: Multifunctional Catalysts for the Detection, Degradation, and Transformation of Phenolic Compounds in Environmental Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phenolic compounds are persistent pollutants in industrial effluents, necessitating integrated strategies for their detection, degradation, and transformation. Layered double hydroxides (LDHs) and their calcined derivatives, layered double oxides (LDOs), are promising multifunctional catalysts for addressing these challenges. LDHs/LDOs can be engineered and modified to enhance surface adsorption and facilitate efficient electron transfer. Sensors based on LDHs/LDOs, particularly those employing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of the perfluorooctane sulfonamide on glucose and lipid metabolism in 3T3-L1 adipocytes and zebrafish larvae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perfluorooctane sulfonamide (PFOSA) is an indirect source of perfluorooctane sulfonic acid (PFOS) in the environment as a precursor; however, toxicological study of PFOSA is limited. This study aimed to investigate the effects of PFOSA on glucose and lipid metabolism in 3T3-L1 adipocytes and in zebrafish larvae. 3T3-L1 adipocytes were treated with PFOSA, PFOS, and rosiglitazone (RSG) for 48 h, and assessed for cell viability, adipogenesis, glucose uptake, and regarding molecular mechanisms....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between long-term exposure to a mixture of ambient air pollutants and the incidences of bladder and kidney cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Long-term exposure to mixtures of air pollutants was significantly associated with increased risks of BC and KC, with consistent positive contributions identified for PM(10), PM(2.5), and SO(2). These findings highlight specific pollutants of concern and emphasize the need for targeted public health strategies to mitigate air pollution exposure and potentially reduce urinary cancer incidence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40882831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250830152235&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>