<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:22:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Interpersonal Needs and Attitudes Toward Suicide on Suicide Risk in Middle-Aged Korean Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Urban residence, perceived poor mental health, and maladaptive attitudes toward suicide are key determinants of suicidal risk among middle-aged Korean women. Findings emphasize the need for a comprehensive suicide risk assessment addressing psychological distress and sociocultural perceptions to enhance suicide prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetic Skyrmion Neurons with Homeostasis for Spiking Neural Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in spiking neural networks (SNNs) have drawn inspiration from the human brain's distinctive capabilities, leading to significant impacts on various aspects of our lives and scientific endeavors. The development of hardware-based Spiking Neural Networks (H-SNNs) is a crucial aspect of the progress in neuromorphic computing, particularly in the context of on-chip implementations. H-SNNs involve the hardware realization of specific functionalities used in SNN algorithms, such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning-Guided Discovery of Sterically Protected High Triplet Exciplex Hosts for Ultra-Bright Green OLEDs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) has been widely used to accelerate the discovery of organic light-emitting diode (OLED) materials, but its application to improving device-level performance has been limited. Here, we develop an ML workflow that explicitly incorporates exciplex-specific design criteria, including exciplex-considered high triplet energy criteria, deep lowest-unoccupied molecular orbital (LUMO) alignment, high bond dissociation energy (BDE), and proper reorganization energy, as factors that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of Microtubule Radial Structure by Competition between Tau and Paclitaxel: Binding and Synchrotron X-ray Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microtubules (MTs) are a major component of the eukaryotic cytoskeleton. MT architecture is highly regulated by microtubule-associated proteins (MAPs) such as Tau as well as a number of MT-targeted chemotherapeutic agents such as paclitaxel (PTX). In this study, we examined the ability of each of the six different alternatively spliced isoforms of human wild-type (WT) Tau (4R2N, 4R1N, 4R0N, 3R2N, 3R1N and 3R0N) and PTX to bind to MTs as well as their effects upon MT structure. MTs were assembled...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the Reliability of Calibration Constants in Heat Flux Meters Using an ISO 5660-1 Cone Heater]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates the reliability of calibration constants for heat flux meters (HFMs) using a secondary standard under controlled thermal conditions provided by an ISO 5660-1 cone heater. Six HFMs (three new and three previously used) were examined by comparing manufacturer-provided (MFG) and secondary-standard-based (SEC) calibration constants. The bias between the MFG and SEC calibration constants varied substantially depending on the manufacturer, calibration method, service history, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Therapeutic Effect of a Biodegradable Long-Acting Intravitreal Implant Containing CGK012 on Neovascular Age-Related Macular Degeneration by Promoting β-Catenin Degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Neovascular age-related macular degeneration (nAMD) poses a serious threat to the eyesight of older adults, representing a leading cause of irreversible vision loss. Anti-vascular endothelial growth factor (anti-VEGF) treatments are effective but require repeated intraocular injections and show poor responses in some patients. CGK012 is a novel derivative of decursin that inhibits the Wnt/β-catenin pathway. This study aimed to elucidate the mode of action of CGK012 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Molecular Detection of Orthohantaviruses (<em>Orthohantavirus hantanense</em> and <em>O. jejuense</em>) in Trombiculid Mites from Wild Rodents in the Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orthohantaviruses are zoonotic pathogens that cause severe diseases in humans primarily through inhalation of aerosols from rodent excreta. Recent studies suggest that ectoparasites may be potential vectors for Orthohantaviruses. This study aimed to obtain molecular evidence of Orthohantavirus in trombiculid mites collected from wild rodents. In April 2025, 4963 trombiculid mites were collected from 128 wild rodents captured in 17 regions of the Republic of Korea (ROK). Among them, 1660 mites...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and Challenges in Vaccination and Therapeutic Strategies Against Japanese Encephalitis Virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Japanese encephalitis virus (JEV) remains a major cause of viral encephalitis in Asia, and recent epidemiological shifts driven by the predominance of genotype I and the re-emergence of genotype V have renewed concerns regarding control efforts. Licensed vaccines have a reduced incidence of more than 90% in several endemic regions; however, evidence of reduced cross-neutralization against heterologous genotypes indicates that vaccines derived from genotype III strains may not fully match the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic Landscape and Interaction Potential of SGLT2 Inhibitors: Bridging In Vitro Findings and Clinical Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sodium-glucose cotransporter 2 (SGLT2) inhibitors are widely used in type 2 diabetes and cardiometabolic diseases, and their pharmacokinetic characteristics generally confer a low risk of clinically relevant drug-drug interactions (DDIs). Most clinical studies demonstrate that these agents can be co-administered safely with commonly prescribed medications without dose adjustment, although strong enzyme inducers such as rifampin can reduce systemic exposure, and pharmacodynamic interactions may...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic Evaluation of GB-5001, a Long-Acting Injectable Formulation of Donepezil, in Healthy Korean Participants: Population Pharmacokinetics with Phase 1 Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Oral donepezil, an acetylcholinesterase (AChE) inhibitor for Alzheimer's disease, faces adherence challenges. Long-acting injectable (LAI) formulations like GB-5001 aim to enhance adherence by reducing dosing frequency. This Phase 1, open-label, active-controlled, dose-escalation study evaluated the safety, tolerability, pharmacokinetics (PK), and pharmacodynamics (PD) of GB-5001 in healthy male adults. Methods: Participants were assigned to cohorts receiving GB-5001A or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Packed-Type Reconfigurable Air Filtration System for Removal of Particulate Matter and HCHO]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A flexible and packed-type air filter ball (AFB) system was developed for the efficient removal of particulate matter (PM) and formaldehyde (HCHO). The Mg/Si-embedded AFB (Mg/Si-AFB) was synthesized through sequential physical etching of a sponge, oxidation of glass fiber, and subsequent formation of Mg-Si components. The resulting Mg/Si-AFB exhibited a highly porous and roughened architecture with enhanced surface reactivity. A disk-type filtration device loaded with Mg/Si-AFBs demonstrated a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRISPR/Cas9-Targeted Gene Editing of Allergenic Profilin-Encoding <em>Lyc e1</em> in Tomato Fruit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tomato (Solanum lycopersicum L.), one of the most widely consumed horticultural crops worldwide, is also a notable source of food allergens, with a higher prevalence of allergic reactions in pollen-sensitized patients. Profilin, a small actin-binding protein, is a major allergen in tomato fruits encoded by two homologous genes, Lyc e1.01 and Lyc e1.02. Although various strategies have been proposed to reduce allergenicity in foods, no prior study has successfully achieved the complete...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of High-Power Laser Cleaning on Oxide Layer Formation on 304L Stainless Steel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a kW-level high-power Nd:YAG nanosecond laser was adopted to eliminate a corrosion layer on a 304L stainless steel (SS304L) surface. Four different laser cleaning (LC) processes with various hatch distances and loop counts were adopted. The energy-dispersive X-ray spectroscopy (EDX) analysis revealed that the corrosion layer was successfully eliminated via the LC process. However, the electron probe X-ray microanalysis (EPMA) analysis confirmed that a Cr-based oxide layer with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving the Cycling Stability of Next-Generation Si Anode Batteries Using Polymer Coatings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silicon is widely recognized as a next-generation anode owing to its exceptional theoretical capacity, yet its practical deployment in lithium-ion batteries is constrained by severe volume expansion, particle fracture, loss of electrical percolation, and solid electrolyte interphase layer instability. Polymer-based strategies have emerged as accessible solutions to engineer extensive volume changes and interfacial compatibility, while preserving pathways for charge transport. Viscoelastic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nano Carbon-Based Hybrid Strategies for Mitigating Silicon Anode Expansion in Lithium-Ion Batteries: A Comprehensive Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silicon is considered one of the most promising anode materials for lithium-ion batteries because of its high theoretical capacity and low lithiation potential. However, its practical application is limited by significant volume expansion, unstable solid-electrolyte interphase formation, and poor intrinsic conductivity. This review summarizes recent advances in hybrid strategies using multi-walled carbon nanotubes (MWCNTs), single-walled carbon nanotubes (SWCNTs), graphene, carbon nanofibers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Accuracy of Non-Contrast CT for Acute Appendicitis in the Emergency Department: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Contrast-enhanced computed tomography (CT) is widely regarded as the gold standard for diagnosing acute appendicitis. However, the use of contrast agents may be contraindicated in patients with renal impairment or a history of allergic reactions. Non-contrast CT (NCCT) offers a potential alternative, but its diagnostic performance has been variably reported across studies. This systematic review and meta-analysis aimed to evaluate the pooled diagnostic accuracy of NCCT...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison Between Anterior and Posterior Decompression for Degenerative Cervical Myelopathy With Multilevel Foraminal Stenosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Anterior and posterior decompressive surgeries are reliable for the surgical treatment of DCM with multilevel foraminal stenosis and showed similar outcomes for both myelopathy and upper extremity radicular symptoms. The major etiology compromising the clinical outcome was a higher incidence of CASP in the anterior group and persistent or recurrent upper extremity radicular symptoms in the posterior group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polynucleotide (DOT-PN) for Accelerated Healing of Lip Necrosis After Filler-Induced Vascular Compromise]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Further controlled studies are warranted to define optimal PN dosing intervals, timing of administration, and comparative effectiveness versus other adjunctive treatments for filler-induced ischemic complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus from the Asian conference on tumor ablation working group on image-guided thermal ablation for lung tumor: 10 key questions and answers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Percutaneous image-guided thermal ablation (IGTA) is increasingly utilized for the management of primary and metastatic lung tumors. Several academic societies across various countries have issued clinical practice guidelines, opinion statements, and recommendations for IGTA in the treatment of lung tumors. However, unresolved conceptual and practical challenges persist, underscoring the need for a more comprehensive consensus on the safe and effective application of IGTA, particularly in Asian...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative CT Measurements of Interstitial Lung Disease: Same-Day Variability Between Two Vendors-A Prospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Clinical application of quantitative CT (QCT) measurements of interstitial lung disease (ILD) for longitudinal monitoring of disease progression requires understanding of how such measurements vary across vendors. Objective: To evaluate same-day variability between vendors for QCT measurements of fibrosis extent in patients with ILD. Methods: This prospective study recruited participants with diagnosed ILD from January 2023 to August 2024. Participants underwent two serial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basal EMG Amplitude in REM and NREM Sleep as a Predictor of Disease Progression in Isolated REM Sleep Behavior Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Elevated basal EMG amplitude during both REM and NREM sleep in iRBD patients shows potential as a prognostic marker, indicating muscle tone dysregulation beyond REM atonia loss and underscoring the need to consider broader sleep stages in iRBD evaluation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soft Tissue Substitutes: Current Biomaterials and Indications at Teeth and Implant Sites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soft tissue augmentation around teeth and dental implants is a central aspect of periodontal and peri-implant plastic surgery. Autogenous soft tissue grafts are generally regarded as the gold standard for increasing keratinized mucosa, mucosal thickness, and soft tissue height, supported by extensive long-term evidence. However, limitations such as restricted tissue availability, increased surgical time, and donor-site morbidity have encouraged the development of soft tissue graft substitutes,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of long working hours with the use of combustible cigarettes, electronic cigarettes, and heated tobacco products among young adults: a population-based study of South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Long working hours is linked to the use of various forms of tobacco products among young adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploiting Mg-Interdiffusion-Driven Work-Function Reduction in Ti/Mg/Ti Multilayers to Achieve Low-Resistivity Ohmic Contacts to (001) β-Ga<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Low-resistivity Ohmic contact formation in β-gallium oxide (β-Ga(2)O(3)) is crucial for high-efficiency power electronics and deep-ultraviolet (DUV) optoelectronic devices. In this study, we successfully developed a Ti/Mg/Ti multilayered metal stack (20 nm/50 nm/20 nm) as an Ohmic contact to (001) β-Ga(2)O(3). The Mg interlayer, with its low work function relative to Ti and the electron affinity of β-Ga(2)O(3), effectively reduces the Schottky barrier, enabling low contact resistivity. The Ti...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applying the technology acceptance model to predict digital therapeutics use in South Korea: The roles of digital literacy, online information trust, and privacy concern]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings highlight the complex interplay among digital literacy, trust, and privacy in influencing DTx adoption. Emphasis on user-centered design, strong privacy protection, and digital literacy education will be essential for fostering broader acceptance of digital therapeutics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A deep learning-based early prediction framework for weight management using real-world lifelog data: GRU-ODE-Bayes model development and validation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed model predicted early outcomes in weight management and might contribute to developing effective intervention methods for participants at risk of failure and reducing the burden of frequent self-reporting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting the quality of cookies with oleogel as a shortening substitute using hyperspectral imaging and artificial intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A total of 36 oleogels, made from various waxes and vegetable oils, were utilized as shortening substitutes in cookies, and machine learning incorporating three boosting models (AdaBoost, GBM, and XGBoost) was applied to predict their effects on the quality attributes of the cookies. Carnauba wax oleogels exhibited the highest melting temperature and contributed to stronger cookie texture, while beeswax oleogels produced cookies with greater spreadability and lower hardness. Similar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Saccharomyces cerevisiae</em>-Fermented Salmon Placental Protein Inhibits Muscle Loss in a Mouse Model of Sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Addressing sarcopenia and frailty in aging populations is crucial for improving quality of life and reducing healthcare dependence among these patients. Although no specific drugs have been approved for treating sarcopenia, protein supplements rich in branched-chain amino acid (BCAA) have been reported to increase muscle mass and function in elderly individuals. Fermentation of salmon placenta protein is an effective approach to improve BCAA content compared to previous sarcopenia-related...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the safety and efficacy of a donepezil depot injection in dogs with canine cognitive dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canine cognitive dysfunction (CCD) is an age-related neurodegenerative disorder for which effective treatments remain limited, and objective diagnostic and therapeutic assessment tools using biomarkers or neuroimaging are still lacking compared with human Alzheimer's disease. This study evaluated the safety and efficacy of a long-acting donepezil depot injection in dogs with CCD, using behavioral scores and serum neurofilament light chain (NfL) as primary outcomes, with baseline MRI for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Athlete data sovereignty: addressing the legal and policy gaps in sports technology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative tadalafil for recovery of continence and voiding function after radical prostatectomy for prostate cancer: a single-center experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Postoperative tadalafil is associated with improved recovery of erectile and voiding function, as well as higher continence rates, without compromising oncologic outcomes. These findings support its consideration as part of routine postoperative management in selected RP patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<sup>18</sup>F-florastamin positron emission tomography/computed tomography in men with clinical suspicion of prostate cancer: A phase I prospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ^(18)F-Florastamin is a promising PET tracer that correctly identifies foci of cancer within the prostate with a higher accuracy than conventional imaging (MRI), and may be helpful in stratifying patients with low to intermediate PSA levels to better assess the need for an invasive biopsy. Our cohort study suggests triage with ^(18)F-Florastamin PET/CT has the potential to reduce unnecessary biopsies in 9/20 (45%) patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The dose-volume histogram-based evaluation of predictors for gross hematuria after postprostatectomy radiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results suggest that gross hematuria after PPRT occurs frequently, especially among patients on anticoagulant/antiplatelet therapy and those with an absolute bladder V40 Gy ≥median and relative bladder V65 Gy ≥median during PPRT. Although most cases of gross hematuria were self-resolved, up to 16.1% required invasive surgical intervention. Limiting PPRT dose exposure to the bladder may also reduce the incidence of gross hematuria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oncologic outcomes of salvage radiotherapy and lymphadenectomy for positron emission tomography-positive lymph nodes in biochemical recurrence: A systematic review to inform treatment decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite salvage LND or RT, about half of BCR patients with PET-positive nodal recurrence showed disease progression, suggesting limited effectiveness of focal therapies alone. RT appeared to provide better short-term disease control than LND, highlighting the importance of treatment selection. The study underscores the necessity for further investigation into optimal salvage management strategies for BCR using PET in prospective clinical studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical implication of peri-seminal vesicle soft-tissue invasion in patients with pT3b prostate cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In pT3b patients, peri-SV soft-tissue invasion and lymph node metastasis are common. These findings suggest that a more radical surgical approach is warranted in patients with suspected SVI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of 7-tesla <em>ex vivo</em> and conventional 3-tesla magnetic resonance imaging for prostate cancer staging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The 7T ex vivo MRI enhances the diagnostic accuracy, clarity, and reproducibility of EPE assessment and reduces tumor size underestimation compared to 3T MRI, supporting its potential role in optimizing preoperative prostate cancer staging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of pentosan polysulfate therapy in patients with interstitial cystitis for relief of lower urinary tract symptoms: 15-year single center experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PPS provides clinical benefits in urinary symptoms voiding symptoms and QoL over time, arriving plateau within 3 months. Such benefits based on the IPSS tend to be more evident in younger patients, suggesting that PPS mostly benefits early treatment if suspected for IC/BPS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence-driven digital pathology in urological cancers: current trends and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) in digital pathology has gained attention owing to its potential in urological cancer diagnosis and management. This review highlights AI's applications and challenges in three major urological cancers. Prostate cancer studies have demonstrated reliable diagnostic performance and promising prognosis prediction. Renal cancer study shows potential but faces challenges in generalizability and prognosis. Bladder cancer studies are limited by the lack of large-scale...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-dependent Increase in Cortisol after 1-mg Overnight Dexamethasone Suppression Test in Adrenal Incidentalomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cortisol levels after 1-mg ODST increased over time, suggesting an age-related effect and highlighting the need for age-tailored diagnostic and management strategies for MACS in older patients with AI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Job Crafting as the Missing Link: Understanding Its Role in Nurses' Work Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nurses with higher positive psychological capital and those working in a positive work environment are more likely to be involved in job crafting, which in turn enhances their work engagement. These findings suggest that both individual and organizational strategies are essential in promoting individual nurses' job crafting and work engagement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of Venoarterial Extracorporeal Membrane Oxygenation as a Procedural Support Tool in Cardiovascular Instability: A Case Series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The use of venoarterial extracorporeal membrane oxygenation (VA-ECMO) is increasing worldwide. Patients with cardiogenic shock were the first indication for VA-ECMO according to the Extracorporeal Life Support Organization (ELSO) guidelines. However, recent studies have shown that VA-ECMO is not beneficial in patients with cardiogenic shock. This report describes the case of three patients who presented with infarct-related cardiac arrest without cardiogenic shock and received VA-ECMO to support...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epitope-level analysis of cross-reactive human HLA antibodies against genetically modified swine leukocyte antigens in xenotransplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cross-reactive anti-SLA antibodies are common in highly sensitized human sera, driven by antibody specificity and epitope conservation. Despite glycan xenoantigen deletion, sensitized sera maintain IgG-mediated cross-reactivity and cytotoxicity against gene-edited pig cells. These findings highlight the need for detailed epitope-level analysis to refine immunologic risk assessment and recipient selection to reduce antibody-mediated rejection in clinical xenotransplantation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residue dynamics and metabolic pathways of sulfoxaflor in Cirsium japonicum var. maackii and Olea europaea L]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings contribute to our understanding of the residue and metabolic characteristics of sulfoxaflor and provide fundamental data for establishing safe pesticide use guidelines and MRLs for thistle and olive cultivation. © 2025 Society of Chemical Industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Super-Resolution Tracking of mtDNA Remodeling and Inflammatory Release with a Selective Fluorescent Probe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondrial DNA (mtDNA) is vital for mitochondrial function and cellular homeostasis, with its spatiotemporal dynamics are tightly linked to development, metabolism, and disease progression. However, super-resolution tracking of mtDNA in live cells remains limited by lack of selective, photostable small-molecule probes. Here, we present mtNARed, a rationally engineered, wash-free fluorescent probe featuring a large Stokes-shift, and high photostability that enables super-resolution tracking of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Autologous Blood-Derived Extracellular Vesicles on Skin Regeneration and Anti-Aging: A Clinical Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates the clinical efficacy and safety of autologous blood-derived EVs in facial rejuvenation, supporting their potential as a non-invasive cosmetic treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Challenges and Clinical Implications of Microsatellite Instability/Mismatch Repair Deficiency in Solid Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mismatch repair (MMR) system plays a crucial role in correcting replication errors; when the MMR system is deficient (dMMR), replication errors (particularly within microsatellites) accumulate throughout the genome, leading to microsatellite instability (MSI). The key MMR genes include MLH1, MSH2, MSH6, and PMS2. Germline mutations in these genes are associated with Lynch syndrome, whereas in sporadic solid tumors, dMMR is often caused by hypermethylation of the MLH1 promoter. As the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Features and Outcomes of Endoscopic Resection of Superficial Nonampullary Duodenal Tumors in South Korea: A 15-Year Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ER is effective and safe for SNADETs, achieving high curative resection rates, low recurrence, and acceptable complication risks. Selection of resection method should be individualized, with cold EMR and underwater EMR offering safe and efficient alternatives for the treatment of smaller lesions, while ESD may be reserved for the treatment of larger lesions or complex cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased Heart Failure Risk with Gastric Cancer Progression: A Nationwide Population-Based Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with gastric cancer, the risk of heart failure requiring hospitalization increased with worsening cancer stage. Even in young patients and those without metabolic risk factors, close monitoring for heart failure development following cancer treatment is essential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Dual Role of A20 (TNFAIP3) in Viral Infection: A Context-Dependent Regulator of Immunity and Pathogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A20 (TNFAIP3) is a ubiquitin-editing enzyme that plays a central role in the regulation of inflammation and cell death, primarily through modulation of NF-κB signaling. In the context of viral infection, A20 exhibits a dual nature: it can both suppress antiviral immune responses to facilitate viral replication and act as a host-protective factor to prevent immunopathology. This review synthesizes current findings on the context-dependent roles of A20, focusing on its capacity to switch between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful Surgical Excision of a Chronic Abscess in a Hawksbill Turtle (<em>Eretmochelys imbricata</em>): A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In sea turtles, soft tissue abscesses typically present with a solid, caseous consistency and respond poorly to pharmacological treatment. A hawksbill turtle (Eretmochelys imbricata) exhibited a chronic subcutaneous mass near the cloacal region that had persisted for three years. Histopathological examination confirmed the existence of an abscess composed of concentric necrotic layers and chronic inflammatory cell infiltration, with no detectable pathogens. The lesion was surgically excised...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr Virus Promotes Gastric Cancer Progression by Modulating m6A-Dependent YTHDF1-TSC22D1 Axis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr virus (EBV) infection is closely associated with gastric cancer, yet its role in m6A-dependent gene regulation remains poorly understood. In this study, we investigated how EBV infection alters the m6A methylation pattern in gastric cancer cells and examined its impact on TSC22D1 mRNA stability through interaction with the m6A reader protein YTHDF1. m6A RNA immunoprecipitation sequencing (MeRIP-seq) revealed a significant reduction in m6A methylation of TSC22D1 in EBV-infected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergence of Multidrug-Resistant and Biofilm-Producing <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em> from Raw Poultry in Algeria: Implications for Public Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Staphylococcus aureus is a common foodborne pathogen, posing significant concern due to the emergence of its multidrug-resistant (MDR) strains. The aim of this study was to assess the antibiotic resistance profiles in S. aureus isolated from raw poultry, the associated resistance genes, and their ability to form biofilms. S. aureus was isolated and identified using conventional microbiological methods. Antimicrobial susceptibility profiles were assessed using the disk diffusion method, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An <em>rpoB</em> Sequence Type Network as a Framework for the Evolutionary Investigation of <em>Clostridium perfringens</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clostridium perfringens is an opportunistic Gram-positive bacterium that causes necrotic enteritis and other severe infections in animals, as well as food poisoning in humans. In this study, we introduce a framework consisting of rpoB sequence typing (RSTing) and network analysis to investigate the evolutionary trajectories of C. perfringens. By analyzing 319 rpoB sequences-300 from public databases and 19 newly sequenced isolates from chicken and cattle sources-we identified 84 rpoB sequence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr Virus Silences GSDME and Pyroptosis in Gastric Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr virus (EBV)-associated gastric carcinoma (EBVaGC) represents a distinct molecular subtype characterized by extensive DNA methylation and altered cell death signaling. This study investigated the regulation and function of gasdermin E (GSDME), a key mediator of pyroptosis, in EBVaGC. Transcriptomic analysis of The Cancer Genome Atlas (TCGA) data revealed that GSDME expression was selectively suppressed in EBV-positive gastric cancer, while other gasdermin family members were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub>: An Oxide Semiconductor for Thin-Film Transistors, a Short Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the discovery of amorphous oxide semiconductors, a new era of electronics opened. Indium gallium zinc oxide (IGZO) overcame the problems of amorphous and poly-silicon by reaching mobilities of ~10 cm²/Vs and demonstrating thin-film transistors (TFTs) are easy to manufacture on transparent and flexible substrates. However, mobilities over 30 cm²/Vs have been difficult to reach and other materials have been introduced. Recently, polycrystalline In(2)O(3) has demonstrated breakthroughs in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Co-Reactant Engineering for Au Nanocluster Electrochemiluminescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Co-reactants are essential in co-reactant-based electrochemiluminescence (ECL) systems because they generate reactive intermediates that can oxidize or reduce ECL luminophores, thereby driving ECL emission. In the context of ECL, gold nanoclusters (Au NCs) have emerged as innovative luminophores, owing to their tunable electronic structures and excellent biocompatibility. However, their efficiency in ECL applications is often compromised by challenges such as limited excited-state generation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive Evaluation of a Passive Upper-Limb Exoskeleton in Agricultural Tasks: Integrating Physiological, Postural, and Cognitive Measures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the effects of a passive upper-limb exoskeleton in agricultural work using a repeated-measures design with 24 adult males across three exoskeleton conditions (No Exo, Prototype, and Airframe), three work directions (left, front, and right), and two work distances (near and far). Outcomes included muscle activity, center of pressure travel, task completion time, perceived exertion, body part discomfort, and usability. Airframe use significantly reduced shoulder and upper-arm...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does Coxsackievirus B3 Require Autophagosome Formation for Replication? Evidence for an Autophagosome-Independent Mechanism: Insights into Its Limited Potential as a Therapeutic Target]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Coxsackievirus B3 (CVB3), a neurotropic enterovirus, is a major causative agent of viral encephalitis and myocarditis, yet no protective vaccine or effective antiviral therapy is currently available. Autophagy plays a dual role in viral infections, acting as both an antiviral defense and a process that can be exploited by certain viruses. Although CVB3 has been proposed to utilize autophagosomes as replication platforms, the underlying mechanisms remain controversial....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Herbal Inhalation Therapy for Allergic Rhinitis: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Allergic rhinitis (AR) is a common immunological disorder characterized by nasal symptoms and impaired quality of life. Despite advances in pharmacotherapy, symptom control often remains inadequate. Herbal medicine atomized inhalation (HMAI), a modern adaptation of traditional East Asian fumigation, may offer an effective adjunct or alternative therapy. This systematic review and meta-analysis evaluated the clinical efficacy and safety of HMAI, emphasizing its role as a localized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rosuvastatin Versus Atorvastatin for Cardiovascular Disease Risk in Patients with Type 2 Diabetes: A Korean Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Rosuvastatin and atorvastatin are indicated for cardiovascular protection in patients with type 2 diabetes (T2D) but may differ in clinical effectiveness and safety. This study compared real-world cardiovascular and safety outcomes associated with rosuvastatin versus atorvastatin in patients with T2D, with an emphasis on older adults. Methods: This retrospective cohort study used electronic health records from 10 Korean hospitals standardized to the Common Data Model. Adults (≥18...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Potential of <em>Gynostemma pentaphyllum</em> (Thunb.) Makino Against COVID-19 Identified Through Network Pharmacology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The ongoing challenges posed by COVID-19 have highlighted the need for multi-target therapeutic strategies addressing both acute immune responses and systemic complications. Gynostemma pentaphyllum (Thunb.) Makino, a traditional herbal medicine rich in flavonoids and saponins, exhibits diverse pharmacological activities, including immunomodulatory and cardiovascular effects. In this study, we investigated the potential of G. pentaphyllum as a complementary treatment for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coixol and Sinigrin from <em>Coix lacryma-jobi</em> L. and <em>Raphanus sativus</em> L. Promote Fat Browning in 3T3-L1 Adipocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Obesity, a metabolic disorder resulting from an energy imbalance, often leads to excess fat and related diseases. Browning of white adipose tissue, which increases energy expenditure, is a promising anti-obesity strategy. Herbal medicines are considered safer than conventional drugs, but their fat browning mechanisms remain unclear. Therefore, this study aims to examine the effects of Coix lacryma-jobi L. and Raphanus sativus L., alongside their active compounds, coixol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing PROTAC Discovery Through Artificial Intelligence: Opportunities, Challenges, and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proteolysis Targeting Chimeras (PROTACs) represent a transformative modality in drug discovery, enabling the selective degradation of disease-relevant proteins through the ubiquitin proteasome system. Despite their therapeutic promise, the rational design of PROTACs remains a complex and resource-intensive process, involving multiple parameters such as target and ligase compatibility, ternary complex formation, linker optimization, and degradation efficiency. Recent advances in artificial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptome-Guided Drug Repurposing Identifies Homoharringtonine (HHT) as a Candidate for Radiation-Induced Pulmonary Fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Radiation-induced pulmonary fibrosis (RPF) remains a major burden of successful lung cancer radiotherapy. Clinically validated drugs targeting RPF remains scarce. Methods: We employed a transcriptome-based drug repurposing approach using REMEDY, a computational platform built on the Library of Integrated Network-Based Cellular Signatures (LINCS). Differentially expressed genes (DEGs) derived from radiation-induced lung injury (RILI) models were used as a query to identify compounds...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategic Combinations of Antibody-Drug Conjugates from 2023 to 2025: From Dual Therapies to Innovative ADC-Based Regimens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs) are a potent class of targeted cancer therapies that combine the specificity of monoclonal antibodies with the cytotoxic potency of chemotherapeutic agents. By targeting tumor cells with minimal impact on healthy tissues, ADCs achieve a favorable balance between efficacy and systemic toxicity. This therapeutic modality has demonstrated significant clinical success, as evidenced by the FDA approval of 15 ADCs by 2025, with one later withdrawn due to safety...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Senotherapeutic Potential of Araliadiol in Senescent Human Dermal Fibroblasts: An In Vitro Study Using Three Senescence Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: With the rapid aging of the global population, the interest in therapies for age-related diseases has increased substantially. The skin is particularly important, as aging-related changes are visible and negatively impact quality of life. Therefore, the identification of senotherapeutic candidates that are effective against skin aging is of considerable importance. Given the cost and reproducibility limitations of existing senescence models, this study established three...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valorization of Potato Peel Waste into Bioactive Compounds and Sustainable Bioplastics Production Through a Novel Biorefinery Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study deals with the successful exploitation of easily available and renewable potato peel waste (PPW) as an excellent feedstock in the production of PHA using Ralstonia eutropha. The process entailed the extraction of bioactive components from PPW by use of solvent-based procedures and screening of their antioxidant and antidiabetic activity. The extracted PPW biomass was subject to acid hydrolysis using different concentrations of sulfuric acid for hydrolysis and solubilization of sugar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical Behavior of Carbon-Fiber-Reinforced Polymer Composites (Towpreg) Under Various Temperature Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the hydrogen economy rapidly expands, carbon-fiber-reinforced polymer composites (Towpreg) have become key materials for next-generation hydrogen pressure vessels, offering superior processability, reproducibility, and storage stability compared to conventional wet-winding composites. Since hydrogen storage vessels are evaluated at three representative service temperatures (-40, 25, and 85 °C), Towpreg materials must maintain consistent mechanical performance across this range to meet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fish Consumption and the Risk of Depression: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis of Observational Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This systematic review and meta-analysis of observational studies aimed to assess the association between fish consumption and the risk of general and pregnancy-related depression, with implications for public health promotion. Methods: We retrieved 5074 articles from PubMed and Embase through November 2023 and included 35 observational studies in the analysis. We synthesized effect estimates as relative risks (RRs) with corresponding 95% confidence intervals (CIs) using a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioconversion-Based Postbiotics Enhance Muscle Strength and Modulate Gut Microbiota in Healthy Individuals: A Randomized, Double-Blind, Placebo-Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: KP supplementation produced a modest within-group improvement in grip strength, potentially through gut-muscle axis modulation involving irisin and anti-inflammation pathways. These preliminary findings suggest that kefir-derived postbiotics may have potential relevance for muscle health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iodine Intake and Risk of Mortality: Evidence from a Nationally Representative Korean Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Iodine intake influences thyroid-related and metabolic diseases that have important public health implications. However, longitudinal evidence of the association between iodine intake and mortality remains scarce and limited to Western populations. Given the markedly high iodine intake among Asians and possible ethnic or regional differences in iodine sensitivity, population-based data from Asian cohorts are needed. Methods: We analyzed 5497 adults from the Korean National...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Copper Oxide Nanoparticles on Adventitious Shoot Regeneration, Axillary Shoot Multiplication, Rooting, and Bioactive Compounds in <em>Ajuga multiflora</em> Bunge]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study investigated the effects of copper oxide nanoparticles (CuO NPs) at concentrations of 0, 5, 10, 20, and 40 mg/L on micropropagation and the accumulation of lipophilic metabolites in Ajuga multiflora, a medicinally valuable ornamental species. The highest number of adventitious shoots (29.4 shoots per explant) was obtained on the shoot induction medium with 5 mg/L CuO NPs. Shoot production gradually decreased at higher CuO NPs concentrations, falling to just 1.1 shoots per...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping Endangered Plant Distributions, Species Richness, and Climate Refugia Under SSP Climate Scenarios in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change significantly threatens the survival and distribution of endangered plants. This study quantified current and future patterns of habitat suitability and species richness for legally protected vascular plants in South Korea under two SSP climate scenarios. We modeled the distributions of 69 species designated as Class I or Class II endangered wild plants and evaluated in the Korean National Red List using IUCN criteria. Random Forest (RF) species distribution models were fitted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Channel-Free Micro-Well-Template-Assisted Magnetic Particle Trapping for Efficient Single-Particle Isolation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a channel-free, micro-well-template-assisted magnetic particle trapping method for efficient single-particle isolation without the need for microfluidic channels. Dual-surface silicon micro-well arrays were fabricated using photolithography, PE-CVD, and DRIE processes, featuring hydrophilic well interiors and hydrophobic outer surfaces to enhance trapping performance. The proposed method combines magnet-assisted sedimentation with rotational sweeping of a glass slide placed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Metal-Enhanced Fluorescence Nanorods on Micro Post Arrays for Portable Detection of Human Semen Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rapid and reliable on-site identification of body fluids is essential in forensic and field diagnostic applications. Commercial kits provide only single results and often suffer from cross-reactivity, while conventional microarrays offer multiplex capability but lack sufficient fluorescence intensity for field-deployable systems. In this study, we present a highly sensitive nanorods on micro post array (NMPA) substrate and a smartphone-based portable detection system. The NMPA substrate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simple Process for Flexible Light-Extracting QD Film and White OLED]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum dots (QDs) have tremendous potential for next-generation displays due to their high color purity, photoluminescence efficiency, and power efficiency. In this work, we present a simple and cost-effective method for fabricating flexible single- and multiple-layer films, and they can be detached and attached to the outside of OLEDs as a light-scattering and color-conversion layer. Light extraction efficiency is enhanced by forming low-density structures by using the reactive ion etching...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Process Optimization for Metal-Contact Etching in 3D Integration Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates a metal-contact etching process that differs from conventional device contact etching by focusing on the film-stack configuration and the associated super-contact etching characteristics. Because metal-contact etching is closely linked to both physical profiles and electrical performance, evaluating a single parameter provides limited insight; thus, the physical profile characteristics of metal-contact etching and 3D-integrated super-contacts were comprehensively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual Surfactant-Assisted Hydrothermal Engineering of Co<sub>3</sub>V<sub>2</sub>O<sub>8</sub> Nanostructures for High-Performance Asymmetric Supercapacitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a dual surfactant-assisted hydrothermal approach for the synthesis of Co(3)V(2)O(8) (CoVO) nanostructures and their surfactant-modified derivatives, PVP-assisted Co(3)V(2)O(8) (P-CoVO) and PVP-SDS co-assisted Co(3)V(2)O(8) (P/S-CoVO), which were directly grown on nickel foam. The use of PVP and SDS enabled controlled nucleation and growth, yielding a hierarchical nanoflower-like morphology in P/S-CoVO with increased porosity, a higher surface area, and uniform structural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication of Nanostructures on Surface of Micro-Lens Arrays Using Reactive Ion Etching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we fabricated a nanostructure on the surface of the micro-lens array (MLA), which is one of the light extraction technologies of organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs), by performing the Reactive Ion -Etching (RIE) process. The MLA consists of a lensed area and a lens-less bottom (flat film area). We performed a systematic analysis to find ways to improve the light extraction efficiency of the MLA surface and flat film area. By controlling the RIE process time and type of gas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selection of Base Materials for Repair Welding Using BWM-TOPSIS and BWM-RADAR Approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this paper, the selection of the optimal base material to be used in the repair welding process is presented. The aim of the study was to determine which of the available materials has the best characteristics, based on an analysis conducted in a company engaged in construction works. Three base materials were considered in the study: ABRADUR 58, E DUR 600, and CrWC 600 electrodes. Repair welding was performed on components for a construction machinery facility using the manual metal arc...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Photoelectrochemical Performance of BiVO<sub>4</sub> Photoanodes Through Few-Layer MoS<sub>2</sub> Composite Formation for Efficient Water Oxidation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoelectrochemical water splitting (PEC-WS) provides a sustainable route to transform solar energy into hydrogen; however, its overall efficiency is constrained by the inherently slow kinetics of the oxygen evolution reaction. Bismuth vanadate (BiVO(4)) is considered an attractive visible-light-responsive photoanode due to its suitable band gap (~2.4 eV) and chemical stability; however, its efficiency is restricted by limited charge transport and significant charge carrier recombination. To...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Study on Hollow Mesoporous Silica Nanoparticles with Long-Term Cycling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As electronic technologies continue to advance, the demand for high-performance and safe batteries has steadily increased. However, silicon-based anode materials experience severe volume expansion and poor structural stability during cycling, which limits their practical application. In this study, we synthesized hollow mesoporous silica to develop an anode material with long-term cycling stability. Electrochemical analysis revealed that the material exhibited low-capacity decay, decreasing from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Anxiety Symptoms of Mood Disorders Across Bipolar and Major Depressive Disorder Using Network Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Anxiety is prevalent in patients with major depressive disorder (MDD) and bipolar disorder (BD). Understanding its interaction with mood disorders may provide deeper insight into symptom clustering, severity, and interventions. We compared the networks of MDD and BD using the Beck Anxiety Inventory (BAI) to identify central symptoms and interconnections. Materials and Methods: This cross-sectional study involved 815 individuals with MDD (n = 332) and BD (n = 483) who...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Local Anesthetics on Experimental Postoperative Adhesion: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis with Trial Sequential Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: We performed a systematic review and meta-analysis using trial sequential analysis (TSA) to investigate the potential preventive postoperative antiadhesive effects of local anesthetics (LA). Materials and Methods: A comprehensive search was conducted using Ovid-MEDLINE, Ovid-EMBASE, Web of Science, and Google Scholar to identify animal studies that explored the postoperative antiadhesive effect of LA applied in the surgical area. The primary outcome was the macroscopic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of a Fluid-Collection Device for the Duodenoscope Biopsy Channel During Endoscopic Retrograde Cholangiopancreatography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Fluid leakage through the biopsy port during endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography (ERCP) is a common procedural challenge that can compromise efficiency and increase the risk of contamination. In this study, we aimed to evaluate factors associated with fluid leakage and describe the performance of a novel leakage-collection device. Materials and Methods: A total of 183 patients who underwent ERCP between June and September 2024 at a single center were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma Exchange as an Adjunctive Therapeutic Option for Severe and Refractory Antineutrophil Cytoplasmic Antibody-Negative Microscopic Polyangiitis and Granulomatosis with Polyangiitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: This study investigated and compared the efficacy of therapeutic plasma exchange (PEX) between antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody (ANCA)-positive and ANCA-negative patients with microscopic polyangiitis (MPA) and granulomatosis with polyangiitis (GPA) presenting with diffuse alveolar haemorrhage (DAH) and rapidly progressive glomerulonephritis (RPGN). Materials and Methods: A total of 336 patients with ANCA-associated vasculitis were screened, and 34 patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Cancer Incidence Trends in Korea (2001-2020): An Age-Period-Cohort and Joinpoint Analysis with a Focus on Younger Cohorts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Cancer incidence patterns in South Korea have shifted markedly over the past two decades, with notable increases among younger generations. Despite growing concern regarding early-onset cancer, comprehensive assessments of long-term age-, period-, and cohort-specific trends across multiple cancer types remain limited. This study examined nationwide cancer incidence trends from 2001 to 2020 using Joinpoint regression and age-period-cohort (APC) modeling. Materials and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating the Therapeutic Pathway and Optimal First-Line Systemic Therapy for Hepatocellular Carcinoma in the Era of Immune Checkpoint Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) remains a prevalent form of cancer with a poor prognosis and requires systemic therapies for most advanced cases. In this review, we summarize considerations for selecting treatment options for HCC, particularly with regard to immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs). Traditional chemotherapy has been surpassed by molecular-targeted therapies and ICIs, such as cytotoxic T-lymphocyte-associated antigen 4 (CTLA-4), programmed death-1 (PD-1), and programmed death-ligand 1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prenatal Diagnosis and Postnatal Outcomes of Fetal ADPKD: A Single-Center Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Autosomal dominant polycystic kidney disease (ADPKD) is the most common hereditary renal disorder; it is typically diagnosed in adulthood, but occasionally presents antenatally as very-early onset ADPKD. Despite advances in prenatal ultrasonography, knowledge regarding the postnatal course of fetal ADPKD remains limited, restricting reliable prognostic assessment and prenatal counselling. This study aimed to evaluate the prenatal sonographic features of fetal ADPKD and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the Controlling Nutritional Status (CONUT) Score and the Systemic Immune-Inflammation Index (SII) for Predicting Leakage and Surgical Complications After Head and Neck Free Flap Reconstruction: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: While many factors are known to influence adverse outcomes after head and neck cancer ablation with free flap reconstruction, two low-cost inflammatory-nutritional indices-the Controlling Nutritional Status (CONUT) score and the Systemic Immune-Inflammation Index (SII)-are not widely used. This pilot study evaluated their accuracy for predicting surgical complications, including flap-site leakage, and explored data-driven cutoff values. Materials and Methods: We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A preliminary study on the development of a chronic disease self-management curriculum for disability support workers: educational needs analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results of this study can be used as a basis for developing a chronic disease self-management education program for disability support workers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Secondary infection in severe COVID-19 patients: clinical and microbial patterns at a tertiary hospital in Vietnam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tau proteoforms as plasma biomarkers in Alzheimer's disease: mechanisms, measurement, and Medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Blood-based tau proteoforms have emerged as specific, scalable biomarkers of Alzheimer's pathology, addressing the limitations of symptom-based diagnosis, neuroimaging, and invasive cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) testing. This review synthesizes advances in tau phosphorylation and truncation biology, evaluates translation from CSF to plasma with state-of-the-art proteomics, and outlines the analytical standards and cross-matrix calibration needed for clinical adoption.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of BPH-LUTS according to the PM₁₀ exposure: A longitudinal nationwide cohort-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study is significant that, based on Korean standards, even normal PM₁₀ exposure is a risk factor for the development of BPH-LUTS. This study provides a basis for establishing health policies related to exposure to PM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term bladder and renal outcomes after cutaneous vesicostomy closure in pediatric patients with non-neurogenic bladder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Vesicostomy in non-neurogenic bladder patients was associated with recovery of BC, preservation of continence, and improved renal function. Parenchymal abnormalities on ultrasonography predicted lower GFR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of COVID-19 on testicular torsion: A single-center retrospective study from a children's hospital]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The current study shows that pandemic-related delays in treatment may worsen ischemic injury in testicular torsion, emphasizing the importance of timely intervention even during global crises.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and genotype distribution of human papillomavirus among Korean males: Implications for vaccination strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These data support including males in national HPV vaccination strategies using the current 9-valent vaccine and underscore the need for ongoing genotype surveillance to monitor non-vaccine high-risk types and inform public health policy, and support inclusion of males in national HPV vaccination strategies using the current 9-valent vaccine.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic syndrome and its components as independent risk factors for nocturia: A national cross-sectional analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MetS and its components are independently associated with nocturia. The observed sex-specific differences suggest that metabolic contributors to nocturia may differ by sex supporting nocturia as a potential clinical marker of underlying cardiometabolic dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic accuracy of prostate-specific antigen and prostate-specific antigen density in patients suspected of having prostate cancer in South Korea: A large, multi-institutional registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that diagnostic yield may not be impacted by merely lowering the PSA cutoff. Rather, combining PSA, PSAD, and patient age enhances screening accuracy while minimizing unnecessary biopsies and overdiagnosis. Our results highlight the need for more data to refine national screening guidelines and promote a more tailored approach to prostate cancer screening in Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preoperative serum albumin level is associated with postoperative short- and long-term renal function deterioration in patients who underwent radical cystectomy for bladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Serum albumin level <4.1 g/dL was associated with short- and long-term renal function decline after RC, suggesting that close monitoring of renal function after RC might be considered in these patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence-based personalized oncological outcome prediction model for upper urinary tract urothelial carcinoma after radical nephroureterectomy: A development and multicenter validation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AI-based model effectively predicts disease-free and OS outcomes for upper-urinary tract urothelial carcinoma patients with post-radical nephroureterectomy, showcasing robust performance across multicenter settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41469902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lessons from Failed Attempts of Computationally Guided Synthesis of Aluminosilicate STF and IFR Zeolites in Hydroxide Media]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although zeolites are primarily aluminosilicates in terms of chemical composition, not all zeotypes have been successfully synthesized as aluminosilicates to date. This study aims to contribute answering the long-standing question of why some zeotypes cannot, or have not yet been, synthesized as aluminosilicates, using a computational approach that combines big data, artificial intelligence, accurate descriptors, and an algorithm for designing quaternary ammonium organic structure-directing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Constructing High-Performance Solar Cells by Incorporating an A1-A2-Type Polymer Donor as a Guest Material]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Owing to the intramolecular push-pull electron effect between the electron donor (D) unit and electron acceptor (A) unit, the D-A type based polymer donors display outstanding device performance. However, the imperfect energy levels lead to the D-A-type-based polymer device exhibiting high voltage loss. In this study, an A1-A2-type copolymer M1 was developed with 1,3-bis(2-ethylhexyl)-5,7-di(thiophen-2-yl)benzo[1,2-c:4,5-c']dithiophene-4,8-dione (BDD) as the A1 unit and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MIRA: A Transformer-Based Framework for Idler Roller Anomaly Detection and Localization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monitoring the condition of belt conveyor idlers is critical for ensuring safe and efficient operation of industrial conveying systems. However, existing methods often suffer from limited scalability and delayed fault detection, particularly under variable environmental conditions. In this work, we propose MIRA, a transformer-based framework for monitoring idler roller anomalies, which detects and localizes faults using acoustic and vibration signals collected from low-cost sensors. MIRA employs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surface Passivation with Lattice-Matched Bidentate Ligand Enabling High-Performance Perovskite Quantum Dot Photodetectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface halide vacancies are prevalent on lead halide perovskite (LHP) quantum dots (QDs) due to their intrinsically low formation energy, and they serve as dominant non-radiative recombination centers that degrade optoelectronic performance. While ligand exchange has been commonly used to mitigate these surface defects, the influence of multidentate ligand geometry on binding interactions with QD surfaces remains largely unexplored. In this study, we demonstrate that controlling the spatial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Field Emission Control via Work Function Modulation in Semimetallic Graphene Edge Cathodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graphene, the bandgapless 2D crystal, uniquely combines metal-like conductivity with an electrostatically tunable Fermi level-an ability that conventional metals lack. Here, we exploit this semimetallic property to realize a vacuum edge emitter whose current can be directly modulated through work function control rather than relying on vacuum-channel field reshaping. We demonstrate a graphene edge-emitter nanoscale vacuum transistor with an off-channel gate, enabling spatial separation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multicompartmental analysis of microbiome alterations under radiation stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual attachment of the buccinator muscle at the pterygoid hamulus: implications for pterygoid implant surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study revealed a dual attachment of the buccinator muscle to the pterygoid hamulus and emphasized its close proximity to the maxillary tuberosity. Additionally, low BV/TV values in some specimens highlight the anatomical variability of this region. Understanding individual differences in bone structure and the precise location of soft tissue attachments is essential for safer and more predictable pterygoid implant placement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunable Charge Transport Properties Through Precise π-Stacking Modulation in Isostructural Porous Molecular Conductors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the structure-property relationships in electrically conductive metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) is critical for their rational design toward practical applications. Since single crystals of MOFs with through-space conductive π-stacked columnar structures are relatively easy to obtain, their structures can be determined with high accuracy. However, elucidating those structure-property relationships without interference from carrier scattering and variations in carrier concentration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fast-Ion-Conductor Multiscale Nanoconfinement Overcomes Ion-Transport Limitations in All-Solid-State Sodium Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Composite polymer electrolytes (CPEs) hold significant potential for high-performance all-solid-state sodium batteries, yet their development remains hindered by compromised ionic transport kinetics arising from limited conduction pathways and strong Na^(+) coordination. Here, we report a fast-ion-conductor multiscale nanoconfinement strategy that enables continuous high-throughput Na^(+) migration in CPEs by embedding polyethylene glycol (PEG)-confined boron-rich covalent organic framework...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PEX14 powers OPTN (optineurin) to drive peroxisome turnover]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cells maintain organelle integrity and metabolic balance through tightly coordinated quality control systems. Autophagy plays a central role by recycling damaged and unnecessary cellular components, with selective pathways providing specificity through dedicated receptors. Although OPTN is well-established as a receptor for mitophagy, aggrephagy, and xenophagy, its role in pexophagy, the selective autophagic degradation of peroxisomes, has only recently been recognized. Our recent work...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asymmetric synthesis of (+)-gomadalactones A and (-)-B: contact sex pheromones of white-spotted longicorn beetle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The white-spotted longicorn beetle (Anoplophora malasiaca), a serious fruit tree pest, relies on contact sex pheromones for mating purposes. The asymmetric synthesis of the pheromonal components, (+)-gomadalactones A and (-)-B, was achieved using an improved enantioselective version of our previous racemic synthesis method. The key 3-oxabicyclo[3.3.0]octane framework was constructed using a combination of Vassilikogiannakis one-pot, photodriven cyclopentenone synthesis with DBU-mediated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of hemophilia B treatment via population PK modeling of rIX-FP, including a 3-week regimen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: rIX-FP supports individualized prophylaxis with extended intervals up to 3 weeks in patients ≥12 years while younger children typically require more frequent dosing due to higher weight-normalized clearance. These PK-based insights can guide shared decision-making to balance protection, treatment burden, and patient preference across pediatric and adolescent age groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moving the Fine Print to the Front Page: Transparent Communication of Facial Genetics Research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AI-enabled facial genetics research has transformative potential for biomedical and forensic applications, but raises serious ethical, legal, and social challenges. Candor and clarity promote the advancement of science and facilitate the development of evidence-informed and ethically sound policy guardrails for scientific applications. Expanding upon our recent Comment on Difface, here we examine some of the ethical dimensions of AI-enabled facial genetics research, illuminate a lack of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum human chorionic gonadotropin can predict live birth 7 days after frozen-thawed blastocyst transfer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We determined the hCG cutoff values for live births after frozen-thawed blastocyst transfer. We suggest that it is possible to predict pregnancy outcomes as early as the 7th or 8th day after frozen-thawed blastocyst transfer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diaphragmatic curvature analysis using dynamic digital radiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The value of ΔAUD was smaller according to the severity of COPD. ΔAUD can be helpful in distinguishing healthy subjects from COPD patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Established and emerging new approach methodologies in neuroscience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing need for ethical, human-relevant, and efficient alternatives to animal testing is driving the development of New Approach Methodologies (NAMs) in safety assessment and drug development. However, the inherent complexity of neurological diseases presents a significant challenge to fully replace animal models in this field. In neuroscience, a range of NAMs, from traditional 2D cell cultures to advanced brain organoids and alternative vertebrate models like zebrafish, demonstrate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Efficacy and safety of tranexamic acid administration for subarachnoid hemorrhage: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fneur.2025.1617817.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcome of patients with curative-intent treatment for primary pulmonary sarcoma: Results from an international multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with curative-intent multimodal treatment for PPS, an encouraging 5-year survival rate of 49% can be achieved in expert centers. Independent prognostic factors may aid in selecting patients for curative treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood pressure indices for predicting incident cardiovascular disease: A 13-year follow-up study in Japanese population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MAP was the strongest predictor of incident CVD in the Japanese population. These findings underscore the importance of BP phenotyping and suggest that gender and age may modify the utility of MAP in cardiovascular risk stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41473017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Precisely Bromo-Functionalized [9]Cycloparaphenylene as a Platform for Late-Stage Multisite π-Extension Toward Chiral Nanohoops]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Selective functionalization of [n]cycloparaphenylenes ([n]CPPs) has remained a significant synthetic challenge due to their inherent ring strain. In this study, we present the synthesis of a [9]CPP derivative in which bromo groups are orderly introduced at the 2,5-positions of three benzene rings in the [9]CPP framework, each separated by two phenylene units. The use of our developed Au-mediated CPP synthetic method enabled efficient and scalable access to the target compound in five steps with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41472412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vision-Based Trajectory Reconstruction in Human Activities: Methodology and Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Modern civil engineering structures, such as footbridges, are increasingly susceptible to vibrations induced by human activities, emphasizing the importance of accurately assessing crowd-induced loading. Developing realistic load models requires detailed insight into the underlying crowd dynamics, which in turn depend on the coordination between individuals and the spatial organization of the group. A deeper understanding of these human-human interactions is therefore essential for capturing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improvement in Random Noise for Pixel-Parallel Single-Slope ADC with Consideration of Flicker Noise Effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose and demonstrate a low-random-noise (RN) design for pixel-parallel single-slope ADCs (SS-ADCs), achieving 2.2 e-rms in a 3.24 µm pixel. In this paper, we discuss AC-based RN estimation with respect to the comparator bias current and a bandwidth-limiting capacitor in digital-pixel sensors (DPSs). RN is composed of thermal noise (TN) and flicker noise (FN), where FN can be a major contributor in DPSs because of its area limitation. We express the concise equation to estimate the FN/TN...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WISEST: Weighted Interpolation for Synthetic Enhancement Using SMOTE with Thresholds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Imbalanced learning occurs when rare but critical events are missed because classifiers are trained primarily on majority-class samples. This paper introduces WISEST, a locality-aware weighted-interpolation algorithm that generates synthetic minority samples within a controlled threshold near class boundaries. Benchmarked on more than a hundred real-world imbalanced datasets, such as KEEL, with different imbalance ratios, noise levels, geometries, and other security and IoT sets (IoT-23 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of the Insulin Receptor in Mediating Cytosolic Delivery of Proteins by a Modified Cell-Penetrating Peptide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Intracellular delivery of high-molecular-weight proteins is limited by the cell membrane. Cell-penetrating peptides (CPPs) offer a potential solution, but effective cytosolic delivery remains hindered by endosomal sequestration. Pas2r12, a CPP-derived peptide, facilitates cytosolic delivery of proteins including immunoglobulin G. Because Pas2r12 internalization occurs via caveolae-dependent endocytosis, we hypothesized that cell-surface receptors contribute to uptake. Methods: HEK293...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Double-Antigen Sandwich ELISA for Oz Virus and a Seroepidemiological Survey in Wild Boars in Miyazaki, Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oz virus, an emerging tick-borne thogotovirus, has been reported to cause fatal human infection in Japan. However, its ecology and geographic distribution remain largely unknown. In this study, we developed a double-antigen sandwich enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay (DAgS ELISA) for detecting Oz virus antibodies in animals and used it to conduct a seroepidemiological survey of wild boars (Sus scrofa) in Miyazaki Prefecture, Japan. Recombinant Oz virus nucleoprotein was expressed in E. coli and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Skin Penetration of Fluorescent Dissolved Formulations Using Confocal Laser Scanning Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Transdermal formulations are widely utilized in the pharmaceutical and cosmetic fields because they enable non-invasive administration and sustained local drug delivery. Conventional ex vivo skin permeation experiments using Franz diffusion cells have limitations in capturing the spatial and temporal dynamics of skin penetration. This study aimed to develop a confocal laser scanning microscopy (CLSM)-based approach to visualize and semi-quantitatively assess the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dermal Formulation Incorporating Isoconazole Nitrate Nanoparticles Offers High Absorption into Skin and Antimicrobial Effect Against <em>Candida albicans</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Isoconazole nitrate (ISN), an antifungal agent that inhibits ergosterol synthesis by blocking lanosterol 14α-demethylation, is widely used to treat candidiasis, and improving its skin retention and permeability can enhance its therapeutic efficacy. Therefore, we developed an ISN nanoparticle (ISN-NP) gel by wet-bead milling in the presence of methylcellulose (MC). Methods: These ISN nanoparticles were incorporated into a carboxypolymethylene hydrogel (Carbopol). The ISN concentration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41471035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovering Anticancer Effects of Phytochemicals on MicroRNA in the Context of Data Mining]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: miRNA is linked to a variety of human diseases, including cancer. The expression levels and profiles can be related to disease prevention and the promotion of good health. Understanding the beneficial changes in miRNA expression mediated by micro- and macronutrients is vital for maintaining optimal health. However, it remains unknown which phytochemicals affect miRNA expression, thereby hindering the identification of novel dietary functions. Methods: We searched for and investigated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic and Epigenetic Mechanisms Underpinning Biotic Stress Resilience of <em>Brassica</em> Vegetables]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Breeding for disease-resistant varieties is a sustainable solution to reduce substantial production losses caused by pathogenic infestations in Brassica vegetables, bypassing environmentally risky disease management practices. Host-resistant genetic mechanisms aid breeders to identify resistance loci and linked markers for the clubroot, Fusarium yellows, downy mildew, black rot, stem rot, soft rot, white rust, and turnip mosaic virus diseases in Brassica vegetables. Introgression of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incorporation of Temperature Impact on Hot-Carrier Degradation into Compact Physics Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We extend our compact physics model (CPM) for hot-carrier degradation (HCD) to cover the impact of ambient temperature on HCD. Three components of this impact are taken into account. First, variations in temperature perturb carrier transport. Second, the thermal component of Si-H bond rupture becomes more prominent at elevated temperatures. Third, vibrational lifetime of the bond decreases with temperature. While the first and the third mechanisms impede HCD, the second one accelerates this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Initial Relative Density on Liquid-Phase Sintering Behaviors of Al Powder Using Al-Cu Eutectic Alloy Aid: In Situ Observations Using Tomography and Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aluminum (Al) powder with low sinterability is difficult to use in binder jetting (BJT) additive manufacturing, which involves sintering a metal powder after forming a green body. A liquid-phase sintering process for Al powder using Al-Cu eutectic alloy powder as a sintering aid has recently been developed. In this study, to clarify the applicability of liquid-phase sintering to BJT additive manufacturing, the effect of the initial relative density of green bodies (ρ(rel,0) = 50-90%) on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in Minimally Invasive Esophagectomy-An Overview of Recent Developments and a Novel Classification of Innovations in Treatment of Thoracic Esophageal Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Minimally invasive esophagectomy (MIE) has become increasingly prominent in the surgical management of esophageal cancer (EC) over the past three decades. The adoption of minimally invasive techniques has significantly enhanced oncologic esophageal surgery by improving safety, achieving oncological radicality, preserving physiological function, and elevating the postoperative quality of life of the patients. The complexity of MIE lies in its technical nuances, which critically influence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral, Vaginal, and Placental Microbiota Profiles in Japanese Pregnancies with Preterm Birth and Chronic Abruption-Oligohydramnios Sequence (CAOS): A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Preterm birth (PTB) imposes a substantial medical and economic burden on perinatal care. Recent advances in 16S rRNA gene sequencing help detailed microbiota analysis. Understanding microbiota's contribution may help in understanding PTB pathogenesis. We aim to investigate the microbiota profiles of the oral, vaginal, and placental microbiota in pregnant Japanese women hospitalized for care of preterm labor and examine the association between them and perinatal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MOGEDN: small-sample cancer subtype classification with encoder-decoder networks for missing-omics recovery and biomarker discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Effective cancer subtype classification from multi-omics data remains challenging due to incomplete omics data and limited sample sizes. While graph convolutional networks (GCNs) have been used to incorporate inter-sample relationships for enhancing small-sample classification, their performance deteriorates when a certain omics modality is entirely missing. Here, we propose MOGEDN, a novel framework for cancer subtype classification using multi-omics encoder-decoder networks designed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reframing gastric lymph nodes as a parapancreatic lymph chain: an embryology-driven rationale for omento-bursectomy and omentum-preserving gastrectomy to facilitate safe infrapyloric lymph node dissection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The infrapyloric lymph nodes (LNs) are defined as No. 6 LNs and as one of the regional gastric LNs in the Japanese classification of gastric carcinoma. No. 6 LNs are recommended to be dissected completely even in D1 lymphadenectomy for distal and total gastrectomy in the Japanese Gastric Cancer Treatment Guideline. Omento-bursectomy, whose survival advantage for advanced gastric cancer patients was not shown by the Japanese Clinical Oncology Group 1001 trial, has been proposed to be a useful...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41470024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JAK-STAT pathway activation compromises nephrocyte function in a <em>Drosophila</em> high-fat diet model of chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic kidney disease is a major health issue and is gaining prevalence. Using a Drosophila model for chronic kidney disease, we show that a high-fat diet (HFD) disrupts the slit diaphragm filtration structure in nephrocytes, the fly functional equivalent of mammalian podocytes. The structural disruption resulted in reduced filtration function in the affected nephrocytes. We demonstrate that HFD activates the JAK-STAT pathway in nephrocytes, which has previously been linked to diabetic kidney...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental health disparities across demographic and social groups in Abu Dhabi]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mental health disparities are increasingly shaped by intersecting demographic and socioeconomic conditions. Anchored in the Social Determinants of Health framework, this study investigates variations in mental well-being among adults in Abu Dhabi using data from the 5th Cycle of the Abu Dhabi Quality of Life Survey (2023-2024), which included over 100,000 respondents. Drawing on a subset of 65,203 adults, we analysed key mental health indicators-such as sadness, anxiety, loneliness, fear,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reassessing the 2023 International Society for Cardiovascular Infectious Diseases Duke clinical criteria for infective endocarditis: Impact of excluding fever and updating diagnostic definitions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Exclusion of fever as a minor criterion within the updated Duke-ISCVID framework substantially improved specificity without compromising sensitivity. These findings challenge the traditional role of fever in IE diagnosis and support a broader re-evaluation of longstanding diagnostic criteria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Vitamin D Status and Nocturnal Lower Urinary Tract Symptoms: A Pooled Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Vitamin D deficiency is a significant risk factor for nLUTS; supplementation may offer therapeutic benefits. Assessing vitamin D status could guide nLUTS management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterizing the extended language network in individuals with multiple sclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We identified network-level functional and structural measures to potentially characterize language dysfunction in MS. Further studies leveraging these features may reveal mechanisms and predictors of language dysfunction specific to MS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward Digital Assessment of Developmental Dyslexia in Mainland China: Establishing Nationwide Norms With a GAMLSS Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Existing diagnosis instruments for developmental dyslexia (DD) in mainland China are limited in generalizability and typically rely on traditional norming approaches, which require large sample sizes to achieve precision. This study aims to develop and validate the Beijing Normal University Diagnostic Tool for Chinese Mandarin Developmental Dyslexia (BNU-DTCMDD), a DD diagnostic tool with regression-based norms for elementary school students in mainland China. A nationally representative sample...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a deep learning-based model for predicting prostate cancer in patients with gray-zone PSA levels: a comparative study with clinician observations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The multimodal CNNs, integrating ADC and T2WI data, demonstrated high accuracy for PCa detection in patients with gray-zone PSA levels, comparable to senior radiologists. This model can aid clinical decision-making, assist in challenging cases, and help reduce unnecessary biopsies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Child Life: the heartbeat of healing in pediatric care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exception from Informed Consent and Waiver of Informed Consent for Comparative Effectiveness Trials in Emergency Care Research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For many of the decisions made in the clinical care setting, clinicians lack evidence to inform which treatment would result in the best patient outcomes. This problem is particularly common in emergency care, a field in which the condition of the patient and the urgent nature of the treatment often preclude research conducted using prospective informed consent. Large-scale comparative effectiveness clinical trials could address the evidence gaps in clinical medicine and improve patient outcomes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic Factors Modulating the Connection Between Diabetes and Pulmonary Alterations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Lower FEV1 and FVC in diabetes are linked to insulin resistance, impaired clearance, and higher insulin doses, all of which result in higher insulinemia and likely represent underlying pathogenic mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Altered Metabolites at Birth in Individuals With Later Inflammatory Bowel Disease: A Danish Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enantioselective Synthesis of Functionalized 2,2-Disubstituted Piperidines Enabled by Pd-Catalyzed Decarboxylative Asymmetric Allylic Alkylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, we report a palladium-catalyzed decarboxylative asymmetric allylic alkylation (Pd-DAAA) for the synthesis of enantioenriched 2,2-disubstituted piperidines. This method efficiently constructs aza-quaternary stereocenters with high enantioselectivity and broad functional group compatibility. Its utility is demonstrated through access to synthetically useful azacyclic building blocks, a formal synthesis of arbornamine, and the identification of potent antileukemia agents, establishing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clarifying power-mediated aerosol effects and enhancing statistical rigour in in utero electronic cigarette exposure research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skin-Derived Precursors-Derived Exosomes Alleviated Acne Inflammation via TLR2/MyD88/NF-κB Signaling Pathway: In Vitro and In Vivo Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skin-derived precursors (SKPs) isolated from the dermis are poorly immunogenic and capable of modulating the allogeneic immune responses. Previous studies implied mouse SKPs-derived exosomes (mSKPs-exo) might possess immunomodulatory functions. In the present study we collected mSKPs-exo using ultracentrifugation method and characterized them. We then explored mSKPs-exo's impact on acne inflammation with Cutibacterium acnes (C. acnes)-challenged murine monocyte-macrophages RAW264.7 and Sprague...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41474360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251231142203&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>