<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 07:37:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adherence to Animal Research: Reporting of In Vivo Experiments Guidelines in Stem Cell Studies in Animal Models of Parkinson's Disease: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The reporting of key design principles in animal stem cell research related to PD was insufficient both before and after the introduction of the ARRIVE guidelines in 2010. Both researchers and journal editors should pay more attention to the accurate, comprehensive reporting of animal studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-energy CO<sub>2</sub> mineralization of asbestos-containing waste (ACW) via ammonium salt leaching: A route to detoxification and carbon sequestration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The safe management of asbestos-containing waste (ACW) remains an environmental and public health priority. This study proposes a low-energy treatment strategy integrating ammonium salt leaching with aqueous CO(2) carbonation to chemically stabilize fibrous asbestos structures. Although Ca^(2+) was not significantly leached from ACW using ammonium sulfate, the system achieved up to 99.9% conversion efficiency of dissolved Ca^(2+) to crystalline calcite (CaCO₃) during carbonation. XRD analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling Weather-Independent Gas Detection through Deep Learning on Light-Activated Sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Light-activated gas sensors offer a low-temperature, low-power approach for detecting target species, and their high-performance capabilities make them ideal for practical applications. The direct integration of Bi-doped In(2)O(3) nanofibers onto micro light-emitting diode (μLED) platforms enables high-performance sensors for simultaneous NO(2) and H(2)O detection. Introducing Bi into In(2)O(3) matrices facilitates the formation of oxygen vacancies and the dissociative adsorption of H(2)O,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonclinical safety evaluation and pharmacokinetics of Ab612, a novel anti-L1CAM (CD171) therapeutic antibody candidate against solid cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[L1 cell adhesion molecule (L1CAM, CD171) is a transmembrane glycoprotein important for nervous system development. Conversely, L1CAM is overexpressed in many human solid tumors with poor prognosis. Nonclinical safety evaluation and pharmacokinetics (PK) of Ab612, a human anti-L1CAM monoclonal antibody (mAb), were conducted to support a first-in-human (FIH) clinical trial for the treatment of L1CAM overexpressing tumors. A tissue cross-reactivity (TCR) assessment showed that Ab612 exhibited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colossal Spin Hall Conductivity in Charge-Massive Topologically Nontrivial Semimetal Phase of Bi<sub>1-<em>x</em></sub>Sb<sub><em>x</em></sub> (012)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Topologically nontrivial semimetals (TSMs) possess spin-momentum locked topological surface states (TSS) with high charge conductivity (σ), offering a platform for low-power spintronic applications. However, its spin Hall conductivity (σ(SH)), another important factor for spintronic applications, remains largely unexplored. Here, we demonstrate that Bi(1-x)Sb(x) in the TSM phase (x = 0.6-0.8), when grown along the distinct (012) orientation, exhibits a colossal σ(SH), far exceeding that of Pt....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superhydrophilic Silica-Coated Au Nanoislands for Efficient Capture and Enhanced SERS Detection of Airborne Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exhaled breath aerosols contain critical biomarkers for noninvasive and cost-effective early detection of respiratory and other infectious diseases. However, current methods still struggle with a low capture efficiency and limited detection sensitivity for trace biomarkers in complex aerosols. Here we report superhydrophilic ultrathin silica-coated gold nanoislands (scAuNIs) for the highly efficient capture and SERS detection of airborne biomarkers. The scAuNIs are wafer-level fabricated by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Multiomics Validation of Key <em>MUC</em> Gene Expression for the Signature Biomarker in the Pakistani Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In conclusion, our findings suggest MUC3A/MUC4/MUC13/MUC16 as robust diagnostic and prognostic biomarkers and liquid biopsy as a noninvasive approach to be integrated into daily clinical practice. This analysis can also be extended to other malignancies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum Computing Based Design of Multivariate Porous Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multivariate (MTV) porous materials exhibit unique structural complexities based on their diverse spatial arrangements of multiple building block combinations. These materials possess potential synergistic functionalities that exceed the sum of their individual components. However, the exponentially increasing design complexity of these materials poses significant challenges for accurate ground-state configuration prediction and design. To address this, we propose a Hamiltonian model for quantum...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Far-field wireless power transmission module with MEMS-based laser steering for optogenetic applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a far-field wireless power transmission system utilizing a mobile laser steering module (MOLASM) for optogenetic applications. The system integrates a MEMS-based active micromirror and features a battery-free architecture, enabling a miniaturized, lightweight, and mobile operation. This design allows for precise laser steering while maintaining a compact form factor. Additionally, laser superimposition using multiple MOLASMs enhances wirelessly transmitted power,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning Multidimensional Electronegativity of Selected Atom Types in Organic Molecules Using Graph Neural Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electronegativity can be considered a data-driven concept that has been widely used since Pauling proposed this property. However, updating the electronegativity based on the vast amount of high-quality experimental and computational data has been overlooked. Thus, advances in artificial intelligence (AI), with its ability to manage large data sets and identify underlying patterns, necessitate reconsidering data-driven concepts such as electronegativity. In this work, we present a data-driven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional Testing of Human Disease Missense Variants in <em>Caenorhabditis elegans</em> by Targeting <em>COQ2</em> Variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings provide insights into human genetic disease-associated missense variants and demonstrate that C. elegans can be used as a simple, cost-effective in vivo model for testing undetermined missense variants in human disease genes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical composition, aroma profile, antioxidant activity, and sensory attributes of beer according to roasting degree and malt type]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the effects of malt roasting degree on the chemical composition, aroma profile, antioxidant activity, and sensory attributes of brewed beer. Roasting increased carbohydrate content, diastatic power, and Maillard products such as melanoidins and Amadori compounds, contributing to deeper color and enhanced antioxidant activity. Aroma profiling with an electronic nose revealed that roasting shifted key volatile classes, including esters, terpenes, pyrazines, and sulfur...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of smart watch mobile application on the risk treatment of type 2 diabetes mellitus (iSMART-DM)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although short-term glycemic control showed no significant difference, the smartwatch-based mobile intervention significantly enhanced self-care behaviors in patients with T2DM. These findings highlight the behavioral benefits of wearable-integrated mHealth platforms and support their broader application in lifestyle modification strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial Accessibility to Emergency Departments and Surgical Treatment for Patients with Acute Appendicitis in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The current results suggested that regions with low population density experienced low access to surgical care, revealing significant regional variation linked to population density. Given the rapidly aging population and the concentration of residents in urban areas in South Korea, urgent policy action is needed to ensure the adequate delivery of emergency general surgery services in low-density regions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between Color Vision Deficiency and Police Officer Tasks in South Korea: A Prospective Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated a correlation between the results of clinical color vision tests and police-related simulation tests. Particularly, the score for recognizing traffic signs or analyzing dashboard camera recordings was lower even in those with mild CVD than in those with normal vision.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene Expression Profiling and Pathway Analysis of the Effect of Dienogest on Ovarian Endometriosis: A Comparative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Comparison of the dienogest-treated and untreated groups before endometriotic ovarian cyst surgery revealed pathways related to immune system function, inflammatory response, cell signaling and adhesion, and metabolic regulation. These findings suggest that dienogest may play a role in controlling inflammation and immune regulation, potentially alleviating endometriosis-related symptoms and delaying recurrence. Although further studies are required for validation, our preliminary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immediate Postoperative AbnobaVISCUM<sup>®</sup> F as an Adjuvant Treatment in Patients Receiving Standard Care after Pancreatic Cancer Resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Viscum treatment significantly improved OS in patients with completely resected stage I and II pancreatic cancer, particularly among those unable to tolerate adjuvant chemotherapy. This anticancer effect, based on immune enhancement, should be further investigated, and large-scale randomized controlled study is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antenatally Diagnosed Ventriculomegaly: Postnatal Clinical Course and Neurodevelopmental Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Larger initial ventricle size in antenatal VM was associated with poorer neurodevelopmental outcomes. Normal antenatal findings can obscure postnatal CNS abnormalities. Advanced imaging and postnatal evaluation are essential for timely diagnosis and perinatal counseling and management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Functional Mobile Games to Enhance Attention in Individuals with Mild Cognitive Impairment: A Study Using The Montreal Cognitive Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The intervention demonstrated a significant improvement in attention as measured by MoCA and a slower progression of cognitive decline as indicated by CDR, highlighting its potential effectiveness in enhancing cognitive function and mitigating cognitive decline in older adults. These findings support using such interventions as a viable strategy for cognitive improvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral Branched-Chain Amino Acids as a Cost-Effective Option for Managing Hepatic Encephalopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Oral BCAAs for HE prevention may contribute positively to both the clinical status of the patient and the national healthcare budget.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Function Piezo-Photocatalytic Systems for Sustainable Hydrogen Evolution and Environmental Remediation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen (H(2)) production and environmental cleanup, including pollutant breakdown, nano-plastic removal, and CO(2) reduction, are crucial for achieving environmental sustainability. Piezo-photocatalysis has appeared in an optimistic approach to address environmental pollution and the escalating energy crisis. Although several reviews on H(2) production and environmental cleanup using piezo-catalytic technologies have been recently published, there is no review specifically focused on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Haloaromatic Reduction-Induced Formation of a High Surface Work Function Protective Layer on a Lithium Electrode for Stable Lithium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A liquid-phase strategy for stabilizing lithium metal electrodes in lithium metal batteries using halogen-substituted benzophenone compounds (4-X-BzPh, X = F, Cl, and Br) is performed. These compounds undergo spontaneous haloaromatic reduction upon contact with lithium, forming thin and uniform protective layers of lithium halides (LiX, where X = F, Cl, and Br). This process enables homogeneous passivation without the need for complex fabrication techniques. Among the LiX species, LiF exhibits...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fit prediction for filtering facepiece respirator using 3D face shape]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to develop and demonstrate a methodological framework for enhancing the predictability of filtering facepiece respirator (FFR) fit using 3D face-shape elements and evaluating their advantages over traditional anthropometric measurements for improved predictive modeling. Data was collected from 202 participants, including their 3D face scans and quantitative fit factor scores for one N95 respirator. An automated process was used to extract face shape data from 3D scans. Principal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chromosome-level genome assembly of IR64 near-isogenic line harboring Saltol reveals novel genomic regions associated with salinity tolerance in rice (Oryza sativa L.)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change-induced sea level rise significantly exacerbates soil and groundwater salinization, posing a substantial threat to global agriculture, particularly impacting salt-sensitive crops like rice (Oryza sativa L.). Significant advancements have been made in identifying the genetic factors that influence salinity tolerance. A well-studied quantitative trait locus (QTL), known as Saltol, is located on chromosome 1 and provides notable salinity tolerance during the seedling stage by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The new Bruton's tyrosine kinase inhibitors SPA8007 and SPA8009 reduce stemness and invasiveness of patient-derived glioblastoma tumorspheres]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma (GBM), the most prevalent primary brain tumor, remains incurable due to the presence of cancer stem cells (CSCs), which can be isolated as tumorspheres (TSs) that exhibit classical characteristics of CSCs, including stemness and invasiveness. The significantly elevated expression of Bruton's tyrosine kinase (BTK) in GBM tissues identifies BTK as a potential therapeutic target in GBM. Consequently, ibrutinib, an FDA-approved BTK inhibitor for hematological malignancies, has been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of lung abnormalities in smokers with rheumatoid arthritis screened for lung cancer with low-dose chest computed tomography imaging in routine clinical care: Results from a large multi-hospital system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with RA had higher prevalence of positive screening, fibrotic changes, and bronchiectasis detected by low-dose chest CT performed for lung cancer screening. Approximately 1 in 4 RA patients meeting USPSTF lung cancer screening criteria had a positive screen, while 1 in 20 had lung cancer. These results emphasize the importance of lung cancer screening among eligible RA patients and may inform screening strategies for other lung abnormalities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resolving Heterophile Antibody Interference in Viral Serology Using Blocking Tubes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite their clinical utility, immunoassays are susceptible to various types of interference. In this study, we aimed to assess the extent of interference from heterophile antibodies in routine clinical tests and evaluate the effectiveness of heterophile blocking tubes (HBT) in mitigating such interference. We collected 185 residual serum samples that tested positive or equivocal in at least one IgM assay for Epstein-Barr virus (EBV), viral capsid antigen (VCA), herpes simplex virus (HSV),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled, multicenter study to evaluate the efficacy and safety of adjunctive cenobamate in Asian patients with focal seizures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: This randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled study (NCT04557085), conducted in China, Japan, and the Republic of Korea, evaluated the efficacy and safety of adjunctive cenobamate in patients with uncontrolled focal seizures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social and Environmental Determinants of Secondhand Smoke Exposure and Physical and Mental Health among Immigrant-Origin Youths in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Secondhand smoke is understudied among immigrants in Korea. We examined the impact of smoking rates in the parents' countries of origin on secondhand smoke exposure at home and adolescents' physical and mental health, focusing on immigrant-origin status. Further, we explored the social and environmental determinants of secondhan smoke exposure. Data from the 2021 Korea Youth Risk Behavior Web-based Survey involving 38,690 middle and high school students were used. The relationships between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of immunogenicity of Rh antigens using in silico analysis of binding to human leukocyte antigen peptide, Basic/Translational Research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The association between human leukocyte antigen (HLA) types and blood group alloimmunization remains unclear. Previous studies have predominantly focused on predicting immunization events in cancer immunotherapy, but not blood group antigens. In this study, we investigated whether HLA peptide binding could predict the immunogenicity of blood group antigens. We performed in silico binding analysis of Rh antigens and representative HLA class II alleles using NetMHCpan-4.1 and NetMHCIIpan-4.1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and burden of anhedonia among patients with major depressive disorder in South Korea: A cross-sectional, observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first study in South Korea to estimate the prevalence of anhedonia in patients with MDD, highlighting the disease burden and unmet medical needs. Furthermore, disparities observed between patients and physicians in the goals and expectations of MDD treatment underscore the need to monitor anhedonia for treatment optimization.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frailty and nutritional inadequacy in older Korean adults: A gender-stratified analysis using National Survey Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While frailty has traditionally been conceptualized through physical decline, it is increasingly recognized as a complex concept encompassing emotional, psychological, and social factors. This study employed a multidimensional framework to investigate the association between nutritional status and frailty levels across genders. In addition, it aims to provide foundational insights for developing targeted dietary and preventive health policies that support interventions tailored to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of a new detector automatic exposure control in portable anteroposterior chest radiography: a retrospective examination of radiation dose optimization and image quality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundAutomatic exposure control (AEC) devices are necessary to reduce the radiation dose and enhance image quality in radiography. However, AEC devices are not being used in portable X-ray systems due to technical issues.PurposeTo evaluate the radiation dose and image quality of a new AEC for a wireless portable X-ray system compared to the standard fixed radiation dose of manual controls in chest radiography.Material and MethodsThis retrospective analysis evaluated the performance of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compliance and factuality of large language models for clinical research document generation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: LLMs offer value in clinical research document generation but must be adapted and rigorously evaluated for high-stakes applications. Our benchmark and framework provide a foundation for improving and assessing LLM-generated outputs in compliance-critical domains.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decontamination of pollutants present in water, air, and soil through phytoremediation: a critical review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phytoremediation is a technique that uses plants to decontaminate polluted environments, such as soil, water and even air. Plants employ several mechanisms to remove, stabilize or degrade contaminants, depending on the nature of the pollutant and the environmental conditions. The main mechanisms include: phytoextraction, phytodegradation, phytovolatilization, phytostabilization and rhizofiltration. The uptake of heavy metals by plants is influenced by several key factors. Soil characteristics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lacticaseibacillus rhamnosus BELR47 Mitigates Inflammatory Response in a Gardnerella vaginalis-Induced Bacterial Vaginosis Mouse Model via Gut Microbiome Modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, Lacticaseibacillus rhamnosus BELR47 showed the highest lactate production, adhesion to HeLa cells, biofilm formation, and antimicrobial activity against three major bacterial vaginosis (BV)-associated pathogens: Gardnerella vaginalis, Fannyhessea vaginae, and Candida albicans. Moreover, BELR47 exerted anti-inflammatory effects in lipopolysaccharide-induced RAW 264.7 macrophages by suppressing pro-inflammatory cytokine production. In BV-induced mice, oral BELR47 administration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Explainable opportunistic osteoporosis screening from chest X-rays: a retrospective comparison of foundation models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings underscore the necessity of incorporating explainability as a key criterion when selecting deep learning models for opportunistic osteoporosis screening. Furthermore, the proposed framework can be readily extended to other medical tasks, fostering the development of more trustworthy and interpretable AI-assisted screening tools.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase-Selective Growth of Violet Phosphorus Crystals via Sn-Bi Flux]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Violet phosphorus (VP), an allotrope of phosphorus, is a two-dimensional van der Waals layered semiconducting material with a tunable band gap ranging from 1.4 to 2.0 eV. Despite its potential for optoelectronic applications, the scalable synthesis of phase-pure, high-quality VP crystals remains a major challenge due to competition from other phosphorus allotropes during growth. Here, we report a phase-selective synthesis strategy based on a Sn-Bi binary metal flux, enabling the growth of VP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-SNPS2: A Multi-Layered LC-MS/MS Platform Integrating Molecular Networking and Retention Time Prediction for Identifying Controlled and New Psychoactive Substances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of unknown controlled substances poses a significant challenge in forensic and analytical sciences. While liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry (LC-MS/MS) enables identification of compounds through spectral database matching, it remains limited for synthesized analogues not present in existing libraries. To address this gap, we developed AI-SNPS2 (Artificial Intelligence Screener for Narcotic Drugs and New Psychoactive Substances 2), an enhanced version of our previously...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circadian Rhythm: Biological Functions, Diseases, and Therapeutic Targets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circadian rhythms are intrinsic 24-h biological cycles that govern various physiological processes. In addition to the hypothalamic suprachiasmatic nucleus, the circadian system is organized in multiple peripheral tissues, such as the brain, heart, bone, liver, and lung. Emerging evidence suggests that disruptions in these rhythms, which are regulated by a network of clock genes, play pivotal roles in human health. A deeper understanding of the interplay between circadian rhythms and tissue...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medical guidelines for fibrodysplasia ossificans progressiva]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fibrodysplasia ossificans progressiva (FOP) is an ultra-rare genetic condition characterized by congenital malformations of the great toes and progressive heterotopic ossification (HO) in specific anatomic patterns. Present management summarized here is focused on early diagnosis, assiduous avoidance of injury and iatrogenic harm, symptomatic amelioration of painful flare-ups, and optimization of residual function. Twenty-one members of the International Clinical Council on FOP (ICC) and seven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measurement of twenty-one serum steroid profiles by UPLC-MS/MS for the diagnosis and monitoring of congenital adrenal hyperplasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our UPLC-MS/MS method provides a sensitive and specific tool for the comprehensive profiling of adrenal steroids, offering improved diagnostic accuracy for CAH. Its ability to differentiate between various CAH subtypes highlights its potential clinical utility in both diagnosis and monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utility of the bright and dark personality inventory in assessing personality pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The BDPI's Dark 5 may offer complementary value to existing trait-based assessments by capturing additional expressions of maladaptive personality traits. Further research should validate these findings in clinical populations and explore the measurement of Anankastia-relevant constructs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prosthetic reconstruction of a fractured canine tooth in a dog using post and core]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 6-year-old spayed female poodle dog weighing 5 kg was presented with a fractured right upper canine tooth (#104). Dental examination using an intraoral camera and radiography confirmed a tooth fracture with an exposed pulp, resulting in the loss of ~2/3 of the crown. Tooth #104 was diagnosed with a complicated crown fracture. Consequently, root canal therapy was undertaken, involving root canal preparation with hand files and subsequent canal filling with appropriate filling materials. After...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of an Electronic Constant-Speed Injector in Reducing Pain of Local Anesthesia in a Scalp Procedure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The electronic constant-speed injector effectively reduced pain associated with local anesthetic infiltration compared with the manual injection method.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences of COVID-19 dedicated ward nurse managers in South Korea: a qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nurse managers in COVID-19 dedicated wards need to establish rules and guidelines within the ward to prevent and reduce confusion. They also need to collaborate with hospital administrators to ensure that staff nurses assigned to COVID-19 dedicated wards receive relevant training and are assigned accordingly. Intervention programs for COVID-19 dedicated ward nurse managers need to be developed and implemented. Policymakers need to develop government-level policies and systems to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health literacy and adherence to physical activity guidelines among adults with hypertension: evidence from a Korean National Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Health literacy is a key determinant of physical activity in adults with hypertension. Enhancing health literacy may improve hypertension management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Divided by discipline? A systematic literature review on the quantification of online sexism and misogyny using a semi-automated approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several computational tools have been developed to detect and identify sexism, misogyny, and gender-based hate speech, particularly on online platforms. These tools draw on insights from both social science and computer science. Given the increasing concern over gender-based discrimination in digital spaces, the contested definitions and measurements of sexism, and the rise of interdisciplinary efforts to understand its online manifestations, a systematic literature review is essential for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights into research trends on recurrent laryngeal nerve damage in thyroid surgery (1974-2024): a bibliometric review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This bibliometric analysis underscores the increasing global research focus on RLN injury in thyroidectomy, highlighting the need for enhanced surgical techniques, international collaboration, and standardized practices to improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pleomorphic adenoma with extensive oncocytic change in the parotid gland: a case report and review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Recognition of this oncocytic variant of PA requires a multidisciplinary diagnostic approach to avoid misdiagnosis and overtreatment. Total parotidectomy with facial nerve preservation provides favorable functional and oncologic outcomes. Awareness of this rare variant and proper diagnostic evaluation are essential for optimal patient management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone morphogenetic protein-2-derived osteogenic peptide promotes bone regeneration via osteoblastogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: OP5, a low-molecular-weight peptide with strong osteogenic potential, may be a viable alternative to BMP-2 for clinical bone regeneration, minimizing BMP2-associated adverse effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature-independent and photocrosslinkable hydrolyzed GelMA with tunable mechanics for biofabrication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermoresponsive and photo-crosslinkable hydrogels are highly desirable for biofabrication; however, conventional gelatin methacryloyl (GelMA) exhibited thermal gelation below 30 °C and high viscosity, restricting its compatibility with concentration-dependent tunability and lower critical solution temperature-type systems. To address these issues, hydrolyzed GelMA (hGelMA) was developed by subjecting GelMA to controlled enzymatic degradation, effectively eliminating thermal gelation while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laying the groundwork for an inter-ministerial One Health response to antimicrobial resistance in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The initiative operationalized the core principles of One Health, i.e., integration, multisectoral collaboration, data sharing, sustainability, and policy integration, while addressing structural gaps in AMR preparedness. Although challenges remain in stewardship, surveillance coverage, and long-term governance, the project provides a durable foundation for the national strategy for future AMR in South Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying key features for determining the patterns of patients with functional dyspepsia using machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Through supervised learning, we identified the most important features for PI. Additionally, we proposed a novel unsupervised learning approach for identifying patterns from the patient data. This study could facilitate clinical decision making as it pertains to patients with FD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contribution of Structural Changes in Cellulose Fibers Induced by Alkali Treatment to Their Nanofibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of this study is to explore the effect of strong alkali pretreatment on manufacturing cellulose nanofibrils (CNFs) with mechanical grinding. The structural change (from cellulose I to cellulose II) and a sharp reduction in the yield of the hemicellulose component (xylose) of cellulose fibers (bleached kraft pulp) were observed after strong NaOH (20 wt %) pretreatment. However, the differences depending on treatment time (1 or 2 h) were not significant. The subsequent mechanical grinding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights into the membrane repair mechanism by the coiled-coil-mediated oligomerization of TRIM72]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[TRIpartite Motif-containing 72 (TRIM72, also known as MG53), a RING-type E3 ubiquitin ligase, is critical for plasma membrane repair. Like other TRIM family proteins, TRIM72 has a conserved architecture comprising RING, B-box, coiled-coil, and C-terminal PRY-SPRY domains. While the coiled-coil domain mediates homo-oligomerization, its specific contribution to the membrane repair machinery remains unclear. In this study, we characterized the structural and dynamic properties of the TRIM72...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional Evaluation of <em>PKD1</em> Intronic Variants by Minigene Assays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Critically Important Cancer Outcomes to Report in Kidney Transplant Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reporting Quality of Randomized Controlled Trials in Antineutrophil Cytoplasmic Autoantibody-Associated Vasculitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although the overall adherence of RCTs in AAV to both CONSORT checklists is good, the reporting of some key items, such as randomization, blinding, adherence to trial protocol, and similarity of interventions is lacking.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Utility of a Multiplex PCR Assay in Detecting Common Mutations of the α-Globin Gene in α-Thalassemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alpha-thalassemia is a hereditary hemoglobin disorder characterized by reduced or absent α-globin gene, and its severity is associated with the number of affected alleles. Several methods are available for detecting α-thalassemia, such as multiplex ligation-dependent probe amplification (MLPA) and PCR-based hybridization strip assay. Multiplex PCR offers a faster, more convenient, and cost-effective alternative. In this study, we aimed to optimize a current PCR-based method for α-thalassemia...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commentary: AI psychosis is not a new threat: Lessons from media-induced delusions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The phenomenon is not new in principle, but interactivity potentially changes the risk profile. Clinically aware LLMs that detect and gently redirect early psychotic ideation, while encouraging professional help seeking, could reduce harm. Design should be guided by therapeutic principles and evidence about current model failures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping the research trends and hotspots of exercise and nutrition in diabetes: a bibliometric and visual analysis (2005-2025)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Over the past two decades, attention to this field has steadily increased, with strong collaboration established among countries, institutions, and journals. Emerging research trends in exercise and nutrition in diabetes are shifting toward a life course-oriented paradigm, personalized self-management support, and more innovative, adaptable intervention formats tailored to accommodate modern lifestyles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The cognitive consequences of fear of falling: assessing the mediating role of social engagement and physical activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Cognitive function is crucial for older adults' independence and quality of life. This study investigated the longitudinal relationship between fear of falling and cognitive function using data from the Korean Longitudinal Study of Ageing. Specifically, it examined whether social engagement (regular informal contact and social activities) and physical activity mediate the impact of fear of falling on cognitive function, informing targeted strategies to mitigate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of reactive oxygen species in the pathogenesis and treatment of endometrial cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reactive oxygen species (ROS) play dual roles in the pathophysiology of endometrial cancer (EC). Oxidative stress induced by ROS can promote the survival and proliferation of cancer cells, whereas excessive accumulation of ROS can lead to various forms of programmed cell death-including ferroptosis and apoptosis-making ROS potential therapeutic targets in cancer treatment. EC is the most common gynecologic malignancy in developed countries, and its global incidence and mortality rates have been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Edible insect larvae as sustainable sources of chitosan: Influence of species and drying method on functional and structural properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chitosan-a biopolymer produced by the deacetylation of chitin-finds numerous applications and is primarily obtained from the byproducts of marine crustacean processing. Given that this production method has numerous limitations, edible insects have drawn considerable attention as an alternative chitosan source. Herein, chitosan was extracted from the larvae of Protaetia brevitarsis, Allomyrina dichotoma, and Tenebrio molitor subjected to hot-air drying and freeze-drying, and its physicochemical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Schiff base crosslinking in biopolymeric food packaging films: Dynamic covalent chemistry for advanced food preservation systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biopolymeric films (BFs) offer sustainable packaging alternatives but face limitations in mechanical strength and moisture resistance. This review explores dynamic covalent chemistry via Schiff base reactions (SBRs) as a transformative strategy to enhance BFs. Crosslinking amino-rich biopolymers (e.g., chitosan, gelatin) with aldehyde donors (e.g., dialdehyde polysaccharides, plant aldehydes) improves film stability, barrier properties, and stimuli-responsive behavior. Plant aldehydes serve dual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prompt engineering for single-best-answer multiple-choice questions in licensing examinations: a narrative review with a case study involving the Korean Medical Licensing Examination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of large language models (LLMs) has generated growing interest in their potential applications for medical assessment and item development. This practice-oriented narrative review examines the potential of LLMs, particularly ChatGPT, for generating and validating single-best-answer multiple-choice questions in health professions licensing examinations, using a Korean Medical Licensing Examination (KMLE)-focused case perspective. We frame LLMs as human-in-the-loop tools rather than...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BiV<sub>1-<em>x</em></sub>O<sub><em>y</em></sub>/Noble Metal Nanoparticle Domains with Reverse Charge Transfer Improves Photoelectrochemical Glycerol to Dihydroxyacetone Conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoelectrochemical glycerol oxidation (PecGO) using a BiVO(4) photoanode is a promising strategy for producing high-value-added dihydroxyacetone (DHA), but the selectivity and efficiency are limited to inferior adsorption and activation ability of secondary hydroxyl groups via surface-exposed Bi atoms. Herein, we report a strong metal-support interaction (SMSI) strategy to enrich the surface Bi atom exposure ratio in a BiVO(4) photoanode, while modulating the Bi p-band center through a reverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of sleep duration on the incidence of new-onset chronic kidney disease in community-dwelling adults: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This research identified a relationship between the amount of sleep and CKD in Korean adults. Maintaining an appropriate sleep duration of 7-8 h/day is important for preventing new-onset CKD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Anticancer Treatment Efficacy With Lycopene: A Comprehensive Review of Clinical and Preclinical Evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lycopene (LYP), the red pigment found in tomatoes, is a non-provitamin A carotenoid recognized for its biological significance and anticancer potential. Beyond its direct anticancer effects, LYP has been shown to enhance the efficacy of various anticancer agents when used in combination. Herein, we have conducted a literature survey using PubMed and ClinicalTrials.gov databases, following the Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses (PRISMA) guidelines, to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liposomal Hyaluronic Acid Enhances Skin Permeation and Hydration: Evidence from In Vitro, Ex Vivo, and In Vivo Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Topically applied hyaluronic acid (HA) hydrates the skin without efficient penetration. This study compared the penetration efficiency of liposomal hyaluronic acid (LPS-HA) against that of conventional HA across different models. Dynamic light scattering revealed that particles of LPS-HA (226.1 nm, PDI 0.2898) were smaller than those of HA (798.4 nm, PDI 0.8709). In Strat-M® membrane assays, permeability over 24 h was higher with LPS-HA (629.37 ± 103.26%) than that of HA (508.04 ± 93.80%;...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AOSNP-ADAPTR resource level-based recommendations on practical diagnostic strategies for WHO CNS5 adult-type diffuse gliomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fifth edition of the WHO classification of CNS Tumors (WHO CNS5) has revised the diagnostic and grading criteria for Adult-type Diffuse Gliomas (ADGs) by integrating molecular parameters with histologic features. Conducting molecular testing for most ADGs is now crucial in fulfilling the WHO CNS5 diagnostic criteria. However, due to additional costs and technical barriers, implementing molecular diagnostics is often not feasible in Low-Income Countries (LICs) and Lower Middle-Income...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunometabolic Crosstalk in Adipose Tissue Remodeling: Mechanisms and Therapeutic Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adipose tissue is a dynamic immunometabolic organ whose cellular heterogeneity and functional plasticity are central to systemic energy balance and metabolic regulation. Disruption of immune-adipocyte interactions is closely linked to the development of obesity and related metabolic disorders. In this review, we summarize current advances in understanding of the immune landscape in adipose tissue, with an emphasis on the distinct roles of immune cell subsets. Recent approaches including global...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ligand-Substrate Self-Sorting in Silica-Encased Rh-Nanopetals as Model Catalyst for Hydroformylation of Arylalkenes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Self-regulated ligand-substrate interaction with the metal center is fundamental to enzymes and homogeneous complexes, yet similar phenomena in heterogeneous systems remain underexplored. Simultaneous control of reactivity and selectivity becomes challenging due to the competitive molecular-adsorption-mediated blocking of reaction-sites. Here, we address this dichotomy by introducing the concept of ligand-substrate self-sorting (LSS) in a silica-encased Rh-nanopetals (Rh-NPLs) model platform for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, POSTECH, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selective and Long-Term Stable Ammonia Electrolysis Using Pt-WO<sub>x</sub> Catalysts with Suppressed NO<sub>x</sub> Formation and Enhanced Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ammonia electrolysis presents a promising strategy for low-voltage hydrogen production; however, its advancement is impeded by limitations in electrocatalyst performance due to sluggish reaction kinetics and deactivation caused by strongly adsorbed nitrogen-containing intermediates. In this study, a photodeposited Pt on tungsten suboxide (WO(x)) nanowires (Pt-WO(x) (P)) is introduced as a bifunctional electrocatalyst for ammonia electrolysis. The photodeposition induces strong metal-support...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature-Driven Abrupt Changes in the Electronic Structure of 2D Si<sub>2</sub>Te<sub>3</sub>: A First-Principles Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Si(2)Te(3) has emerged as a promising two-dimensional material due to its compatibility with existing silicon-based semiconductor processes, its intrinsic p-type conductivity, which is rare among 2D materials, and its potential for diverse applications. Recently, experimental studies have suggested that Si(2)Te(3) exhibits temperature-dependent changes in its optical and electrical properties. Although these observations are potentially linked to changes in Si-Si dimer orientations, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scale-Up Synthesis of Porous Silicon Structures by Rotary Magnesiothermic Reduction of Silica for Advanced Energy Storage Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 1L-scale dynamic magnesiothermic reduction (DMR) of nonporous silica (1.8 μm in diameter) was conducted using a rotary reactor system to produce porous silicon (pSi) particles for lithium-ion battery (LIB) anodes. The effects of the NaCl (heat scavenger)-to-silica weight ratio (0.8, 3.0, 5.0, and 10.0) were systematically investigated in terms of (i) exothermic reduction heats (monitored in situ and estimated by enthalpy balance), (ii) porosity development in the resulting pSi particles, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of eFOV CT distortion on surface-guided radiotherapy registration: Phantom-based analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This phantom study demonstrated that eFOV reconstruction can compromise SGRT alignment accuracy, particularly when beam centers are located near distorted regions. Alignment remained within clinically acceptable limits when reference points were sufficiently distant from distortion. These findings provide important baseline data under controlled conditions, and clinical validation with patient cohorts is warranted to confirm their generalizability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zoonotic disease detection at the point-of-care: the best of RPA and CRISPR-Cas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biosensors are increasingly crucial in detecting biomarkers for emerging zoonotic diseases at the point-of-care (POC). This imminence was recently highlighted by the deficient response during the SARS-CoV-2 pandemic. While polymerase chain reaction (PCR) is the common nucleic acid (NA) testing method for zoonotic diseases in laboratory settings, it is impractical for the POC settings due to the equipment-related cost, lack of portability and user-friendliness. Recent advances in NA amplification...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic impact of pleural lavage cytology in EGFR-stratified resected non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PLC positivity was identified as an independent prognostic indicator of RFS and indicated biological aggressiveness that approximated stage III disease in terms of early recurrence. PLC-positive, EGFR-mutated patients might benefit from adjuvant osimertinib therapy, as supported by ADAURA findings, although prospective validation is needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-year effectiveness and safety in young children aged 2-6 years with type 1 diabetes using an automated insulin delivery system: A real-world prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: One-year use of an AID system in young children with T1D was safe and associated with improved glycaemic management and reduced parental burden, with limited impact on time in hypoglycaemia and related parental fear.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eight decades of research on the long-term health effects of radiation in atomic bomb survivors and their offspring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This year marks the 80th anniversary of the atomic bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. Over the past eight decades, large-scale cohort studies of atomic bomb survivors and their offspring conducted by the Radiation Effects Research Foundation and its predecessor, the Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission, have provided critical insights into the long-term health effects of radiation exposure. Key findings include early identification of radiation-associated leukemia, as well as excess risks of all...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[History and current developments of RERF dosimetry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Studies of the health effects among Japanese atomic bomb survivors, including radiation-induced carcinogenesis, necessitate accurate radiation dose estimates for individual survivors from the Hiroshima and Nagasaki bombings. Efforts toward this goal commenced shortly after the bombings in 1945, resulting in a series of dosimetry systems developed over the years to calculate survivor doses for a roster currently numbering 135 852 survivors. These systems estimate a survivor's dose based on data...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors associated with taxane-associated acute pain syndrome in pancreatic cancer patients receiving gemcitabine and nab-paclitaxel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study identified BMI ≥ 25 kg/m² as a risk factor and baseline use of mild analgesics as a preventive factor for T-APS development in a real-world GEM + nab-PTX regimen for pancreatic cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Author Reflections: Technical Challenges and Solutions in Pancreaticoduodenectomy After Perihilar Cholangiocarcinoma Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41144133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current Surgical Management for Acral Melanoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Melanoma is one of the most aggressive and lethal forms of skin cancer, with acral melanoma (AM) associated with the poorer prognosis among melanoma subtypes. Historically, it was considered that more extensive surgery could prolong survival; however, multiple randomized trials have demonstrated that greater surgical intervention does not improve survival. Over the past few years, novel therapeutic agents including immune checkpoint inhibitors and molecular-targeted drugs have remarkably...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polygenic risk scores in healthcare contexts: what's the scope? An interview study of European healthcare providers and researchers' perspectives on ethical challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the last decade, substantial research efforts have started worldwide to foster the clinical translation of Polygenic Risk Scores (PRS). Understanding the views of key relevant groups becomes timely to critically inform the socio-ethical debate, impact future health policy, and support the development of guidelines for best practices in healthcare contexts. We performed 26 in-depth semi-structured interviews to investigate the perspectives of European researchers and healthcare providers from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author's response to letter to editor "Comment on: Effectiveness of treatment initiation for secondary fracture prevention in the older population: Japanese Bone-fracture Osteoporosis in Late-stage population Database study (J-BOLD)-emulation of a randomized target trial" (OSIN-D-25-01923)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cyclo-glycylproline, a food-derived diketopiperazine, inhibits bacterial indole production: Implications for diabetic nephropathy prevention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic nephropathy is a kidney disease aggravated by the uremic toxin indoxyl sulfate, which is produced from indole by the gut microbiota. Targeting the bacterial enzyme tryptophan indole-lyase (TIL), which produces indole from L-tryptophan, could be a promising therapeutic strategy. This study investigates diketopiperazines, particularly cyclo-glycylproline [cyclo(Gly-Pro)], as potential TIL inhibitors. Cyclo(Gly-Pro) and other diketopiperazines moderately inhibited indole production from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wet-State Densification of Ionically Cross-Linked Nanocellulose Gels for Producing Stiff Porous Structures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cellulose nanofiber (CNF) aerogels can offer both transparency and thermal insulation but typically suffer from mechanical weakness. Here, we report a wet-state densification strategy to overcome this limitation. Flowable CNF dispersions were converted to self-supporting hydrogels via inter-CNF cross-linking with zirconium ions (Zr^(4+)), followed by uniaxial compression and supercritical drying to produce aerogels with bulk densities of 25-95 mg cm^(-3). The compression induced a uniform...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AFragmenter: schema-free, tuneable protein domain segmentation for AlphaFold protein structures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SUMMARY: Protein domain segmentation is a crucial aspect of understanding protein functions and interactions, and it is vital for protein modelling exercises and evolutionary studies. Current segmentation methods often rely on predefined classification schemes, leading to inconsistencies and biases. AFragmenter provides a schema-free and tuneable approach to protein domain segmentation based on network analysis of AlphaFold-predicted structures. Utilizing Predicted Aligned Error values,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput synthesis of multi-element alloy nanoparticles using solvothermal continuous-flow reactor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-throughput synthesis of multi-element alloy nanoparticles (MEA NPs) is essential for accelerating the discovery of advanced materials with complex compositions. Herein, we developed an automated continuous-flow reactor system capable of synthesising a wide variety of MEA NPs under controlled solvothermal conditions (up to 400 °C and 35 MPa). The system demonstrates a high screening throughput, capable of preparing up to 20 distinct samples in a single, automated run, with each synthesis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Myosin XI-1 Mediates Salt Tolerance through a Na+ Transport Pathway in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salt stress significantly affects plant growth and productivity; therefore, it is important to understand the molecular mechanisms underlying salt tolerance. Myosin XI, a primary driver of intracellular trafficking and organelle movement in plant cells, has recently been implicated in abiotic stress responses. However, their specific roles in salt tolerance remain unclear. In this study, we demonstrate that the expression of Arabidopsis myosin XI isoforms AtXI-K, AtXI-2, and AtXI-1 is induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Gamification on Task Engagement During an Eye-Tracking Test Battery in 5-Year-Old Children Born Preterm: Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the potential of serious games in eye-tracking-based cognitive assessments for 5-year-old children born preterm. Specifically, gamification might reduce missing values and increase participant engagement, leading to higher retention rates and more effective tests, without significantly lengthening testing procedures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterogeneity in Histological Evaluation of Microscopic Colitis in Randomized Clinical Trials: An Umbrella Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This umbrella review highlights the heterogeneity in the definitions of histological outcomes in MC RCTs. The summarized evidence will support ongoing efforts to develop consensus definitions for histological outcomes in order to facilitate clinical trials of medical therapies for MC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry-based profiling of phosphoinositide: advances, challenges, and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phosphoinositides (PIPs), the phosphorylated derivatives of phosphatidylinositol (PI), are low-abundance yet critical components of eukaryotic membranes. They play pivotal roles in a wide array of cellular processes, including signal transduction, membrane trafficking, and cell motility. The seven PIP subclasses, generated by phosphorylation at the 3-, 4-, and 5-positions of the inositol ring, are tightly regulated in both spatial and temporal contexts. Dysregulation of PIP metabolism is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flagella of <em>Aeromonas veronii</em> biotype sobria promote biofilm formation by biofilm-derived outer membrane vesicles (bOMVs)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aeromonas veronii biotype sobria is a gram-negative rod-shaped bacterium commonly found in various water sources. A. veronii sobria can form biofilms and has been implicated in sporadic infections associated with medical devices like catheters. Previous studies have noted that biofilm-derived outer membrane vesicles (bOMVs) can enhance biofilm formation, though the impact varies across different strains. It remains uncertain whether these variances are attributable to bacterial characteristics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-Activity Relationships of Azaquinazolinone Derivatives as <sup>18</sup>F-Labeled PET Probes Targeting Ghrelin Receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ghrelin receptor (GHSR) is expressed in various organs including the brain, pancreas, stomach, and intestine, and is involved in many physiological functions. In vivo imaging of GHSR with positron emission tomography (PET) is expected to contribute to elucidation of the functions and pathophysiology of ghrelin-related diseases. In the present study, to develop novel PET probes targeting GHSR, we newly designed and synthesized 14 azaquinazolinone derivatives and evaluated their utility. Among...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystal engineering enables room-temperature triplet-DNP in cocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the crystal engineering of cocrystalline polarization matrices for triplet-dynamic nuclear polarization at room temperature. Cocrystals were designed using nicotinamide as a hydrogen bonding coformer to enable the triplet-DNP of aliphatic dicarboxylic acids. The rigid molecular frameworks formed through controlled hydrogen-bonding and π-π interactions maintain sufficiently long T(1) values for spin diffusion, leading to room-temperature triplet-DNP. This crystal engineering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient increase in skeletal-related events after discontinuation of high-dose denosumab in cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SREs increased significantly 6-15 months after high-dose denosumab discontinuation. Elevated ALP was associated with post-discontinuation SREs. These findings emphasize that discontinuation contributes to SRE risk, possibly via rebound bone resorption, and underscore the importance of continuation of therapy whenever possible.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined statistical-biophysical modeling links ion channel genes to physiology of cortical neuron types]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neurons have classically been characterized by their anatomy, electrophysiology, and molecular markers. More recently, single-cell transcriptomics has enabled an increasingly fine genetically defined taxonomy of cortical cell types, but the link between the gene expression of individual cell types and their physiological and anatomical properties remains poorly understood. Here, we develop a hybrid modeling approach to bridge this gap: our approach combines statistical and mechanistic models to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry-based analysis of rheumatoid factor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Rheumatoid factor (RF) are autoantibodies that are found in approximately two thirds of patients with rheumatoid arthritis, a chronic autoimmune disease characterized by potentially destructive inflammation of the joints. RF consists of polyclonal antibodies targeting the Fc part of immunoglobulin G. Despite its clinical relevance, RF is not specific for RA, and conventional assays for RF detection, predominantly solid-phase tests detecting IgM RF, suffer from poor harmonization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unmet supportive care needs among head and neck cancer survivors beyond 5 years after diagnosis: a multinational cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: This study investigates unmet supportive care needs (SCNs) among head and neck cancer (HNC) survivors beyond 5 years after diagnosis and examines the association with sociodemographic, clinical and lifestyle factors, and differences in European and non-European regions and healthcare systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening and machine learning-based prediction of translation-enhancing peptides that reduce ribosomal stalling in <em>Escherichia coli</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We previously reported that the nascent SKIK peptide enhances translation and alleviates ribosomal stalling caused by arrest peptides (APs) such as SecM and polyproline when positioned immediately upstream of the APs in both Escherichia coli in vivo and in vitro translation systems. In this study, we conducted a comprehensive screening of translation-enhancing peptides (TEPs) using a randomized artificial tetrapeptide library. The screening focused on the ability of the peptides to suppress SecM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primed human pluripotent stem cell-derived blastocyst-like cell aggregates with partial lineage specification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This work introduces a more accessible platform for generating human blastocyst-like cell aggregates from primed hPSCs, broadening their utility for investigating early development events. Insights gained from blastocyst-like cell aggregates have the potential to advance the modelling of early-onset diseases, drive innovations in regenerative therapies, and contribute to the development of assisted reproductive technologies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of permeability in deep tissue capillaries using a new method reflects the nutrient supply status in a healthy heart]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We have developed a method to assess capillary permeability in deep tissue. This research will improve our understanding of how capillaries exchange substances and support tissue function. This new method will not only provide new insights into studies of cardiac disease risk and sex differences, but also assist in developing more advanced in vitro models. It will further aid in refining the best cell transplantation techniques.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Muscle-tendon properties assessed by three-dimensional ultrasound in clinically well-performing clubfoot patients treated with the Ponseti method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Clubfoot is a congenital birth defect affecting musculoskeletal tissues of the affected lower legs, resulting in the typical appearance and changes in muscle-tendon properties. These properties change during development due to growth and activity, but how these properties differ across ages in clubfoot remains not fully understood. This study aimed to describe plantarflexor muscle-tendon volumes between affected and unaffected legs in unilateral clubfoot patients and explore the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Technical success and initial clinical outcome of partial frozen elephant trunk in various aortic arch pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The clinical outcomes of total arch replacement using the partial FET technique were satisfactory. However, surgeons must exercise caution when employing this method for chronic aortic dissection due to its weak radial and spring back forces.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of prehospital pupillary diameter with return of spontaneous circulation and neurological outcome after out-of-hospital cardiac arrest: A multicenter retrospective analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prehospital pupillary diameter is independently associated with both ROSC and 30-day neurological outcome. Although extreme dilation (≥7-8 mm) provides a highly specific marker of futility, low sensitivity precludes its use as a stand-alone criterion. Pupillary assessment may nonetheless contribute, in combination with other prehospital indicators, to a multimodal framework for early decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Home-Based sensing of the nervous system with clinical neurophysiology technologies: IFCN handbook chapter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Future advancements are expected with new generations of wearable systems capable of providing long-term monitoring with minimal maintenance. Beyond epilepsy and sleep disorders, home-based technologies are also being investigated in other neurological diseases including movement disorders and neurodegenerative diseases showing the expanding scope of home-based technologies in neurology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between positive preadmission screening and COVID-19 community transmission: A retrospective observational study during an emergent novel infectious disease pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: After COVID-19 emerged, hospitals adopted preadmission screening to detect asymptomatic cases and avert nosocomial outbreaks; whether such clinical screening should be routine policy remains debated and has not been quantified in Japan.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Thermoplastic Materials Using Cellulose Acetate as a Backbone via Melt Kneading Extrusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To develop a highly biomass-based thermoplastic resin using cellulose acetate (CA) derived from woody biomass as the base material, cellulose acetate-graft-polylactic acid (CA-g-PLA) composites were successfully synthesized by a transesterification reaction through the melt kneading method using 2-ethylhexanoic acid tin-(II) as a catalyst. Various characterization methods, such as Fourier-transform infrared spectroscopy (FTIR), proton nuclear magnetic resonance (¹H NMR), differential scanning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanism of Action and Anti-Inflammatory Activity of Pestalotioquinol A, a Fungus-Derived Cytoprotective Compound]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pestalotioquinol A (pesA) is a novel cytoprotective natural compound previously discovered among Pestalotiopsis microspora metabolites. PesA protects PC12 cells against cell death induced by a peroxynitrite donor, a reactive nitrogen species (RNS). In this study, we analyzed the mechanism of action of pesA and aimed to identify its target proteins. We revealed that the cytoprotective activity of pesA was specific to RNS, such as peroxynitrite and nitric oxide. A cellular thermal shift assay...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alteration of Coal Fly Ash Induced by Aging Treatment: Insights from Mineral Quantification Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mineral composition of coal fly ash (FA) subjected to an aging treatment was analyzed using mineral liberation analysis (MLA) to elucidate the alteration behavior of FA, including changes in the leaching behavior of toxic elements such as B, As, and Se. Three types of FA generated from a coal-fired power plant in Japan, with initial pH values of 4, 9, and 12, were subjected to leaching experiments. These FA samples exhibited different alteration behaviors depending on their initial pH. FA1,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced isoprenoid production in <em>Escherichia coli</em> cells harboring the archaeal mevalonate pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial production of isoprenoids has attracted interest as a white biotechnology approach that yields valuable compounds, such as medicinal, biofuel, and sustainable industrial materials. Enhancement of isoprenoid production in microbial cells has been achieved through metabolic engineering, usually by exploiting one of the biosynthetic pathways supplying the precursors for isoprenoids, i.e., isopentenyl diphosphate and dimethylallyl diphosphate. The pathways used include the naturally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Andexanet alfa-induced heparin resistance during percutaneous coronary intervention for ST-elevation myocardial infarction: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Andexanet alfa is a recombinant modified factor Xa decoy protein used to reverse the anticoagulant effects of direct oral factor Xa inhibitors, including apixaban, rivaroxaban, and edoxaban. While effective in controlling life-threatening bleeding, it may induce heparin resistance, which complicates anticoagulation during procedures requiring urgent revascularization. Its potential to cause significant heparin resistance during percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI) has been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling Transmembrane 6 Superfamily Member 2 p.Glu167Lys-associated Steatotic Liver Disease Using Androgen-treated Human Induced Pluripotent Stem Cell-derived Hepatocyte-like Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We report an improved human hepatocyte differentiation model to investigate metabolic dysfunction with functional VLDL secretory profiles influenced by TM6SF2 gene variant. Our combinatorial analysis of in vitro and human data indicates that male testosterone modifies the effect of E167K on hepatic steatosis but not insulin sensitivity. These data support the hypothesis that male-predominant T2D in E167K carriers is not causative but rather a consequence of persistent steatosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proliferative Cell Targeting and Epithelial Cell Turnover Fuels Hepatitis E Virus Replication in Human Intestinal Enteroids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Overall, we established a robust HEV-HIE model that yields high titers of infectious nonenveloped virions. Proliferative cells and the fast intestinal epithelial cell turnover are important features that facilitate efficient HEV replication, and likely also its dissemination. This study suggests that the gut is an HEV reservoir, capable of producing some of the nonenveloped HEV shed in the feces.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring anti-cancer activities of epidermal growth factor-immobilized polymeric nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cytotoxic agents targeting the epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR) exhibit significant potential for cancer therapy as EGFR is overexpressed in various cancers. As alternatives to conventional EGFR inhibitors (EGFRi), which exert side effects on non-cancer cells, EGF-immobilized gold nanoparticles exhibit selective cytotoxicity in EGFR-overexpressing cancer cells by locally enhancing EGFR activation and modulating signal transduction through a signal condensation mechanism. However,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research priorities on physical-mental comorbidity in children and adolescents: an international consensus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Physical-mental comorbidity in children and adolescents is an emerging global health concern, yet research remains fragmented and lacks a coordinated agenda. We conducted a global priority setting exercise using the Child Health and Nutrition Research Initiative method. A total of 134 research ideas were scored by 45 experts against five criteria: answerability, effectiveness, potential for paradigm shift, potential for translation and implementation, and impact on equity. The highest-ranked...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Micro-photoluminescence spectroscopy of detonation nanodiamonds containing germanium-vacancy centres]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A germanium-vacancy (GeV) centre in nanodiamond is a promising candidate for bright single-photon emitters, fluorescence labelling and quantum sensing due to its narrow zero-phonon line (ZPL) and large Debye-Waller factor. Recently, the GeV centre-containing nanodiamond (GeV-ND) was fabricated by a detonation process, which provides a scalable method capable of producing large quantities of ND particles. However, the optical properties of the GeV-ND at the single-particle level have not been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Human Intestinal Fluids after the Administration of a Solid Meal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Most available data on the composition and solubilizing properties of postprandial human intestinal fluid (HIF) are derived from studies involving liquid meals. These data inform the development of simulated intestinal fluids, widely used in in vitro assays for predicting intestinal drug behavior. However, the typical human diet primarily consists of solid meals, and the physical form of food has been shown to influence gastrointestinal transit and digestion, thereby affecting drug disposition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superior Antithrombogenic Syndiotactic Poly(Substituted Methylene) with Densely Packed Methoxyethyl Ends of Highly Extended Side Chains at the Solid Film Surface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A syndiotactic poly(substituted methylene) (st-PM) featuring (2-methoxyethoxy)carbonyl side chains (st-PMECM) exhibited considerably superior antithrombogenicity compared to a typical conventional antithrombogenic polyacrylate comprising the same side chain (i.e., poly(2-methoxyethyl acrylate); PMEA). The number of adherent platelets on the surface of the st-PMECM films was 0.8 × 10³ mm^(-2), which was one-fourth of that on the PMEA films (3.2 × 10³ mm^(-2)), and 75% of these platelets were in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genotype-guided dual antiplatelet therapy in minor stroke or transient ischemic attack with metabolic syndrome: A post hoc analysis of CHANCE-2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among CYP2C19 LOF carriers with minor stroke or TIA, patients with MetS received more clinical benefit from TIC-ASA versus CLO-ASA compared to those with non-MetS. Registry: ClinicalTrials.gov, TRN: NCT04078737.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coarse-Graining Self-Assembly by the Stochastic Landscape Method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inferring the dynamics of many-body stochastic systems from data remains a fundamental challenge in statistical physics, particularly when models must provide both predictive power and physical interpretability. Nonequilibrium self-assembly, where molecular components are driven to form ordered structures from disordered building blocks, is a prime example, central to nanotechnology, material science, and biology. Markov state models (MSMs) have emerged as a powerful framework for representing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk reduction and precision prevention across the Alzheimer's disease continuum: a systematic review of clinical trials combining multidomain lifestyle interventions and pharmacological or nutraceutical approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To effectively combat dementia onset and progression, lifestyle-based interventions targeting multiple risk factors and disease mechanisms through a multidomain approach - tailored and implemented early in the disease process - have emerged as promising. Electronic databases and relevant websites (clinicaltrials.gov, euclinicaltrials.eu, PubMed and EMBASE) were systematically searched for randomized controlled trials (RCTs) testing the combination of multidomain lifestyle and pharmacological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role for artificial intelligence in identifying combination therapies for Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite substantial investment in biomedical and pharmaceutical research over the past two decades, the global prevalence of Alzheimer's disease (AD) and AD-related dementias (AD/ADRD) is still rising. This underscores the significant unmet need for identifying effective disease-modifying therapies. Here, we provide a critical perspective on the application of data science and artificial intelligence (AI) to the rational design of drug combinations in AD and ADRD, addressing their potential to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Add-on combination therapy with monoclonal antibodies: Implications for drug development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Three anti-amyloid monoclonal antibodies (MABs) including aducanumab, lecanemab, and donanemab have been approved by the FDA and lecanemab and donanemab are available in the US market and a variety of other national markets. The increasing use of anti-amyloid MABs to treat early AD will require that development of novel agents occur as add-on treatment to MABs. There is limited experience with add-on therapy to anti-amyloid agents. In most cases, it is prudent to initiate novel agents after at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alzheimer Combination Therapies: Overview and Scenarios]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Progress in understanding the complexity of Alzheimer's disease informs the search for combination therapies that can successfully prevent or substantially slow the progression of the disease. Anti-amyloid monoclonal antibodies are the first approved disease targeted therapies; they slow disease progression by approximately 30 %. Building on these agents in add-on therapies is one avenue to designing combination treatments. Development of combination drugs consisting of two or more novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modified radical nephrectomy in the treatment of pediatric unilateral Wilms' tumor: Emphasizing a template-based regional lymphadenectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The MRN demonstrated safety and feasibility in the surgical treatment of pediatric uWT. It enables LN sampling from all relevant draining stations and avoids the limitations of random sampling. However, these findings require validation in larger, prospective, multicenter studies to determine whether this approach is superior to current practice in improving staging accuracy and patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Periodontal Therapy on Salivary Extracellular Vesicle Cargos: An Exploratory Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This exploratory study demonstrated that NSPT led to clinical improvements accompanied by changes in the composition and cytokine cargo of salivary host EVs. Alterations in salivary host EV sub-populations and cytokine profiles may have potential utility as biomarkers for monitoring treatment outcomes in periodontitis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frontier advances in chimeric antigen receptor T cells and chimeric antigen receptor regulatory T cells therapies for autoimmune diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autoimmune diseases (AID) are disorders in which the immune system mistakenly attacks the body's own tissues. However, current immunosuppressive therapies seldom achieve durable, drug-free remission, indicating the urgent need for therapeutic strategies that are both more precise and longer-lasting. Chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) -T cells are generated by genetically engineering T cells to specifically recognize and kill cells that express particular antigens, thereby providing a novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical analysis of six eosinophilia cases with Löeffler endocarditis as the main clinical feature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To improve the understanding of Löeffler endocarditis, we retrospectively analyzed six patients with eosinophilia, predominantly characterized by Löeffler endocarditis, who were treated at the First Affiliated Hospital of Soochow University from January 2019 to October 2024. Among the 6 patients, 5 were male, with a median age of 45.5 years (31-77 years). All patients demonstrated increased white blood cell count and eosinophil count in peripheral blood. Clinical symptoms and imaging examination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Renal response and prognosis of newly diagnosed patients with multiple myeloma with renal impairment applying VRD and autologous hematopoietic stem cell transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To investigate the feasibility of the bortezomib, lenalidomide, and dexamethasone (VRD) regimen combined with autologous hematopoietic stem cell transplantation (auto-HSCT) in patients with multiple myeloma (MM) and renal impairment, analyze treatment efficacy and renal responses stratified based on renal dysfunction severity, and explore the prognostic significance of early renal response and its affecting factors. Methods: This retrospective study, conducted at the First Affiliated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation for the treatment of BCR::ABL-negative neutrophilic myeloid neoplasms: a clinical analysis of 12 cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To investigate the efficacy and safety of allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation (allo-HSCT) for the treatment of BCR::ABL-negative chronic neutrophilic leukemia (CNL) and MDS/MPN with neutrophilia. Methods: This study retrospectively analyzed 12 cases of CNL and MDS/MPN with neutrophilia that underwent allo-HSCT from March 2017 to June 2024, comprising 7 males and 5 females with a median age of 48 (IQR: 28, 59) years. The 2-year overall survival (OS), disease-free...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput sequencing in identifying somatic hypermutation in immunoglobulin heavy chain variable regions with complex clonal backgrounds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To compare the performance of next-generation sequencing (NGS) and Sanger sequencing in investigating somatic hypermutation (SHM) status of immunoglobulin heavy chain variable region (IGHV) genes. It specifically focuses on identifying key factors contributing to discrepancies between the two methods, particularly under complex clonal backgrounds, to inform optimized strategies for clinical application. Methods: This retrospective analysis included 53 samples, comprising 43 identified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic value of the FS-15 frailty score in patients with myelodysplastic syndromes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To identify the prognostic value of the Revised 15-item Myelodysplastic Syndrome-specific frailty scale (FS-15) in Chinese patients with myelodysplastic syndromes (MDS) . Methods: This retrospective study analyzed 812 patients with newly diagnosed MDS admitted to the Institute of Hematology and Blood Diseases Hospital, Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences, and Peking Union Medical College from August 2016 to June 2023. Patients were assessed using the FS-15 and subsequently categorized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identify the factors associated with treatment-free remission outcomes after imatinib discontinuation in children and adolescent patients with chronic myeloid leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To identify factors influencing treatment-free remission (TFR) outcomes in children and adolescent patients with chronic myeloid leukemia (CML) after imatinib (IM) discontinuation. Methods: This multicenter retrospective study analyzed 36 children and adolescent patients with CML from eight hematology centers in China (December 1, 2016, to September 27, 2024) who discontinued IM therapy with documented post-cessation outcomes. Clinical characteristics and molecular response dynamics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of tibiofemoral component divergence on clinical outcomes in patients receiving mobile-bearing unicompartmental knee arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To investigate the correlation between preoperative tibial tubercle-trochlear groove distance (TT-TG) and postoperative tibiofemoral prosthesis divergence angle (DA) in mobile-bearing unicompartmental knee arthroplasty (MB-UKA) for knee osteoarthritis, and to assess the clinical effect of DA on functional outcomes. Methods: This retrospective study included the consecutive patients undergoing MB-UKA at the Third Hospital of Hebei Medical University from January to December 2023....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-inflammatory therapy for recurrent in-stent restenosis (AI-ISR): study protocol for a prospective, randomised, open-label, multicentre clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Recurrent in-stent restenosis (RISR) remains a major therapeutic challenge in patients undergoing percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI), with a high incidence of repeat revascularisation and increased mortality. Immune-mediated inflammation has been implicated in the pathogenesis of RISR. This trial aims to evaluate the clinical efficacy and safety of two anti-inflammatory strategies-low-dose colchicine and prednisone-on reducing ISR recurrence and cardiovascular events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nicotine consumption and folate insufficiency in pregnancy: a population-based cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tobacco smoking increases the risk of insufficient folate stores among pregnant women. However, healthcare providers should assess the folate status of all pregnant women and consider proactive screening, such as RBC folate testing, complemented by integrated strategies addressing tobacco use and nutritional risk. Proactive screening for smokers should be revisited once the prevalence of insufficient folate stores has been reduced at the population level.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetics of teicoplanin in paediatric patients-A systematic review of current literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Teicoplanin PK in children is highly variable, with target trough levels often not achieved, making universal dosing recommendations challenging. Future studies should define indication-dependent targets. Therapeutic drug monitoring could improve clinical efficacy. Defining unbound exposure and its clinical correlates should be a priority for future research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiomyocyte Nucleoporin 35 regulates pathological cardiac remodeling through Wif1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cardiomyocyte Nup35, via its regulation of Wif1 mRNA transport in cardiomyocytes, alleviates pathological cardiac remodeling. Our study highlights potential therapeutic target in cardiac pathological remodeling.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bringing Back Theorizing Medical Hypotheses to Spine Surgery Research in an Age of Overreliance on Randomized Controlled Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A recalibrated, hybrid evidence ecosystem-combining RCT rigor with systematically evaluated observational science-can better capture the realities of spine surgery, accelerate safe innovation, and keep patient needs at the center of evidence generation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prehabilitation Reimagined as Policy: A Multidimensional Framework to Reduce Pain, Opioid Use, and Surgical Risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Traditional surgical prehabilitation emphasizes biomechanical conditioning. In a pain landscape shaped by opioid exposure, trauma histories, and psychosocial distress, this reductionist approach is insufficient.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus statement on the clinical application of extracorporeal shock wave therapy for diabetic foot ulcers (2025 Edition)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic foot ulcers (DFUs) are among the most severe late-stage complications in patients with diabetes. It is characterized by complex pathogenic factors, challenging treatments, and high rates of disability and mortality. Therefore, DFUs have become a major therapeutic challenge for patients with diabetes. In recent years, extracorporeal shock wave therapy (ESWT) has emerged as a novel modality for promoting the healing of both acute and chronic superficial wounds. An increasing number of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bed-based care as a response to the overdose crisis: an approach to informing and evaluating proposed expansion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[All-perovskite tandem solar cells with dipolar passivation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-radiative recombination loss at the hole transport layer (HTL)/perovskite interface in the narrow-bandgap (NBG) subcell constrains the power-conversion efficiency (PCE) of all-perovskite tandem solar cells ^(1,2). Minimizing charge recombination at the buried interface of lead-tin (Pb-Sn) based NBG perovskite solar cells have proven particularly challenging, as conventional long-chain amine-based passivation strategies often induce carrier transport losses, thereby limiting both the fill...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A matrix-confined molecular layer for perovskite photovoltaic modules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal halide perovskites with remarkable optoelectronic properties have become a competitive candidate for supporting the efficiency progression of photovoltaics. As the latest record on power conversion efficiency (PCE) of research-cells being comparable to the commercialized silicon cells^(1-3), the industrialization of perovskite solar cells (PSCs) is on the horizon^(4,5). Most high-efficiency inverted perovskite solar cells using self-assembled molecules (SAMs) face the challenges due to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multifunctional Injectable Hydrogel Accelerates Hemostasis and Wound Healing via Synergistic Tissue Adhesion, Antimicrobial Activity, and ROS Scavenging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Injectable hydrogels have great potential in wound repair applications due to their simple operation and ability to adapt to irregular wounds. However, the current injectable hydrogels have poor biocompatibility, insufficient hemostatic performance, and low wound healing efficiency, which limit their application in wound repair. In this study, an injectable hydrogel (TS@EP) was constructed through a catalyst-free amide reaction between NHS ester-terminated four-arm poly(ethylene glycol)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251028033751&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>