<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:21:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural polymorphism in bent-core liquid crystals: from helical nanofilaments to heliconical-layered microcylinders with light-responsive properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the self-assembly behavior and light-responsive polymorphism of azobenzene-containing bent-core liquid crystal dimers exhibiting B4 crystal phases. By systematically varying the terminal alkyl chain length, the supramolecular morphology transitions from helical nanofilaments (HNFs) with negative Gaussian curvature to heliconical-layered microcylinders (HLµCs) exhibiting cylindrical curvature. Dimers with short terminal chains form exclusively tightly packed HNFs, while those with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST, Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of a Potent Tat-Binding Antiretroviral Compound Using a Two-Step Screening Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The transcription of the HIV-1 long-terminal repeat (LTR), driven by the viral transactivator Tat, represents a distinct and druggable step in HIV-1 replication. Targeting Tat-mediated transcription is a promising antiretroviral strategy due to its mechanistic distinction from host cell transcription, although specificity remains a challenge due to potential off-target effects. To identify selective inhibitors, a two-step screening approach was employed. A time-resolved fluorescence resonance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection and classification of microplastics in green tea using SERS with gold nanoparticle substrates integrating chemometrics and deep learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Green tea is consumed worldwide for its health-promoting properties, but it remains vulnerable to microplastic contamination during packaging and processing. Microplastics such as polystyrene (PS) and polyethylene terephthalate (PET) pose potential risks to human health and food safety, underscoring the need for effective detection methods. In this study, Surface-Enhanced Raman Scattering (SERS) using gold nanoparticle substrates was applied to detect and classify PS and PET contamination in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long term dataset of Eu isotope ratio of NIST3117a Eu standard solution determined via multi-collector inductively coupled plasma mass spectrometry during 2017-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article provides an update to a previously published data article and associated data set regarding Eu isotope ratio of NIST3117a Eu chemical solution, determined over the period 2017-2024. The Eu isotope ratios were measured via MC-ICP-MS using various Sm isotope pairs -^(147)Sm-^(149)Sm, ^(147)Sm-^(154)Sm, ^(149)Sm-^(154)Sm and ^(150)Sm-^(154)Sm-based on the exponential law over the eight-year period. Measurements were conducted under both wet plasma conditions (using spray chamber) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxidative rearrangement of alkynes to chiral α-arylalkanoic esters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chiral α-arylalkanoic esters, valued as anti-inflammatory agents, are synthesised through an enantioselective oxidative rearrangement of alkynes under green, metal-free conditions. This study achieves this transformation using chiral iodine(iii) reagents with para-toluenesulfonic acid and various alcohols, producing the esters in up to 91% yield and 99% enantiomeric excess. The scope of the reaction particularly includes electron-rich non-terminal arylalkynes. Density functional theory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of oblique lumbar interbody fusion and posterior lumbar interbody fusion for L5-S1 level: clinical and radiological outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: OLIF may offer advantages over PLIF in L5-S1 level interventions, particularly for sagittal alignment restoration and long-term back pain management. Its ability to accommodate larger and more lordotic cages and to provide greater flexibility in cage positioning allows for more patient-specific surgical planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A prospective, single-center longitudinal study on the operational definition of sarcopenia in patients undergoing total knee arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TKA improved physical performance longitudinally, whereas muscle strength and mass did not. Grouping according to the operational definition revealed no postoperative differences in physical performance or muscle strength. The current operational definition of sarcopenia may be unsuitable for patients with severe knee osteoarthritis, as joint pain influences physical performance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroprotective effect of Continentalic acid by targeting NF-κB/Bcl-2 and oxidative stress signaling in traumatic brain injury in male BALB/c mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results demonstrated that CA (50 mg/kg) exhibited neuroprotective activity in TBI by attenuating inflammation, neuronal apoptosis, and oxidative stress.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neoadjuvant gamma knife surgery for metastatic brain tumor: clinical use and impact on leptomeningeal seeding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Indoor Temperature Level and Mental Health Among Community-Dwelling Older Adults: Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings highlight the need to develop evidence-based guidelines to improve mental health by managing indoor temperature levels in the community. Improving housing conditions through policy support could enhance the mental health of community-dwelling older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical performance of the VITEK REVEAL fast antimicrobial susceptibility test within a real-world workflow for gram-negative bacteremia: comparison with QMAC-dRAST and conventional methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fast antimicrobial susceptibility testing (AST) is essential for appropriate antimicrobial therapeutic guidance in patients with bloodstream infections, reducing the time required for optimal treatment. We aimed to evaluate the clinical performance of the VITEK REVEAL (REVEAL), a volatile organic compound-based fast AST system, compared with our already established AST workflow for bloodstream infections. We prospectively collected a total of 107 gram-negative isolates from positive blood...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unbiased microRNA-Disease Association Prediction Using ICD-11 Codes and Negative Sampling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We developed a computational model, called "Unbiased microRNA-disease association predictor (UBMDA)," to predict microRNA-disease associations. UBMDA has two major differences from those reported previously. First, we did not apply a similarity-based feature extraction method, which is the main basis of previous studies. Instead, we used International Classification of Diseases 11th Revision disease codes and microRNA nucleotide sequences as input features. Thus, UBMDA can be applied to newly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Narrative Persuasion by Celebrity Source: The Moderating Role of Involvement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Based on constructs from source credibility and narrative engagement theory, this research examines (a) the mediators or processes whereby celebrity (vs. non-celebrity) sources enhance narrative persuasion and (b) the moderators or conditions under which celebrity (vs. non-celebrity) sources persuade. The study employed a two-group (celebrity vs. non-celebrity) between-subjects experimental design with 360 participants. Results showed that, compared to the non-celebrity source, the celebrity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multicentre prospective phase II study of rituximab combined with bortezomib, lenalidomide and dexamethasone, followed by lenalidomide maintenance (R-VRD) in patients with Waldenström's macroglobulinaemia (KMM1803)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Waldenström's macroglobulinaemia (WM) has heterogeneous clinical features and limited standard therapeutic options. Although rituximab-based combinations and Bruton's tyrosine kinase inhibitors have improved outcomes, challenges like incomplete responses and toxicity remain. This prospective, multicentre, phase II study evaluated the efficacy and safety of rituximab, bortezomib, lenalidomide and dexamethasone (R-VRD) induction therapy, followed by lenalidomide maintenance in patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AA amyloidosis with clinically overt cardiac involvement confirmed by amyloid A deposition in aortic valve fibroelastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phenoxysulfonyl azide: a new diazo-transfer reagent for the metal-free conversion of amines to azides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phenoxysulfonyl azide (PSA, 1) was synthesized from 1,1'-sulfonylbis(2-methyl-1H-imidazole) (2) and studied for its diazo-transfer reactivity. The reaction with 1 was found to convert primary amines 3 into their corresponding azides 4, even without a metal catalyst. Accordingly, PSA is a new diazo-transfer reagent for the metal-free conversion of amines to azides, thereby facilitating the preparation of organic azides from biomolecules.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multidimensional housing poverty, physical activity, and depression among young single-person households in Seoul, South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Multidimensional housing poverty was associated with elevated depression and varying physical activity patterns by sex. Policy efforts should reflect these differential vulnerabilities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and safety of thread embedding acupuncture for facial nerve palsy sequelae: a protocol for a multicenter, assessor-blinded, randomized, controlled clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This randomized controlled trial will assess the effectiveness and safety of thread-embedding acupuncture treatment alongside electroacupuncture for facial nerve palsy, using proper sample sizes and rigorous methodologies to address previous research limitations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Organizational Silence and Related Factors Among Shift Work Nurses in Korea: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Organizational silence is shaped by both individual characteristics and organizational conditions. Workplace bullying not only has a direct effect on organizational silence but also mediates the relationship between leader-member exchange and organizational silence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Hemodynamic Implications of Mitral Annular Calcification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitral annular calcification (MAC) is an inflammatory process that shares characteristics with atherosclerosis and results in calcium deposition in the fibrous ring supporting the mitral valve. It is commonly encountered at older ages and in people with chronic kidney disease. MAC is an important prognostic marker of adverse cardiovascular events and atrial fibrillation, as well as cardiovascular and non-cardiovascular death. When severe it can cause valvular dysfunction including mitral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conservative Treatment With Teriparatide for Symptomatic Incomplete Atypical Femoral Fractures: A Retrospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The result of this study suggests that the conservative treatment with teriparatide injection may be a potentially effective option for patients with SIAFF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biofilm comes back: Controlling regrowth by mitigating the cell-matrix interaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biofilms wield a notorious impact on biological infections and environmental sanitation in daily life. Tremendous efforts have been made to develop antimicrobial agents that effectively kill bacterial cells, but preventing biofilm reformation remains unsolved. For instance, a hydrogen peroxide (H(2)O(2)) and peracetic acid (PAA) mixture can inactivate almost 100 % of Pseudomonas aeruginosa cells in a biofilm within 10 min, but why do cells regrow and recover the biofilm within a day? We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SNUPI: A Computational Framework for Rapid Mechanical Analysis of Structured DNA Assemblies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structural DNA nanotechnology enables the programmable construction of nano- to microscale assemblies with high resolution, yet predicting their mechanical behavior prior to synthesis remains challenging. In this paper, we introduce SNUPI, a computational framework that predicts the shape and mechanical responses of structured DNA assemblies using finite element-based analysis. SNUPI uses design files from caDNAno and performs static analysis, normal-mode analysis, and Langevin dynamics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bee venom-derived phospholipase A<sub>2</sub> modulates microglial activity to promote antidepressant effects in a menopausal mouse model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Bee venom phospholipase A2 (bvPLA2) exhibits therapeutic potential in inflammatory disorders through the modulation of microglial activation, a mechanism implicated in the pathogenesis of depression. However, its effects in the context of menopausal depression remain uncharacterized. This study investigated the antidepressant effects of bvPLA2 and its underlying mechanisms in an ovariectomized (OVX) mouse model subjected to chronic restraint stress.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Affecting Late-Period Retear That Occurs More than 2 Years After Rotator Cuff Repair]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although the incidence was lower than that in the early period after RCR, retears also occurred >2 years after RCR. Compared with early-period retears, DM was significantly associated with late-period retears. In addition, the risk of late-period retear was high among patients who were current smokers and those with uncontrolled DM in the presence of a small-sized ML tear.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective Multicenter Study Comparing Magnetic Resonance Imaging and Ultrasonography for Second Breast Cancer Surveillance in Women With Prior Breast Cancer and Dense Breasts: KBCSG-27 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Surveillance guidelines following breast cancer surgery recommend mammography as the sole imaging modality. However, the accuracy of mammography is low in younger women and in those with dense breast tissue. Additional imaging modalities, such as ultrasonography and magnetic resonance imaging (MRI), may offer diagnostic benefits. This prospective, multicenter study (KBCSG-27) aims to compare the diagnostic performances of mammography, ultrasonography, and MRI for detecting second breast...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Role of Preoperative Axillary Ultrasound for Lymph Node Metastasis and Recurrence in Early Stage Breast Cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preoperative axillary US might help assess lymph node metastasis in clinically node-negative patients. Moreover, US positivity was associated with an increased risk of long-term recurrence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Randomized Trial of Sentinel Node Biopsy Omission After Neoadjuvant Systemic Therapy in Clinically Node-Negative or Selected Node-Positive Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Axillary surgery is increasingly omitted in patients with early-stage breast cancer undergoing upfront surgery, as supported by trials such as SOUND and INSEMA. However, in the neoadjuvant setting, the omission of axillary surgery has only been explored in small single-arm studies involving highly selected patients with confirmed breast pathologic complete response (pCR). The NeoNAUTILUS trial aimed to evaluate the oncologic safety of omitting sentinel lymph node biopsy (SLNB) in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation Between Margin Status and Ipsilateral Breast Tumor Recurrence in Patients With Breast Cancer Undergoing Breast-Conserving Surgery With Whole-Breast Radiation Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: IBTR rates were higher in close and positive margin groups under the 120-degree definition, particularly when superficial and deep margins were excluded. Although positive margins did not always show the highest recurrence, margin status still influenced IBTR risk. Re-excision should be individualized based on imaging, pathology, and clinical judgment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental Study of Umbilical Cord Graft and Established Sling Materials for Frontalis Suspension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Frontalis suspension surgery is the preferred treatment option for patients with poor levator function ptosis. This procedure connects the affected eyelid to the brow using sling material, harnessing the action of the frontalis muscle to elevate the upper eyelid. Various sling materials have been used, most commonly silicone rods and fascia lata. However, both have notable limitations: silicone rods carry a relatively high risk of postoperative inflammation and ptosis recurrence, while fascia...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoconfined Photocatalytic Cascade Reaction in Vinylene-Linked Covalent Organic Frameworks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanoconfined catalysis and cascade reactions taking place in two-dimensional covalent organic frameworks (2D-COFs) hold great promise for tackling the long-standing challenges such as uncontrollable reactive intermediates and low selectivity in aerobic oxidation. Herein, for the first time, a nanoconfined photocatalytic cascade reaction system based on vinylene-linked nitrogen-rich 2D-COFs (N-2D-COFs) have been developed for selective generating oxazole derivatives which are privileged building...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assembly of small silica nanoparticles using lipid-tethered DNA 'bonds']]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-stranded DNA molecules modified with cholesterol functional groups are physically tethered to silica nanoparticles (diameter 25 nm) that are encapsulated in a lipid bilayer. Such tethering increases the azimuthal mobility of the DNA molecules across the nanoparticle surface and enables nonspecific bonding, eliminating the need for specialized surface chemistries (such as silane or thiol ligands). To induce assembly, double-stranded DNA 'bridge' molecules are then added with complementary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-Related Deficits in Executive Function and Their Contribution to Depressive Symptoms in Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Age-related deficits in self-organization/problem-solving significantly contribute to depressive symptoms in older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supramolecular dyes: advancing precision medicine through molecular engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precision medicine is aimed at achieving a more personalized approach tailored to individual characteristics and urgently requires the development of precise diagnostic and therapeutic methods. Small-molecule dyes play indispensable roles in medical imaging and surgery procedures, attracting significant attention regarding disease diagnosis and therapy. However, their widespread utilization for accurate tumor localization and long-term intraoperative imaging remains hindered by their inherent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reconstruction of the nearly complete mitochondrial genome of a Danish isolate of Hymenolepis diminuta (Cyclophyllidea: Hymenolepididae) with extension of the noncoding region]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a nearly complete mitochondrial genome (mitogenome) of Hymenolepis diminuta from a Danish isolate, which was reassembled and comprehensively annotated using whole-genome sequencing data retrieved from the Sequence Read Archive (accession No. ERS056110). Although 2 mitogenomes of H. diminuta have previously been submitted to GenBank (accession No. AP017664, Danish isolate; NC_002767, putative German laboratory strain), the former lacks noncoding regions, while the latter harbors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of intestinal parasites in leopard cat fecal samples using shotgun metagenomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The leopard cat (Prionailurus bengalensis) is a wild felid species that serves as a reservoir of zoonotic parasites. In this study, we investigated intestinal parasite taxa by reanalyzing previously published shotgun metagenomic sequencing data from fecal samples of wild leopard cats using a custom 18S rRNA gene reference database constructed from the NCBI nucleotide database. Among 11 metagenomic samples, 5 parasite species were identified: Toxoplasma gondii, Clonorchis sinensis, Strongyloides...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vaccinia virus expressing MIC8 and AMA1 provides protection against Toxoplasma gondii ME49 infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Toxoplasma gondii is an intracellular protozoan parasite capable of causing chronic infection by forming persistent cysts in the brain. Despite its global burden, no approved vaccine exists. Virus-like particle vaccines expressing microneme protein 8 (MIC8) or apical membrane antigen 1 (AMA1) of T. gondii have previously shown efficacy. In this study, we generated recombinant vaccinia viruses (rVVs) expressing MIC8 and AMA1 and evaluated their efficacy against T. gondii ME49 infection. BALB/c...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catatropis indicus (Digenea: Notocotylidae) from ducks in Indonesia with a brief review of the genus Catatropis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adult notocotylid flukes (Digenea: Notocotylidae) were recovered from the ceca of Pitalah ducks (Anas sp.) in Aceh Province, Indonesia. These flukes were morphologically characterized by a median ventral ridge with 2 lateral rows of ventral papillae and the absence of both a ventral sucker and pharynx, consistent with the characteristics of the genus Catatropis. They exhibited a genital pore located just posterior to the oral sucker, 10-11 pairs of ventral papillae, a deep and multi-lobed ovary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Cyanoarene Photocatalysts to Resolve Deactivation Challenges in Organocatalyzed ATRP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyanoarene-based photocatalysts (PCs) have been widely utilized in organic transformations including photo-mediated controlled radical polymerization (CRP). Despite favorable photophysical and electrochemical properties, these PCs have exhibited limited efficacy in photoinduced organocatalyzed ATRP (O-ATRP). We identified that reduced performance arises from preferential formation of [PC^(•+…)Br^(-)] complexes, which facilitates detrimental back electron transfer (BET), generating bromine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Portable Device for Wound Care: An Electrosprayable Zinc Basic Salt-Tranexamic Acid Nanohybrid System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Portable, point-of-care wound dressings that combine rapid hemostasis with pro-regenerative cues are a clinical priority. We report two handy electrospinning strategies that integrate tranexamic acid-intercalated zinc basic salts (TXA-ZBS, via co-precipitation) with polycaprolactone (PCL) nanofibers: i) embedded (TXA-ZBS/PCL), formed by blending TXA-ZBS into the PCL spinning solution, and ii) surface-coated (TXA-ZBS@PCL), produced by electrospinning TXA-ZBS onto preformed PCL nanofiber mats....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bruceantin and Brusatol: Molecular Insights and Therapeutic Promise of Quassinoids in Cancer Drug Discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer remains a leading cause of mortality worldwide, with treatment resistance posing a major obstacle to effective therapies. Natural compounds, including quassinoids such as bruceantin and brusatol, derived from Brucea javanica (L.) Merr., have demonstrated potential as novel cancer chemopreventive agents. Bruceantin exhibits cytotoxic effects against diverse cancer cell lines, including leukemia, lymphoma, and myeloma, primarily through inhibition of protein synthesis and induction of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carvacrol improves neurological function by inhibiting TRPM7-mediated BBB disruption and hemorrhage after TBI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a real-time tongue motion monitoring system for managing swallowing-induced motion in neck cancer radiation therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Real-time tongue-motion monitoring provides a predictive signal for swallowing onset and can aid management of swallowing-induced motion in head-and-neck radiotherapy. By enabling early detection of swallowing events, the system has the potential to reduce dose-delivery errors and improve treatment accuracy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A prospective cohort study on progestin-primed ovarian stimulation vs. GnRH antagonist in IVF-ICSI cycles: effects on clinical pregnancy and neonatal outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: In assisted reproductive technology, preventing premature ovulation is crucial for achieving successful pregnancy outcomes. The traditional GnRH antagonist protocol is commonly used to suppress the luteinizing hormone (LH) surge, while the progesterone-primed ovarian stimulation (PPOS) protocol has gained attention due to its simplicity, lower cost, and fewer side effects. This study compared the PPOS and GnRH antagonist protocols in frozen embryo transfer (FET) cycles, focusing on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid and aggressive recurrence of pulmonary sarcomatoid carcinoma after curative resection: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pulmonary sarcomatoid carcinoma requires immediate and optimal therapeutic intervention because of its aggressive nature and narrow therapeutic window. In health care systems with limited access to immunotherapy, emphasis must be placed on achieving complete surgical resection and intensive postoperative surveillance. This case highlights the need for health care policy discussions regarding expanded access to immunotherapy for patients with favourable biomarker profiles, as current...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-based prediction of SPPB scores using questionnaires of abilities: findings from the national health and aging trends study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The proposed AI methods enable prediction of SPPB component scores, supporting indirect functional assessment when SPPB testing is not feasible. These tools can help reduce unnecessary clinical burden and cost by guiding SPPB administration decisions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early prediction of liver metastasis in pancreatic cancer using routine clinical data: an externally validated machine learning model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Projection of temperature-related severe injuries under climate change: a nationwide study of South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Association Between Child Abuse and Sleep Problems in Adolescents: Moderated Mediation Effects of Depression and Perceived Teacher Support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the mediating role of depression in the relationship between child abuse and sleep problems, as well as the potential buffering effect of perceived teacher support. A total of 793 adolescents (mean age = 16.50 ± 1.29 years, 53.6% female) were recruited from eight middle schools and seven high schools in South Korea in October 2023. Participants completed self-report questionnaires assessing their experiences of child abuse, depression, sleep problems, and perceived teacher...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonlinear kinematic impacts on nanofluid flow across rough surface with numerical simulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The current study demonstrates the intricate thermo-solutal transportation features of a nanofluid experiencing non-linear kinematics as it flows across a rough porous stretched interface. Previous work has typically been limited to smooth geometries, narrow parameter ranges, and few physical intuitions. However, this paper extends the analysis to include surface roughness, porosity effect, nonlinear stretching and essential physical phenomena like effect of magnetic field, Brownian motion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell genome analysis of a feminizing <em>Wolbachia</em> in <em>Eurema</em> butterflies reveals a shared origin with male-killing <em>Wolbachia</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wolbachia is a ubiquitous endosymbiont in arthropods that is maternally transmitted and affects host reproduction in various ways. Among these, skewing the host sex ratio towards females, either by killing males (male killing) or producing exclusively functional females (feminization or parthenogenesis), is considered advantageous for Wolbachia. In the butterfly Eurema mandarina, individuals harbouring the Wolbachia strain wFem exclusively produce female offspring. This occurs through a two-step...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postmastectomy radiation therapy for autologous breast reconstruction: a systematic review and meta-analysis for the 2022 Japanese Breast Cancer Society Clinical Practice Guideline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PMRT following autologous breast reconstruction was associated with a higher risk of fat necrosis, but not with a significantly increased rate of major complications. With careful patient selection and monitoring, PMRT after autologous breast reconstruction can be considered a safe and acceptable treatment option.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A 10-step guide to standardising patient-reported outcomes data collection in healthcare: insights from the health outcomes observatory (H2O) project on overcoming implementation barriers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Safety and Effectiveness of Fluticasone Furoate/Umeclidinium/Vilanterol in Patients with Asthma: Final Analysis of a Post-Marketing Surveillance in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FF/UMEC/VI was well tolerated and effective in the treatment of patients with asthma in Japan. ADRs were reported in 8.4% of patients and the incidence of CV events was low. No new safety concerns were identified.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A phase 2 study of ibrutinib with venetoclax in Japanese patients with untreated CLL and SLL]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of effective and safe therapies for chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL)/small lymphocytic lymphoma (SLL) in Japan remains a key focus of research. We conducted a phase 2, open-label, multicenter, non-comparative study to evaluate the safety and efficacy of fixed-duration venetoclax plus ibrutinib in 10 patients with previously untreated CLL/SLL (7 CLL/3 SLL). The primary endpoint was the rate of complete remission (CR)/CR with incomplete marrow recovery (CRi) assessed by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Consensus Statement on the management of Vertebral Fractures in CKD stages G4-G5D]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skeletal fragility has long been overlooked by the nephrology community, despite patients with chronic kidney disease (CKD) facing double the risk of hip fracture compared with the general population. Consequently, the term CKD-associated osteoporosis was recently coined to increase awareness. In this context, vertebral fractures are even less studied. Vertebral fractures predict increased fracture risk, and especially in advanced CKD show a strong association with aortic and iliac vascular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electric Field Modulation of Interlayer Coupling via Piezostrain in a Synthetic Antiferromagnet]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Controlling the interlayer exchange coupling (IEC) in synthetic antiferromagnets (SAFs) using an electric field is a promising approach for developing energy-efficient spintronic devices, as it enables magnetization switching without electrical current. In this study, the modulation of the IEC through electric field-induced strain in a Co/Ru/Co SAF on a Pb(Mg(1/3)Nb(2/3))O(3)-PbTiO(3) (PMN-PT) multiferroic heterostructure is demonstrated. It is found that both the IEC and the uniaxial magnetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Translation, Cultural Adaptation, and Validation of the Japanese eHealth Literacy Questionnaire Among Users in a Super-Aged Society: Mixed Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Japanese version of the eHLQ is robust and is likely to be a reliable and effective tool for assessing digital health literacy among Japan's population. There were no notable differences between scores of those aged above and below 65 years, or those with and without chronic disease(s). The findings also suggest that current systems may be tailored to frequent digital health users. The Japanese version of the eHLQ is expected to be used to effectively monitor digital health...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of the drug target of the anti-tuberculosis compound OCT313: phosphotransacetylase is a potential drug target for two anti-mycobacterial agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis (TB) is one of the most common infectious diseases caused by bacteria worldwide. The increasing prevalence of multidrug-resistant TB (MDR-TB) and latent TB infection (LTBI) has intensified the global TB burden. Therefore, the development of new drugs for MDR-TB and LTBI is urgently required. We have reported that the derivative of dithiocarbamate sugar derivative, 2-acetamido-2-deoxy-β-D-glucopyranosyl N,N-dimethyldithiocarbamate (OCT313), exhibits anti-mycobacterial activity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid, point-of-care antigen tests for diagnosis of SARS-CoV-2 infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Accurate rapid diagnostic tests for SARS-CoV-2 infection could help manage the COVID-19 pandemic by potentially increasing access to testing and speed detection of infection, as well as informing clinical and public health management decisions to reduce transmission. Previous iterations of this review provided clear and conclusive evidence of superior test performance in those experiencing possible signs and symptoms of Covid-19. However, test performance in asymptomatic individuals...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perfluoroalkyl Chain-Modified Artificial Viral Capsid for Enhanced Intracellular Delivery of mRNA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Therapeutic mRNA has received significant attention as a new class of nucleic acid-based medicine due to its promising potential toward protein replacement therapy, vaccine development, and genome editing. Unlike DNA-based therapies, which depend on nuclear entry, mRNA works directly in the cytoplasm to produce proteins. Nevertheless, the delivery of large nucleic acids, such as mRNA, remains an unresolved challenge due to their instability, limited cellular uptake, and the cytotoxicity commonly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A frailty-intrinsic capacity index to predict disability in community-dwelling older Japanese adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The novel FR-IC index can predict future disability among community-dwelling older Japanese adults. Integrating IC into frailty assessments provides a more comprehensive measure of aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic characterization of cefotaxime-resistant Proteobacteria isolated from a bat-harboring cave in Zambia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bats are widely recognized as reservoirs of emerging and re-emerging pathogens, and their ecological interactions with humans and livestock present important opportunities for the transmission of infectious agents and antimicrobial resistance (AMR). However, little is known about the occurrence of resistant bacteria in bat-associated environments in Zambia or their potential role in the maintenance of AMR outside clinical and agricultural settings. This study investigated the genomic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics and Outcomes of 1500 Lung Transplantations in the Leuven Lung Transplant Program: Turning Past Lessons Into Tomorrow's Foundations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lung transplantation has become an established life-saving treatment for selected patients with end-stage pulmonary disease. In December 2024, our center reached the milestone of 1,500 lung transplants, providing an opportunity to evaluate long-term trends, outcomes, and challenges. We analyzed donor and recipient demographics, procedural evolution, and graft survival. Contemporary guidelines and consensus recommendations were also reviewed to contextualize current practice and highlight unmet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Marked enhancement of synergistic antioxidative activity of astaxanthin and curcumin by co-encapsulation in a liposomal formulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Natural antioxidants may help prevent oxidative stress-mediated aging. Astaxanthin (Asx) is a powerful antioxidant that has been used in various dietary supplements and cosmetics. Previously, we reported that combination of Asx with tocotrienol (T3) or capsaicin (Cap) exhibited synergistic antioxidative effects; however, the synergistic increase in activity was unremarkable. Herein, we employed curcumin (Cur) to more effectively enhance the antioxidant activity of Asx. The antioxidative activity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of strength training of large muscle groups on quality of life]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Muscle-strengthening activities reduce the risk of various diseases and promote overall health. Physical activities targeting large muscle groups, such as weightlifting or resistance exercises, provide an additional health benefit. The present study investigated the relationship between strength training and health-related quality of life (HRQOL) through a cross-sectional study of 50 adults participating in large muscle group strengthening activities (LMG) and 50 adults who did not (NLMG). HRQOL...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting <em>Helicobacter pylori</em> in liver-impaired populations: a systematic review of efficacy and safety]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liver impairment can alter the metabolic capacity of the organ significantly, potentially affecting the efficacy and safety of Helicobacter pylori (H. pylori) eradication regimens. Although this issue is highly significant, no standardized guidelines currently exist for H. pylori eradication therapy in patients with liver dysfunction. To bridge this gap, we systematically reviewed studies on the efficacy and safety of H. pylori eradication therapy in individuals with liver impairment. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of autonomic function in patients with functional dyspepsia using real-time wearable devices and smartphone applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autonomic dysfunction is involved in functional dyspepsia (FD) however, the details have not been elucidated. The aim is to clarify the relationship among autonomic nervous system (ANS) activity, life events, and abdominal symptoms by real-time recordings. This is a prospective multicenter study including 9 patients with FD and 23 healthy controls (HC). The ANS activity was recorded for 24 ‍h using a T-shirt-type wearable device. Life events and abdominal symptoms were simultaneously recorded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41312002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNA-Mediated Inhibition Mechanism of Liquid-Liquid Phase Separation and Subsequent Aggregation Revealed by Raman Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liquid-liquid phase separation (LLPS) is a phenomenon where homogeneous solutions of biomacromolecules separate into two liquid phases and generate liquid droplets enriched in specific biomolecules. LLPS of neurodegeneration-related proteins, including fused in sarcoma (FUS), promotes their aggregation, causing fatal diseases such as amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS). Recent studies showed that RNAs regulate LLPS of these proteins and inhibit their aggregation, which may play an important role...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Tryptophan Positional Isomerism on Physicochemical and Biological Properties: A Case Study Using Gramicidin A Analogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tryptophan (Trp) displays unique physicochemical properties due to its C3-substituted indole ring, containing a hydrophobic benzene ring and a hydrophilic N-H bond. Herein, we synthetically incorporated five Trp positional isomers with C2/4/5/6/7-substituted indoles in place of the Trp of residue 11 in gramicidin A, a 15-mer linear peptidic natural product. Gramicidin A conducts monovalent cations across the cell membrane and exhibits potent toxicity against both bacterial and mammalian cells....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[At the "Peak" of Vis-to-UV Upconversion: Clear Advantages of TIPS Substituents for a Biphenyl Annihilator]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sensitized triplet-triplet annihilation systems enable the efficient conversion of two low-energy photons from a low-intensity, noncoherent light source into one high-energy photon, opening avenues for diverse applications. The attachment of triisopropylsilylethynyl (TIPS-ethynyl) groups to aromatic compounds has led to the development of many annihilators with high upconversion quantum yields. Here, we synthesized a series of novel symmetrical biphenyls bearing silylethynyl substituents of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation of medication review type 2a in community pharmacies: a longitudinal survey study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Repeated surveys offer timely insights into MR2a implementation in community pharmacies. The slow progress confirms existing obstacles and stresses the importance of continued support and improved interprofessional collaborations. These insights are expected to inform MR implementation locally and internationally.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing ROCK biology to revolutionize diabetic nephropathy: decoding mechanisms, designing therapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetes remains a major cause of kidney failure globally, presenting substantial challenges to healthcare systems worldwide. Although significant progress has been made in understanding its pathogenesis, residual risks persist despite current therapies. Emerging evidence underscores the pivotal role of small GTPases-particularly Rho and Rho-associated coiled-coil-containing protein kinase (ROCK)-in the progression of diabetic nephropathy. This comprehensive review consolidates current knowledge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid disease progression and hydrocephalus following tarlatamab therapy initiation: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tarlatamab is a novel bispecific T-cell engager immunotherapy that has demonstrated efficacy against small-cell lung cancer (SCLC) in terms of noteworthy anticancer activity and survival outcomes. However, no studies have detailed the patterns of disease progression during tarlatamab treatment. Herein, we present a case of acute disease progression after tarlatamab initiation in a 71-year-old male patient with extensive-stage SCLC. Following tarlatamab administration, he developed symptoms of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexible Bayesian quantile regression for counts via generative modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Count data frequently arises in biomedical applications, such as the length of hospital stay. However, their discrete nature poses significant challenges for appropriately modeling conditional quantiles, which are crucial for understanding heterogeneous effects and variability in outcomes. To solve the practical difficulty, we propose a novel general Bayesian framework for quantile regression tailored to count data. We seek the regression parameter on the conditional quantile by minimizing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preventing Differentiation Towards Primitive Macrophages in Stem Cells With Down Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Down syndrome (DS) is characterised by delayed brain development and intellectual disabilities. Brain macrophages originate from primitive macrophages that arise from mesodermal cells in the yolk sac and play a role in brain development. Previously, we showed a reduced number of brain macrophages in Ts1Cje foetuses, a murine model of DS. However, the mechanism underlying this reduction in Ts1Cje embryos remains unknown. First, in this study, we identified that the reduced brain macrophages in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41311054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and preliminary functional, physical, and psychosocial effects of high-intensity functional training for adults with mobility disabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A community-based HIFT program for individuals with mobility disabilities is feasible; however, the small sample size limits the ability to attribute changes to the intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Location and aetiology are determinants of fibroblast activation and heterogeneity in the failing human heart]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings provide a comprehensive framework for understanding fibroblast dynamics, highlighting the heterogeneity and spatial complexity of fibrosis in human end-stage HF, and offering potential therapeutic targets to mitigate fibrosis while preserving scar integrity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mating frequency mediates personality expression in facultatively polyandrous mites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study suggests that the mating frequency can critically influence female personality expression after mating and highlights the importance of considering mate-related variables in animal personality research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Antigravity muscle density on computed tomography and health-related independence in normal weight patients with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patients and healthcare professionals' perspectives on the implementation of shared decision making in multiple myeloma: a multinational qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While SDM is partially applied in MM care, there remains room for improvement. This can be done by amplifying the role of haematology nurses and other multidisciplinary team members in the SDM process. Additionally, efforts should focus on increasing the role of patient organisations in raising awareness about SDM and empowering patients to actively participate in SDM. The recommendations derived from this study along with the insights for PtDA development can serve as an initial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A four-year retrospective study on epidemiological updates of dermatophytosis in Kuwait]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide enzooticity of ovine toxoplasmosis and neosporosis in Türkiye]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In conclusion, T. gondii was found to be widespread among sheep in Türkiye, whereas N. caninum had a more limited yet notable distribution. Given the zoonotic importance of toxoplasmosis, it is crucial to strengthen biosecurity and implement region-specific, risk-based control strategies. This study lays a scientific foundation for future preventive measures by enabling nationwide epidemiological mapping of ovine toxoplasmosis and neosporosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The importance of intrafamilial cognitive phenotyping by the case of 22q11.2 deletion, 15q11.2 deletion, and families with inherited copy number variants of unknown significance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results suggest that our approach for determining intrafamilial IQ correlation effectively captured the impact of de novo 22q11.2 microdeletion and additive parental background effect on cognitive impairment, consistent with the modest but detectable effect of 15q11.2 deletions. Parental cognitive data could assist with classifying inherited CNVs of unknown significance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of carperitide on clinical outcomes among patients with acute heart failure: a meta-analysis of randomized and propensity‑matched studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This meta-analysis suggested that carperitide therapy may not be superior to noncarperitide therapy in terms of reducing in-hospital mortality rates or improving long-term outcomes in patients with AHF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting gestational diabetes before conception for personalized interpregnancy weight management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41310377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrochemically Driven Carbon-Nitrogen Bond Formation of the Lactams]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This electrochemical protocol provides a versatile platform for the synthesis of anabolic β- and γ-lactams under mild, metal-free conditions. It is evident that due to their structural diversity, these lactam motifs are indispensable building blocks in organic synthesis and materials science. The method aligns with green chemistry principles by employing electrons from an electric current as a traceless reductant and utilizing cost-effective graphite electrodes, thereby demonstrating excellent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Methylobacter arcticus</em> sp. nov. isolated from a coal mine biofilm in the high Arctic Svalbard]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An aerobic methanotroph was isolated from a biofilm of coal mine Gruve 7 (Svalbard) and designated strain G7^(T). Cells of strain G7^(T) were Gram-stain-negative, pink-pigmented and motile rods. Strain G7^(T) could grow at pH 6.8 and at temperatures ranging from 4 to 21 °C. The genome size was 4.00 Mb with a (digital) DNA G+C content of 47.7 mol%. Strain G7^(T) represents a member of the family Methylomonadaceae of the class Gammaproteobacteria. It displayed 94.6-99.7% 16S rRNA gene sequence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-omics profiling identified two epithelioid sarcoma molecular subtypes with distinct signaling and immune characteristics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SegORG: Report Generation of Oral Potentially Malignant Disorders Image Based on Lesion Segmentation-Enhanced LLM]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: By enhancing visual feature extraction and achieving efficient text alignment, SegORG offers an effective technical pathway for OPMDs reports automation. While single-center validation shows promise, multicenter trials are needed to assess generalizability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating explainable artificial intelligence with multiomics systems biology and electronic health record data mining for personalized drug repurposing in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is characterized by region- and patient-specific molecular heterogeneity, which hinders therapeutic design. In this study, we introduce PRISM-ML (PRecision-medicine using Interpretable Systems and Multiomics with Machine Learning), an open-source integrated analysis pipeline that combines interpretable machine learning with systems biology and electronic health records data mining to elucidate the molecular diversity of AD and predict promising drug repurposing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A network analysis of the interplay between psychological distress and academic buoyancy in medical university students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The connections between academic buoyancy and psychological distress such as depression, anxiety, and uncertainty stress in university students have consistently been highlighted, yet the intricate interplay between these factors remains underexplored. This study employed network analysis to investigate these relationships within Chinese medical university students, who face unique academic pressures and family expectations. Through multi-stage cluster random sampling, 3,622 students from a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Eye Tracking Screening for ASD in Nursery: Is Early Diagnosis Possible? A Large-scale Real-life Experiment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crossroads of cell fate: miR-34-mediated regulation of apoptosis and autophagy in glioblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma (GBM) is the most aggressive and treatment-resistant form of primary brain tumor, characterized by rapid proliferation, extensive heterogeneity, and evasion of programmed cell death. Among emerging molecular regulators, microRNA-34 (miR-34) has gained attention as a potent tumor suppressor with the ability to modulate key signaling pathways involved in cell survival and death. This review explores the dual role of miR-34 in orchestrating apoptosis and autophagy, two fundamental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The next chapter of Quality of Life Research: an update from the editors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-assessment and rest-activity rhythm monitoring for effective bipolar disorder management: a longitudinal actigraphy study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights the potential of digital tools, such as digitally administered self-assessments and actigraphy, to enhance the management of BD by providing valuable insights into mood states and detecting relapse. Further research is needed to refine and optimize these tools for widespread clinical application, such as informing personalized treatment plans.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Types and Causes of Stampede-Related Injuries in Religious Mass Gatherings in Asia: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study was conducted to identify the types and underlying causes of human stampede incidents resulting in fatalities and injuries during religious mass gatherings. The PRISMA guidelines were followed to conduct this systematic review. The protocol for this review has been registered in PROSPERO under the code CRD42024529095. Relevant studies were extracted from reliable data sources, including PubMed, Scopus, Web of Science, Science Direct, Google Scholar, ISC, SID, and MagIran....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Efficacy of Talquetamab vs. Real-World Physician's Choice of Treatment in Triple-Class-Exposed Relapsed/Refractory Multiple Myeloma: Updated Analyses of MonumenTAL-1 vs. LocoMMotion/MoMMent]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: With longer follow-up, these comparative analyses further demonstrate the clinical benefit of talquetamab over RWPC in patients with TCE RRMM, irrespective of prior TCR therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated analysis of the oncogenic value of CPNE3 in non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CPNE3 regulates tumor cell migration, invasion, VM formation and immune evasion by acting as an oncogene in NSCLC, implying that CPNE3 can serve as a potential anti-angiogenesis target for NSCLC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utility of in Vivo and Ex-vivo Models in Food Allergy Research: Lessons for Shrimp Allergy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We are living in an era where food allergy is increasingly prevalent, and shrimp allergy (SA) is among the most common and potentially severe reactions worldwide. Significant efforts have been made to improve diagnostic accuracy and treatment options. However, diagnosing SA remains challenging due to its diverse clinical presentations and the complexity of shrimp allergens. The pathogenesis of SA is complicated by various allergens sensitization, epithelial barrier disruption and gut microbiota...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of intercellular adhesion molecule 1 (ICAM-1) (rs5498) genetic polymorphism and dengue in Sabah East Malaysia population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The ICAM-1 rs5498 GG genotype and G allele are significantly associated with increased susceptibility to dengue infection in the Sabahan population, particularly among females. These findings highlight the potential role of ICAM-1 as a genetic biomarker for dengue risk and underscore the importance of considering ethnic and gender differences in genetic epidemiology studies of infectious diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of the inhibitor development for SARS-CoV-2: a systematic approach for drug design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONTEXT: The main protease (M^(pro)) of SARS-CoV-2 is highly conserved with low variability. It plays a key role in viral replication, making it a target for COVID-19 treatment. Currently, drugs like Paxlovid have significant side effects and high costs, so new alternatives are urgently needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining Factors That Impact Speech Acceptability and Intelligibility in 4- to 7-Year-Old Children With Cleft Palate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectiveExamine factors that impact ratings of speech acceptability and parent-reported speech intelligibility using the Intelligibility in Context Scale (ICS).DesignProspective, cross-sectional study.SettingPublic research university.PatientsThirty children 4 to 7 years old with a repaired cleft palate.VariablesPerceptual ratings derived from the Cleft Audit Protocol for Speech-Augmented-Americleft Modification, ICS, percent consonants correct (PCC), age, and sex.Main Outcome Measure(s)Factors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Baculovirus expression and purification of nucleocapsid protein of canine distemper virus for its evaluation as a diagnostic antigen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canine distemper is a highly contagious disease of domestic dogs and various species of wild animals, and is associated with high mortality. It is caused by canine morbillivirus (formerly known as CDV or canine distemper virus), a member of the Morbillivirus genus under Paramyxoviridae family. The disease is endemic in many parts of the world, including India. For effective control of the disease, reliable diagnostic tools are of utmost importance. The circulating CDV strains in India belong to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Chlorhexidine, Chlorhexidine with anti-discoloration system, and Polyvinylpyrrolidone-iodine on early wound healing after dental implant placement: A randomized clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: All tested mouth rinses demonstrated comparable efficacy in promoting early wound healing and infection control after implant surgery. CHX ADS showed superior patient acceptance, suggesting its potential as a preferred option based on subjective tolerability. Standardization of healing assessment indices is recommended for future studies to enhance comparability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between MR neurography-based objective quantitative parameters in inferior alveolar nerve and lingual nerve injuries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This investigation establishes, for the first time, the clinical validity of aNMCNRi/h as a quantitative imaging parameter correlating with symptom severity and prognostic trajectories in mild-to-moderate IAN/LN injuries. The proposed parameter demonstrates potential for guiding patient-specific clinical decision-making, with implications for standardizing diagnostic protocols and optimizing rehabilitation strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of novel CASQ1 variants in two families with unusual phenotypic features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study expands the spectrum of pathogenic CASQ1 variants. The morphological changes in the SR-feet indicate a novel pathogenetic mechanism.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Melioidosis imported to Northern Germany: a case report series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Melioidosis is a severe infection with variable clinical presentations, including fever, night sweats, weight loss, dyspnoea, and abscess formation at different sites. The broad spectrum of symptoms complicates diagnosis. Therefore, melioidosis should be considered in returning travellers from endemic regions presenting with compatible clinical features. Prolonged antibiotic treatment is essential for effective infection control.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Duchenne Muscular Dystrophy with Hepatoblastoma in a Female Child: Authors' Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Ethics Consultation: Ethics matter to all of us!]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clinical Ethics Consultation (CEC) provides support to treatment teams in complex decision-making situations, focusing on patient autonomy, interprofessional collaboration and the legal framework. Following the introduction of CEC at the Vienna General Hospital and the Medical University of Vienna, a structured service has been established that systematically integrates ethical issues into everyday clinical practice. As well as conducting ethics case consultations, the initiative includes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prophylactic use of vitamin k in special neonatal populations: a quality assessment of clinical guidelines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Clinical practice guidelines for vitamin K prophylaxis in special neonatal populations show poor quality and inconsistency. There is a need for high-quality research to clarify individualized supplementation strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors affecting the management of change in Saudi Arabian healthcare environments: a stakeholder assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: This study evaluates the factors affecting successful implementation of management of change (MOC) in Saudi Arabian healthcare environments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum amyloid A in HFpEF and cardiometabolic diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heart failure with preserved ejection fraction (HFpEF) accounts for more than half of all heart failure cases, and its prevalence is projected to rise further. Among its heterogeneous subtypes, cardiometabolic HFpEF, which is driven by metabolic dysfunction, represents a globally predominant form. Recent advances in preclinical models have highlighted metabolic disturbances and systemic inflammation as key contributors to HFpEF pathogenesis. While much attention has focused on classical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of TyG index and TG/HDL ratio with hyperuricemia in patients with H-type hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: these results suggest that the TyG index and TG/HDL ratio could serve as predictive biomarkers for hyperuricemia in H-type hypertension, particularly in females.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adaptive laboratory evolution of Saccharomyces cerevisiae CEN.PK 113-7D to enhance ethanol tolerance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Saccharomyces cerevisiae is a widely used yeast for industrial production of ethanol. However, elevated ethanol, temperature, and osmotic stress adversely affect fermentation efficiency. In this study, adaptive laboratory evolution for S. cerevisiae CEN.PK 113-7D on higher concentrations of ethanol was performed. After 144 days, the maximum specific growth rate (µmax) increased from 0.0240 h-1 to 0.1150 h-1 for the strain evolved on 9% v/v ethanol, and from 0.0002 h-1 to 0.0530 h-1 for the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smartphone and AI Workflow for 3D Printed Plate for Presurgical Therapy in Cleft Lip and Palate: Retrospective Evaluation of Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectiveTo explore clinical feasibility of smartphone and AI-assisted workflow for presurgical orthopedic therapy in newborns with unilateral cleft lip and palate (UCLP).DesignRetrospective exploratory cohort study.SettingA tertiary craniofacial center.PatientsTwenty consecutive (13 females, 7 males) with non-syndromic complete UCLP treated 2022-2024.InterventionsPassive presurgical plates fabricated through smartphone scanning of impressions, AI-assisted automated plate design and 3D...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is the Patient Compliance Rate for Nasopharyngoscopy as Documented in Clinical Reports?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectiveAssess the patient compliance rate for nasopharyngoscopy as documented in clinical reports.DesignCross-sectional.SettingThirteen cleft teams in North America.PatientsPatients aged 3 to 21 years old with a repaired cleft palate.InterventionsNasopharyngoscopy.Main Outcome MeasurePatient compliance rate for nasopharyngoscopy.ResultsPatient compliance was documented in 128 of 158 reports (81%). Of the 128 reports, patient compliance was reported as "good/excellent" in 65% (n = 83),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Message Evaluation Equivalence in Pre Versus Postproduction Tobacco Education Ads]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Results suggest that message evaluation assessments of preproduction ads are likely a good indicator of message evaluation assessments for postproduction ads. Public health practitioners may consider incorporating quantitative copy testing earlier in the formative testing process to identify the most promising ad concepts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeted Drugs, PADN, and Transcatheter Closure for Atrial Septal Defect-Associated Pulmonary Hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Targeted drug therapy and subsequent transcatheter closure are effective in treating atrial septal defects in patients with severe pulmonary arterial hypertension. Nevertheless, despite sufficient pharmacological therapy, many patients do not satisfy the hemodynamic criteria for transcatheter closure under the current guidelines. Here, we report 2 patients with atrial septal defect complicated by pulmonary arterial hypertension, in which successful transcatheter occlusion was achieved through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis of Spinal Cord Stimulation for Chronic Nonsurgical Refractory Back Pain With or Without Leg Pain (Persistent Spinal Pain Syndrome Type 1)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: All included studies of SCS for PSPS-T1 indicated significant improvements in pain intensity, physical function, and HRQoL when compared with CMM or baseline.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exome-wide association study of bleeding events in patients receiving direct oral anticoagulants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundDirect oral anticoagulants (DOACs) are first-line medications for stroke prevention in non-valvular atrial fibrillation (AF). However, variability in drug response poses risks of hemorrhagic or thromboembolic events.ObjectivesAlthough genetic influences on DOACs safety are increasingly recognized, robust evidence directly linking specific polymorphisms to bleeding risk remains limited.DesignMulti-center observational case-control study including exome-wide association analysis of 196...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A pathway to synthesize 2-methylbenzothiazole derivatives <em>via</em> a hydrogen sulfide promoted tandem reaction of calcium carbide and 2-iodoaniline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Benzothiazoles, a significant class of nitrogen- and sulfur-containing heterocyclic compounds, are widely utilized in the fields of pesticides and pharmaceuticals. In this study, a novel method for synthesizing 2-methylbenzothiazole derivatives was developed through a multicomponent tandem reaction of 2-iodoaniline, CaC(2) and H(2)S. It was found that H(2)S reacts with CaC(2) to form a pivotal intermediate, ethanethial, which subsequently reacts with 2-iodoaniline to synthesize diverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative distribution of the hypothalamic neurons activated during wakefulness and paradoxical (REM) sleep using male TRAP2-red mice: contribution of orexin, MCH, Lhx6 and a new marker Meis2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study identifies new neuronal populations activated during PSR in AHA, ZI and tuberal nucleus. We further provide evidence that Meis2 is expressed in novel populations of neurons activated during PSR. In summary, our results using male TRAP2-red mice characterize the cell populations activated during Wakefulness and PSR, opening experimental paths for determining their function regarding vigilance states.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[S···O Conformation Locks Synergistic Alkoxy Chain Engineering of NIR-II Phototheranostic Molecules for Precision Hepatocellular Carcinoma Theranostics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[NIR-II phototheranostics offers a promising strategy for precisely managing deep-seated and refractory tumors. However, the overall optimization of molecular functional properties remains a challenge, and due to the lack of a comprehensive design strategy, there have been limitations in achieving long-wavelength phototherapy, high-fluorescence quantum yield, and photothermal/photodynamic conversion efficiency. This study initially proposes an innovative strategy that involves S···O confirmation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Weight Gain Among Children and Adolescents on Dolutegravir in Spain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective real-world study analyzed Body Mass Index (BMI) and obesity in 257 Spanish children/adolescents with HIV receiving DTG-based or non-INSTI regimens over five years. DTG-based regimens increased BMI Z-scores without clear clinical relevance. Continuous monitoring of weight trajectories is essential to protect long-term cardiovascular health in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evidence-based classification of genes implicated in skeletal disorders using the ClinGen curation framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[More than 770 genetic skeletal disorders have been described, most with disease-causing variants reported in one of over 550 different genes. The ClinGen Skeletal Disorders Gene Curation Expert Panel was established to determine the strength of evidence that supports specific gene-disease relationships. Such information can assist clinical testing laboratories in choosing genes that should be included on diagnostic panels. Nine genes accounting for the most frequently encountered skeletal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent drinking in alcohol use disorder as a modifiable risk factor of postural tremor and instability in mild cognitive impairment: An initial study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Age, irrespective of diagnosis, imbues liability onto postural stability, evidenced by longer sway paths and greater tremor velocity, especially under challenging conditions. Although the MCI group showed no evidence for disturbed balance metrics beyond those observed in controls, MCI participants comorbid for AUD exhibited deficits at similar levels to those shown by AUD participants in quiet standing, indicating recent drinking in individuals with a history of AUD as a modifiable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ca<sup>2+</sup>/Zn<sup>2+</sup> alginate hydrogel electrolyte for high-performance zinc-ion batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing energy crisis has intensified the focus on green energy, sparking widespread interest in aqueous zinc-ion batteries. However, their development has been hindered by issues in the zinc anode. Here, Ca^(2+)/Zn^(2+) alginate hydrogel electrolyte was designed to effectively suppress dendritic growth and parasitic side reactions. The Ca^(2+) primary cross-linking provides a regular "egg-box" network framework for fast ion transport, whereas secondary cross-linking with Zn^(2+) creates a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From macroscopic clearance to molecular eradication: paradigm shift and future perspectives in the detecting of residual lesions after transurethral resection of bladder tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Residual lesions after transurethral resection of bladder tumor (TURBT) are a major contributor to recurrence in bladder cancer. Advances in diagnostic technology are shifting postoperative management from conventional macroscopic evaluation toward molecular-level assessment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photo-immuno nano-bomb for co-delivery of Ce6 and R837 potentiates immunogenic cell death and amplifies anti-tumor efficacy in cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma (cSCC) remains a formidable clinical challenge, constrained by the drawbacks of current treatments such as functional loss from surgery, radioresistance, and low adherence to protracted topical regimens. To address these issues, we designed a "photo-immuno nano-bomb" composed of polydopamine nanoparticles (PDA NPs) for co-delivering the photosensitizer chlorin e6 (Ce6) and toll-like receptor 7 agonist imiquimod (R837), thereby integrating photothermal (PTT),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Field Evolution Rule Governs the Dynamics of Representational Drift in Mouse Hippocampal Dorsal CA1 Region]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hippocampal place codes change substantially across days, yet the mechanisms governing their temporal evolution remain incompletely understood. To quantitatively characterize this process, longitudinal one-photon calcium imaging of dorsal CA1 neurons in mice is performed for up to 56 days across multiple goal-oriented navigation tasks. Parallel to mice's improvements in maze learning and navigational performance, thousands of place fields exhibit complex evolutionary trajectories characterized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution, prevalence of non-tuberculous mycobacteria on Hainan Island and antibiotic resistance of <em>Mycobacterium abscessus</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-tuberculous mycobacteria (NTM) infections are increasingly recognized as a public health concern, yet their distribution and antibiotic resistance patterns on Hainan Island, China's tropical hotspot, remain understudied. This study analyzes 158 clinical respiratory samples from 2015 to 2018 across 14 cities, identifying 118 NTM isolates from 24 species. Predominant species include Mycobacterium abscessus (23.73%), M. intracellulare (22.03%), and M. simiae (14.41%). Spatial mapping reveals...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial for "Prospective Comparison of DWI-Derived Virtual MR Elastography and Conventional MR Elastography in Metabolic Dysfunction-Associated Steatotic Liver Disease and Healthy Volunteers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quorum-sensing regulator LsrR modulates avian pathogenic <em>Escherichia coli</em> pathogenicity through direct regulation of <em>cysN</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Avian Pathogenic Escherichia coli (APEC) is a major cause of economic loss in poultry, exacerbated by the rising prevalence of antibiotic resistance. While sulfur metabolism is essential for bacterial growth, its specific role and regulation in APEC virulence remain poorly understood. This study identifies the LsrR-cysN axis as a novel regulatory pathway that critically governs APEC virulence. We demonstrate that the quorum-sensing regulator LsrR directly binds to the cysN promoter, activating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Initial Development of a Multidimensional Computerized Adaptive Test for Intensive Longitudinal Assessment of Suicide Risk: Development and Usability Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The CAT-SRP effectively personalized EMA survey content to respondents, which reduces the repetitiveness and perceived burden of intensive longitudinal research designs. Continuous domain scores from multidimensional computerized adaptive testing (MCAT) also provided more nuanced measurement compared to traditional approaches that struggle with zero-inflation in EMA and appeared to produce stronger predictive relationships. Overall, the CAT-SRP demonstrated strong methodological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of GOLD 2023 Initial Inhalation Therapy Recommendations in COPD patients: a real-world adherence and prognosis analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In the real world, many patients with COPD do not receive the initial inhalation therapy recommended by the GOLD 2023 report. However, adherence to the GOLD 2023 report may decrease the risk of future exacerbation. It implied that improved the dissemination and uptake of GOLD 2023 recommendations is needed in the clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mannoprotein Cig1 contributes to the immunogenicity of a heat-killed F-box protein Fbp1 <em>Cryptococcus neoformans</em> vaccine model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Currently, no fungal vaccine exists for clinical use, while fungal infections are responsible for over 1.5 million deaths every year. Our previous studies identified a Cryptococcus neoformans mutant strain fbp1Δ as a potential vaccine candidate. This strain contains deletion of the F-box protein Fbp1, a key subunit of the SCF E3 ligase complex necessary for ubiquitin-mediated proteolysis. Vaccination with heat-killed fbp1Δ (HK-fbp1) can elicit an interferon gamma (IFN-γ)-dependent Type 1 immune...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of a Gabapentinoid-Loop-Diuretic Prescribing Cascade in U.S. Nursing Home Residents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Approximately 1 in 20 NH residents who initiate gabapentinoids receives a loop diuretic within 3 months. Potentially modifiable predictors included existing polypharmacy and titrating gabapentinoid doses. NH clinicians should monitor for edema soon after gabapentinoid initiation and consider dose reductions or discontinuation before adding a loop diuretic.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing eHealth Interventions to Improve Diabetes Management in Emerging Adulthood: Qualitative Formative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Emerging adult feedback supports the acceptability and use of these intervention components and will be used to refine the interventions. Feedback was especially positive regarding cultural and other tailoring efforts, as well as content directed at their pending transition to full independence. At the same time, their input suggests the need for multiple specific modifications, highlighting the importance of intensive and detailed feedback from end users.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tooth-Supported 3D-Printed Surgical Guide for Titanium Mesh Placement in Bone Augmentation of the Esthetic Zone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The guide enabled precise intraoperative positioning of the titanium mesh in accordance with the preoperative design. The maximum intraoperative titanium mesh displacement was 1.59 mm, with an average deviation of 0.42 mm. The average overall bone augmentation volume deviation was 0.057 ± 0.031 cm³(SD), 95% CI: (0.025 cm³, 0.089cm³), corresponding to a bone augmentation accuracy of 91.67%.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Digital Mental Health: The Society of Digital Psychiatry's Three-Pronged Road Map for Education, Digital Navigators, and AI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital mental health tools such as apps, virtual reality, and artificial intelligence (AI) hold great promise but continue to face barriers to widespread clinical adoption. The Society of Digital Psychiatry, in partnership with JMIR Mental Health, presents a 3-pronged road map to accelerate their safe, effective, and equitable implementation. First, education: integrate digital psychiatry into core training and professional development through a global webinar series, annual symposium,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of the Social Media-Based Prevention Program "Leduin" for German Adolescents on Instagram: Mixed Methods Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The study underlines the potential of various Instagram features and content posting schedules for health interventions to meet adolescent preferences and interests. Challenges with reaching the target group effectively emphasize the need for targeted recruitment strategies and optimizing initial content to boost engagement, underscoring the critical implications for prevention research and policy in leveraging digital platforms to enhance adolescent health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mineral Dynamics Revealed by Fe<sup>2+</sup>-Catalyzed Recrystallization of U-Incorporated Goethite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Iron (oxyhydr)oxides are capable of structurally incorporating and releasing trace elements through Fe^(2+)-induced recrystallization. However, estimation of the extent of recrystallization varies among studies using isotopic tracers and those examining the release of occluded trace elements. To provide further insight into the dynamics of Fe^(2+)-catalyzed iron (oxyhydr)oxide recrystallization, and to accurately interpret the isotopic and elemental compositions of iron (oxyhydr)oxides in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Giant SHG Switching in a Molecular Crystal via Pressure-Driven Conformational Isomerization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Second-harmonic generation (SHG) switching materials are of great significance for advanced optoelectronic applications, and their design is often guided by the "anionic group theory", which states that the nonlinear optical (NLO) effect of a material originates from microscopic polar groups and their geometric superposition. Therefore, external stimulus-triggered structural transformations are recognized as an effective strategy to achieve SHG switching. However, pressure-induced conformational...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular evidence on phenotypic variation in the poorly known acanthocephalan species Rhadinorhynchus cololabis Laurs &amp; McCauley, 1964 (Echinorhynchida: Rhadinorhynchidae)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acanthocephalans of the genus Rhadinorhynchus parasitize various marine fishes worldwide. However, the true diversity of Rhadinorhynchus is still unclear. In this study, we found an example of phenotypic variation in trunk spines of the poorly known rhadinorhynchid species R. cololabis Laurs & McCauley, 1964. According to the number and distribution of trunk spines, the present specimens of R. cololabis can be divided into two distinct morphotypes, which may erroneously be recognized as distinct...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Phenylenediamines via (4 + 1 + 1) Photocycloaddition of 1,3-Dienes and Isocyanides Enabled by a Gallium(I)/(III) Redox: The Key Role of a Phenalenyl-Based Ligand]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A gallacyclopentene complex is generated via (4 + 1) cycloaddition of a Ga(I) complex bearing a phenalenyl-based ligand with a 1,3-diene. Upon visible-light irradiation, the Ga(III) complex undergoes homolytic cleavage of a Ga-C bond, facilitating the subsequent mono- and double-insertion reactions with isocyanides. The double insertion complex undergoes C-C bond formation to afford 1,2-phenylenediamine, achieving a (4 + 1 + 1) cycloaddition of 1,3-dienes and isocyanides via a stoichiometric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel diagnostic strategy of differential diagnosis of tuberculous meningitis and non-tuberculous meningitis: a retrospective observational cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculous meningitis (TBM) leads to severe disability and mortality rates, making early diagnosis critical. However, it is challenging to distinguish it from other common forms of non-tuberculous meningitis (non-TBM), including bacterial meningitis, cryptococcal meningitis, and viral meningitis. This study aims to construct a diagnostic model between TBM and non-TBM. A total of 543 patients were enrolled, and 405 subjects remained and were subsequently divided into a training set and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An effective DNA extraction protocol optimized for tropical swamp peat samples]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peatlands are waterlogged ecosystems that store large amounts of carbon, harbor highly specialized endemic biodiversity, and play a crucial role in climate regulation. However, the microbial communities of tropical peatlands, particularly in the Atlantic Forest, remain largely unexplored. Molecular tools are essential for characterizing these communities, yet conventional DNA extraction kits are often ineffective for peat soils, likely due to their high organic matter content, low pH, and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative volatilomics identifies ubiquitous sulfur compounds inhibiting the fungal pathogen <em>Rasamsonia argillacea</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Members of the phylum Actinomycetota, particularly Streptomyces species, are prolific producers of bioactive metabolites, and bioprospecting in unique environments may uncover novel species producing previously undescribed antifungal compounds. In previous work, Streptomyces strains isolated from cave moonmilk deposits completely inhibited the growth of Rasamsonia argillacea, an emerging fungal pathogen associated with chronic granulomatous disease (CGD) and cystic fibrosis (CF). Cross-streak...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Bifidobacterium animalis</em> subsp. <em>lactis</em> Probio-M8 enhances chondroitin efficacy for knee osteoarthritis in postmenopausal women via the gut-joint axis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Knee osteoarthritis (KOA) is a chronic joint disease marked by cartilage degradation and inflammation. Probiotics exhibit anti-inflammatory properties and may influence the gut-joint axis. Thus, a 4-month human trial was conducted to assess the adjunctive effects of Bifidobacterium animalis subsp. lactis Probio-M8 on KOA in postmenopausal women. Sixty-five KOA patients were randomly allocated to the probiotic group (n = 37; Probio-M8 and chondroitin sulfate) or placebo group (n = 28; placebo and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41313018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251128142122&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>