<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 07:38:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simultaneous Targeting of Multiple Hallmarks of Cancer With Recombinant Methioninase, Rapamycin and Chloroquine Is Specific and Synergistic to MiaPaCa-2 Pancreatic-Cancer Cells in Contrast to Hs-27 Normal Fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The combination of rMETase, rapamycin and chloroquine had highly synergistic and selective efficacy against PDAC cells in vitro compared to normal cells, supporting its potential as a precision-targeted metabolic clinical therapy for pancreatic cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of a Cynomolgus Macaque Model for Human Adenovirus Type 55-Induced Respiratory Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study establishes a cynomolgus macaque model that recapitulates key clinical and immunological features of HAdV-55-induced respiratory disease in humans. The model provides a robust platform for advancing our understanding of HAdV-55 pathogenesis and for the preclinical evaluation of candidate vaccines and therapeutics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of High-Dose Pioglitazone as Add-on Therapy in Patients with Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus Inadequately Controlled with Dapagliflozin and Metformin: Double-Blind, Randomized, Placebo-Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Addition of pioglitazone 30 mg/day to T2DM patients who did not reach the target HbA1c (≤7%) with treatment of dapagliflozin 10 mg/day and metformin over 1,000 mg/day showed effective glucose lowering efficacy without significant hypoglycemia and good tolerability with low prevalence of edema in spite of modest weight gain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robotic and On-Flow Solid Phase Extraction Coupled with LC-MS/MS for Simultaneous Determination of 16 PPCPs: Real-Time Monitoring of Wastewater Effluent in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceuticals and personal care products (PPCPs) are recognized as emerging contaminants of concern, even at ultra-trace concentrations. However, the current detection systems are prohibitively expensive and typically rely on labor-intensive, lab-based workflows that lack automation in sample pretreatment. In this study, we developed a robotic and on-flow solid-phase extraction (ROF-SPE) system, fully integrated with online liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry (LC-MS/MS), for the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rheological and Thermal Properties of Salecan/Sanxan Composite Hydrogels for Food and Biomedical Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rational design of advanced composite gels requires rigorous rheological analysis to decode their flow-deformation mechanisms, a prerequisite for optimizing performance in food and biomedical applications. However, systematic thermal analysis and rheological profiling of Salecan/Sanxan hydrogels remain unexplored, constituting a critical knowledge gap in this field. This study engineered Salecan/Sanxan hydrogels and systematically probed Salecan-dependent rheological and thermal properties....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibody-Integrated Solid-to-Gel Microfilm for Protection Against Botulinum Neurotoxin Type A]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibodies are indispensable for protection against biological toxins and pathogens, yet their conventional liquid formulations impose severe constraints, including dosing inaccuracy caused by residual fluid remaining in the syringe and limited user convenience such as pain caused by fluid-induced tissue distension and nerve stimulation as well as instability in ambient temperature, and the requirement for low-temperature storage and logistics. These limitations critically impair rapid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No-Signaling in Steepest Entropy Ascent: A Nonlinear, Non-Local, Non-Equilibrium Quantum Dynamics of Composite Systems Strongly Compatible with the Second Law]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lindbladian formalism models open quantum systems using a 'bottom-up' approach, deriving linear dynamics from system-environment interactions. We present a 'top-down' approach starting with phenomenological constraints, focusing on a system's structure, subsystems' interactions, and environmental effects and often using a non-equilibrium variational principle designed to enforce strict thermodynamic consistency. However, incorporating the second law's requirement-that Gibbs states are the sole...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNA Degradation in Pluripotent Stem Cells: Mechanisms, Crosstalk, and Fate Regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pluripotent stem cells (PSCs) exhibit remarkable self-renewal capacity and differentiation potential, necessitating tight regulation of gene expression at both transcriptional and post-transcriptional levels. Among post-transcriptional mechanisms, RNA turnover and degradation together play pivotal roles in maintaining transcriptome homeostasis and controlling RNA stability. RNA degradation plays a pivotal role in determining transcript stability for both messenger RNAs (mRNAs) and non-coding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NSUN-Mediated m5C RNA Modification in Stem Cell Regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA modifications comprise a core epigenetic dimension of gene regulation; among these, N6-methyladenosine (m6A) and 5-methylcytosine (m5C) have been most intensively investigated. While the functions of m6A in stem cell biology have been well characterized, the contributions of m5C remain comparatively less well defined. This review focuses on m5C modifications catalyzed by the NSUN family of RNA methyltransferases and their roles in regulating stem cell identity, pluripotency, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis and Structure-Activity Relationship Study of 2-(amino)quinazolin-4(3<em>H</em>)-one Derivatives as Potential Inhibitors of Methicillin-Resistant <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em> (MRSA)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The rise in methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA) demands new therapeutic strategies. In this study, a series of 2-(amino)quinazolin-4(3H)-one derivatives were synthesized and evaluated for antistaphylococcal activity. Methods/Results: Through screening against S. aureus ATCC25923 and USA300 JE2, several submicromolar inhibitors were identified. Among them, compound 6l, which contains a 7-chloro substituent on the key parental scaffold, exhibited strong...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MetalloGen: Automated 3D Conformer Generation for Diverse Coordination Complexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conformer generation is crucial for computational chemistry tasks such as structure-based modeling and property prediction. Although reliable methods exist for organic molecules, coordination complexes remain challenging due to their diverse coordination geometries, ligand types, and stereochemistry. Current tools often lack the flexibility and reliability required for these systems. Here, we introduce MetalloGen, a novel algorithm designed for the automated generation of 3D conformers of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FOXO3a upregulates DNA repair activities by transcriptional activation of target genes and provides the resistance to gamma radiation and the extension of lifespan in mouse]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To verify whether DNA repair is regulated by FOXO3a, a tet-on flag-h-FOXO3a transgenic mice were used. RT-q-PCR and western blot analysis showed that the mRNA and protein levels of flag-h-FOXO3a, XRCC4, XPC, APE1 and MSH2 increased dose dependently by doxycycline. DNA repair activities like non-homologous end joining (NHEJ), nucleotide excision repair (NER), base excision repair (BER), mismatch repair (MMR) also increased in a doxycycline dose dependent manner. MEF (mouse embryonic fibroblast)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Membrane Tethering of Honeybee Antimicrobial Peptides in Drosophila Enhances Pathogen Defense at the Cost of Stress-Induced Host Vulnerability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial peptides (AMPs) represent a promising alternative to conventional antibiotics in combating multidrug-resistant pathogens, yet their clinical translation is hindered by proteolytic instability, cytotoxicity, and poor bioavailability. Herein, it is demonstrated that glycosylphosphatidylinositol-mediated membrane tethering of honeybee defensin1 (Def1) in Drosophila melanogasterenhances its antimicrobial efficacy by ≈ $$\approx$$ 100-fold compared to secreted or untethered forms,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between adherence to cancer prevention guidelines and cancer risk: a comprehensive systematic review and dose-response meta-analysis of cohort studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: No systematic review and meta-analysis has comprehensively assessed the association between adherence to major cancer prevention guidelines and risks of cancers in cohort studies. We aimed to evaluate the associations of adherence to the 2018 and the 2007 World Cancer Research Fund/American Institute for Cancer Research (WCRF/AICR) and the 2012 American Cancer Society (ACS) guidelines with risks of multiple cancer outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BINOL-3,3'-Dicarboxylic Acid: Resolution for the Key Intermediate of (S)-bepotastine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[(S)-Bepotastine is a highly selective histamine H1-receptor antagonist in the treatment of allergic rhinitis and other allergic diseases. We achieved a facile and convenient synthesis of (S)-bepotastine by resolving an early stage synthetic precursor. We devised a new class of resolving agent, BINOL-3,3'-dicarboxylic acid which could be considered as an axial version of tartaric acid. As the first example, we successfully resolved racemic piperidinyl ether by (S)-BINOL-3,3'-dicarboxylic acid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the service readiness of a Paraguay public healthcare center for the primary healthcare system using the WHO SARA tool]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that merely implementing health system-related policies, such as national health plans or service coverage mandates, is insufficient without targeted strategies addressing health workforce distribution, resource allocation, and health infrastructure development. The term 'inequality gaps' refers specifically to disparities in healthcare access, particularly in the distribution of healthcare workers and essential medical resources. This study provides novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robust Metal and Semiconductor Phase Transition Memristor Using Ag-Intercalated Transition Metal Dichalcogenide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal (1T/1T')-semiconductor (2H) phase transition memristors (PTMEMs) based on intercalated alkali metal ions (Li^(+)) in transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDs) exhibit excellent electrical properties, including heterosynaptic plasticity. However, the low stability of Li^(+) ions limits retention and on/off ratios of the PTMEMs. Here, a phase transition in MoTe(2) induced by intercalated Ag^(+) ions is demonstrated for the first time, enabling robust memristor operation. The migration of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-time rodent behavior classifier using color-based body segmentation (R2C2)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The heavy reliance of animal studies on human observers makes them prone to observer-specific biases. To mitigate such shortcomings, much research has been focused on computerizing the characterization of animal behavior. Such automation can lead to more reliable and cost-effective behavior quantifications. Yet, there remain challenges in developing end-to-end solutions that allow users to easily train custom behavioral classifiers with minimal data while maintaining low computational demands....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triglyceride-glucose index variability and risk of all-cause and cardiovascular mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triglyceride-glucose (TyG) index is a reliable marker of insulin resistance with predictive value for cardiovascular risk. While metabolic variability independently impacts cardiovascular outcomes and mortality, the clinical significance of TyG index variability remains unclear. We investigated whether higher TyG index variability increases the risk of mortality. This retrospective cohort study analyzed data from 3,094,062 individuals who participated in the National Health Screening Program...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of Pseudotime from Texture Parameters of [<sup>18</sup>F]fluorodeoxyglucose PET/CT in Resectable Pancreatic Ductal Adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings indicate that pseudotime is a meaningful prognostic biomarker in resectable PDAC patients undergoing surgery, with stronger predictive power than established metabolic parameters. Stratification performance improved when it was combined with conventional markers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interpretable distance adaptive GCN-autoencoder for soft sensor validation and remote reconstruction in urban air quality monitoring networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The air quality monitoring system (AQMS) has attracted considerable attention due to its environmental significance and impact on human health. AQMS are critical for facilitating early-warning mechanisms to implement policies and protect urban communities. However, existing frameworks rely on physical sensors compromised by degradation, leading to unreliable decision-making. To overcome this limitation, this study introduces a region-wide soft sensor validation using a memory-integrated graph...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of delayed post-polymerization on physical, chemical, and biological properties of a 3D printing interim resin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: This study evaluated the effects of delayed post-polymerization on color, degree of conversion (DC), flexural strength (FS), and cellular response of a 3D-printed dental interim resin.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interpreting the afternoon disadvantage: accounting for mediation, weighting and secular trends: a reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between normal systolic blood pressure maintenance and the risk of coronary artery calcification progression in asymptomatic non-diabetic and diabetic adults: a retrospective cohort study using data from the Korea initiatives on coronary artery calcification registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Maintaining normal systolic blood pressure was associated with a significantly attenuated CAC progression, especially in clinical conditions without established diabetes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Re: Comments on "Impact of <em>RNF213</em> Polymorphism in Isolated Intracranial Arterial Steno-Occlusive Disease"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Identification of CGG-Repeat Expansions in <em>LRP12</em> in Korean Families With Oculopharyngodistal Myopathy Type 1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Bedtime Digital Media Use on Sleep Across Age Groups: Insights From a Nationwide Survey in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Bedtime digital media use and resulting sleep procrastination are highly prevalent. Older adults are particularly susceptible to insomnia linked to bedtime digital media use and have a lower awareness of its negative effects. These results indicate a need for public health initiatives to increase awareness and mitigate the negative impacts of digital media on sleep.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Critical Reappraisal and Validation of the Bern Score System for Diagnosing Spontaneous Intracranial Hypotension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Bern score showed high specificity but limited sensitivity in our cohort, indicating it should not be used alone as a screening tool. A lower cutoff may improve its diagnostic performance, and timing from symptom onset should be considered when interpreting the score.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Olfactory Dysfunction in Patients With Acetylcholine-Receptor-Antibody-Positive Myasthenia Gravis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Olfactory dysfunction was significantly more prevalent in the MG patients than in the healthy controls. These findings highlight the need for further research into the underlying mechanisms and potential clinical implications of olfactory impairment in MG.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevention of Unbearable Situations and Harms Protocol: A Quality Improvement Initiative in Neurological Delirium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The PUSH protocol significantly reduced delirium-related harms, enhanced clinical workflow efficiency, decreased staff burnout, and increased satisfaction, supporting its broader implementation in neurological settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Clopidogrel Genetic Polymorphism With Efficacy and Safety for Ischemic Stroke or Transient Ischemic Attack: A Systematic Review and Updated Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Carriers of CYP2C19 LoF alleles treated with clopidogrel had a higher risk of stroke or TIA recurrence than non-carriers. This risk was higher in Asian populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Implications of an Integrated Clinical and Biological Staging Scheme for Alzheimer's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The integration of clinical and biological staging has significant potential in clinical practice by providing information about copathologies, underlying neurodegeneration, and the progression of AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Single Biomarkers: Toward Integrated Staging in Alzheimer's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Anticoagulation in Large Volume Cardioembolic Stroke: Rethinking the Optimal Initiation Time]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clearance of <em>TP53</em> Mutations in ctDNA Reflects Therapeutic Response in Advanced Pancreatic Cancer Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Dynamic changes in ctDNA, particularly the disappearance of TP53 mutations, serve as a sensitive biomarker for chemotherapy response in advanced PDAC, even when traditional markers like CA 19-9 are unreliable. Longitudinal ctDNA profiling offers a promising approach to guide early treatment evaluation and may inform therapeutic strategies targeting resistant subclones.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JI-CJ002, a Natural Herbal Formula, Enhances the Antitumor Efficacy of FOLFOX in Colorectal Cancer by Suppressing the DDR Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: JI-CJ002 augments the therapeutic effect of FOLFOX by suppressing DNA damage response and inducing aberrant cell cycle progression, thereby supporting its development as a chemo-sensitizing agent for colorectal cancer therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Analysis of Dynamic Conformal Arc Therapy and Volumetric-modulated Arc Therapy in Lung Stereotactic Body Radiation Therapy: Evaluating Dosimetric Performance, Treatment Delivery Efficiency, and Plan Robustness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DCAT demonstrated clinically acceptable dosimetric results comparable to those of VMAT for lung tumor SBRT, while offering superior treatment efficiency and robustness to MLC positional errors. These findings suggested that DCAT is an effective alternative to VMAT in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nodal Modulator Regulates Chemo- and Radioresistance in Lung Cancer <em>via</em> the Chk2 Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: NOMO and the Chk2 pathway are involved in chemo- and radioresistance in lung cancer, highlighting NOMO as a potential target for the development of gene therapies for the treatment of patients with lung cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Focused Ultrasound-mediated Disruption of Plasma Protein Binding Enhances Chemotherapeutic Effects of Paclitaxel on Xenografted Ovarian Cancer in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FUS can reversibly unbind PTX from albumin, increasing its bioavailability specifically at tumor sites. This targeted approach enhances chemotherapeutic effectiveness without elevating systemic toxicity or causing off-target damage, highlighting FUS as a promising adjuvant strategy for improving anticancer drug delivery in solid tumors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated Prediction of Pathological Complete Response to Neoadjuvant Chemotherapy in Breast Carcinoma Using Deep Learning on Pretreatment Core Needle Biopsy Samples]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our AI-based model accurately predicted pCR to NAC in breast carcinoma using only a limited number of high-cellularity image patches and basic clinical metadata, without requiring expert annotation. This approach may facilitate earlier treatment decisions and improve preoperative outcome prediction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-Perceived Response to Medical Treatment in Hemifacial Spasm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of smoking cessation and post-cessation weight change on suicide mortality in type 2 diabetes: A nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Smoking cessation was associated with a reduced risk of suicide mortality in people with T2DM. This effect persisted even among those who gained or maintained weight after quitting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sociodemographic determinants and comorbidities associated with polypharmacy among the adult population in Korea: a nationwide claim analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings may help reduce the burden of polypharmacy by facilitating the development of targeted strategies tailored to patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Topographic Progression of Geographic Atrophy and Visual Acuity in Non-Exudative Age-related Macular Degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The overall GA growth rate was 1.96 mm2/year in the 5-year follow-up of our Korean cohort. Changes in the GA growth rate in the nasal perifoveal region (Zone 2) may be associated with subsequent clinically meaningful visual decline.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SeamXSim: Seamless-textured virtual colonoscopy simulator via unpaired long-term video translation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colonoscopy is a critical procedure for diagnosing and treating gastrointestinal diseases, but its complexity requires extensive training for proficiency. Complication rates are frequently higher and procedure times frequently longer when colonoscopy is performed by novice endoscopists, indicating a need for effective training tools like virtual simulators. The unrealistic colors and textures of current simulators, however, diminish immersion, thereby limiting their practical utility. To address...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extended follow-up after gastrectomy in elderly patients: Improved postrecurrence survival but no overall survival benefit in patients aged 73 years or older]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Extended follow-up improved postrecurrence survival but not overall survival in patients aged ≥73 years. These findings suggest that follow-up strategies for this population may need to be individualized, considering overall health status and potential benefit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biologically calibrated and quantitative spiciness measurement based on a TRPV1-Responsive biosensing platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Scoville Heat Unit (SHU) scale has long been regarded as the standard for measuring pungency. However, its reliance on subjective human sensory panels inherently limits its accuracy and reproducibility. To overcome this limitation, we developed a biologically grounded spiciness assessment platform based on the activation of the transient receptor potential vanilloid 1 (TRPV1) channel, a key pain receptor triggered by capsaicinoids and mediates the burning sensation associated with pungency....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutation testing, treatment patterns, and outcomes in patients with unresectable stage III EGFR-mutated non-small cell lung cancer treated with chemoradiotherapy: Final analysis of a global real-world study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this rw study in patients with unresectable stage III EGFR-mutated NSCLC, CRT alone was the most common first treatment and EGFR-TKIs were the most common first subsequent treatment. OS was substantial despite relatively short rwPFS, which may be attributed to subsequent EGFR-TKIs. The findings highlight the unmet need for alternative treatments in this setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship: Is it an innocent economic actor, or a factor that could harm ecological sustainability? Evidence from the group of Seven economies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The escalating ecological threats, including climate change, degradation, and ecological footprints, have driven worldwide initiatives to strike a balance between economic growth and ecological sustainability. Despite being the engine of innovation and economic progress, entrepreneurship impacts environmental quality-some see it as harmful due to resource use, whereas others view it as a catalyst for green innovation. In this study, the impact of entrepreneurship on ecological sustainability in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intramedullary screw and plate combination technique for stabilization of anterior pelvic ring: when and how? - A technical note and case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The SPC technique is a feasible and effective approach for stabilizing challenging APR injuries, offering favorable clinical and radiologic outcomes while minimizing the risks associated with traditional plating.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Compliance of a Working Memory Multitasking Task Mobile Intervention for Children With Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder: Single-Arm, Pre-Post Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A 4-week gamified intervention improves attention and hyperactivity-impulsivity in children with ADHD, irrespective of medication status, demonstrating its potential effectiveness and acceptability as a treatment option. As this is a small pilot study and underpowered, larger studies with appropriate control groups are needed in future research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of Prophylactic Ureteral Stents in Colorectal Surgery: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The association between prophylactic ureteral stents (PUS) and postoperative complications was evaluated. Five electronic databases were searched to identify studies involving patients undergoing colorectal surgery (CRS) with PUS. Primary outcomes were acute kidney injury (AKI), ureteral injury (UI), urinary tract infection (UTI) and hematuria. Risk ratios (RR) and mean differences (MD) were calculated using a random-effects model. Seventeen retrospective cohort studies involving 104 162...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Telecare legislation priorities: A Delphi study grounded in ethical challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundThe growing incorporation of telenursing into the conventional healthcare system has raised urgent ethical and legal questions concerning the scope and standards of nursing practice. As nursing expands beyond traditional in-person care into digitally mediated environments, the lack of a legal framework in South Korea presents challenges to protecting patient rights and ensuring professional accountability.AimThis study aims to support the development of a regulatory framework for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerated Progression of Gait Impairment in Parkinson's Disease and REM Sleep Without Atonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: People with Parkinson's disease (PD) and rapid eye movement (REM) sleep without atonia (RSWA) often have more severe gait disturbances compared to PD without RSWA. The association between the presence and expression of RSWA and the rate of progression of gait impairment in PD is unknown. This study examined the changes in spatiotemporal gait metrics over 3 years in people with mild-to-moderate PD (median 1.5 years since diagnosis at baseline) with (PD+RSWA, n = 16) and without RSWA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol for in vitro transfection of mRNA-encapsulated lipid nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipid nanoparticle (LNP) platforms are promising for mRNA therapeutics; however, while highly effective in vivo, commercial mRNA-LNPs show reduced transfection efficiency in vitro under serum-starved conditions, limiting mechanistic studies and cell engineering applications. Here, we present a new standard for in vitro transfection of mRNA-LNPs, including cell culture preparation, mRNA-LNP treatment in complete media, and mRNA expression level quantification. This protocol improves efficiency...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microcirculation-Promoting Effect of Escin on Cutaneous Tissue via Gsk3β Down-Regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microcirculation in cutaneous tissue is essential to balance oxygen delivery and maintain the health of the skin. Senescence contributes to microcirculatory dysfunction through mechanisms involving chronic inflammation, structural remodeling of microvessels, and disturbances in hemodynamics. In this study we investigated the promoting effect of escin on blood flow through topical application. To elucidate the molecular mechanisms of escin, kinase phosphorylation changes in human umbilical vein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Saucerneol D Suppresses the Growth of <em>Helicobacter pylori</em> and Their Virulence Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Helicobacter pylori infects the human stomach and causes various gastrointestinal diseases. Saucerneol D is a type of lignan, which is a polyphenol compound that exists naturally in plants, and it is abundant in flaxseed, sesame seeds, whole grains, vegetables, and fruits. Saucerneol D is found in Saurus chinensis extract and has been reported to exert a variety of effects, such as antioxidant and anti-inflammatory abilities. However, its antibacterial effect against H. pylori has not been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of a Natural Polyherbal Extract on Alleviating Scopolamine-Induced Memory Deficits in C57BL/6 Mice via Enhancing Cholinergic Function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurological condition with limited effective pharmaceutical treatments, often accompanied by side effects. This has increased interest in plant-based alternatives. This study examined the cognitive effects of a Natural Polyherbal Extract (NPX) on scopolamine-induced memory deficits in mice. Male C57BL/6 mice (10 weeks old, n = 36) were divided into four groups: control (saline), scopolamine (1 mg/kg, i.p.), tacrine (10 mg/kg, oral), and NPX (1000 mg/kg,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strain-Dependent Contact Engineering in Monolayer MoS<sub>2</sub>: Enhancing Charge Carrier Transport through 1D Edge Contacts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Contact engineering is crucial for optimizing the performance of two-dimensional (2D) devices. Despite the remarkable mechanical flexibility, there is insufficient understanding of how applied strain influences the contact properties and charge carrier dynamics at junction interfaces. Electrical characterization and theoretical calculation revealed that tensile strain significantly reduces contact resistance (R(C)) and Schottky barrier height (SBH) in 1D edge contacts. Specifically, the R(C) of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An In-Hospital Mortality Prediction Model for Acute Pesticide Poisoning in the Emergency Department]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pesticide poisoning remains a significant public health issue, characterized by high morbidity and mortality, particularly among patients presenting to the emergency department. This study aimed to develop a 14-day in-hospital mortality prediction model for patients with acute pesticide poisoning using early clinical and laboratory data. This retrospective cohort study included 1056 patients who visited Soonchunhyang University Cheonan Hospital between January 2015 and December 2020. The cohort...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of the Chemical Components of PM<sub>2.5</sub> in the Dangjin Region, South Korea, and Evaluation of Emission Source Contributions During High-Concentration Events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fine particulate matter (PM(2.5); aerodynamic diameter ≤ 2.5 µm) remains a challenging policy for industrialized coastal regions throughout East Asia. In this study, we present a multi-year chemical characterization of PM(2.5) and identify key factors contributing to extreme pollution events in Dangjin, a heavy-industry hub on Korea's west coast. Between August 2020 and March 2024, 24-h gravimetric filters (up to n = 245; 127-280 valid analyses depending on constituent) were collected twice...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined Repeated-Dose Toxicity Study with the Reproduction/Developmental Toxicity Screening Test of Calcium Nitrate Tetrahydrate in Sprague Dawley Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Calcium nitrate tetrahydrate, used in fertilizers, wastewater treatment, and concrete admixtures, has limited toxicity data despite extensive industrial use. This study evaluated its repeated-dose and reproductive/developmental toxicity in Sprague Dawley rats following OECD TG 422, which combines TG 407 and 421 to extend dosing than TG 407 and reduce animal use compared with separate studies. Rats were administered 0, 100, 300, or 1000 mg/kg/day. Males were treated for 49 days and females from 2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proximal Effects of Blood Flow Restriction on Shoulder Muscle Function and Discomfort During Low-Intensity Exercise]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to examine the proximal effects of blood flow restriction (BFR) training on shoulder muscle function and subjective discomfort during low-intensity external rotation exercise. Twenty-four healthy adults were randomly assigned to a BFR group or a control group and performed shoulder stabilization exercises with or without BFR. Outcome measures included shoulder external rotation range of motion, maximal isometric strength, muscle endurance, electromyographic activity of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunogenicity and Contraceptive Potential of a Classical Swine Fever Viral Vector Live Vaccine Strain Containing Pig Gonadotropin-Releasing Hormone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Flc-LOM-GnRHx3 demonstrates potential as a dual-function oral vaccine that can eradicate CSFV and impair reproductive capacity in wild boars, offering a novel approach for integrated disease control and population management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and Prospects of Lignin-Derived Hard Carbons for Next-Generation Sodium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lignin-derived hard carbon (LHC) has emerged as a highly promising anode material for sodium-ion batteries (SIBs), owing to its renewable nature, structural tunability, and notable electrochemical properties. Although considerable advancements have been made in the development of LHCs in recent years, the absence of a comprehensive and critical review continues to impede further innovation in the field. To address this deficiency, the present review begins by examining the intrinsic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polymeric Frontiers in Next-Generation Energy Storage: Bridging Molecular Design, Multifunctionality, and Device Applications Across Batteries, Supercapacitors, Solid-State Systems, and Beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymer materials have become promising candidates for next-generation energy storage, with structural tunability, multifunctionality, and compatibility with a variety of device platforms. They have a molecular design capable of customizing ion and electron transport routes, integrating redox-active species, and enhancing interfacial stability, surpassing the drawbacks of traditional inorganic systems. New developments have been made in multifunctional polymers that have the ability to combine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rational Approach for Evaluating Fire Resistance of Prestressed Concrete Beams Strengthened with Fiber-Reinforced Polymers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A rational approach is proposed for evaluating the fire resistance of fiber-reinforced polymers (FRP)-strengthened prestressed concrete (PC) beams. This approach expands on conventional fire design principles for PC beams, while incorporating the effects of FRP reinforcement and fire insulation into strength calculations under fire exposure. Simplified equations are utilized to evaluate the cross-sectional temperature distribution in fire-exposed FRP-strengthened PC beams, considering both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anticancer Activity of Snake Venom Against Breast Cancer: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer remains a leading cause of cancer-related mortality worldwide, necessitating innovative therapeutic approaches. This scoping review summarizes experimental evidence on the anticancer activity of snake venom and its bioactive components against breast cancer, drawing from a variety of in vitro and in vivo studies. Aimed at critically evaluating the therapeutic potential and underlying mechanisms, this review consolidates findings on venoms from multiple snake species, including both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monoplane Simpson's Method Is Reliable for Left Atrial Volume Assessment in Small Dogs with Myxomatous Mitral Valve Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Left atrial enlargement is a key marker of disease progression and prognosis in dogs with myxomatous mitral valve disease. Echocardiographic assessment of left atrial volume provides a more comprehensive measure than linear dimensions, yet different two-dimensional methods may yield variable results. This study aimed to compare the monoplane Simpson's method of discs and the biplane area-length method for estimating left atrial volume indexed to body weight in dogs across different stages of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suspected Tumor-Related Hemorrhage as a Rare Complication of Stereotactic Body Radiotherapy in a Dog with Cranial Mediastinal Mass: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stereotactic body radiotherapy (SBRT) has been increasingly used in dogs for mediastinal tumors and is generally considered a precise and relatively safe treatment, with clinically significant complications reported only rarely. A cranial mediastinal mass was incidentally identified in a 10-year-old Pomeranian dog and cytologically diagnosed as a carcinoma. SBRT was performed using volumetric-modulated arc therapy, with a total dose of 27 Gy delivered in three fractions on alternate days. One...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Temperature, pH, and Relative Humidity on Growth of <em>Penicillium crustosum</em> OM1 Isolated from Pears and Its Penitrem A Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Penitrem A, an indole-diterpenoid neurotoxin, is produced by several species of Penicillium on cereal grains, meat, dairy products, and fruits. Penicillium crustosum is a well-known penitrem A producer, but much is unknown about physiological characteristics of P. crustosum. In this study, we isolated penitrem A-producing P. crustosum OM1 from pears, and investigated the influence of temperature, pH, and relative humidity [RH] on its growth and penitrem A production. The fungal species exhibited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Insights into Organoid-Derived Extracellular Vesicles and Their Biomedical Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles (EVs) play a crucial role in cell-to-cell communication by transporting functionally active molecules, including proteins, lipids, and nucleic acids. While extensive research has focused on EVs generated from traditional two-dimensional (2D) monolayer cultures (2D-EVs), the emergence of three-dimensional (3D) organoid systems has led to the development of organoid-derived EVs (OEVs), which more closely mimic the physiological conditions of native tissues. In contrast to 2D...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acellular Extracellular Matrix Scaffolds in Regenerative Medicine: Advances in Decellularization and Clinical Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decellularized extracellular matrix (dECM) scaffolds preserve native tissue structure and biochemical cues while minimizing immune responses, creating biomimetic templates that promote cell integration and tissue remodeling. This review examines the current state of dECM research, encompassing decellularization methods, scaffold quality evaluation assays, and tissue-specific applications across dermis, nerve, heart, lung, adipose, and placental ECMs. We analyze commercially available dECM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nano-Enabled Agrochemicals for Heavy Metal Remediation in Agriculture: Current Status, Mechanisms, and Future Prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heavy metals (HMs) contamination in agricultural soils poses significant risks to crop production and human health through bioaccumulation in the food chain. While traditional remediation techniques exist, they often face limitations including high operational costs, low efficiency, and time-intensive processes. Nano-enabled agrochemicals have emerged as a promising solution for HM remediation in contaminated soils. In this review, we highlight distinct nano-enabled mechanisms involved in HMs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomass-Derived Hard Carbon Anodes for Sodium-Ion Batteries: Recent Advances in Synthesis Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biomass-derived hard carbon (BHC) has attracted considerable attention as a sustainable and cost-effective anode material for sodium-ion batteries (SIBs), owing to its natural abundance, environmental friendliness, and promising electrochemical performance. This review provides a detailed overview of recent progress in the synthesis, structural design, and performance optimization of BHC materials. It encompasses key fabrication routes, such as high-temperature pyrolysis, hydrothermal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Irreversible Plastic Flows and Sedimentary Ecological Entrapment: A Critical Review of Legacy Risks and Governance Strategies for Planetary Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plastic pollution has emerged as a pervasive and systemic driver of ecological and biogeochemical disruption in freshwater and marine environments. Unlike natural materials that circulate within closed biogeochemical loops, synthetic polymers predominantly follow unidirectional and irreversible trajectories, a phenomenon we describe as "irreversible plastic transport." These flows culminate in sedimentary entrapment, where plastics persist as long-term ecological stressors and potential vectors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative Genomic and Clinicopathologic Characterization of Pure Primary Ovarian Large Cell Neuroendocrine Carcinoma: A Case Report and Molecular Insight]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary ovarian large cell neuroendocrine carcinoma is an extremely rare and aggressive gynecologic malignancy with poorly defined molecular characteristics and no standard treatment protocols. We present a case of pure ovarian LCNEC in a postmenopausal woman who underwent optimal cytoreductive surgery followed by platinum-based chemotherapy. Histopathologic and immunohistochemical analyses confirmed the diagnosis. Next-generation sequencing (NGS) revealed a pathogenic BRCA2 frameshift mutation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Phase Ib Study of Indirect Immunization with Oregovomab and Toll-like-Receptor-3 Stimulation with Hiltonol<sup>®</sup> in Patients with Recurrent Platinum-Resistant Ovarian Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: This phase Ib study assessed the safety and compatibility of indirect oregovomab immunization and Toll-like-receptor-3 (TLR3) stimulation with immune adjuvant Hiltonol^(®) (poly-ICLC) and induced clinically relevant CA125-specific anti-tumor immunity in heavily pretreated patients with progressive platinum-resistant ovarian cancer (PROC). Methods: Patients with elevated serum CA125 level >50 U/mL received four intravenous infusions with 2 mg oregovomab followed by 2 mg Hiltonol^(®)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-Based Understanding of Cu<sup>2+</sup> Coordination in Fluorescent Proteins for Metal Biosensor Applications-A Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Copper ions play essential roles in biological systems, but they can cause toxicity following dysregulation or excessive accumulation. In addition, environmental overexposure to Cu^(2+) can lead to serious agricultural and ecological issues. Accurate detection of Cu^(2+) is therefore critical in both medical diagnostics and environmental monitoring. Fluorescent proteins (FPs), which are widely used in molecular and cell biology, have been suggested as attractive modalities for metal ion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Freshness Indicator (FI) for Skate Sashimi (<em>Zearaja chilensis</em>) to Detect Trimethylamine Content During Storage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The seafood industry is increasingly adopting intelligent packaging to preserve product quality and improve freshness transparency. This study developed and evaluated a pH-sensitive freshness indicator (FI) for skate sashimi (Zearaja chilensis). This product is consumed at varying stages of fermentation. The FI incorporated bromothymol blue (BTB) and bromocresol purple (BCP) in a polymer matrix. It targeted volatile basic nitrogen (VBN) compounds, with trimethylamine (TMA) as the primary marker....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designing Light for Emotion: A Neurophysiological Approach to Modeling Affective Responses to the Interplay of Color and Illuminance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the influence of indoor environments on human emotional regulation and cognitive function becomes increasingly critical in modern society, there is a growing need for intelligent lighting systems that dynamically respond to users' emotional states. While previous studies have investigated either illuminance or color in isolation, this study concentrates on quantitatively analyzing the interaction of these two key elements on human emotion and cognitive control capabilities. Utilizing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design and Flight Experiment of a Motor-Directly-Driven Flapping-Wing Micro Air Vehicle with Extension Springs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents the design, control, and flight experiments of a motor-directly-driven flapping-wing micro air vehicle with extension springs (MDD-FWMAVES). The flapping wing actuation utilizes the resonance of a linear extension spring and a flapping wing. The analysis results of the proposed MDD-FWMAVES revealed a resonant frequency of 19.59 Hz for the flapping-wing mechanism, and actual flapping experiments confirmed this to be 20 Hz. Using a six-axis load cell, we demonstrated the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bio-Derived Metamaterials: A Hierarchical Biomimetics-Based Evaluation System for Cross-Scale Performance in Chaozhou Woodcarving]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For centuries, artisans have resolved intricate engineering conundrums with intuitive ingenuity, bequeathing a legacy of design wisdom that remains largely untapped in contemporary biomimetics. This "anthro-creative" form of biomimicry, deeply embedded within traditional crafts such as Chaozhou woodcarving, is predominantly tacit and qualitative, which has traditionally eluded systematic interpretation. To address this, we propose the Hierarchical Biomimetics-Based Evaluation System (HBBES), a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced 3D In Vitro Liver Fibrosis Models: Spheroids, Organoids, and Liver-on-Chips]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liver fibrosis (LF) is a progressive and increasingly prevalent condition, yet current therapeutic options remain limited. This underscores the growing demand for advanced three-dimensional (3D) preclinical models that better recapitulate the complex pathophysiology of human LF and overcome the limitations of conventional systems. Although a number of in vitro models have been proposed in recent years, many still rely on two-dimensional (2D) hepatocyte cultures, which fail to represent the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alternative Lengthening of Telomeres: A Prognostic Paradox in Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Telomere maintenance enables unlimited cell proliferation by counteracting telomere erosion. While the majority of tumors activate telomerase, a significant subset-approximately 10-15%-utilizes alternative lengthening of telomeres (ALT), a recombination-based mechanism. ALT-positive cancers are classically associated with genomic instability, anaphase bridges, chromosomal rearrangements, and resistance to DNA-damaging therapies. This process is closely associated with genetic instability, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Antimicrobial Resistance and Hypervirulent Traits of <em>Klebsiella variicola</em> Isolates Collected in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction: Klebsiella variicola, a member of Klebsiella pneumoniae complex, has emerged as an opportunistic pathogen for human infection; however, antimicrobial resistance and hypervirulent characteristics of K. variicola have rarely been investigated in South Korea. Methods: We analyzed 76 clinical K. variicola isolates collected from 12 hospitals between September 2022 and October 2023. Bacterial identification was performed by MALDI-TOF MS. Antimicrobial susceptibility was tested by disk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Attitudes of Cancer Patients Towards Vaccination in a Multiethnic Middle-Income Country: A Qualitative Inquiry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study underscores the need for tailored vaccination education for cancer patients, highlighting the importance of addressing misinformation and fears to improve vaccine uptake. These findings can guide future strategies to enhance vaccine acceptance in this vulnerable population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A 3D Printed Poly(ε-caprolactone)-Collagen Hybrid Mesh (TissueDerm) for Breast Reconstruction after Mastectomy in a Pig Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The study found that TissueDerm has advantages over ADM in terms of easier tissue invasion and reduced spheroidization in a porcine model. The results showed that TissueDerm is a promising new mesh for implant-based breast reconstruction (IBBR) and could potentially replace ADM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precious-metal-free rGO/NiMnB nanoarchitectonics with covalent metal support interaction for efficient and durable alkaline water splitting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To accelerate the widespread adoption of green hydrogen energy, developing cost-effective, sustainable electrocatalysts that can replace precious metals is essential. This study introduces a bifunctional electrocatalyst for overall water splitting, comprising 2D reduced graphene oxide (rGO) integrated with NiMnB nanosheets into a tailored nanohybrid (rGO/Ni(1.5)Mn(0.5)B). The integration enhances both crystal growth and catalytic activity by promoting rapid nucleation and efficient electron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obstructive Sleep Apnea and Cerebral Microbleeds in Middle-Aged and Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, moderate to severe OSA was independently associated with an increased risk of incident CMBs over an 8-year follow-up. These results add to the evidence for the importance of sleep apnea to brain health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a weighted Subjective Memory Complaints Questionnaire (SMCQ-R) for early symptomatic Alzheimer's disease detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundSubjective memory complaints are potential early indicators of Alzheimer's disease (AD), but their diagnostic utility is limited by high prevalence in cognitively normal older adults. The original Subjective Memory Complaints Questionnaire (SMCQ) shows suboptimal specificity and assigns equal weight to all items.ObjectiveTo develop and validate a revised SMCQ (SMCQ-R) with improved diagnostic accuracy through systematic item selection and empirical weighting.MethodsUsing a development...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Short-Term Surgical Outcomes for Thymectomy with Various Minimally Invasive Approaches: A Single-Center Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: All three minimally invasive approaches for thymectomy demonstrated comparable short-term outcomes, although robot-assisted thoracic surgery procedures had longer operative times. These findings suggest that lateral video-assisted thoracoscopic surgery, lateral robot-assisted thoracic surgery, and subxiphoid robot-assisted thoracic surgery are all safe and effective options, enabling surgeons to select the most appropriate technique based on individual patient characteristics and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From childhood trauma to complex PTSD: a network analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Network analysis enables the understanding of complex posttraumatic stress disorder (CPTSD) as interconnected symptoms, with Bayesian networks allowing causal inference. However, existing network studies have included populations with varied trauma types and durations, yielding mixed results, and have rarely incorporated trauma histories into the analyses, despite their etiological significance.Objective: This study examines the structural relationships and potential pathways between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reversible Chemistry for Cancer Therapy and Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reversible chemistry strategies in cancer treatment and diagnosis have attracted significant attention due to their unique ability to dynamically respond to both exogenous (e.g., light, ultrasound, and magnetic fields) and endogenous (e.g., pH, redox potential, and hypoxia-normoxia) stimuli, thereby modulating the functional characteristics of materials. Reversible cancer therapy offers distinct advantages over irreversible cancer therapy including sustainable cyclic function, shape-specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Ink Writing of Skin-Mountable Free-Form Thermoelectric Sensors Based on Ag<sub>2</sub>Te Composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flexible thermoelectric sensors convert temperature gradients into electrical energy, allowing rapid, real-time responses to subtle temperature changes without relying on external power sources or mechanical vibrations. These features allow seamless integration into wearable electronics and humanoid robotic systems, where mechanical flexibility, environmental stability, and customizable design are essential. In this study, a skin-mountable free-form thermoelectric sensor was fabricated through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breast Cancers Detected and Missed by AI-CAD: Results from the AI-STREAM Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose To evaluate the characteristics of breast cancers detected and missed by artificial intelligence-based computer-assisted diagnosis (AI-CAD) during screening mammography. Materials and Methods This retrospective secondary analysis was conducted using data from the Artificial Intelligence for Breast Cancer Screening in Mammography trial (ClinicalTrials.gov: NCT05024591), a prospective, multicenter cohort study performed from 2021 to 2022. AI-CAD results were categorized into nine subgroups...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biphasic MoO<sub>2</sub>/Mo<sub>2</sub>C-Passivated Graphite Anodes for Fast-Charging Lithium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fast charging of commercial lithium-ion batteries severely compromises long-term cycle durability, particularly in cells using high mass-loading thick electrodes. Such performance decay originates from interfacial kinetic limitations in the graphite anode as follows: (i) a sluggish Li^(+) desolvation at the electrolyte-graphite interface, (ii) a hindered Li^(+) diffusion across the solid electrolyte interphase (SEI), and (iii) a restricted Li^(+) insertion into the graphite, which collectively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunicate-Inspired Carboxymethyl Cellulose Hydrogel Filler for Treating Age-Associated Vocal Fold Atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For the treatment of dysphonia and aspiration induced by presbylaryngis, injection laryngoplasty is widely conducted. Here, the feasibility of carboxymethyl cellulose hydrogel modified with pyrogallol (CMC-PG) is checked for injection laryngoplasty. CMC-PG, owing to its low viscosity, is easily injectable in liquid form and can self-polymerize into a hydrogel without the need for oxidative cross-linking agents. Moreover, the CMC-PG hydrogel demonstrates improved stability, tissue adhesiveness,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum nanoplasmonic alchemy: transforming yttrium into an on-chip hydrogen sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a nanoplasmonic hydrogen sensor based on a gold-yttrium-platinum plasmonic waveguide, numerically investigated using rigorous coupled wave analysis (RCWA). Upon hydrogen absorption, the yttrium layer undergoes a reversible phase transition from metallic to semiconducting, which alters its dielectric permittivity and modulates the optical response of the device. These hydrogen-induced changes lead to a pronounced plasmon resonance red-shift (Δλ) and enhanced differential reflectance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and Validation of Dynamic Prediction Model for Thromboembolic and Bleeding Risk in Patients With Atrial Fibrillation Initiating Direct Oral Anticoagulants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These dynamic prediction models offer a novel approach for reassessing thromboembolic and major bleeding risks in patients with atrial fibrillation receiving DOACs, demonstrating superior performance compared with existing models. Enabling regular risk updates based on the patient's current status, these tools support personalized and dynamic risk assessments in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Combining Traditional East Asian and Conventional Western Medicine on Acute Stroke Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TM, when integrated into CM care, may be linked to less favorable functional outcomes after AIS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxygen-terminated Ti<sub>3</sub>C<sub>2</sub>T<sub><em>x</em></sub> MXene <em>via</em> electrophoretic functionalization for electrochemical nitrate reduction to ammonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electrochemical nitrate reduction reaction (eNO(3)RR) is a promising method for efficiently producing ammonia (NH(3)), which is a carbon-free fuel and hydrogen carrier. However, eNO(3)RR suffers from low NH(3) selectivity due to the sluggish protonation steps (*NH(2) → *NH(3)), widely regarded as the rate-determining step (RDS), competing with N(2) formation. Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXene (MX) has emerged as a potential electrocatalyst for eNO(3)RR due to its excellent NO(3)^(-) adsorption capability,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Charged Polyampholyte Interfaces: Synthesis, Properties, and Antifouling Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biocompatible hydroxyapatite (HA) is a biomaterial widely used in the regeneration and replacement of dental and bone tissue. On these HA surfaces, complex multicellular communities known as biofilms are established by pathogenic microorganisms, contributing to 75% of all bacterial infections and presenting a significant public health concern. Among the various charged polymers, zwitterionic polymers are commonly used for antifouling applications due to their ability to form a strong hydration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in reactive carbon capture <em>via</em> carbonate/bicarbonate electrolysis for efficient CO<sub>2</sub> utilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical reduction of carbon dioxide (CO(2)RR) offers a crucial pathway for converting CO(2) into value-added chemicals. Despite significant progress in catalyst and electrolyzer development, the practical application of the CO(2)RR remains hampered by challenges stemming from limited CO(2) conversion efficiency by carbonate (CO(3)^(2-)) and bicarbonate (HCO(3)^(-)) formation. Reactive carbon capture (RCC) integrates CO(2) capture and electrochemical conversion, directly utilizing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heteroepitaxial Strain Engineering and Interfacial Energy Transfer Boosting Optoelectronic Properties in C<sub>60</sub>/WS<sub>2</sub> van der Waals Heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Engineered van der Waals (vdW) heterostructures, combining molecular semiconductors and atomically flat nanomaterials, offer vast opportunities to tailor optoelectronic properties at heterointerfaces. Here, the heteroepitaxial assembly of C(60) molecules on monolayer tungsten disulfide (ML-WS(2)), where an anisotropic compression strain within the C(60) lattice at the heterointerface induces the formation of 1D polymeric C(60) strings and activates otherwise symmetry-forbidden S(1) → S(0)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frequency and Associated Factors of Interruptions During the Medication Administration Process Among Nurses in South Korea: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings highlight the importance of understanding the distinct characteristics of interruptions and developing targeted strategies based on their sources and contributing factors. Creating supportive environments and fostering an organisational culture that actively prevents unnecessary interruptions are essential for enhancing medication safety and workflow efficiency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PRDX5 Regulates Mitochondrial Function and Nuclear Spreading in Myogenesis and Acts With PRDX3 to Delay Muscle Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings reveal a previously unidentified role of PRDX5 in coordinating mitochondrial function and nuclear positioning during myogenesis and muscle regeneration. The combined deficiency of PRDX3 and PRDX5 accelerates muscle aging by exacerbating oxidative stress and mitochondrial dysfunction, suggesting that enhancing their activity may be a promising therapeutic strategy to prevent sarcopenia and age-related muscle degeneration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strain-Insensitive Heater on Wrinkled Surface Integrated with Carbon Nanotube Bundles for Wearable Thermal Therapy and Multimodal Tactile Displays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flexible or stretchable heaters can generate heat despite their deformation, making them suitable for various applications such as wearable devices and human-machine interfaces. This study presents the development and characterization of a highly stretchable heater integrating vertically aligned carbon nanotubes (VACNTs) on a wrinkled elastomer substrate designed to maintain consistent heating performance under mechanical strain. Through a synergistic design considering both material and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the healing rate with meniscal repair concomitant with anterior cruciate ligament reconstruction and isolated meniscal repair based on magnetic resonance imaging signal intensity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: IMSI is a simple and conventional parameter for the assessment of meniscal healing. The healing rate of meniscal repair concomitant with ACL reconstruction compared with isolated meniscal repair using IMSI was similar to that of MRI reading. Thus, concomitant ACL reconstruction significantly improves the healing process of meniscus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Quadriceps Muscle Fatigue With Return to Preinjury Sports Following Primary Anterior Cruciate Ligament Reconstruction Using Hamstring Autograft and Tibialis Anterior Allograft]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The work fatigue, SLHD, IKDC score, and KOOS Sport and Recreation subscale were better in patients who returned to preinjury sports levels than in those who did not. Work fatigue of the quadriceps muscle and SLHD were associated with return to preinjury sports levels, whereas work fatigue of the quadriceps muscle, SLHD, and IKDC score were associated with postoperative sports levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the robustness of slide-level AI predictions on out-of-focus whole slide images: A retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings empirically suggest that the typical levels of WSI blurriness encountered in clinical practice may not significantly compromise the robustness of slide-level AI classification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PDGFRα+ fibroblast ablation exacerbates pathologic features in house dust mite-induced allergenic asthma model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Asthma, a chronic inflammatory airway disease, remains a major global health concern. Fibroblasts, the cell type responsible for tissue repair and fibrosis, are therefore a potential therapeutic target for asthma-related lung disease. However, the role of fibroblasts in the onset and progression of asthma is poorly understood. Thus, we sought to determine the consequence of fibroblast loss on lung homeostasis and asthma development using a transgenic mouse model to ablate PDGFRα+ fibroblasts. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of colorectal cancer in kidney transplant recipients and patients with end-stage renal disease undergoing hemodialysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The risk of CRC after KT remained significantly lower than that of patients undergoing dialysis, even after landmark analysis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Healthcare Photonic Nanomaterials and Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between coronary artery calcium and the progression of calcific aortic valve disease: a hospital population-based observational retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CAC was significantly associated with the progression of CAVD. Particularly, CAC≥400 was linked to progression toward significant AS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41146380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct NO<sub>2</sub> formation from N<sub>2</sub>-O<sub>2</sub> supercritical fluid plasma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate a novel approach for the direct formation of nitrogen dioxide (NO[Formula: see text]) in a supercritical nitrogen-oxygen mixture using laser-produced plasma. By tightly focusing a nanosecond laser pulse into the dense fluid, we generate a high electron density plasma that enables chemical reactions not accessible under ambient conditions. Optical emission and absorption spectroscopy confirm the in-situ formation of NO[Formula: see text], and parametric investigations reveal that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41145655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved 5-year survival with robot-assisted resection for locally advanced rectal cancer compared to laparoscopic and open surgery: A real-world cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Robot-assisted surgery demonstrated superior short- and long-term outcomes and the lowest total hospitalisation cost compared with other approaches. These results demonstrate the potential of robot-assisted surgery as a new standard of treatment for locally advanced rectal cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Cognitive and executive functions of top level para-karate athletes with intellectual disability" [Psychology of Sport and Exercise 82 (2026) 102998]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41152093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brain representation of numerosity across the senses and presentation formats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Humans can extract numerosity from different senses and a variety of context. How and where the brain abstract numerical information from low-level sensory inputs remains debated. Using multivariate pattern decoding and representational similarity analysis applied to fMRI data (collected from both male and female participants), we comprehensively investigate how numerical information (range 2-5) across different modalities (auditory, visual) and presentation formats (sequential, simultaneous;...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clarifying the real challenge: adherence, not efficacy, is the barrier to exercise as medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive protection by Lithium in bipolar disorder: Long-term, but not short-term, possible role of GSK-3]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the letter to the editor: "Structural challenges in using Japanese claims databases for real-world evidence in osteoporosis research"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating fine- and coarse-grained structural correspondences between deep neural networks and human object image similarity judgments using unsupervised alignment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The learning mechanisms by which humans acquire internal representations of objects are not fully understood. Deep neural networks (DNNs) have emerged as a useful tool for investigating this question, as they have internal representations similar to those of humans as a byproduct of optimizing their objective functions. While previous studies have shown that models trained with various learning paradigms-such as supervised, self-supervised, and CLIP-acquire human-like representations, it remains...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-salt intake exacerbates endolymphatic hydrops and alters aldosterone regulation in a Ménière's disease animal model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sodium excess is associated with worsening EHs in ES dysfunction, suggesting a relation between sodium intake and EHs formation in MD. These results support further studies, including a low-salt group, to clarify whether and how sodium restriction could improve MD symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A call for more robust and interpretable models in predicting treatment-resistant depression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variations in job turnover factors among internationally educated and U.S.-trained nurses: Insights from the 2018 and 2022 National Sample Survey of Registered Nurses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Retention strategies should address distinct organizational and personal factors influencing turnover in different nurse subgroups to strengthen workforce stability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overprotective parenting, parental perceptions of child vulnerability and developmental outcomes in children with congenital heart disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Healthcare providers may need to consider the diverse parental and child factors identified to initiate interventions aimed at parenting practices, realistic perceptions of their child's vulnerability, and reducing overprotectiveness to support favorable developmental outcomes in Lebanese children with CHD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defect of Dectin-1-mediated signaling promotes burn wound healing through attenuated oxidative stress and inflammatory responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results suggest that Dectin-1-mediated signaling inhibits burn wound healing by inducing the production of inflammatory cytokines and oxidative stress. Furthermore, topical administration of the Dectin-1 antagonist laminarin may serve as a promising novel treatment for healing after burn.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morphology of the subgenital plate gland in Solenopsis males (Hymenoptera, Formicidae)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The male subgenital plate gland was discovered by Janet in 1902, but has never been described in detail. We studied this gland in Solenopsis geminata and Solenopsis invicta using light and electron microscopy and are able to show the original section image of Janet. The unpaired gland is very large and occurs underneath the subgenital plate (= sternite 9). It is made up by over 1500 spherical to polygonal class-3 secretory cells of which the accompanying duct cells open through the ventral part...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gram-negative and Gram-positive bacteria induce different osteolysis progression profiles over time in fracture-related infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Gram-negative pathogens pose significant clinical challenges and there is an urgent need to broaden the focus on GN infections in FRIs. This study provides new clinical insights into the role of pathogen-specific osteolytic patterns in FRIs. Gram-negative bacteria exhibit the most rapid and destructive bone loss, emphasizing the need for early recognition and timely intervention. Radiographic osteolysis appearing early should raise suspicion for GN infections. These findings also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41151183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Baroplastic Effect of Aliphatic Polyester Block Copolymers for Degradation-Free Multicycle Processing of Poly(l-lactide)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advancing sustainable plastics is crucial to achieving a circular plastic economy. Baroplastics, block copolymers exhibiting order-disorder transitions under pressure, allow polymer processing at ambient temperatures, reducing energy use and avoiding thermal degradation. Their application, however, has been limited by structural constraints. This study introduces poly(ε-caproclactone-random-5-ethyleneketal ε-caprolactone)-block-poly(l-lactide) (PmCL-b-PLLA) as a "baroplasticizer" for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ColabReaction: Accelerating Transition State Searches with Machine Learning Potentials on Google Colaboratory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We have developed a rapid and automated transition state (TS) search method for chemical reactions by combining the double-ended method, Direct MaxFlux (DMF), with machine learning (ML) potentials. Compared to conventional quantum mechanical (QM) scan-based approaches, this method achieves approximately 2 orders of magnitude speedup, typically locating TS structures within 10 min. To promote broad accessibility, this method is implemented on Google Colaboratory (Colab), leveraging its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and Preliminary Effects of Community-Based High-Intensity Functional Training for Adults with Mobility Disabilities and Overweight/Obesity: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A community-based HIFT program is feasible and may improve health outcomes in adults with MD and overweight/obesity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compressive Strength Prediction of Green Concrete with Recycled Glass-Fiber-Reinforced Polymers Using a Machine Learning Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fiber-reinforced polymer (FRP) materials are increasingly used in the construction and transportation industries, generating growing volumes of waste. This study applied a machine learning model to predict the compressive strength of eco-friendly concrete incorporating recycled glass-fiber-reinforced polymer (GFRP) waste. Based on 119 laboratory mixes, the model achieved a good prediction accuracy (R² = 0.8284 on the test set). The analysis indicated that compressive strength tends to decrease...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ganglioside Binding Assay: A Complementary Approach for Enhanced Tetanus Toxoid Quality Control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vaccine quality control has long relied on animal testing, which involves time, cost, and ethical constraints. This study introduces a ganglioside binding (GB) assay as a complementary in vitro screening tool for tetanus toxoid quality control, which was validated in a single-laboratory environment as a foundational proof-of-concept. The assay reproduces tetanus toxin binding to gangliosides on microplates using simplified procedures. Validation with samples at different inactivation stages...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bactericidal and Anti-Inflammatory Effects of <em>Ashitaba</em>-Extract Ameliorate the Gingivitis and Halitosis in Dogs with <em>Porphyromonas gulae</em>-Infected Periodontal Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ashitaba (Angelica keiskei) is a perennial herb native to Japan, traditionally consumed as a health-promoting food and herbal medicine. This study evaluated the antimicrobial, anti-halitosis, and anti-inflammatory effects of Ashitaba extract on canine periodontal disease (PD) caused by Porphyromonas gulae (P. gulae). In vitro, Ashitaba extract (0.006-0.1%) significantly inhibited P. gulae viability by up to 80% and reduced biofilm formation by approximately 10% at 0.1%. The extract also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of a Highly Toxigenic <em>Clostridium tetani</em> Strain from a Calf's Castration Site]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Whole-genome sequencing and immunoassay findings suggest that the rapid progression of tetanus in this calf could be associated with the strong toxin-producing capacity of the OPLHC-2022-Y645 strain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41150085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[6FDA-Based Co-Polyimide Membranes Incorporating Modulated MOF-808s for Olefin/Paraffin Gas Separations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MOF-808 was synthesized using different (perfluoro)carboxylic acid modulators, including acetic acid (AA), butyric acid (BA), trifluoroacetic acid (TFAA) and heptafluorobutyric acid (HFBA). These samples were incorporated into co-polyimide 6FDA-DAM:DABA (6FDD), and the performance of the resulting MMMs was assessed for C(2) and C(3) olefin/paraffin separation. Enhanced permeability was observed for both C(2)H(4)/C(2)H(6) and C(3)H(6)/C(3)H(8) mixtures thanks to the introduced porosity upon...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effect of Visual Attention Dispersion on Cognitive Response Time]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In safety-critical systems like nuclear power plants, the rapid and accurate perception of visual interface information is vital. This study investigates the relationship between visual attention dispersion measured via heatmap entropy (as a specific measure of gaze entropy) and response time during information search tasks. Sixteen participants viewed a prototype of an accident response support system and answered questions at three difficulty levels while their eye movements were tracked using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of Myasthenic Crisis and Emerging Roles of Molecularly Targeted Therapies: A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Myasthenia gravis (MG) is a chronic autoimmune disorder characterized by fluctuating skeletal muscle weakness. Myasthenic crisis (MCr), a severe and potentially life-threatening complication, presents with respiratory failure and requires intensive care and rapid immunomodulatory intervention. Conventional MCr treatments-such as plasma exchange (PLEX), intravenous immunoglobulin (IVIG), and intravenous methylprednisolone (IVMP)-remain standard treatments; however, they present significant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyethyleneimine-Assisted Fabrication of Poly(Lactic-Co-Glycolic Acid) Nanoparticles Loaded with Tamibarotene (Am80) for Meflin Expression Upregulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tamibarotene (Am80) is a promising anti-tumor drug that induces the expression of Meflin (a glycosylphosphatidyl inositol-anchored protein) in cancer-associated fibroblasts, thereby improving the tumor microenvironment. However, Am80, which is approved only for oral administration owing to its poor water solubility, has the challenge of poor tumor penetration. In this study, we developed poly(lactic-co-glycolic acid) nanoparticles loaded with Am80 (Am80-PLGA nanoparticles) as a potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41149714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerebrospinal Pharmacokinetic Modeling and Pharmacodynamic Simulation of High-Dose Cefazolin for Meningitis Caused by Methicillin-Susceptible <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Cefazolin is being increasingly used to treat central nervous system infections caused by methicillin-susceptible Staphylococcus aureus (MSSA) to mitigate the side effects of existing anti-Staphylococcal drugs. This study aims to develop a cerebrospinal pharmacokinetic (PK) model to predict the cefazolin concentration in cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) and to individualize the dosing regimen for MSSA meningitis. Methods: A cerebrospinal PK model was developed based on the existing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lipiodol marking for CT-guided radiofrequency ablation of adrenal aldosterone-producing adenomas: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CT-guided RFA with Lipiodol marking facilitated the effective treatment of aldosterone-producing adrenal adenomas in three patients by significantly enhancing lesion visibility. Adrenal arterial embolization should be addressed with caution to avoid damaging the small blood vessels of the adrenal gland.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cervical cancer in the modern era: cutting-edge strategies for diagnosis and treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cervical cancer remains a major cause of mortality among women worldwide, highlighting the need for advances in diagnostic and therapeutic strategies. This review provides a comprehensive overview of recent developments in histopathological classification based on human papillomavirus association, as well as progress in imaging and treatment approaches supported by current research. Emerging technologies, such as artificial intelligence-assisted imaging, targeted molecular therapies, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rare nodal involvement as the initial presentation of lymphomatoid granulomatosis, mimicking metastatic carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metal tolerance and recovery mechanisms of Priestia sp. Mn7 under pH 1.5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacterial metal recovery is regarded as an environmentally friendly alternative to chemical hydrometallurgical waste metal recycling. However, conventional studies are generally conducted under neutral pH conditions, even though typical acidic metal leachate is strongly acidic. Previously, we isolated the bacterial strain Priestia sp. Mn7, which can grow under neutral pH and recover metals (Co, Cu, Li, Mn, and Ni) under pH 1.5. This study aimed to clarify this strain's metal tolerance and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corneal higher-order aberrations after trabecular microbypass stent implantation combined with phacoemulsification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Following iStent inject W implantation IOP is reduced whereas, corneal HOAs remain stable for up to 3 months.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-term changes in retinal pigment epithelium after anti-vascular endothelial growth factor therapy for neovascular age-related macular degeneration evaluated by polarization-sensitive optical coherence tomography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: After anti-VEGF treatment for type 1 or type 2 MNV, RPE melanin distribution at the MNV and the surrounding area distinctly changed. They were associated with visual function. The present study supported deterioration of visual function in eyes with type 2 MNV after anti-VEGF treatment resulted not only from subretinal scar formation but RPE atrophy surrounding the MNV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical manifestations of immunoglobulin G4-related gastrointestinal disease: a nationwide multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: IgG4-GID exhibits characteristic pathological findings and various endoscopic features. Although many patients respond to treatment, some undergo surgery; thus, increased awareness may help avoid unnecessary surgeries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41148248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Metabolites of Fairy Chemicals in Tea and Coffee: Methylated AHX and AOH]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fairy chemicals (FCs), such as 2-azahypoxanthine (AHX), 2-aza-8-oxohypoxanthine (AOH), and imidazole-4-carboxamide, are molecules with diverse functions in plants. Methylation of plant hormones is recognized to affect the physiological functions of plants. We predicted that plants regulate the physiological activity of FCs through methylation and launched a project searching for methyl derivatives of FCs. We synthesized 7-methyl-AHX (1), 9-methyl-AHX (2), 7- methyl-AOH (3), 9-methyl-AOH (4), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41147966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251029033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>