<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 07:47:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sit-to-Stand Power From 2D Pose Estimation as an Indicator of Muscle Strength in Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Peak STS power correlated more strongly with muscular strength, while 5x-STS and 30-s STS tests were more closely related to physical performance. These findings align better with and provide stronger support for the AWGS 2019 framework.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex-specific difference on anxiety- and depressive-like behavior in neuronal growth regulator 1-knockout mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates that, in Negr1^(-/-) mice, both sexes show general behavioral alterations. However, female Negr1^(-/-) mice exhibit greater vulnerability to fear learning impairments and depression-like behavior, whereas males Negr1^(-/-) mice show heightened anxiety responses. These behavioral differences were associated with opposing ER stress responses and differential apoptotic signaling between the sexes in peripheral tissues. Our findings highlight the importance of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two-in-one protein tag enables the soluble expression and calcium-dependent purification of single-chain antibody fragments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-chain variable fragments (scFvs) antibodies are used in diagnostic and therapeutic biopharmaceuticals. However, its production is limited due to insoluble expression and lack of a universal purification ligand. Here, we report a novel two-in-one protein tag, termed CSQ-tag, utilizing a calsequestrin (CSQ) protein to enable the soluble expression and calcium-dependent purification for scFvs. The CSQ-tag enhanced the solubility of four different therapeutic scFvs with an average solubility...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasonic pulse transmission through an acoustic barrier using a metamaterial with input impedance matching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study proposes an input impedance-matching metamaterial to enable the transmission of ultrasonic pulses by attaching to only one side of a barrier. The metamaterial facilitates ultrasonic pulse transmission through the barrier by mitigating the mismatch between the characteristic impedance of the incident medium and the input impedance at the incident boundary of the barrier. The problem of designing the metamaterial is divided into two sub-problems by introducing a virtual intermediate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of organ-specific radiation dose reduction by integrated shielding configuration in mammography: A Monte Carlo simulation and experimental validation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Scatter radiation to out-of-field radiosensitive organs such as the eyes, thyroid, and axilla can contribute to peripheral dose during mammography. This study evaluates a system-integrated shielding configuration designed to reduce such exposure.&#xD;Methods: A high-density lead-glass face guard (LG-FG) and a hybrid compression paddle with stainless-steel (HCSS-paddle) were modeled using MCNPX for 25-35 kV Mo/Mo spectra under CC-view geometry. Simulation outputs were validated using OSLD and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Paulobutalipin, a Lipid Accumulation Inhibitor from a <em>Streptomyces sp</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new microbial secondary metabolite, paulobutalipin (1), was isolated and characterized from the culture of a mountain soil-derived Streptomyces strain. The structure of paulobutalipin (1) was elucidated through a combined analysis of spectroscopic data, single-crystal X-ray diffraction, chemical modifications including application of the modified Mosher's method, and electronic circular dichroism calculations. In an in vitro hepatocellular steatosis model induced by palmitic and oleic acids,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Longitudinal Impact of Discrimination on Substance Use among Filipino and Korean American Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial Correlations of Charge Density Wave Order across the Transition in 2H-NbSe_{2}]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Charge density waves (CDWs) involve coupled amplitude and phase degrees of freedom, but direct access to local amplitude correlations remains experimentally challenging. Here, we report cryogenic four-dimensional scanning transmission electron microscopy measurements of CDW ordering in a 2H-NbSe_{2} flake of 24 nm thickness, enabled by liquid-helium-based cooling. By mapping the spatial distribution of CDW superlattice intensities at nanometer-scale resolution and analyzing their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors influencing elderly patients' intention to use digital healthcare services: A cross-sectional correlational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Developing and providing standardized intervention strategies to enhance social influence and effort expectancy regarding digital healthcare services for elderly patients could improve their intention to use these services.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Removal of Co<sup>2+</sup> Ions in Aqueous Solution via Capacitive Deionization Using a TiO<sub>2</sub> Nanoparticle-Based Electrode]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cobalt contamination from industrial and radioactive sources poses serious environmental and health risks. Conventional removal methods suffer from drawbacks, such as secondary waste generation, high costs, and poor selectivity. Here, we present a capacitive deionization (CDI) system using a TiO(2) nanoparticle-based electrode to utilize their abundant surface hydroxyl groups and strong capability for redox processes. In particular, to enhance the adsorption ability of the electrode, anodized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward zero-calibration MEG brain-computer interfaces based on event-related fields]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Magnetoencephalography (MEG) offers high spatiotemporal resolution, but its application in practical brain-computer interface (BCI) systems remains limited partially due to the need for user-specific calibration and inter-subject variability. We present a zero-calibration MEG-based BCI based on event-related fields (ERFs) by leveraging spatial filters and deep learning techniques. First, we developed an on-line ERF-based MEG BCI with a visual oddball paradigm, achieving the mean classification...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sir2 regulates selective autophagy in stationary-phase yeast cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autophagy contributes to cellular homeostasis by degrading and recycling intracellular components, especially under nutrient-limited conditions. While autophagy is well characterized under acute starvation in synthetic media in Saccharomyces cerevisiae, its regulation during the stationary phase of prolonged growth in nutrient-rich complex media, when cells experience gradual metabolic shifts and sustained stress, remains poorly understood. In this study, we identified Sir2, an NAD + ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing nursing competencies to support healthy aging in the era of super-aged society: A Delphi approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides foundational data, enhancing the professionalism and expanding the roles of nurses by specifically presenting competencies required to support healthy aging in older adults. These competencies can serve as practical and systematic guidelines to advance nursing education and competency development, enabling nurses to effectively support healthy aging in older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sialic acid-guided spatiotemporal hydrogel therapy for liver cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient delivery of plant-derived polyphenolic drugs to tumor sites in hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is challenging due to their rapid metabolism and the limited tumor-targeting capacity of current therapeutic strategies. To overcome these limitations, we developed a pH-responsive hydrogel-based drug delivery system (PA-CB) composed of a chitosan backbone functionalized with boronobenzoic acid (CB) and crosslinked with protocatechualdehyde (PA). Within this scaffold, protocatechuic acid (PCA)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Attenuated <em>Salmonella</em> secreting interleukin-21 activates T-cells and induces anti-tumor effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The tumor microenvironment is characterized by an immunosuppressive state. Although PD-1/PD-L1 blockade therapy activates the immune system against tumors, it has limited long-term efficacy, prompting the development of combination therapies with targeted treatments to improve cancer treatment outcomes. Recent advancements have revitalized interest in using attenuated Salmonella strains as cancer therapeutics that target tumors, induce immune responses, and promote tumor cell death, although...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A reframed landscape of causal emergence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Complex systems can often be analyzed at either the microscale of their individual components or the macroscale of their collective organization, yet it remains debated which level of description offers the most meaningful causal understanding. Hoel's recent study in Patterns addresses this challenge by introducing Causal Emergence 2.0, a novel formalization showing that a system's causal workings are best described by how causal influence is distributed across its hierarchy of scales.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aperiodic EEG signatures: unveiling the interplay between APOE ε4 and mild cognitive impairment subtypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Mild cognitive impairment (MCI) is a cognitive decline syndrome in the elderly, often a precursor to dementia. It is a heterogeneous condition that can signal degenerative disorders like Alzheimer's or non-degenerative conditions such as vascular issues, depression, or poorly managed diabetes. Early detection of MCI is crucial for timely intervention, and differentiating its phenotypes helps in understanding its causes, progression, and treatment. EEG, which records brain electrical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction of Reward Processing Deficits in Youth with Disruptive Behavior and Trauma Exposure: A Pilot Study of Neural Responses to Fluoxetine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We provide preliminary data suggesting that a serotonergic medication can correct reward processing and provide symptom improvement in youth with DBDs and a history of trauma exposure. Given the small sample size, more rigorous studies with larger sample size are needed to confirm these results. The findings of this study could aid future clinical research and treatment for this challenging population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the effectiveness of health checkup services in reducing depressive symptoms in older adults with chronic diseases: a community-based pre-post observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physiological, genetical and morphological alterations in Mycobacterium avium subsp. paratuberculosis mutants generated with the CRISPRi system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generating Training Data for Ureter Segmentation Using Dual-Energy CT Two-Material Decomposition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to evaluate the utility of dual-energy CT (DECT)-based two-material decomposition in facilitating the generation of training data for ureter segmentation. This retrospective two-center study included 180 patients who underwent DECT urography between April and July 2020, including 150 from Institution 1 and 30 from Institution 2. Virtual unenhanced (VUE) images were generated from the late excretory phase (LEP) images using a two-material decomposition technique. Ground truth...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-thermal atmospheric-pressure plasma promotes cellulase production in Neurospora crassa]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microorganisms, particularly filamentous fungi, have become the dominant platforms for industrial enzyme production due to their rapid growth, low cost, and adaptability. However, current production technologies face limitations in yield and cost-efficiency, prompting the need for innovative enhancement strategies. Non-thermal atmospheric-pressure plasma has emerged as a promising tool for stimulating microbial enzyme production. In this study, we have employed micro-surface dielectric barrier...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolution of Susac syndrome with a long interval between the attacks: a diagnostic challenge]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nasal epithelial zonation and turbinate morphology in infant common marmosets (Callithrix jacchus)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The nasal cavity plays a critical role in respiration and olfaction, functions supported by its turbinate architecture and epithelial distribution. The turbinates-primarily composed of the maxilloturbinate and ethmoturbinate-expand the intranasal surface area and provide a structural foundation for epithelial types. Although the common marmoset(Callithrix jacchus) is widely used as a nonhuman primate model in translational research, postnatal nasal turbinate structure and epithelial zonation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid Poly-D,L-Lactic Acid and Autologous Fat Transfer for Forehead Augmentation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The combined PDLLA-fat technique provided stable 12-month outcomes, with minimal decline from 6-month results. PDLLA appears to support adipocyte viability and scaffold integration, contributing to improved retention beyond traditional fat grafting. Longer prospective comparative studies are needed to confirm additive effects and 24-month durability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Operando insights into stability of perovskite-based solar water splitting devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perovskite-based solar water splitting systems are promising candidates for addressing environmental challenges, exceeding the commercialization efficiency of solar-to-hydrogen (STH) at >10%. However, the operational stability remains suboptimal due to insufficient in situ/operando insights into charge carrier dynamics. Here, we investigate the role of charge accumulation on operational stability through operando catalytic modulation via near-infrared (NIR) toggling on a photothermal catalyst....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Food and Beverage Branded Content Targeting Children on YouTube: Advertising Regulation Amid Australia's Social Media Age Policy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Australian children are frequently exposed to persuasive and potentially harmful branded content on YouTube, with limited transparency and weak adherence to existing self-regulatory guidelines. SO WHAT?: The findings highlight gaps in current self-regulatory frameworks and underscore the need for greater policy attention to how children engage with branded food content online. As Australia enacts a social media minimum age restriction, this study provides timely evidence that can...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategies for expanding the role of advanced practice providers in the Korean nursing workforce: a mixed-methods approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: To effectively strengthen APP roles, it is essential to build on the existing advanced practice nurse (APN) framework, which already includes structured curricula and national certification. Furthermore, integrative strategies should be developed to incorporate experienced clinical nurses without APN licenses into the APN system.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multidimensional factors influencing the completion of advance directives among community-dwelling older Koreans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among older Koreans, AD completion represents more than a documentation process; it reflects a complex decision-making process shaped by their values and life circumstances, underscoring the need for supportive interventions. As the highest AD completion rates are found among older adults, related policies should be aligned with older adult-centered policy frameworks.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research ethics and emerging challenges in the era of coexistence with artificial intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hierarchical Al<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub>-carbon bio-waste microsphere composite as an effective adsorbent for phosphate recovery: Insights into adsorption kinetics and isotherms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phosphate contamination in aquatic systems is a major environmental concern due to its contribution to eutrophication, thus creating an urgent demand for effective and sustainable removal strategies is essential. This study investigates the phosphate adsorption performance of Al(2)O(3) and Al(2)O(3)/biomass-derived carbon composites with varying carbon loadings (10%, 25%, and 50% by mass ratio). The results revealed that incorporating an optimal amount of carbon significantly enhances phosphate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interactive Pathways of Key Prognostic Factors in Severe Asthma: A Bayesian Network Comparison of Clinical Trials &amp; Real-World Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The way in which risk predictors combine and contribute to severe asthma exacerbations may differ between clinical trials and real-world settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A year of significant progress for the Korean Journal of Family Medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of a Horizontal Invasion Length Threshold Predicting Posterior Corneal Flattening after Pterygium Excision]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Pterygium excision leads to significant posterior corneal flattening proportional to HIL, with 3.5 mm identified as a clinically relevant cutoff. Although the refractive impact may be subtle, surgeons should be aware of these posterior corneal changes as a consistent morphological response, especially in eyes with HIL ≥ 3.5 mm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychometric Properties of the Mixed State Severity Index for Patients With Mood Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The MSSI is a reliable and valid instrument for assessing the severity of mixed features in patients with mood disorders. The established cutoff scores enhance its clinical utility, providing robust diagnosis and treatment planning support.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Psychiatric Disorder Comorbidities With Global and Orbital Ablative Surgeries: A Real-World Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Globe and orbital ablative surgeries were associated with significantly increased psychiatric risk, particularly in younger men. Higher comorbidities and socioeconomic status appeared to mitigate this risk. Integrated mental health support should be considered in postoperative care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Psychiatric Morbidity in People Living With Human Immunodeficiency Virus: A Population-Based Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PLWH had a greater likelihood of experiencing psychiatric morbidities compared to those without HIV in South Korea. Our research findings indicate the importance of public health policy in addressing the declining mental health of individuals living with HIV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Psychiatric Disorders Following Carpal Tunnel Syndrome: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This comprehensive, longitudinal study indicated that CTS is associated with an increased long-term risk of psychiatric disorders. The findings emphasize comprehensive management strategies that integrate mental health screening and interventions tailored to age and sex among patients with CTS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Monitoring of Micro- and Macro-Movement Regularity in Psychiatric Inpatients With Depression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Digital monitoring provides an objective and continuous method to assess depression severity. By capturing macro- and micro-level movement regularity across day and night in an inpatient environment, this approach offers practical relevance for psychiatric care. However, results should be considered preliminary due to the limited sample size.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sinking skin flap syndrome masquerading as Chiari malformation: failed syringomyelia treatment rescued by cranioplasty. Illustrative case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Syringomyelia is most often associated with Chiari malformation, for which posterior fossa decompression is the standard treatment. Treatment failure should raise suspicion for alternative mechanisms, particularly in patients with a history of supratentorial craniectomy. In such cases, sinking skin flap syndrome (SSFS) may alter intracranial-extracranial pressure gradients, impair CSF dynamics, and result in an acquired Chiari malformation with secondary syrinx formation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Potential of HSP90 Inhibitor 17-DMAG in Regulating METTL3 for Kidney Fibrosis Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: N-terminal HSP90 inhibition, along with subsequent c-Jun suppression, contributed to the mechanism underlying 17-DMAG-induced METTL3 downregulation. Through this regulatory pathway, 17-DMAG effectively suppressed METTL3 expression and attenuated kidney fibrosis in both in vitro and in vivo models.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patent Foramen Ovale Closure in Stroke and the PASCAL Classification System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION AND RELEVANCE: Among young and middle-aged patients with PFO and otherwise cryptogenic stroke, the PASCAL classification algorithm distinguished the 4 of every 5 patients in the probable and possible groups with net benefit and the 1 of every 5 patients in the unlikely group with net harm from closure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive task analysis-based education and expansion of pure laparoscopic donor hepatectomy for the next generation: a comparative study of surgical outcomes between expert and fellowship-trained surgeons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CTA-based education effectively prepares FTSs to perform PLDH by establishing comprehensive strategies for LLR. Further research involving larger sample sizes, and extended follow-up is necessary to optimize recipient outcomes and validate this educational method.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of interactions between sealers and irrigants on the physicochemical and surface characteristics of endodontic sealers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CHX and NaOCl affected the physicochemical properties of both sealers. AHP was most affected by NaOCl, exhibiting delayed setting, reduced hardness, and increased solubility. AHPB was primarily influenced by CHX and NaOCl, showing increased solubility, reduced calcium ion release, and retention of irrigants on its surface, while element concentration and alkalinity were not affected by sealer-irrigant interactions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retraction: Recent advances in 2D transition metal dichalcogenide-based photodetectors: a review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retraction of 'Recent advances in 2D transition metal dichalcogenide-based photodetectors: a review' by Anique Ahmed et al., Nanoscale, 2024, 16, 2097-2120, https://doi.org/10.1039/D3NR04994A.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simultaneous Probe of the Charm and Bottom Quark Yukawa Couplings Using tt[over ¯]H Events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A search for the standard model Higgs boson decaying to a charm quark-antiquark pair, H→cc[over ¯], produced in association with a top quark-antiquark pair (tt[over ¯]H) is presented. The search is performed with data from proton-proton collisions at sqrt[s]=13 TeV, corresponding to an integrated luminosity of 138 fb^{-1}. Advanced machine learning techniques are employed for jet flavor identification and event classification. The Higgs boson decay to a bottom quark-antiquark pair is measured...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the STANDARD M10 Flu/RSV/SARS-CoV-2 Fast assay for the detection of influenza A/B viruses, respiratory syncytial virus, and SARS-CoV-2 in nasopharyngeal swab specimens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The STANDARD M10 Flu/RSV/SARS-CoV-2 Fast assay (M10 Fast), recently CE-marked, is an updated version of the STANDARD M10 Flu/RSV/SARS-CoV-2 assay. It includes additional gene targets to improve sensitivity and coverage and reduces run time from 60 min to 36 min. This study evaluated the analytical and clinical performance of the M10 Fast assay. A total of 664 nasopharyngeal swab specimens (108 influenza A-positive, 119 influenza B-positive, 79 respiratory syncytial virus [RSV]-positive, 165...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tolerance to ischemia-reperfusion injury in laparoscopic vs. open living donor hepatectomy with intermittent hepatic inflow occlusion: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We found no evidence that laparoscopic IHIO increases donor risk compared with open IHIO. Instead, LDH was associated with greater tolerance to IHIO-induced hepatic IR injury and lower biliary complication risk. These findings suggest IHIO can be used safely in LDH without added risk to open IHIO.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How the Rossetti Jaw Challenges Modern Beauty and Facial Aesthetic Norms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dante Gabriel Rossetti's portraits-most notably Lady Lilith (1867)-present a distinctive facial structure characterized by a broad mandible, heavy lower face, and a pronounced yet softened lantern jaw. This "Rossetti jaw," repeated across his muses, stands in marked contrast to both Victorian feminine ideals and contemporary aesthetic norms that privilege a V-line taper, reduced mandibular width, and accentuated midfacial contours. By examining Rossetti's visual vocabulary through the combined...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interleukin 12/23 and interleukin 23 inhibitors for moderate-to-severe ulcerative colitis: a systematic review and network meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Risankizumab was most effective in induction, while guselkumab was more effective in maintenance. Head-to-head trials are warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of social and psychological factors on suicidal ideation in elderly people living alone: A cross-sectional correlational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests the importance of identifying various social resources for elderly individuals living alone and exploring supportive measures tailored to individual circumstances. By predicting social risk factors that elderly individuals may face and preventing exposure to negative psychological states, early detection and intervention may reduce suicidal ideation, ultimately contributing to integrated community care policies that enhance the quality of life for elderly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable, scalable nanotechnology approach using filtrate from <em>Raphanus sativus</em> in combating multidrug-resistant pathogens and causing neglected tropical diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The green synthesis of silver nanoparticles (AgNPs) provides a more eco-friendly approach over the conventional chemical procedures. In this study, a fast and sustainable methodology for the production of high-density AgNPs utilizing the aqueous root filtrate of Raphanus sativus is presented.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-specific life expectancies across school districts in the United States: Applying a population weighted geographic crosswalk to aggregate census tract indicators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As standardized geospatial units with social meaning and direct political governance, school districts may be an optimal functional definition of residential neighborhoods. However, few measures of population health are available at the school district level. In this descriptive study, we implemented a novel application of an established geographic crosswalk framework to estimate population-weighted age-specific life expectancies for all 13,592 school districts in the United States for the years...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Historical Review of the Role of Indirect Cell Death in High-Dose Per Fraction Radiation Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Indirect tumor cell death due to tumor vascular injury from radiation exposure has been observed over the last ∼100 years. Vascular damage as well as stimulation of antitumor immunity contribute significantly to the response of tumors to many, if not all, high-dose per fraction radiation therapy regimens.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drug shortage in South Korea: machine learning-based prediction models and analysis of duration and causal factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The KMFDS should continuously monitor drugs with repeated shortage episodes through regular reporting, early-warning systems, and supply-risk assessments. Incorporating supply-side indicators-particularly those related to economic feasibility-into national surveillance programs may help prevent shortages and mitigate their duration. By identifying key predictors associated with shortage causes, this study provides evidence to guide policy prioritization and targeted interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design and Optimization of AlGaN/AlN/GaN L‑SBD for Radiofrequency Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This work presents a comprehensive investigation of the radiofrequency (RF) performance of lateral Schottky barrier diodes (L-SBDs) using an AlGaN/AlN/GaN heterostructure. The study aims to enhance carrier confinement and improve RF figures of merit by introducing a thin AlN interlayer between the AlGaN barrier and the GaN channel. The influence of AlN interlayer thickness (1-3 nm) on two-dimensional electron gas (2DEG) properties, current transport, capacitance, and dynamic behavior are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of concurrent use of conventional and <em>E</em>-cigarettes on rheumatoid arthritis risk among Korean adults: Findings from KNHANES 2015-2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dual use of conventional and e-cigarettes is associated with elevated RA risk, even among individuals with lower cumulative smoking exposure. These findings highlight the need for targeted public health strategies addressing dual users and underscore the importance of including e-cigarette use in RA risk assessments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct commensal bacteria in human nasopharyngeal lymphoid tissue associated with localized immunological memory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The nasopharynx (NP) serves as a primary site for localized immune responses that restrict the spread of SARS-CoV-2 to the lower respiratory tract. The microbiome is increasingly recognized as a key modulator of antiviral immunity but whether it shapes immune responses in upper airway remains uncharacterized. Detailed microbial profiles revealed that S. aureus complex abundance was the primary discriminating factor of microbial community in the NP and the enhanced abundance of S. aureus complex...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Safety Results from the Phase 3b SIERRA Study of Durvalumab and Tremelimumab as First-Line Treatment for Participants with Unresectable Hepatocellular Carcinoma and a Poor Prognosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The safety profile of STRIDE was manageable and consistent with the HIMALAYA study in participants with poorer prognosis than in HIMALAYA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated thermo-mechanical therapy for immediate relief in chronic non-specific lower back pain: a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A single session of ATT provides immediate, significant pain relief in individuals with cNSLBP, supporting its potential as a safe, non-invasive option for managing chronic back pain. Future studies should examine the long-term benefits of repeated ATT sessions and explore mechanistic insights into thermo-mechanical stimulation's effects on pain and function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a multimodal data collection system for adolescent mental health management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study presents a replicable framework for collecting rich, multimodal data from adolescents in real-world settings. By enabling integrative analysis of biological and psychosocial variables, the dataset lays the groundwork for personalized mental health prediction and intervention strategies. Future research should expand longitudinally and optimize context alignment to improve predictive precision and clinical utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of GPT-4o and Gemini Advanced on the Korean National Dental Licensing Examination: Accuracy, consistency, and question generation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: GPT-4o outperformed Gemini Advanced in accuracy, consistency, and alignment with its generated content. However, challenges remain in clinical domains and cross-model understanding, highlighting the potential of LLMs as supportive tools for non-English dental education and question generation while emphasizing the persistent need for expert oversight and domain-specific refinement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ruptured solid pseudopapillary neoplasm in children: a 20-year single-center experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ruptured SPN in children carries a measurable risk of true peritoneal recurrence, but radiologic findings may overestimate relapse. Tumor size and peripancreatic extension may help stratify recurrence risk. Complete resection, thorough peritoneal assessment, and long-term surveillance are essential. Multicenter studies are needed to refine management strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolution and Spread of Regionally Adapted Newcastle Disease Virus Isolates From Live Bird Markets in Nigeria, 2023-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Newcastle disease (ND) virus (NDV) infection ranks among the most important poultry diseases globally. In Nigeria, ND remains a persistent menace to poultry production, marked by recurrent outbreaks. However, there is limited understanding of the evolutionary changes and transmission dynamics of the virus in the region. A molecular epidemiological study was conducted to elucidate the evolutionary and transmission patterns of NDV in Nigeria. Phylogenetic analysis of seven NDV isolates from cases...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-specific prevalence and risk factors for severe activity of daily living disability among older adults residing in long-term care facilities in Korea: A cross-sectional study using first year of a longitudinal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Findings highlight the need for age-specific management strategies: muscle strengthening and exercise programs for young-old females, integrated and simultaneous management for the mid-old, and strategies to maintain core physiological functions for the old-old. These findings support long-term care policies and contribute to developing care systems in an aged society.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multi-Level Intervention to Address Childhood Obesity in Rural Hispanic Communities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although this multi-level community-based intervention did not show an overall intervention effect on BMI z-scores, greater engagement with the intervention components was associated with higher reductions in BMI z-scores. The findings underscore both the promise and the challenges of community-based obesity prevention interventions in rural communities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of non-invasive trigeminal nerve stimulation frequency and duration on cardiovascular responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the effects of trigeminal nerve (TN) stimulation on cardiovascular responses in healthy individuals. Sixty-one participants received electrical stimulation to the ophthalmic and maxillary branches of the trigeminal nerve at different frequencies (2 Hz, 20 Hz, and 200 Hz) while heart rate (HR), pulse arrival time (PAT), and heart rate variability (HRV) were monitored. Results demonstrated frequency-dependent cardiovascular responses, with higher frequencies (particularly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI for developing foundation models in radiology and imaging: engineering perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in generative artificial intelligence (AI) have accelerated the development of foundation models-large-scale, pre-trained systems capable of learning across modalities and tasks with minimal supervision. In the radiology domain, where annotated data are limited and heterogeneous, generative AI plays a critical role not only in enabling self-supervised learning and synthetic data generation, but also in addressing core engineering challenges such as scalability, multimodal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Image registration using MR-based synthetic CT (sCT) generated by cycle-consistent adversarial networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Image registration involves aligning multiple images within a common coordinate system to determine their geometric transformations. This study aims to improve diagnostic accuracy and efficiency by applying deep learning-based image registration between CT and MR images. Initially, the iterative closest point (ICP) technique was utilized to extract point clouds from CT and MR images and their corresponding segmentation masks. Through ICP-based alignment, the Dice Similarity Coefficient (DSC) for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Challenges in functional hydrogel application for chronic tympanic membrane perforation: practical limitations and lessons learned]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic tympanic membrane (TM) perforations often persist due to oxidative stress and hypoxia in the middle ear. A minimally invasive, biocompatible hydrogel addressing these challenges could serve as an effective therapeutic dressing. A thiolated chitosan (CS-SH) and manganese porphyrin (MnP)-conjugated polyethylene glycol maleimide (MnP-PEG-MAL) hydrogel (Ch_MnP) was developed through in situ gelation via Michael addition reaction. Its mechanical properties and antioxidant activities (SOD- and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hidden diversity of crust-like <em>Sebacinaceae</em> (<em>Sebacinales</em>, <em>Agaricomycetes</em>) in Asia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crust-like Sebacinaceae, comprising the genera Helvellosebacina, Sebacina, and Tremelloscypha, represent the only ectomycorrhizal lineage within the Sebacinaceae family. However, species delimitation within this group remains challenging because of their cryptic lifestyles, inconspicuous morphological traits, and limited taxonomic annotation. To address these limitations, we investigated crust-like Sebacinaceae in Asia by integrating two datasets: specimen-derived (barcoding) sequence data and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of SRS MapCHECK for CyberKnife patient-specific quality assurance: challenges with small cone sizes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study evaluates the suitability of SRS MapCHECK for PSQA of the CyberKnife system and highlights its limitations. It demonstrates that while SRS MapCHECK is effective for larger fixed cone sizes, it does not ensure dosimetric accuracy for plans involving very small fixed cones.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship between hand grip strength and lung function among older adults in Korea: Secondary analysis of the Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Findings showed HGS independently aligned with FVC and FEV(1), requiring a significant post-adjustment for confounders. Consistent with prior studies, results suggest HGS could indicate respiratory health in older adults. Despite divergent outcomes from earlier research, a persistent link between HGS and lung function underscores its value in geriatric screenings for early lung-decline detection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors influencing self-decision in withholding or withdrawal of life-sustaining treatments among older patients admitted to general hospital: A retrospective case-control study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The self-decision group (i.e., those in internal medicine, with cancer, admitted to general wards, and maintaining consciousness) chose reduced futile LSTs. These findings highlight the need to develop a standardized protocol for counseling and education to facilitate informed end-of-life decisions among older inpatients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the gaps in care for older adults: Continuity of care, person-centered care, and workforce development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcome of reverse total shoulder arthroplasty (comprehensive system) after failed rotator cuff repair with a medium-term follow-up: comparison with reverse total shoulder arthroplasty for massive rotator cuff tear without osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Considering the worse clinical outcomes of secondary rTSA after failed RCR compared to primary rTSA for mRCT without OA and/or CTA, careful selection of appropriate candidates for RCR or primary rTSA as a treatment option for mRCT without OA is essential, according to their healing potential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How employees of Korean franchise restaurants perceive older adult kiosk accessibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines how employees at franchise restaurants in South Korea perceive the accessibility of kiosks, which are increasingly replacing face-to-face service in the restaurant industry. While kiosks can enhance operational efficiency and reduce labor costs, they may also marginalize older adults, who often face barriers in digital environments. In a super-aged society like South Korea, ensuring equitable access to everyday services has become a critical social issue. To address this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering combination nanomedicines to overcome cancer resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Combination nanomedicine enables the coordinated delivery of multiple therapeutic agents using engineered nanosystems to address tumor heterogeneity, multidrug resistance, and systemic toxicity. Despite extensive preclinical progress, many combination nanomedicine strategies fail to translate clinically due to poor pharmacokinetic coordination, limited predictive models, and manufacturing constraints. This review examines design principles for co-delivery platforms based on liposomal, polymeric,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In-depth Biological Monitoring to Estimate Effects of Red or Processed Meat on Colorectal Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The intake of red or processed meat remains controversial as a crucial factor for CRC. Thus, we performed in-depth biological monitoring. Methods: We performed a case- control study and analyzed various exposure and response biomarkers including 1-OHP, MeIQx, and PhIP, and malondialdehyde (MDA), and heterocyclic amine (HCA)-DNA adducts in Korean cases and controls (N = 218). Results: They consumed 53.4 ± 74.0 g/day of red meat and 1.1 ± 3.7 g/day of processed meat. The CRC presence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of 4 first-line endoscopic biliary drainage modalities in distal malignant biliary obstruction: A systematic review and network meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Clinical success and adverse event rates were comparable among modalities. EUS-CDS-LAMS showed superior technical success and shorter procedural time. In contrast, EUS-HGS showed fewer reinterventions and better stent patency than ERCP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recalibrating academic expertise in the age of generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of generative AI (GenAI) into academic workflows represents a fundamental shift in scientific practice. While these tools can amplify productivity, they risk eroding the cognitive foundations of expertise by simulating the very tasks through which scientific competence is developed, from synthesis to experimental design to writing. Uncritical reliance can lead to skill atrophy and AI complacency. We propose a framework of essential AI meta-skills: strategic direction, critical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dispatcher-assisted cardiopulmonary resuscitation for out-of-hospital cardiac arrest patients: a site-level analysis of the PAROS trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Both intervention packages improved BCPR rates, with most sites showing steeper improvements post-intervention. However, variations in timing and magnitude between sites highlight differing levels of system readiness and implementation rigor. Reduced variability has been observed post-intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Omniphobic Polymer/Graphene Oxide-Coated PVDF Membrane for Stable Membrane Distillation in Surfactant-Containing Seawater]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graphene oxide (GO) coatings can improve the stable operation of membrane distillation (MD) membranes in the presence of organic contaminants by enabling the transport of water vapor through narrow interlayer spacings. However, GO's intrinsic hydrophilicity requires complex, multistep functionalization to achieve antiwetting properties, posing scale-up challenges. Here, we demonstrate a scalable fabrication of omniphobic polymer-graphene oxide (OGO) coatings on commercial PVDF membranes via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successive-cyclic movement in humans and neural language models: testing wh-filler-gap dependencies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates whether auto-regressive language models (GPT-2, GPT-Neo, OPT) replicate human-like sensitivity to covert intermediate phrasal structures (CP vs. NP) during the processing of wh-filler-gap dependencies. We extend this inquiry to backward sluicing, an elliptical construction that provides a robust test for the representation of abstract syntactic structure. Across two experiments measuring processing difficulty via surprisal, we found a significant divergence from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A compensatory relationship between working and long-term memory for emotional faces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Previous research has presented contradictory findings regarding emotional memory enhancement, often demonstrating an "angry face advantage" in working memory (WM) and a "happy face advantage" in long-term memory (LTM). However, the relationship between emotional memory enhancements in WM and LTM, particularly at the individual level, remains unclear. This study investigated the change in emotional memory for happy versus angry faces from immediate to delayed recognition and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring practitioners' frames of reference for discomfort management of nursing home residents with dementia: A Q-methodology study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Utilizing nursing home practitioners' frames of reference for managing demented residents' discomfort can be used for developing strategies that can be used in practitioners' education and promoting practice that can reduce discomfort of nursing home residents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A call for creating nursing evidence for older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing a framework for infection control education in nursing homes: Applying the mixed-methods Delphi technique]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: By integrating expert insights and validating the framework through the Delphi technique, the proposed framework enhances infection control training and education programs in nursing homes, ultimately ensuring resident safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the diagnosis: Unraveling <em>DSPP</em> genotype-phenotype correlations in dentin dysplasia and dentinogenesis imperfecta]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The DSPP gene regulates dentin mineralisation, and its pathogenic variants cause a spectrum of defects ranging from dentin dysplasia (DD-II) to dentinogenesis imperfecta (DGI-II/III). Clinical variability often confounds diagnosis. This systematic review of 48 publications (70 variants, 99 records) delineates quantitative genotype-phenotype correlations. Results revealed distinct molecular clustering: Exon 5 harboured 61 % of variants, predominantly frameshifts disrupting the repetitive dentin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical management of green nail syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic significance of dynamic changes in systemic inflammatory markers on mortality after liver transplantation: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose: Liver transplantation (LT) is a risky but life-saving treatment for end-stage liver disease. Dynamic changes in systemic inflammation can inform disease progression and postoperative recovery. This retrospective study investigated the prognostic impact of these chronological changes in patients undergoing LT. Methods: Inflammatory statuses were assessed using the neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio (NLR), monocyte-to-lymphocyte ratio (MLR), and platelet-to-lymphocyte ratio (PLR) measured...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational Resolution Enhancement of Mitochondria monitoring in Multiple Organs using Intravital Two-Photon Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objective: Understanding living cell mechanisms and enabling intracellular monitoring requires advanced and often costly imaging technologies. Conventional fluorescence microscopy is widely used but suffers from resolution limitations, making it challenging to capture fine subcellular structures like mitochondria. While super-resolution microscopy may overcome these constraints, it introduces tradeoffs, including its limitation in intravital imaging fields and complexity in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ATOMIC: a graph attention network for atopic dermatitis prediction using human gut microbiome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Atopic dermatitis (AD) is a chronic inflammatory skin disease driven by complex interactions among genetic, environmental, and microbial factors; however, its etiology remains unclear. Recent studies have reported the role of gut microbiota dysbiosis in AD pathogenesis, leading to increased interest in microbiome-targeted therapeutic strategies such as probiotics and fecal microbiota transplantation. Building on these findings, recent advances in computational modeling have...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of exercise on angiogenesis biomarkers in cancer patients: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Regular exercise was associated with only small and nonsignificant changes in angiogenesis biomarkers in patients with cancer. Although these preliminary patterns suggest potential interactions with angiogenic and immune pathways, the low certainty of evidence limits firm conclusions. Future randomized controlled trials are needed to confirm these effects and clarify how exercise prescriptions at different treatment stages influence angiogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical-based filler injection techniques for the midcheek groove and infraorbital region: Narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: An anatomy-based, layer-specific approach can enhance predictability and safety for infraorbital-midcheek rejuvenation, but current recommendations are largely experience-driven. Future work should prioritize controlled clinical validation, complication registries, and population-specific optimization of technique with robust, quantitative and patient-centered outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Ustekinumab in Asian Patients with Moderately to Severely Active Ulcerative Colitis: A Subpopulation Analysis of UNIFI Long-Term Extension through 4 Years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite the small sample size which limited data interpretation, long-term UST 90 mg SC treatment is safe and efficacious in Asian patients with moderately to severely active UC demonstrating clinical benefit, consistent with the global population. In addition, Asian patients with relatively stable clinical condition may benefit from UST 90 mg SC when administered in a q12w treatment regimen given its sustained efficacy and low discontinuation rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contrasting Patterns in Ambient PM<sub>2.5</sub> Exposure Disparity Across Population Subgroups in Urban and Rural India]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ambient PM(2.5) exposure poses the greatest environmental risk to public health in India. While several studies have quantified the changing patterns of exposure, the extent of inequality in exposure among population subgroups at the sub-national scale remains unknown. In this study, we examined the disparity in ambient PM(2.5) exposure across various population subgroups in urban and rural India and analyzed its changes in recent years by integrating satellite-derived PM(2.5) concentrations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41583010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Respiratory Coinfections on Outcomes of Pneumocystis jirovecii Pneumonia in Solid Organ Transplant Recipients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In SOT recipients with PCP, bacterial coinfection was associated with higher mortality, while CMV and non-CMV viral coinfections were mainly associated with morbidity. Respiratory co-pathogens may indicate illness severity; whether pathogen-directed strategies can modify outcomes requires further study.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Echocardiographic predictors of successful weaning from extracorporeal membrane oxygenation in paediatric and CHD patients with cardiogenic shock]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Left ventricular ejection fraction and velocity time integral provide valuable echocardiographic information for predicting successful weaning from extracorporeal membrane oxygenation in pediatric patients and may support clinical decision-making during weaning assessments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large joint line convergence angle is associated with accelerated coronal alignment progression in osteoarthritic knees: A longitudinal analysis of 10,841 knees]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Approximately one-third of limbs with baseline HKAA ≤ 177° and about one-quarter of those with HKAA ≥ 183° exhibited ≥0.50° progression toward varus and valgus, respectively. Accelerated alignment change was associated with greater baseline HKAA, JLCA and higher baseline K-L grade, suggesting characteristics of this potential phenotype.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction of 4D-Proteomics: A Breakthrough in Analyzing the Plant Proteomes During Stress Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proteomics is defined as the identification, quantification, and characterization of the complete set of proteins expressed in a cell or tissue under specific conditions. The last two decades have witnessed rapid advancements in proteomics technologies, including the development of the Data-Independent Acquisition (DIA) mode, which has significantly improved the sensitivity, reproducibility, and depth of proteome coverage. These advancements, together with the development of cutting-edge data...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Pyrene Induced Cardiotoxicity Using Dual-Cardiotoxicity Evaluation Method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pyrene (Pyr), a representative subtype of polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons, is primarily generated during the incomplete combustion of organic matter. As an environmental pollutant, Pyr has been reported to exert adverse effects on various physiological systems. However, data regarding its cardiotoxicity remain limited. In this study, we investigated the acute cardiotoxic effects of Pyr using human induced pluripotent stem cell-derived cardiomyocytes (hiPSC-CMs). hiPSC-CMs were exposed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redox-Responsive Multimodal Nanoplatform Based on Porous Silicon Nanoparticles with Copper Silicate Layer for Synergistic Anticancer Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional cancer therapies have been limited by severe side effects and low treatment specificity, leading to reduced survival rates and a reduced quality of life. In particular, the heterogeneity of the reductive conditions, such as high glutathione (GSH) and H(2)O(2) levels and acquired drug resistance, remains a major obstacle that traditional drug delivery systems (DDS) struggle to overcome. While GSH is especially essential for maintaining cellular redox, its upregulation in cancers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydro/Fluoro-phosphoro(di)thiolation of Allenamides: Toward S<sub>N</sub>2-Selective Transition-Metal-Free Formal Hydrocarbonation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two versatile synthetic strategies for β-H/F-enamide-tagged phosphoro(di)thioates from allenamides are disclosed, relying on electrophilic activation via β-H and F-iminium species. These developed straightforward protocols demonstrate broad applicability in complex molecular contexts with remarkable chemo- and regioselectivity. The synthesized allylphosphorothioates (APTs) act as potent electrophiles, enabling S(N)2-selective allylic substitution with (hard)C-nucleophiles of all hybridizations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alterations of Cortical Thickness in High Suicidality Patients with Panic Disorder and Their Relationship with Symptomatology and Treatment Response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggest that suicidality in PD may be associated with CT in specific EFN regions related to suicidal brain and that CT in these regions could play a critical role in anxiety symptomatology in PD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting and Early Detection of Delirium through Motion Patterns: A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Delirium is a common acute neuropsychiatric syndrome, and its early detection may improve clinical outcomes. This narrative review synthesized findings from 11 original studies and two systematic reviews that employed wearable sensors (actigraphy) to predict or detect delirium. In surgical, intensive care unit, and geriatric populations, delirium has consistently been associated with disrupted rest-activity rhythms, including lower daytime activity, increased nighttime activity, and fragmented...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brexpiprazole for the Treatment of Agitation Associated with Dementia due to Alzheimer's Disease: Clinical Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dementia is a neuropsychiatric disorder that primarily affects the elderly, leading to a widespread decline in cognitive function and significant impairment of occupational, social, and personal functioning. In addition to cognitive deficits, dementia is frequently comorbid with behavioral and psychological symptoms of dementia (BPSD), such as agitation. When present, these secondary symptoms can exacerbate the clinical course of the disease, reduced treatment responsiveness, increased rates of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean Medication Algorithm Project for Depressive Disorder 2025: Comparisons with Other Treatment Guidelines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The sixth edition of the Korean Medication Algorithm Project for Depressive Disorder (KMAP-DD) was published in 2025. This review compared KMAP-DD 2025 with four major international clinical practice guidelines: Canadian Network for Mood and Anxiety Treatments Clinical Guidelines for the Management of Major Depressive Disorders, National Institute for Health and Care Excellence Depression Guideline, Royal Australian and New Zealand College of Psychiatrists Clinical Practice Guidelines for Mood...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploration of Naegleria-preferentially secreted proteins for identifying diagnostic candidates to detect Naegleria fowleri]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Naegleria fowleri is a free-living amoeba that can cause primary amebic meningoencephalitis (PAM), a very serious infection of the central nervous system. Early diagnosis of PAM is challenging, and the condition is almost always fatal. In this study, we conducted 2-dimensional gel electrophoresis (2-DE) analysis using N. fowleri trophozoite lysates and conditioned media to identify preferentially secreted proteins. As a result of the 2-dimensional gel electrophoresis analysis, 1 protein was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated with Clinical Outcomes of Repeat Gamma Knife Radiosurgery for Cerebral Arteriovenous Malformations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Repeat GKRS for incompletely obliterated AVMs may provide favorable obliteration rates. Adequate volume response after initial GKRS and lower SM grades may predict successful complete obliteration. Patients with prior hemorrhage and AVMs located in the posterior fossa may be at greater risk of hemorrhage after repeat GKRS. Larger treatment volume and shorter intervals between initial and repeat GKRS were associated with AREs. Extending the interval between initial and repeat GKRS may...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual Inhibitory Activity of 1-ethyl-3-(4-(hydrazinecarbonyl)-phenyl)urea Derivatives Against DNA Gyrase and Topoisomerase IV of Streptococcus pneumoniae as Antibacterial Agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compounds 18GP06-15 and 18GP06-08 exhibited potent dual inhibitory activity against S. pneumoniae DNA gyrase and Topo IV, with low cytotoxicity. These findings support their potential as lead candidates for further optimization in the development of novel antibacterial agents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127024727&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature-Dependent Chain Structures during Solution-Grown Crystallization via Atomic Force Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Semi-crystalline polymers are widely utilized due to their favorable cost, and their crystallization behavior is significantly influenced by crystallization temperature. In this study, we employed AFM-based SMFS (single-molecule force spectroscopy) to investigate single-chain folding structures in Polyethylene Oxide (PEO) at various crystallization temperatures (T(c)) to elucidate the temperature effect. We utilized force-volume (FV) mode for SMFS, which enables the measurement of single-chain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasmids as persistent genetic reservoirs of bacterial defense systems in wastewater treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In summary, our results demonstrate that UWS reduce the abundance and diversity of bacterial defense system genes. However, plasmid-associated defense systems can persist through shared mobile genetic reservoirs. These findings underscore the critical role of plasmids in bacterial immunity and provide new insights into defense system dynamics within urban wastewater environments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wnt10a exhibit spatiotemporal singularity in the temporal changes of angiogenesis in regenerated pulp-like tissue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: During angiogenesis in pulp regeneration, when SHED differentiate into blood vessels, Canonical Wnt signaling and VEGF-A are activated to form microvessels, and Tie-2 expression is enhanced to increase vessel circumference. Furthermore, Wnt10a was found to be activated in its early stages and decreased in its mature stages, with spatio-temporal specificity. Because its expression is very low, Wnt10a could be a biomarker to monitor the regenerative status of pulp regeneration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary fibre promotes chronic gut parasite infection via direct and time-dependent modulation of innate immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These data reveal T. muris-induced dysbiosis as a consequence rather than a causative factor of diet-driven changes in host susceptibility, and establish a direct link between dietary fibre and host defence at mucosal surfaces. Video Abstract.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HIBISCUS trial (hernia incidence with continuous barbed vs interrupted suturing in colorectal surgery with small incisions): a contemporary study protocol for a multicenter randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Incisional hernia is the most common long-term complication after abdominal surgery, including minimally invasive colorectal procedures. In Japan, fascial closure of small midline incisions is generally performed using interrupted suturing, but high-quality evidence comparing continuous barbed suturing with interrupted suturing is limited. Continuous closure may reduce the risk of incisional hernia; however, robust randomized data in laparoscopic and robot-assisted colorectal surgery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for recurrent cases of early-stage uterine sarcoma after complete surgical resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In stage I ULMS, a high mitotic count was associated with an increased risk of recurrence after complete surgical resection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare utilization and satisfaction: a cross-sectional study among Indian immigrants in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Employment status, gender, and residency duration were associated with healthcare patterns among Indian immigrants in Japan. While overall satisfaction was high (75-80%), higher health literacy paradoxically correlated with greater dissatisfaction. Future research should explore interventions to improve healthcare accessibility for recent immigrants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-organelle DNA-sequencing of chloroplasts and mitochondria in Arabidopsis thaliana]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organelle genomes govern bioenergetics and stress responses, yet bulk sequencing masks heterogeneity. We establish single-organelle DNA-sequencing by adapting a droplet-based workflow to mitochondria and chloroplasts, using a sorbitol-based isolation that preserves organelles for encapsulation, amplification, and sorting. In Arabidopsis thaliana leaves, 313 of 384 single-organelle amplified genome libraries passed quality control (261 mitochondrial, 52 chloroplast). Genome coverage breadth at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bulk RNA sequence analysis of the articular disc-retrodiscal tissue complex in a TMJ-OA rat model with anterior disc displacement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first study to establish genetic changes with the ADRC in ADD and identify factors related to TMJ-OA pathologies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The element of surprise distinguishes beauty from pleasure and interest in visuo-tactile perception of art]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening oral health in older adults: accuracy of the Oral Health Screener for use within the interRAI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Menin-MLL inhibitors as a new therapeutic target for middle ear cholesteatoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Middle ear cholesteatoma (cholesteatoma), also known as a cholesteatomatous chronic otitis media, is concerning because it expands into the middle ear with bone destruction and causes irreversible hearing loss. Surgical resection is currently the only curative treatment, but the high recurrence rate remains a major problem, necessitating the development of novel therapies. In our previous study, we demonstrated that histone modifications are involved in the pathogenesis of cholesteatoma and that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential mechanisms of SARS-CoV-2 inactivation by anionic surfactants: a comparative study of fatty acid salts and synthetic surfactants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite advances in COVID-19 vaccines and antivirals, SARS-CoV-2 remains a significant public-health threat. While handwashing helps prevent infection, the anti-SARS-CoV-2 activity of anionic surfactants in hand soaps has not been systematically evaluated. In this study, we compared five surfactants: potassium oleate (C18:1-K), potassium myristate (C14:0-K), potassium laurate (C12:0-K), sodium laureth sulfate (SLES), and sodium dodecyl sulfate (SDS). Viral infectivity assays demonstrated that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-crystalline Ba<sub>x</sub>Sr<sub>1-x</sub>TaO<sub>2</sub>N solid-solution photocatalyst with low defect concentrations for solar-driven water splitting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perovskite-type tantalum-based oxynitride photocatalysts are promising candidates for water splitting due to their suitable band positions and extended light absorption beyond 600 nm. However, their associated photocatalytic activities and quantum yields remain relatively low. Here, we show that a nano-sized single-crystalline Ba(x)Sr(1-x)TaO(2)N solid-solution perovskite photocatalyst exhibits state-of-the-art activity in separate oxygen and hydrogen evolution half-reactions. The improved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skeletal Diversity of Diterpenoids Isolated from the Soft Coral <em>Sclerophytum heterospiculatum</em> in Kikai Island]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Five new compounds with diverse skeletons, namely, lobophytumins G (1, prenylgermacrane-type), H (2, spatane-type), sclerophytumins A (3, kikainane-type), B (4, prenyloplopanone-type), and ent-obscuronatin (5, prenylgermacrane-type), were isolated from the soft coral Sclerophytum heterospiculatum collected from Kikai Island, Kagoshima Prefecture, Japan. Their chemical structures, including their relative configurations, were elucidated by detailed analysis of spectroscopic data such as NMR and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vectorized ULK1/2 and VPS34 Inhibitors for Tissue-Selective Autophagy Inhibition in Oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autophagy, the primary lysosomal degradation pathway, plays a key role in cell survival and homeostasis. In tumors, it is upregulated to support cancer cell plasticity, adaptation to the microenvironment, and therapy resistance, making its inhibition an attractive therapeutic strategy. However, since autophagy is essential in healthy tissues, selective inhibition in tumors is critical. To address this, we designed inhibitors of two autophagy initiation factors (ULK1/2 and VPS34) equipped with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Host range and antibiotic resistance dissemination are shaped by distinct survival strategies of conjugative plasmids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Horizontal gene transfer is a major driver of bacterial evolution and the global dissemination of antibiotic resistance genes (ARGs). Conjugative plasmids play a crucial role in ARG spread across hosts within their host range, yet the genetic and functional determinants shaping plasmid host range remain poorly understood. Here, we systematically analyzed the gene content of conjugative/mobilizable plasmids derived from Enterobacterales from public databases and found that two distinct survival...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Outcomes of Photoimmunotherapy for Oral Sites in Head and Neck Cancer: A Multicentre Subgroup Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Oral-site PIT demonstrated high antitumour activity with frequent but manageable local toxicities, necessitating proactive, multidisciplinary supportive care. This first dedicated multicentre analysis focused on oral illumination corroborates site-specific PIT evaluation and its integration within multimodal treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Standard Laboratory Parameters to Skeletal Muscle Mass: A Novel Prediction Model for Chronic Kidney Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A simple and reasonable predictive model for skeletal muscle mass was developed. This model solely comprised parameters routinely obtained in the daily clinical care for patients with CKD, allowing for longitudinal monitoring and early detection of muscle loss.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fully Automated Sample-to-Answer PCR Detection of Severe Fever with Thrombocytopenia Syndrome Virus in Cat Serum and Whole Blood]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe fever with thrombocytopenia syndrome virus (SFTSV) is a tick-borne pathogen that causes fatal hemorrhagic disease in humans and animals. In addition to transmission via tick bites, infection can occur through contact with body fluids from infected individuals or animals. This study evaluated the POCKIT™ Central Nucleic Acid Analyzer (POCKIT Central), a fully automated system integrating nucleic acid extraction and insulated isothermal PCR as a rapid diagnostic tool to aid in preventing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protein kinase D: Integrating cancer and metabolic disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity and type II diabetes mellitus (T2DM) are intricately linked to elevated cancer risk. Protein Kinase D (PKD) isoforms (PKD1, PKD2, and PKD3) have emerged as pivotal mediators at the centre of metabolic and oncogenic signalling. This review discusses isoform-specific roles of PKDs in the pathophysiology of both metabolic disorders and tumour progression. PKD1 exhibits a context-dependent dual role in cancer, acting as a tumour suppressor by reinforcing epithelial adhesion and restricting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic and transcriptomic profiling of hepatocellular carcinoma in patients with Fontan-associated liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Genomic mutational profiles of FALD and non-Fontan CHS HCCs are distinct from HCCs with other etiologies. Copy number alterations and transcriptional profiles in FALD HCCs classified these into a poor-prognosis group of HCCs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utility of AMOY polymerase chain reaction panel in detecting non-small cell lung cancer using pleural cell block]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pleural effusion cell blocks are a practical and reliable alternative for molecular testing of advanced NSCLC when biopsy is not feasible. The high sensitivity of the AmoyDx PLC panel even for specimens with low tumor cell content underscores its potential clinical utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PlasticEnz: An integrated database and screening tool combining homology and machine learning to identify plastic-degrading enzymes in meta-omics datasets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587207/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PlasticEnz is a new open-source tool for detecting plastic-degrading enzymes (plastizymes) in metagenomic data by combining sequence homology-based search with machine learning techniques. It integrates custom Hidden Markov Models, DIAMOND alignments, and polymer-specific classifiers trained on ProtBERT embeddings to identify candidate depolymerases from user-provided contigs, genomes, or protein sequences. PlasticEnz supports 11 plastic polymers with ML classifiers for PET and PHB, achieving F1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41587207/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ventricular tachycardia in mid-ventricular obstructive hypertrophy: electrophysiological and pathological findings, and optimal surgical procedure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: VT associated with MVOH appears to result from scar-related reentry in the distal LV aneurysm. Extensive endocardial resection of the LV apical aneurysm with circumferential cryothermia at the hypertrophied myocardium may be an effective strategy for eliminating this refractory and life-threatening VT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraoperative completion study using three-dimensional computed tomography angiography in carotid endarterectomy surgery: Technical case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-risk morphology in cystic vestibular schwannomas: an imaging-based scoring system for facial nerve outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selective MYC 5' amplification in postirradiation/lymphedema-associated angiosarcoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We assessed whether an endothelium-specific enhancer is co-amplified with MYC in postirradiation/lymphedema-associated angiosarcoma (PLAS). First, the signal pattern and diagnostic utility of MYC break-apart fluorescence in situ hybridization (FISH) were examined to distinguish PLAS from carcinoma. Next, public data were analyzed to determine the association between the MYC-co-amplified region and cell type-specific active enhancers. Six cases of PLAS were retrieved, including three with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature Dependence of p-Wave Contacts in a Harmonically Trapped Fermi Gas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We study the dependence of the p-wave contact on the Fermi temperature T_{F} and reduced temperature T/T_{F} based on the number of closed-channel molecules. From the anisotropic pattern of dissociated molecules, we resolve the narrow m=0 and m=±1 dipolar splitting of the p-wave Feshbach resonance in ^{6}Li, enabling the independent determination of the contact for all three m components. For each component, we identify a near-resonant scaling with sqrt[T_{F}], indicating the contribution of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Noise-Agnostic Unbiased Quantum Error Mitigation for Logical Qubits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic error cancellation is a quantum error mitigation technique capable of producing unbiased computation results, but it requires an accurate error model. Constructing this model involves estimating a set of parameters, which, in the worst case, may scale exponentially with the number of qubits. In this Letter, we introduce a method called spacetime noise inversion, revealing that unbiased quantum error mitigation can be achieved with just a single accurately measured error parameter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-Dependent Hole States in Multiconfigurational Time-Dependent Hartree-Fock Approaches: A Time-Domain Generalization of Extended Koopmans' Theorem]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We introduce a framework for resolving electron-hole dynamics within wave-function-based multiconfigurational time-dependent Hartree-Fock (MCTDHF) theory. Central to this framework is a time-domain generalization of the extended Koopmans' theorem, which rigorously defines time-dependent hole states through single-electron removal. From this foundation, we prove the existence of exact equations of motion for time-dependent Dyson orbitals, enabling instantaneous construction of photofragments'...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Helicobacter pylori</em> Exploit Short-Chain Fatty Acids-Induced CAPZA1 Overexpression to Emerge CD44v9-Positive Stemness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SCFA-induced CAPZA1-overexpressing cells serve as a scaffold niche that supports CagA activity and promotes CD44v9-positive cancer stem-like cells. This study sheds new light on the early molecular events driving H pylori-associated gastric carcinogenesis and may inform future strategies for early detection and intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41586340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drug Delivery System for the Anticancer Drug Paclitaxel Using Lipocalin-Type Prostaglandin D Synthase Conjugated to a Tumor-Targeting Peptide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many drugs currently under development tend to have poor water solubility and large molecular weights, necessitating the development of systems for solubilizing and delivering these drugs to lesion sites. In this study, we attempted to utilize lipocalin-type prostaglandin D synthase (L-PGDS), which has a typical β-barrel structure and secretory lipid transport activity, as a carrier for the anticancer drug paclitaxel (PTX), which has a molecular weight of 854 and extremely low water solubility....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustained HIF activation in adult cardiomyocytes show transient beneficial effect in murine HFpEF model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sustained HIF signalling activation in adult CM does not impair the cardiac structure and function in normal ageing process and shows transient yet beneficial effect in murine HFpEF model.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical utility of the MAF-5 score for assessing MAFLD/MASLD in a Japanese population with obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The MAF-5 score may serve as a useful noninvasive marker for predicting liver fibrosis in Japanese patients with MASLD, regardless of diabetes status.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Arachniodes × tohtomiensis</em> hyb. nov. (Dryopteridaceae) from Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to characterize a hybrid of Arachniodes (Dryopteridaceae), A. × tohtomiensis, for which molecular evidence of its origin and detailed morphological descriptions are lacking. The genome composition of A. × tohtomiensis, clarified based on plastid DNA and MIG-seq analyses, indicates that it is a diploid hybrid of A. exilis and an undetected species. This origin was also supported by phylogenetic, STRUCTURE, principal component, and neighbor-net analyses. Based on these evidences,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applications, image analysis, and interpretation of computer vision in medical imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review summarizes the current advances, applications, and research prospects of computer vision in advancing medical imaging. Computer vision in healthcare has revolutionized medical practice by increasing diagnostic accuracy, improving patient care, and increasing operational efficiency. Likewise, deep learning algorithms have advanced medical image analysis, significantly improved healthcare outcomes and transforming diagnostic processes. Specifically, convolutional neural networks are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41585084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRUSADE project: Recycling technologies for ELV components to create a sustainable source of market grade materials for EU applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The European Union's ambitions for climate neutrality and digital leadership rely on secure access to CRMs, essential for green and digital technologies but supply risks and geopolitical challenges. The CRUSADE project develops a sustainable, integrated recycling approach targeting underutilized waste streams from ELVs, including PCBs, catalytic converters, batteries and automotive fuel cells. CRUSADE proposes a universal hydrometallurgical process treating up to 500 tonnes of waste annually and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physiological swelling imaging in human calf under stocking compression by sparse Bayesian learning implemented into electrical impedance tomography (SBL-EIT)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Physiological swelling in human calf has been imaged under stocking compression by the sparse Bayesian learning implemented into electrical impedance tomography (SBL-EIT) to evaluate the in situ treatment effect of various compression pressures. SBL-EIT reconstructs conductivity distribution [Formula: see text] to image excessive extracellular fluid in subcutaneous adipose tissue (SAT), indicating the susceptibilities to physiological swelling due to various compression pressures. The SBL-EIT...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41584818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127024726&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>