<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:56:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overcoming Barriers to Dynamic Phase-Only Modulation in Transmissive Metasurfaces via Diffraction Control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Active photonic systems comprising arrays of active metasurfaces─arrays of tunable resonators─offer dynamic wavefront control at subwavelength scales. Transmissive metasurfaces are an essential requirement in cascaded arrays of metasurfaces and enable integration with chip-scale light sources and detectors. However, most existing active phase control metasurface designs are reflective due to fundamental limitations in single-resonance transmissive architectures, which typically exhibit a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allosecurinine Derivative with Two Michael Acceptors Activates Keap1-Nrf2 Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oxidative stress and neuroinflammation drive neurodegenerative diseases, rendering the Keap1-Nrf2 pathway an attractive therapeutic target. Here, we derivatized securinega alkaloids by introducing a 1,4-conjugated Michael acceptor onto the piperidine ring. Among them, 4,5-dehydro-6-oxoallosecurinine, featuring two Michael acceptors (an α,β-unsaturated lactam and an α,β-γ,δ-unsaturated ester), exhibited the most potent Nrf2 activation. This compound promoted Nrf2 nuclear translocation and induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Mixed-Precision Approach to a Preconditioned Eigensolver for Efficient Density Functional Calculations on AI-Focused GPUs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in graphics processing units (GPUs) have substantially broadened the applicability of computational chemistry. Nevertheless, the double-precision (FP64) operations conventionally required in quantum chemistry remain inefficient on artificial intelligence (AI)-focused GPUs, which are predominantly optimized for lower precision arithmetic. Moreover, the limited memory capacity of such GPUs necessitates algorithmic adaptations to traditional approaches in density functional theory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stepwise Activation-Guided Zn Deposition for Ultra-High Capacity in Flowless Zn-Br Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flowless Zn-bromine batteries (FL-ZBBs) are attracting attention as a route to overcome the inherent system-level limitations of conventional flow batteries. However, the difficulty of achieving high ZnBr(2) utilization and ultra-high areal capacity jeopardize practical feasibility: Under practically relevant conditions, Zn-hosting electrodes suffer from top-plating issues and dendrite-triggered "dead" Zn accumulation, which deteriorates reversible Zn plating/stripping. This work presents a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The AENEAS Project: Intraoperative Anatomical Guidance Through Real-Time Landmark Detection Using Machine Vision]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Applying machine vision techniques for anatomical detection in a complex neurosurgical setting is feasible. Although challenges remain in detecting less distinctive structures, the high accuracy achieved for deep anatomical landmarks validates this approach. This study marks an essential step toward the development of machine vision-powered anatomical recognition tools, with the prospective goal of improving intraoperative orientation and reducing variability among surgeons.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-guided engineering of prototype foamy virus Env identifies key residues for heparan sulfate binding and enhances transduction efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Prototype foamy virus (PFV) is an attractive gene delivery platform due to its large cargo capacity and favorable safety profile; however, the structural basis of its interaction with heparan sulfate (HS), a critical attachment factor for viral entry, remains undefined. The objective of this study was to identify the structural determinants of HS recognition within PFV Env and to evaluate whether rational, structure-guided engineering could enhance viral entry and gene transfer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Situ Surface Reconstruction and Carbon Encapsulation for High-Performance Pt-Lean Catalysts beyond Conventional Core-Shell Designs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Over recent decades, extensive efforts have aimed to enhance fuel cell performance. Pt alloys with 3d transition metals are particularly attractive for boosting oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) activity via strain and electronic effects. However, their structural instability and high Pt usage hinder practical application. Here, we report a highly active and durable catalyst with reduced Pt cost, achieved by integrating a Pt-segregated surface and porous carbon shell. Unlike conventional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rural-Urban Migration and Low-Transmission Endemicity of Malaria in Sub-Saharan Africa: A Statistical Inference Approach to Uncover Possible Mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight the importance of incorporating human mobility, particularly seasonal labour migration, into malaria transmission models and control strategies. From a global health perspective, accounting for mobility-driven persistence mechanisms can strengthen malaria elimination programs across Sub-Saharan Africa, where seasonal migration is widespread. By integrating migration dynamics into intervention planning, policymakers can better anticipate epidemic risk and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overpassivization Revisited: Disentangling Syntax and Semantics in Causes of Errors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[English passives and unaccusatives share similarities in both syntactic derivation and semantic properties of the subject argument. However, similarities in syntactic derivation have primarily been discussed in the literature as a core trigger of prevalent overpassivization errors with unaccusative verbs by second language learners of English. In this study, we conducted two experiments to investigate which cue, either syntactic similarity or semantic similarity, is active for incorrectly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Comparative Performance Evaluation of Federated and Centralized Learning for Velum and OTE Segmentation in Sleep Endoscopy Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Septal Deviation on Eye Asymmetry: Implications for Preoperative Facial Evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Eye asymmetry reflects underlying midfacial skeletal imbalance and shows a significant association with bony septal deviation. Among various orbital parameters, SOR height and orbital area asymmetry demonstrated the strongest correlations with the degree of BSD, suggesting that these factors contribute substantially to overall facial asymmetry. Incorporating orbital skeletal assessment into preoperative facial analysis may improve diagnostic accuracy, surgical planning for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization and biological evaluation of a Rh(III) complex featuring Phosphonate-Modified bipyridine ligands]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Pill Low-Dose Triple Combination Therapy vs Standard-Dose Monotherapy in Patients With Mild-to-Moderate Hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Single-pill LDC-ALC achieved BP reductions similar to those with amlodipine and greater than those with losartan monotherapy over 8 weeks, with similar short-term tolerability. These findings support LDC-ALC as an effective and well tolerated alternative initial therapy for mild-to-moderate hypertension, expanding the set of validated strategies alongside established monotherapies. (A Study to Evaluate Efficacy and Safety of HCP1803 in Patients With Essential Hypertension...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commercially Available Artificial Intelligence Score on Preoperative Mammography for Prediction of Future Breast Cancer After DCIS Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Mammographic artificial intelligence (AI) systems have been explored for future breast cancer risk prediction. Objective: To investigate associations of scores from a commercial AI system for mammographic breast cancer detection and diagnosis with development of second breast cancers after DCIS treatment and to compare AI predictive performance with existing clinical risk models. Methods: This retrospective five-center study included 1740 patients (median age, 55.0 years) who...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visual Ordinal Coronary Calcium Scoring on Routine PET/CT for Predicting Perioperative Major Clinical Events After Noncardiac Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: PET/CT is commonly performed during oncologic workup and provides an opportunity for coronary artery calcification (CAC) evaluation. However, technical constraints typically preclude standard Agatston scoring using the attenuation-correction CT images obtained during PET/CT examinations. Objective: To assess the prognostic utility of a simple visual ordinal CAC scoring system applied to PET/CT for perioperative risk stratification after noncardiac surgery. Methods: This retrospective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Caspase-3-Instructed Nanosonosensitizer Disassembly for Real-Time NIR-II Feedback of Tumor Sonodynamic Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sonodynamic therapy (SDT) has emerged as a powerful modality for deep-seated tumor treatment. However, real-time evaluation of its therapeutic efficacy at the molecular level remains elusive. Herein, we report a caspase-3-responsive self-evaluating nanosonosensitizer that enabled precise monitoring of SDT efficacy via near-infrared II (NIR-II) fluorescence feedback. Guided by rational molecular design, we screened diketopyrrolopyrrole (DPP)-based sonosensitizers and developed a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microplastic-Induced Macrophage Dysfunction Drives Lung Tumor Progression through Glutathione Imbalance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microplastics (MPs) are emerging contaminants whose immunological consequences remain poorly defined. Here, we investigated MP-induced immune responses using bone marrow-derived macrophages and a lung tumor model to delineate how MPs modulate tumor immunity. MPs triggered TLR2- and TLR4-dependent signaling pathways in macrophages, which initiated AP-1 signaling and lysosomal destabilization, followed by mitochondrial depolarization and excessive reactive oxygen species production. Despite NRF2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skull Base Surgery in the Pediatric Population-The 2nd International Collaborative Study (1995-2015)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Open approaches were widely used for pediatric skull base tumor resection in the period between 1995 and 2015 but we saw a rise in the use of endoscopic and combined techniques by the end of the period covered by this study. Our results may represent a transitional era in which alternative endoscopic techniques continue to expand.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nail Involvement Is a Key Determinant of Treatment Persistence in Palmoplantar Pustulosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Palmoplantar pustulosis (PPP) is a chronic relapsing inflammatory skin disorder predominantly affecting the palms and soles. Despite the continued use of oral systemic agents, real-world data on their durability and treatment patterns in PPP remain limited. To investigate the treatment patterns, drug survival, and clinical factors associated with treatment persistence in patients with PPP receiving oral systemic therapies. We conducted a retrospective cohort study of patients diagnosed with PPP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chia Seed Mucilage-Based Bilayer Sponges Containing Zinc Oxide Nanoparticles for Wound Dressing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Effective wound management requires dressings that not only protect against infection but also support tissue regeneration. In this work, we present a chia seed mucilage/poly(vinyl alcohol) (CSMP)-zinc oxide (ZnO) bilayer wound dressing composed of a dense CSMP-ZnO hydrofilm as the outer protective barrier and a porous CSMP-ZnO sponge as the inner absorbent layer. The CSMP-ZnO bilayer wound dressing is fabricated via oven-drying and freeze-drying techniques, enabling a clear functional division...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reassessing home blood pressure thresholds: clinical implications of lowering the diagnostic criteria to 130/80 mmHg]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The conventional home BP threshold of 135/85 mmHg may fail to identify a considerable proportion of masked, sustained, and nighttime hypertension. Lowering the threshold to 130/80 mmHg, or designating 130/80-134/84 mmHg as a diagnostic 'gray zone' warranting ABPM confirmation, may improve diagnostic precision and facilitate earlier detection of hypertension in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship between Multiple HPV Infections and Cervical Cytology: Single Center Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cervical cancer remains a significant public health concern, with persistent high-risk human papillomavirus (HPV) infections being a major contributing factor. This retrospective study investigates the correlation between multiple HPV infections and cervical cytology abnormalities in patients tested at a single hospital in Seoul, South Korea. A total of 6,869 HPV genotyping tests conducted between January 2017 and December 2023 were analyzed, with 1,396 cases testing positive for HPV. High-risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomics and phosphoproteomics of human colorectal cancer cells lacking a specific kinase activity reveal kinase-specific compensatory responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell signaling regulates cell proliferation, survival, and migration, and abnormal kinase activity is often implicated in cancer. Although kinases are key targets for anticancer therapy, drug-induced compensatory signaling and pathway rewiring often drive acquired resistance. These compensatory responses enable tumor cells to maintain proliferation and survival, contributing to acquired drug resistance. In this study, we investigated adaptive responses following the knockout of four specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing cancer prognostics with group penalty models: a comparative study on radiomics feature selection in lung adenocarcinomas and meningiomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Group penalty models demonstrated superior feature selection stability while maintaining comparable predictive performance to Lasso. By selecting biologically meaningful feature groups rather than individual features, these models enhance interpretability and align better with clinical reasoning, offering a robust framework for radiomics-based cancer prognostics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethnic Heterogeneity in Reproductive Risk Factors for Breast Cancer, With a Focus on Asian Populations: A Meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to examine differences in the association between reproductive factors and breast cancer (BC) risk across ethnic groups, particularly Asians and non-Asians, and to explore temporal trends through meta-analysis. The study focused on epidemiologic research published up to August 31, 2022, examining reproductive factors related to BC risk and family history. All effect sizes were calculated using a random-effect model. The protective effect of the higher number of childbirths...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Obesity Status Trajectories with Changes in Prediabetes Glycemic Status]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to determine the association between trajectories of obesity status and prediabetes reversion to normoglycemia or progression to diabetes. The study included 14,452 participants from the National Health Insurance Service-National Health Screening (NHIS-HEALS) cohort who continuously had prediabetes glycemic status during the index period (2002-2008), defined by their fasting plasma glucose. The exposure of the study was the trajectories of obesity (defined by body mass index ≥...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Report: Budd-Chiari-like syndrome in a cat with polycystic kidney and liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 9-year-old spayed female Persian Chinchilla cat presented with progressive lethargy and acute right hindlimb pain and lameness. Diagnostic imaging revealed diffuse renal and hepatic cysts, resulting in marked hepatomegaly. Computed tomography (CT) further identified a localized narrowing of the intrahepatic caudal vena cava (CVC), likely due to extrinsic compression by the enlarged liver. Laboratory tests revealed moderate anemia, leukocytosis, hypoalbuminemia, and a hypercoagulable state with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drivers of willingness to communicate with generative AI: the roles of self-efficacy, grit, speaking enjoyment, and anxiety from a self-determination theory perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: English-speaking proficiency is essential for the personal and academic development of English as a Foreign Language (EFL) learners; however, many students demonstrate limited willingness to communicate (WTC) in classroom settings. Although generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) offers considerable potential for enhancing communicative engagement, existing research has predominantly examined WTC in human-to-human interactions, leaving the applicability of established models in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitral valve surgery and maze procedure: the Korean experience in rheumatic versus degenerative disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In a contemporary Korean cohort, surgical ablation during MV surgery provided sustained rhythm control and favorable clinical outcomes in patients with both degenerative and rheumatic disease. Given the continued burden of rheumatic heart disease in Korea, these findings support the routine application of surgical ablation during MV surgery, regardless of underlying etiology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma-derived mitochondria as a minimal manipulation alternative for attenuating inflammatory immune responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platelet-rich plasma (PRP) has long been used to promote tissue repair through its content of cytokines, growth factors and platelet-derived mitochondria (PLT-mito). While effective, PRP often triggers an early M1-type inflammatory response that may worsen symptoms in chronic inflammatory conditions and limit its clinical utility. Harvesting functional PLT-mito usually requires platelet activation or mechanical disruption, which can exceed minimal manipulation thresholds under regulatory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roadmap of Flexible Electrodes for Next-Generation Wearable Electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the rapid growth of smart innovations, flexible electronics recognized for their lightweight, tremendous flexibility, and extraordinary scalability are growing more integrated into our daily life. Flexible electronics, known for their lightweight, high flexibility, and seamless integration with biological and nonbiological systems, are driving advances in wearable and implantable devices. Central to this progress are flexible electrodes, which enable energy storage, sensing, and health...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implantation of cancer cells from transoral endoscopic thyroidectomy: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tumor biology, local environment, technical issues, surgical skills, and the correct management and handling of neoplastic nodules represent crucial clinical pitfalls and important factors that can contribute to local recurrence and malignant cellular implantation following a TOETVA for thyroid surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Esophageal Injury Risk Factors in Patients With Atrial Fibrillation Undergoing Catheter Ablation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Esophageal injury after catheter ablation for atrial fibrillation is not rare, but usually mild. Lower BMI and reduced LVEF were independent risk factors, regardless of ablation type. These results support selective endoscopic screening in high-risk patients to enable early detection and prevent severe complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute Bronchiolitis in Young Children and Future Mental Health Outcome: A 15-Year National Population Study Regardless of Allergic Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Children hospitalized for acute bronchiolitis showed an increased risk of developing mental health disorders. These findings provide epidemiologic evidence supporting the need for long-term mental health surveillance and supportive care in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential Activation of the Multifidus and Erector Spinae During Asymmetric Spinal Stabilizing Exercise in Adolescent Idiopathic Scoliosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ASSE induces posture-specific asymmetric activation of the paraspinal muscles in patients with AIS. Although the side-lying posture produced the largest asymmetry, this reflected increased ES activity for trunk elevation rather than true selective Mu contraction. In contrast, the prone and bird-dog postures demonstrated a greater Mu contribution relative to the ES under rotational loading. These findings suggest that ASSE can be adapted to target specific paraspinal muscle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of the National Health Screening Program for Infants and Children in Detecting Neurodevelopmental Disorders: A Nationwide Population-Based Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Developmental screening tests in the NHSPIC contributed to the early diagnosis of NDDs. This study underscores the significance of the NHSPIC and provides foundational evidence to inform and enhance policies related to child health screenings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes and Predictive Factors of Combination Treatment With Oral Doxycycline, Topical Calcineurin Inhibitor, and Pulsed Dye Laser in Erythematotelangiectatic Rosacea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Combined oral doxycycline, TCI, and PDL therapy is effective and safe for ETR, especially in patients with higher severity. Prompt diagnosis and avoidance of steroid misuse may improve treatment responses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Thoracic Duct Resection on Postoperative Body Composition Trajectory After Oesophagectomy: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the largest study to date to assess longitudinal body composition changes after TDR using serial BIA. TDR was associated with a greater decline in sarcopenia-related indices, particularly within the first 3 months. These effects were transient, reversible and reproducible in early-stage patients. Our findings support the oncologic role of TDR while underscoring the importance of early nutritional and rehabilitative care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synbiotic Combination of <em>Lactococcus lactis</em> LB1022 and Fructo-Oligosaccharides Mitigates the Atopic March by Modulating the Microbiota-Gut-Skin-Lung Axis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dysregulated gut microbiota is increasingly recognized as a major contributor to allergic diseases and their progression. A key clinical manifestation of this progression is the atopic march, in which atopic dermatitis (AD) precedes the development of allergic airway disease. Although prebiotics and probiotics individually improve AD symptoms, their combined use as synbiotics, especially with regard to preventing the progression from cutaneous inflammation to airway hypersensitivity, has not...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision Chemotherapy in Biliary Tract Cancer moving From Empiric Intensification to Biomarker-Guided Treatment: Editorial on "Molecular determinants of outcome to gemcitabine, cisplatin, and nab-paclitaxel in patients with advanced BTC."]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IKK2, calcium, MAP kinase, and PI3 kinase are required for exocytosis and interleukin-8 production in human mast cells stimulated by Trichomonas vaginalis-derived secretory products]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trichomonas vaginalis infection causes vaginitis and cervicitis in women, and asymptomatic urethritis and prostatitis in men. Mast cells play a key role in the inflammatory response against T. vaginalis infection. In this study, we examined the signaling pathways involved in mast cell activation induced by T. vaginalis-derived secretory products (TvSP), focusing on IKK2, calcium, MAP kinase (MAPK), and PI3 kinase (PI3K). TvSP stimulation induced phosphorylation and degradation of IκB, indicating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptomic profiling reveals Trichinella spiralis-mediated attenuation of respiratory syncytial virus-induced inflammation in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Helminth-mediated immunomodulation has been extensively studied in animal models, demonstrating its potential as both a prophylactic and therapeutic option for inflammatory lung diseases. However, its role in attenuating respiratory virus-induced inflammation remains largely unexplored. In this study, we examined whether pre-existing infection with the helminth Trichinella spiralis confers protection against pulmonary pathology induced by respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) infection in mice. Mice...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The spirit of Ewha, carried forward through devotion: an interview with Dr. Kumie Oh, alumna of the 27th graduating class, anesthesiologist]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Positional and ventilatory mechanics in the unexpected resolution of glycopyrrolate-induced tachycardia: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 28-year-old woman developed drug-induced tachycardia in the left lateral decubitus (LLD) position following intravenous administration of glycopyrrolate. The tachycardia was unresponsive to esmolol, labetalol, and fentanyl but resolved unexpectedly after the tidal volume was reduced from 8 to 6 mL/kg. Drug-induced tachycardia or arrhythmia occurring in the LLD position under mechanical ventilation may be attenuated by adopting a low tidal volume ventilation strategy (6 mL/kg).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoscopic vacuum therapy for gastrointestinal transmural defects: clinical outcomes and treatment implications: a retrospective study from Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that EVT is a safe and effective treatment for gastrointestinal transmural defects, with high technical success rates. The number of EVT sessions and the timing of treatment initiation appeared to be associated with complications and overall clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revisiting the multiple roles of T-cadherin and adiponectin in cardiovascular disease: from receptor function to exosome-mediated therapeutic potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardiovascular disease, particularly ischemic heart disease, remains a leading cause of death worldwide. Although advances in pharmacological and device-based therapies have improved clinical outcomes, effective strategies for myocardial repair and regeneration remain limited. T-cadherin, a glycosylphosphatidylinositol-anchored atypical cadherin, has recently been identified as a functional receptor for both low-density lipoprotein cholesterol and adiponectin, a cardioprotective adipokine....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Norovirus infection control in Korea: points to consider]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building on a strong foundation: a new chapter for the Ewha Medical Journal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of high-definition transcranial direct current stimulation combined with digital rehabilitation on upper limb function in stroke patients: study protocol for a randomized, double-blind, sham-controlled confirmatory trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Stroke remains a leading cause of long-term disability worldwide, with a significant proportion of survivors suffering from persistent upper limb impairments despite conventional rehabilitation. High-definition transcranial direct current stimulation (HD-tDCS) has emerged as a promising neuromodulation technique capable of precise cortical targeting, potentially enhancing motor recovery when combined with structured rehabilitation. This study aims to confirm the efficacy and safety...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world outcomes of palbociclib plus endocrine therapy in elderly patients with HR+/HER2- advanced breast cancer in Japan: a subgroup analysis of the P-BRIDGE study by age group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No effect of the short-term learning of object trajectories on multisensory perception within the peripersonal space]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peripersonal space, the space immediately surrounding the body, functions as an interface between the self and the external environment. In interactions with dynamic environments, not only bodily information but also accurate estimation of the dynamics of external objects is required. While numerous studies have demonstrated that real-time estimation of object dynamics, based on bottom-up mechanisms, modulates peripersonal space representation, little evidence supports the involvement of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term clinical outcomes of patients with localized primary ocular adnexal mucosa-associated lymphoid tissue lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Because primary ocular adnexal mucosa-associated lymphoid tissue lymphoma (POAML) is rare, key clinical questions, including the best treatment strategy and the validity of watchful waiting (WW), remain unresolved. Although radiotherapy (RT) is the standard treatment for localized POAML, it is commonly associated with acute and late toxicities. Overall, 128 patients with localized POAML diagnosed and managed at our institution between 1998 and 2015 were retrospectively analyzed. Forty-two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Saying good-bye or final conversations between terminally ill inpatients and family members in the last weeks of life: a nationwide survey of bereaved families]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Clear and timely prognostic communication may help patients convey meaningful last words to their families.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of the locus coeruleus in giant migrating contractions of colonic motility in Suncus murinus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colonic contraction motility, composed of colonic motor complexes (CMCs) and giant migrating contractions (GMCs), is regulated through the coordinated integration of hormonal signals, the nervous system and intraluminal cues. Abnormalities in colonic function and motility can result in conditions such as constipation or diarrhea. It is believed that brain regions involved in regulating colonic motility play a role in colonic dysfunction observed under stress conditions and in Parkinson's...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased intraocular pressure immediately after aflibercept 8 mg intravitreal injection for neovascular age-related macular degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive analysis of DNA repair, morphological remodeling and immune-gene expression in patient-derived biliary tract carcinoma organoids following ionizing radiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biliary tract carcinoma (BTC) is a malignancy with poor prognosis. Current molecular targeted therapies benefit only a limited subset of patients, underscoring the need for novel approaches, such as combining DNA-damaging chemoradiotherapy with an immune checkpoint inhibitor. Although cellular responses following chemoradiotherapy-induced DNA damage are essential, they remain poorly understood in the context of three-dimensional tumor structures. This study aimed to investigate the effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large-Area 2D Metasurface-Based Triboelectric E-Skin Arrays: Contact &amp; Proximity Tactile Mapping with Broadband Acoustic Readouts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in electromechanically coupled, self-powered, flexible transducer-enabled electronic skins are predominantly driven by the capacitive triboelectric nanogenerators (TENGs), which operate intrinsically as multifunctional sensor-cum-energy harvester. The resulting TENG's operability in cutting-edge wearable technologies can be significantly augmented by introducing 2D dielectric metasurfaces, which optimize functionality through enhanced electromechanical coupling. Here, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to Alcántara Montero]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A New Player in Photosystem I Photoprotection under Fluctuating Light]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic exciton for materials, biology, and energy conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid Construction of Tricyclic Carbon Framework for Convergent Synthesis of Manginoid Meroterpenoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Manginoid meroterpenoids are a unique class of monoterpene-shikimate conjugated meroterpenoids. Nine analogues, designated manginoids A-I, were previously isolated from fungi. All analogues feature a common 3',7'-dimethylspiro[cyclohexane-1,5'-indene] skeleton, representing an unprecedented structural motif in natural product chemistry. In this study, we developed a synthetic strategy for the rapid construction of the core skeleton of manginoids for efficient convergent synthesis and analogue...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlabeled NMR Approach with Site-Specific Methyl Assignments for Structural Evaluation of the IgG1 Fc Region]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monoclonal antibodies are the cornerstone biopharmaceuticals whose safety and efficacy critically depend on their higher-order structure (HOS). Nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) spectroscopy has emerged as a promising tool for HOS evaluation, yet its application has largely relied on fingerprinting approaches without residue-level interpretation. Here, we report site-specific assignments of methyl resonances in the Fc region of human IgG1, established through amino acid-selective labeling and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-Hierarchical Transduction of Dynamic Behaviors from Self-Oscillating Microgels to Colloidosomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inspired by living systems, hierarchical materials have been developed to integrate multiple levels of organization, enabling complex behaviors to emerge from interactions among simpler components. However, understanding how dynamic behaviors are transduced across hierarchical levels in synthetic materials remains a major challenge. Here, we demonstrate the cross-hierarchical transduction of dynamic behaviors in life-like autonomous materials by investigating self-oscillating colloidosomes as a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-pot asymmetric sulfoxidation using <em>in situ</em> generated H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub> from H<sub>2</sub> and O<sub>2</sub> catalyzed by rhodium and vanadium complexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper reports the first example of a one-pot asymmetric sulfoxidation using in situ generated H(2)O(2). This reaction is catalyzed by two homogeneous catalysts: a Rh complex for the direct synthesis of H(2)O(2) from H(2) and O(2), and a V complex for the asymmetric oxidation of sulfides.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do early aortic remodeling patterns at 6 months predict mid-term outcomes after frozen elephant trunk for chronic aortic dissection?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A 6-month CT provides simple, actionable risk stratification after total arch replacement with FET for chronic aortic dissection. Absence of EPR identifies a high-risk subgroup (ENR) that warrants closer surveillance and timely distal intervention, optimizing follow-up intensity and treatment timing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practical gEUD optimization technique for stereotactic radiation therapy based on a theoretical reinterpretation using the gEUD curve concept]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: The generalized equivalent uniform dose (gEUD) is a well-established metric for radiotherapy dose optimization, particularly for normal tissues. However, the lack of theoretical clarity in its application has often led to empirical use in clinical practice. This study aims to reformulate gEUD-based optimization in a theoretical framework using the gEUD curve concept, and to develop a robust optimization strategy tailored for stereotactic radiation therapy (SRT), with a specific focus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Legionella</em> employs the multimodal ubiquitination of Sec22b to modulate SNARE pairing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Legionella pneumophila establishes its replicative niche through the deployment of multiple effector proteins. During this process, the host v-SNARE Sec22b is recruited from the endoplasmic reticulum to bacterial phagosomes and engages in non-canonical pairings with plasma membrane syntaxins. We previously reported that Sec22b undergoes polyubiquitination at early stages of infection and that the Legionella deubiquitinase LotB cleaves polyubiquitin chains from Sec22b, resulting in Sec22b...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gaseous CO<sub>2</sub> electrolysis: latest advances in electrode and electrolyzer technologies toward abating CO<sub>2</sub> emissions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The conversion of CO(2) into multicarbon (C(2+)) products via electrochemical reduction is considered a key technology for the sustainable production of fuels and chemicals. The performance of high-rate gaseous CO(2) electrolysis is governed by interrelated factors such as the electrocatalysts, electrodes, electrolytes, and cell architectures. Despite the intensive focus on catalyst research, systematic studies addressing the other components remain scarce, leaving critical gaps in our...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phyllosphere of senescent crops as a microbial N<sub>2</sub>O source]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant residues contribute to the nitrogen cycle in terrestrial ecosystems, as they are recognized as a nutrient source for soil microorganisms. However, the contribution of the microbial community in the phyllosphere of plant residues, such as senescent leaves, itself in the nitrogen cycle remains unclear. In agricultural lands, crop residues contribute to global emissions of the greenhouse gas nitrous oxide (N(2)O), which is an intermediate product of several microbial pathways including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac rupture due to Takotsubo syndrome complicated by a myocardial bridge: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Takotsubo syndrome is characterized by transient left ventricular systolic dysfunction, without obstructive coronary artery disease. Myocardial bridge, where a coronary artery courses intramurally, may provoke ischaemia and trigger Takotsubo syndrome. Although both conditions typically have favourable outcomes, we encountered two cases of fatal cardiac rupture in patients with Takotsubo syndrome complicated by myocardial bridge.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distal coronary sinus-left atrial fistulous communication uncovered during atrial fibrillation ablation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Congenital anomalies of the coronary sinus (CS) are rare and often overlooked on standard imaging. Among these, the unroofed coronary sinus (URCS) is the most recognized, typically involving the proximal CS and frequently associated with a persistent left superior vena cava. In contrast, fistulous communications between the distal CS and the left atrium (LA) are exceptionally uncommon. Their recognition is important during atrial fibrillation (AF) ablation, where unanticipated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41669320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reaction yield oscillates over reaction time in first-order chemical reactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The yield of a first-order chemical reaction normally has a unimodal trend over reaction time. In other words, once the population of a product decreases, it will normally never increase again by elongating the reaction time. However, in analyzing the full reaction path network of the Strecker reaction, we encountered a nontraditional behavior, where the population of an intermediate increased again after decreasing, even in a first-order reaction. Furthermore, simulations on model reaction path...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biosynthesis of Kaitocephalin: A Neuroprotective Natural Product Featuring a Peptide-Like yet Nonpeptidic Scaffold]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kaitocephalin (KCP) is a neuroprotective natural product that acts as an antagonist of ionotropic glutamate receptors, making it a highly promising lead for drug discovery. It possesses a unique scaffold composed of three amino acids connected via C─C bonds, which appears peptide-like but is formed without peptide bonds. In this study, we identified the KCP biosynthetic gene cluster (kpb cluster) in the producing fungus Eupenicillium shearii through integrated genomic and transcriptomic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carrier Mapping in Sub-2nm Node Nanosheet Transistors with Scanning Spreading Resistance Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the semiconductor industry transitions to gate-all-around architectures such as Nanosheet-FETs (NSFETs) for the 2nm node and beyond, controlling parasitic resistance through precise junction engineering is fundamental. This requires characterization methods capable of mapping active carriers with nanometer-scale resolution. This work demonstrates a significant advancement in scanning spreading resistance microscopy (SSRM) that enables, for the first time, carrier mapping within 5.5 nm thick...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atopic Dermatitis Accelerates Skin Physiological Functional Decline and Visible Aging, Suppressed by Skincare Habits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Skincare habits can suppress AD-associated changes in the physiological function of the skin, inflammatory and immune factors in the stratum corneum, and visible aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41668302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soil-Borne Pathogens Reflect Agricultural Land-Use Legacies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41671044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Historical land-use changes shape present-day biodiversity through legacy effects, but the duration and mechanisms of these legacies are poorly understood. We used historical land-use maps in two Swedish landscapes across three centuries to examine the persistent influence of historical land use on plant and soil microbial communities. Overall, bacteria showed stronger legacy effects than fungi, but effects varied across functional groups of plant-associated and free-living taxa. However,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41671044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare provider burden reduction and estimated cost savings realized with electronic case reporting implementation across 3 healthcare organizations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41671029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: By automating patient case reporting, eCR reduced provider burden hours by at least 16-fold and cost savings of 4-fold or higher over a 1-year period.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41671029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medications for Opioid Use Disorder, Opioid Withdrawal, and Opioid Overdose: A Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41671014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: All individuals with OUD should be offered treatment with MOUD to reduce opioid use. Methadone and buprenorphine decrease opioid-associated and all-cause mortality in patients with OUD. Opioid withdrawal symptoms may be treated with opioid agonists, α2-receptor agonists, and medications for pain and nausea. All individuals with OUD should have access to opioid antagonists, such as naloxone, to treat opioid overdose.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41671014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delayed Diagnosis of Anastomotic Leak and Failure to Rescue After Colon Resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41671012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Findings of this study suggest that FTR after OSSI, which served as a proxy for anastomotic leak, was associated with delayed diagnosis, not the leak itself. Early identification of leaks and avoidance of progression to sepsis could reduce FTR rates. Quality initiatives aimed at earlier identification and timely and appropriate management of anastomotic leak may improve the mortality associated with colon resection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41671012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Historically Black College or University Attendance and Cognition in US Black Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study using a national dataset, HBCU attendance was associated with better cognition compared with PWI attendance for aging Black adults, which held for those attending college before and after legal racial segregation and sanctioned racial discrimination in education.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Air Pollution and the Progression of Physical Function Limitations and Disability in Aging Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These findings suggest that air pollution may affect the progression of physical disability and hinder recovery in later life.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of Clinician Well-Being Using a Biometric-Informed Coaching Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study of clinicians and other health care professionals, an asynchronous, biometric-informed coaching platform was associated with meaningful reductions in burnout and improvements in professional fulfillment and self-valuation. These findings suggest that adopting such a platform may be a feasible approach to support health care workers' well-being.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Device-Assisted vs Standard Valsalva Maneuver for Terminating Supraventricular Tachycardia: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Per the results of this randomized clinical trial, the handheld Valsalva assist device significantly enhances VM effectiveness, providing a potentially implementable solution for SVT management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-Year Actigraphy Study of Sleep and Rest-Activity Rhythms as Markers of Relapse in Depression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Actigraphy measures of sleep phase variability and daily activity amplitude were associated with depressive relapse, supporting actigraphy as a potential scalable biomarker to identify high-risk individuals and enable timely, personalized relapse prevention in MDD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Food Ingredients, State Actions, and Federal Preemption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergency Department-Initiated Buprenorphine for Opioid Use Disorder: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: No difference was detected in opioid use disorder treatment engagement on day 7 between the 7-day extended-release and sublingual buprenorphine groups. Both buprenorphine formulations were well tolerated; precipitated withdrawal was rare despite a high prevalence of fentanyl.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of Plaque Volume in Patients With First Diagnosis of Coronary Artery Disease: A Substudy of the PROMISE Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In symptomatic patients without known CAD, coronary plaque volumes and burdens are low but are related to CAD risk factors and independently predictive of MACE. The clinical utility of quantitative CCTA-based cardiovascular risk estimation in early CAD requires prospective evaluation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-harvest pyrethroid drench and injection treatments for quarantine control of imported fire ant (Hymenoptera: Formicidae) colonies infesting field-grown nursery plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is an imported fire ant (IFA) quarantine in the USA to prevent human assisted spread of the invasive, red IFA (Solenopsis invicta Buren), black IFA (Solenopsis richteri Forel), and the S. invicta × S. richteri hybrid. Quarantine regulated articles must be treated following approved protocols and must not be infested with IFA queens or reproducing colonies. Large, post-harvest field-grown nursery plants are an infestation risk because they are difficult to treat effectively with approved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Diet and Metabolome in Childhood and Adolescence: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This review identifies several metabolites consistently associated with specific dietary components across different studies in children and adolescents. These findings support the potential of metabolomics for validating dietary biomarkers and improving the accuracy of dietary assessment in pediatric populations. Although metabolomic markers reflect actual dietary intake, their implications for health outcomes remain to be explored.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of functional murine mitochondrial formyl peptides and their effects on myeloid-derived suppressor cell generation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[N-formyl peptides are cleavage products of bacterial and mitochondrial proteins, which effects on neutrophil activation have been extensively studied. Mitochondrial formyl peptides are also known to play a role in tumor immunity, but the molecular mechanism underlying this role remains largely unexplored. Our previous work suggested that tumor-derived mitochondrial formyl peptides promote tumor growth by enhancing myeloid-derived suppressor cell (MDSC)-mediated cytotoxic T-lymphocyte...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comment on "Axillary management in the post-neoadjuvant setting: dual tracer vs. single tracer for Sentinel lymph node biopsy"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic ultrasound motion metrics combined with deep learning for clinical differentiation of subacromial impingement syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Faster R-CNN enabled more accurate landmark localization than STL-CNN, while vAHD enhanced SIS identification. Combining faster R-CNN with a 1D-CNN demonstrated high diagnostic accuracy, underscoring the potential of deep learning for automated SIS assessment during dynamic ultrasonography. However, the current workflow requires offline video analysis, and future advances should focus on real-time implementation and improved generalizability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Trends and Sociodemographic Differences in Telemedicine Utilization, 2019-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Telemedicine use persists post-pandemic but reflects differences in access by age, race/ethnicity, socioeconomic status, and prior engagement with the patient portal. Targeted policies are needed to ensure equitable telemedicine adoption and accessibility for all patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primary Care Provider Perceptions of a Population Health Management Program to Improve Kidney Care: A Mixed Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: An electronic health record-based PHM approach to increase timely access to nephrology care and multidisciplinary specialty team was viewed by PCPs as a valuable co-management intervention. Future improvements, including a more hands-on approach from the nephrology team to share the burden of implementation, and PCP workflow facilitation are potential opportunities to optimize the PHM intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variation and Drivers of Spending Within 30-Day Emergency Department-Based Episodes of Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ED-based 30-day episode payments vary substantially across hospitals for CHF, COPD, and pneumonia, largely driven by costs from the ED visit and associated hospitalization. Future work should assess whether this variation reflects differences in quality or efficiency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Health Toll of Encampment Sweeps: A Descriptive Analysis of People Who Use Drugs in Massachusetts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As US homelessness grows, so too does the forced removal of individuals and their belongings from where they are staying, also known as encampment sweeps, which have been associated with increased overdose and reduced healthcare access. We examined associations between past-year experiences of encampment sweeps and suboptimal health behaviors, outcomes, and healthcare access from 155 people who use drugs (PWUD) in Massachusetts. Thirty-eight percent of participants experienced a sweep in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of ablation index-guided linear lesions formation for left atrial arrhythmia treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI-guided ablation is associated with significantly higher rates of acute conduction block across MIL, shorter RF times and lower FTI for AL and RFL while complication rates and long-term clinical outcome are comparable to non-AI-guided ablation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Childhood Trauma and Adult Loneliness as Predictors of Sleep Health in Blackfeet American Indian Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The current findings suggest that interventions targeting adult loneliness may reduce the risk for poor sleep health typically associated with high levels of childhood trauma.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PVA-coated 3D-printed molds for rapid prototyping of PDMS microdevices for stem cell culture]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Subcutaneous Derived Stromal Vascular Fraction Endothelial Cells Display Venous and Arterial Markers in Culture and 3D Capillaries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We characterised endothelial cells from human subcutaneous SVF, identifying venous and arterial blood endothelial cells while confirming the absence of lymphatic endothelial cells in vitro. These findings underline that subcutaneous adipose tissue is an attractive cell source due to its ease of isolation and abundance of endothelial cells for skin tissue engineering and regenerative medicine in general.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revealing the Defect-Driven Ferroelectric Mechanisms of Aluminum Nitride]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wurtzite III-nitride compounds are CMOS-compatible with widespread industrial interest to exercise ferroelectricity, despite their polar structure being highly resistant to polarization reversal. Here, we induce and tune ferroelectric properties in w-AlN via direct-write ion-beam processing, using nanoscale patterned defect engineering as a post-growth alternative to conventional cation substitution. Nanometric piezoresponse spectroscopy of the focused He^(+) beam patterned defect concentrations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inherited cancer syndromes in adult oncology: a referral guide based on malignant tumor and polyp features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This comprehensive tool aims to support oncologists in the timely identification of patients eligible for genetic counseling, thereby enhancing therapeutic decisions and improving familial risk assessment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Main confounders associated with the outcome of inpatient incisional hernia repair for decision making in ambulatory surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between Serum Metal Levels and Blood Pressure in Aluminium Smelting Workers: Mediating Role of Gamma-Glutamyltransferase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deficiencies Delaying Prescription Drug Approvals by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration, 2020-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic structural variation underlies cell type-specific betacyanin variegation in Chenopodium quinoa]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The allotetraploid crop quinoa (Chenopodium quinoa) accumulates red/violet betacyanins, which function as vital stress-mitigating antioxidants. We investigated the genetic basis of red/green variegation observed in the aerial organs of the P0429 accession. We demonstrated that this color mosaic is primarily localized to epidermal bladder cells (EBCs), with red EBCs accumulating betacyanin levels ~ 50-fold higher than colorless EBCs. Cell-type-specific RNA-sequencing of EBCs identified the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post partum decision making, letter to the editor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A glycosyltransferase, UGT84J2, regulates the level of anthocyanin in tea plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glycosyltransferase CsUGT84J2 can glycosylate p-coumaric acid and inhibit the expression of flavonol synthase under drought condition, which can both regulate anthocyanin synthesis in tea plants. Anthocyanins are the main substances in plants that produce rich colors, and they have received attention owing to their antioxidative functions. In this study, we identified a tea plant (Camellia sinensis) glycosyltransferase gene, CsUGT84J2, that regulates anthocyanin accumulation through a dual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Characteristics, Treatment Patterns, and Outcomes in Adult Patients Receiving Abrocitinib for Atopic Dermatitis in China: Interim Analysis from the AHEAD Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients enrolled in AHEAD exhibited significant disease burden in AD signs and QoL. Abrocitinib provides early and sustained improvement in disease severity and QoL among Chinese adults with moderate to severe AD, with high adherence and low flare rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of simplified sitting Badunjin effects on symptom burden: a network-based cross-lagged analysis in advanced cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study enhances the understanding of the longitudinal relationships between the SSBDJ intervention, fatigue, sleep disturbances, and QoL among patients with advanced cancer. It could provide an important insight for designing precise symptom management strategies in mind-body exercise interventions among this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AddaVax-Adjuvanted Inactivated Vaccine Confers Protection Against Listeria monocytogenes Challenge in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Listeria monocytogenes (Lm) is a facultative intracellular pathogen responsible for life-threatening listeriosis, characterized by high mortality rates. Currently, there is no vaccine available for the prevention or treatment of listeriosis. Here, we developed two adjuvanted inactivated vaccines and evaluated their safety, immunogenicity, and protective efficacy. The hypervirulent Lm strain XYSN was inactivated with β-propiolactone (BPL) and formulated with AddaVax or Alum to produce inactivated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and testing of a prognostic scoring system for screw-positioning related femoral neck fracture failures for younger adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This research established cannulated screw positioning as a significant prognostic factor in young patients. The newly developed prognostic model shows promise in identifying prognostic-related risks, though additional validation with larger cohorts is required.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medication association analysis of antimicrobial-induced arrhythmias based on FP-growth frequent pattern mining]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibiotic-related arrhythmias represent a major clinical challenge, characterized by risk patterns that remain not fully elucidated. This study employed the FP-growth algorithm to uncover associations between antibiotic classes and specific arrhythmias, and to identify key high-risk patient profiles. We included 246 cases of antibiotic-related arrhythmia from Center for Adverse Drug Reaction Monitoring of Chongqing (2013-2023). In the FP-growth association algorithm, we took antibiotic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Migration background and specialized mental health care utilization in young adults: a register-based study in the Netherlands]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contrast-enhanced ultrasound for precise differentiation of hepatitis-related intrahepatic cholangiocarcinoma and hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The combination of B-mode US and CEUS features demonstrates superior diagnostic performance compared to either modality alone in differentiating hepatitis-associated ICC from HCC. This approach serves as a valuable adjunctive tool, particularly for clarifying diagnosis in equivocal cases or when cross-sectional imaging is contraindicated, thereby facilitating more precise therapeutic decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>In Situ</em> Click Chemistry for Energy-Level-Tunable Mixed Self-Assembled Monolayers in Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Buried interfacial energy alignment critically affects the performance of the inverted PSCs. Achieving an ideal alignment remains challenging as reliable strategies for precisely tuning the electronic structures of individual SAMs are still elusive. Here, we develop an in-situ click chemistry strategy under mild conditions and with high intrinsic reactivity to construct mixed SAMs with tunable energy levels. By modulation of precursor ratios, molecular coupling and energy-level modulation occur...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shifting Patterns of Injection Drug Use in San Francisco, United States: implications for Getting to Zero HIV Infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Methamphetamine supplanted heroin as the drug most often injected in San Francisco, with fentanyl increasing. These drugs' associations with HIV risk may increase transmission unless effective prevention methods such as PrEP can be rapidly scaled up.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Muscle and Anaerobic Performance Relationships With Firefighter Occupational Tasks: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Martin, JR, Abel, MG, Newman, K, Fyock-Martin, M, and Clark, NC. Muscle and anaerobic performance relationships with firefighter occupational tasks: A systematic review and meta-analysis. J Strength Cond Res XX(X): 000-000, 2026-Firefighting requires performing a variety of physically demanding occupational tasks. Subsequently, understanding physical fitness correlates for occupational performance tests (OPTs) is crucial for optimizing firefighter training and readiness. The purpose of this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum: Biodiscovery of <em>Actinomycetota</em> through metabolo-genomics reveals functional diversity across contrasting Mexican ecosystems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spintronic Materials and Devices for Artificial Intelligence Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The core of spintronic technologies lies in the use of electrons' intrinsic spin states, along with their electric charge, for information storage and processing. Spin-based manipulation of electronic devices inherently enables exceptional properties, such as infinite endurance, high-speed operation, scalability, and non-volatility. These attributes make spintronic devices highly suitable for addressing the growing demands of artificial intelligence (AI) for energy-efficient, scalable computing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The randomized controlled trial Fast Track multilevel intervention for children with early-emerging conduct problems breaks intergenerational transmission of violence across three generations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: IPV was intergenerationally transmitted by influencing PCV, with a negative effect on the third generation's mental health. Nevertheless, participation in the Fast Track intervention disrupted this cycle. These findings suggest the importance of policies to support preventive childhood interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multilevel Heterointerface Engineering Breaks the Trap-Barrier Trade-Off in High-Energy-Density Polymer Dielectrics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The low energy density, inefficient operation, and thermal instability of polymer dielectrics hinder the deployment of film capacitors under harsh environmental conditions. Interface engineering has emerged as a powerful strategy to introduce charge traps or construct interfacial barriers, thereby regulating carrier dynamics and enhancing energy storage. Here, we propose a multilevel heterointerface engineering strategy that integrates boron nitride and barium niobate nanosheets through lattice...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasensitive detection of HBsAg and HBV genome analysis in a prospective cohort with chronic hepatitis B after HBV surface antigen loss]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shining a light on Jak inhibition: Partnering with NB-UVB to drive repigmentation in vitiligo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visual Outcomes of Plasma Exchange for Acute Optic Neuritis: A Report by the American Academy of Ophthalmology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Level II and III evidence suggest that PLEX may be associated with improved visual outcomes in acute ON. Severity of vision loss, older age, prior ON in the affected eye, and delay to PLEX all were associated with less visual recovery. Future randomized clinical trials will be required to confirm level I evidence for the efficacy of PLEX treatment in ON and to help determine the optimal timing for treatment and which patients would be most likely to benefit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Involvement of Eosinophil-Driven Intestinal Immune Activation in Different Irritable Bowel Syndrome Subtypes and in the Response to a FODMAP Lowering Diet: A Post Hoc Analysis of the Randomized Controlled DOMINO Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immediate Coronary Angiography for STEMI and Out-of-Hospital Cardiac Arrest: Hospital Variation in the NCDR Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extension Reports: The Neglected Sequel of Cardiovascular Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sirolimus-Eluting Iron Bioresorbable Scaffolds vs Everolimus-Eluting Stents for Percutaneous Coronary Intervention: A Randomized Trial (IRONMAN II)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In IRONMAN-II, the sirolimus-eluting IBS was noninferior to CoCr-EES for 2-year in-segment LLL, QFR, and OCT-derived flow area. Clinical event rates were also comparable between groups although non-ischemia-driven revascularization rates were higher after IBS. Longer-term follow-up is necessary to demonstrate whether late benefits are realized after complete IBS resorption. (A Clinical Investigation to Evaluate the Safety and Efficacy of IBS in Patients With Coronary Artery Disease;...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers for Cardiovascular Drug Development: JACC State-of-the-Art Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circulating and urinary laboratory biomarkers are central to cardiovascular, kidney, and metabolic drug development, and they support diagnosis, risk stratification, dose finding, safety monitoring, and, in selected settings, endpoint definition. Yet only a few materially shape trial design or regulatory decisions, and still fewer meet stringent criteria for surrogate endpoints. This review proposes a context-of-use framework in which circulating biomarkers are assessed along 2 converging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Lesion Delivery and Irrigation Rates on Neurovascular Events With PFA for Atrial Fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These data suggest that workflow factors may account for the 10-fold reduction in neurovascular events before vs after the commercial pause, namely by delivering fewer ablations (32.6 to 21.2) and avoiding stacking lesions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The trajectory of iatrogenic perforation: Mapping progress, gaps, and future trends]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND PRACTICAL IMPLICATIONS: Preoperative risk assessment and guided endodontics in complex cases reduce the incidence of iatrogenic perforations. Advances in biocompatible materials allow for more effective perforation repair, simplify clinical procedures, and minimize the risk of developing tooth discoloration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Close and Enhance the Cancer-Immunity Cycle by Engineered Dual-Targeted Nano-Adaptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The cancer-immunity cycle (CIC) provides a conceptual framework for eliciting effective anti-tumor immune responses by targeting key events in systemic immunity. However, the successful completion of the CIC often requires the coordinated action of multiple therapeutic modalities, necessitating their integration into a unified system to overcome the limitations of conventional combination therapies. Here, we present a multimodal and programmable platform that integrates diverse therapeutic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Photocatalytic Propane Dehydrogenation via Electronic Structure Modulation of Platinum Sites Over Platinum-Based Alloys]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photocatalytic propane dehydrogenation (PDH) offers a promising route for propylene production under mild conditions despite the unsatisfactory propylene yield at present. Herein, we have introduced several second metals into Pt/ZnO catalyst to modulate the electronic structure of Pt by forming PtM alloys. Among all these catalysts, PtPb alloys/ZnO catalyst (PtPb/ZnO) exhibits the optimum photocatalytic PDH activity. Both experiments and density functional theory calculations reveals that PtPb...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Covalent Amorphous Alumina-Hydrogenated Graphene Materials With Integrated Proton Radiation Shielding and Energy Storage Capability for Space Electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of adaptive material platforms that integrate proton radiation shielding with energy storage capabilities is critical for achieving both miniaturization and cost-effective reliability in space electronics. Here, we present an industrially viable technology for fabricating covalent amorphous alumina-hydrogenated graphene (AHG) films that can attenuate energetic protons, store electrical energy, and adapt to downsizing. Specifically, the fabrication involves thermal-driven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid atomic-signal-based in-situ magnetic compensation for unshielded spin-exchange relaxation-free atomic magnetometer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method, which leverages the atomic signal itself, to achieve rapid in situ magnetic field compensation in an unknown geomagnetic environment for an unshielded spin-exchange relaxation-free atomic magnetometer. This method employs a strong bias magnetic field aligned with the pump beam direction to maximize the strength of the magnetic field resonance signal. The compensation process is divided into three sequential stages, each focusing on one of the x, y, and z axes by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient Characteristics Associated With Telehealth Use in a Large Federally Qualified Health Center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Findings can guide strategies to improve telehealth services for underrepresented groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preoperative and Intraoperative Risk Factors for Postoperative Pneumonia After Cardiac Surgery: An Ancillary Study of the STERNOCAT (Catheter Outcomes With Sternotomy Cardiac Operated) Randomized Trial and a Systematic Review With Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights the difficulty of predicting and preventing POP, as most identified risk factors are non-modifiable or require long-term preventive strategies. Perioperative optimization, particularly regarding CPB management and transfusion practices, therefore, remains essential to improving patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of Fitbit measured physical activity and sedentary behavior with mental health in U.S. youth: a quantile regression analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Objectively measured daily steps, MVPA, and sedentary behavior are prospectively associated with adolescent internalizing symptoms. The associations differ substantially among adolescents with varying levels of symptom severity and between sexes. Findings may inform targeted physical activity interventions to enhance adolescent mental health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tulane virus protease as a structural surrogate for inhibitor screening of human norovirus proteases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human norovirus (HuNoV) is a significant cause of gastroenteritis worldwide, affecting people of all age groups. There are currently no vaccines or drugs available, leaving susceptible populations vulnerable to severe or protracted illness. A HuNoV cultivation system is pivotal for screening norovirus antivirals. While the human intestinal enteroid cultivation system allows robust replication of multiple HuNoV strains, it presents technical and cost barriers. Tulane virus (TV), a surrogate for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Mus musculus</em> papillomavirus MmuPV1 resists restriction by human APOBEC3B]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The single-stranded DNA deaminase APOBEC3B (A3B) is capable of potently restricting the replication of a range of viruses, including retroviruses (cDNA) and herpesviruses (genomic DNA). However, these and likely other DNA virus families have evolved host species-specific counter-defenses that are equally potent and serve to protect viral DNA from restriction. Although high-risk human papillomavirus (HPV) infection triggers A3B upregulation, potentially as part of an antiviral response, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An inducible CRISPRi system for phenotypic analysis of essential genes in <em>Pseudomonas aeruginosa</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precise and tunable genetic tools are essential for high-throughput functional genomics. To address this need in the important gram-negative pathogen Pseudomonas aeruginosa, we developed and characterized a tightly regulated CRISPR-interference (CRISPRi) system that enables precise and tunable repression of essential genes. The system utilizes a rhamnose-inducible promoter to control both the Streptococcus pasteurianus-derived dCas9 and gene-specific sgRNAs, each encoded on separate plasmids for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterogeneous associations of polygenic indices of 35 traits with mortality: a register-linked population-based follow-up study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PGIs related to the best-established mortality risk phenotypes had the strongest associations with mortality. They offer moderate additional prediction even when mutually adjusting with their phenotype.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-modal integration of protein interactomes with genomic and molecular data discovers distinct RA endotypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is a heterogeneous autoimmune disease characterized by clinical and molecular heterogeneity, notably in the presence of anti-cyclic citrullinated peptide antibodies (CCP). CCP-positive (CCP+) RA patients exhibit more severe disease progression and distinct treatment responses compared to CCP-negative (CCP-) patients. Although previous studies have investigated cellular and molecular differences between these subtypes, their genetic differences are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Glaphene to Glaphynes: A Hybridization of Two-Dimensional Silica Glass and Graphynes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hybrid two-dimensional (2D) materials have attracted increasing interest as platforms for tailoring electronic properties through interfacial design. Very recently, a hybrid 2D material termed glaphene, which combines monolayers of 2D silica glass and graphene, was experimentally realized. Inspired by glaphenes, we proposed a class of similar structures named glaphynes, which are formed by stacking SiO(2) monolayers onto α-, β-, and γ-graphynes. Graphynes are 2D carbon allotropes with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cycloastragenol Derivatives Improve Tyrosine Metabolism, Regulate TLR4/NF-κB/TERT Signaling Pathways, and Inhibit MPTP Induced Neuroinflammation and PD Symptoms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study focuses on the potential mechanism of CAG derivative R2 in treating PD through "inflammation-aging" research. By inhibiting inflammation and restoring telomerase activity, it breaks the vicious cycle and provides new ideas for the treatment of PD, laying a foundation for the development of drugs using CAG for PD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondrial D-loop region methylation differentiates Parkinson's disease from atypical parkinsonism and Parkinson's disease dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Decreased mitochondrial D-loop methylation in PD-D and APS may reflect disease-specific epigenetic mechanisms rather than clinical characteristics or treatment effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis and biological evaluation of fluorinated bergenin derivatives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bergenin is a natural C-glycoside with multi-target therapeutic potential. Herein, a series of 21 novel derivatives were designed and synthesized through direct hydroxy-fluorination and the incorporation of fluorinated building blocks. Biological activity evaluation results demonstrated that, except for ether derivatives, most fluorine-containing derivatives exhibited superior anti-inflammatory and antitussive activities compared with bergenin, and among these derivatives, the C4-fluorinated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Water Quality of U.S. Drinking Water Kiosks: Lead Release from "Lead-free" Plumbing after Reverse Osmosis Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many Americans distrust tap water, leading them to purchase more expensive drinking water sold from water vending machines (e.g., kiosks) that are poorly regulated and sparingly monitored for quality. Here, we analyzed the water quality of 20 kiosks from 4 different manufacturers across 6 states in the first comprehensive comparison of the chemical and microbial characteristics of kiosk water to paired tap samples. Of the 16 kiosks listing specific water treatment processes (others indicated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Confined Space in Hollow Micro/Nano Structures: Boosting Supercapacitor Performance to New Heights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-performance electrode materials are key to advancing supercapacitor technology. Hollow micro- and nanostructured materials with confined space effects act as precise "nanoreactors." These materials effectively regulate ion transport kinetics, enhance interfacial interactions, and stabilize the electrode/electrolyte interface, achieving rapid ion storage and efficient diffusion. This review systematically summarizes the latest advances in the application of such materials in supercapacitors....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41670213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260211145633&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>