<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 07:45:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and safety of motion style acupuncture treatment for acute neck pain: a multicenter randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MSAT, which integrates acupuncture with guided movement, was associated with more rapid pain relief and functional improvement than conventional acupuncture, without compromising safety. These fundings suggest that MSAT may be a clinically useful option to support early functional recovery in patients with acute neck pain. Trial Registration ClinicalTrials.gov (Identifier: NCT04539184).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of intrathecal morphine compared with truncal nerve blocks on postoperative analgesia in adults : A meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In comparison to TNBs the use of ITM in relatively high dosages (5-10 μg/kg) provides statistically superior analgesia and reduces opioid use within 24 h postoperatively but its association with increased PONV warrants cautious interpretation and further study.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epigenetic suppression of synovial inflammation and osteoclast differentiation in rheumatoid arthritis by I-BET762]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The BRD and extra-terminal domain (BET) family of proteins was inhibited using I-BET762, a small molecule inhibitor, which mimics interaction with acetylated lysin residue in BET protein. We explored the roles of the bromodomain (BRD) of chromatin adapators in regulating synovial inflammation in rheumatoid arthritis (RA). The expression levels of bromodomain proteins, c-Myc, and the components of the MAPK and NF-κB signaling pathways were detected by western blot. The BRD3, BRD4, and c-Myc...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut microbiota-derived isoxanthohumol metabolite, 8-prenylnaringenin, mitigates endothelial dysfunction in Angiotensin II-induced hypertension through G protein-coupled estrogen receptor-mediated eNOS activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Humulus lupulus L. (hops), which is traditionally used in brewing, is a rich botanical source of prenylated flavonoids with potential cardiovascular protective properties. Of these, 8-prenylnaringenin (8-PN), a potent phytoestrogen formed from isoxanthohumol by the gut microbiota, has been implicated in vascular health. Nitric oxide (NO), which is produced by endothelial nitric oxide synthase (eNOS), exerts profound effects on vascular tone and endothelial integrity. This study examined the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune evasion and pathogenesis of henipaviruses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Zoonotic viruses pose an escalating threat to global health, driven by climate change, deforestation, urbanization, and increased human-wildlife interactions. Among these threats, Henipaviruses - particularly Hendra virus and Nipah virus - have emerged as priority pathogens due to their severe clinical manifestations, broad host range, and pandemic potential. Naturally maintained in asymptomatic Pteropus fruit bats, Henipaviruses periodically spill over into humans via intermediate hosts,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase II trial, multicenter, first-line paclitaxel-avelumab treatment of inoperable angiosarcoma (KCSG UN 18-15)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Avelumab plus weekly paclitaxel demonstrated preliminary evidence of efficacy and tolerability in inoperable angiosarcoma. Given the rarity of angiosarcoma, further multicenter, collaborative, and translational studies are warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roles of Glia in Synapse Nano-organization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glia, which are nonneuronal cells in the central nervous system, include astrocytes, microglia, and oligodendrocyte lineage cells. Historically, their passive roles in maintaining central nervous system function-such as supplying substrates for neuronal energy, buffering neurotransmitters, and improving neural conductance-have been primarily highlighted. Importantly, recent research has revealed that glial cells express genes directly related to controlling synapse nano-organization. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A combined genetic and chemical approach for identifying novel antifungal compounds against <em>Fusarium graminearum</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chemical fungicides act by targeting specific proteins or pathways, known as modes of action (MoAs). In this study, we established a systematic screening platform using Fusarium graminearum gene knockout mutants to evaluate the efficacy of fungicides and identify novel antifungal compounds. Target genes corresponding to major fungicide classes were deleted by homologous recombination, and the resulting mutants exhibited altered sensitivity to the corresponding fungicides compared with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptome Analysis Provides Insights into Avenanthramide Biosynthesis in Oats under Methyl Jasmonate and Abscisic Acid Cotreatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Avenanthramides are phenolic alkaloid derivatives uniquely found in oats (Avena sativa L.). We conducted transcriptomic analysis to investigate the global changes of gene expression in oat seedlings cotreated with methyl jasmonate (MJ) and abscisic acid (ABA). The cotreatment significantly enhanced avenanthramide accumulation in oat seedlings, reaching 1171.7 mg/kg fresh weight, representing a 5.5-fold increase compared to the 4 day control sample (221.5 mg/kg FW). A total of 4841 genes were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex Differences in Mortality and Functional Outcomes Across Stroke Subtype: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this national cohort, sex disparities in stroke outcomes differed by subtype. Despite lower adjusted mortality in females, functional outcomes were not uniformly better. These findings underscore the importance of adopting sex- and subtype-specific approaches to stroke care, secondary prevention, and rehabilitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoglin Regulates Pluripotency and Differentiation in Human Embryonic Stem Cells Through Wnt and TGF-β Signaling Crosstalk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although endoglin (ENG) is traditionally recognized as a coreceptor in TGF-β signaling, its role in human pluripotent stem cells (hPSCs) remains unexplored. Here, we report that ENG knockout (ENG^(-/-)) hPSCs maintain core pluripotency markers yet undergo spontaneous differentiation and exhibit markedly reduced potential to form mesoderm, ectoderm, and endoderm lineages. Contrary to expectations, pharmacological inhibition of TGF-β signaling failed to replicate or rescue this phenotype,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term biogas slurry fertilization alters rhizosphere soil metabolite profiles and microbial communities in poplar plantations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biogas slurry, a nutrient-rich organic fertilizer, has unclear impacts on plant-soil interactions. Rhizosphere metabolites serve as a bridge between plants and soil microorganisms, significantly influencing soil health and microbial activity. This study employed high-throughput sequencing and untargeted metabolomics to investigate microbial community and metabolite profiles in rhizosphere soil of poplar plantations treated with biogas slurry at different concentrations (Con: untreated; Low: 250...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electroacupuncture mitigates Bacillus Calmette-Guérin (BCG)-induced depression-like behavior and neuroinflammation via BDNF and NF-κB pathway in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Depression induce by chronic neuroinflammation disrupts daily life and work, underscoring the importance of its treatment. It this study, depressive- and anxiety-like behaviors were induced in mice by injecting bacillus Calmette-Guérin (BCG), resulting from chronic neuroinflammation. Daily stimulation with specific acupuncture points (Baihui and Yintang, GV20 and GV29) with electroacupuncture (EA) for 14 days significantly alleviated depressive- and anxiety-like behaviors. Additionally, it also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laser-Architected Shape-Configurable Vertical Graphene Thermoacoustic Loudspeakers for 3D Acoustic Emission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566636/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in thermoacoustic (TA) loudspeakers have focused on freeform, conformal audio systems that enable conformal integration, spatial sound control, and seamless transformation between 2D and 3D geometries. However, their practical use remains limited by low sound pressure levels (SPLs) and poor mechanical adaptability, primarily due to insufficient thermal dissipation and structural rigidity. Here, we report a high-performance, shape-configurable TA loudspeaker based on vertically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566636/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional Shotgun Metagenomic Insights into Gut Microbial Pathway and Enzyme Disruptions Linking Metabolism, Affect, Cognition, and Suicidal Ideation in Major Depressive Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The gut microbiome changes might contribute to activated peripheral NIMETOX pathways in MDD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient selection and management for successful cementless total knee arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Total knee arthroplasty (TKA) is a widely performed procedure for end-stage arthritis, with cemented fixation historically dominating owing to its immediate stability and ability to compensate for minor bone defects. However, concerns over the long-term durability of cemented implants, particularly in younger and more active patients, have renewed interest in cementless TKA as a viable alternative. Advances in implant design, including hydroxyapatite coatings and porous metal surfaces, have...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes in newly diagnosed patients with Waldenström's macroglobulinaemia treated in a tertiary academic centre]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Waldenström's macroglobulinaemia (WM) is a rare B-cell lymphoproliferative disorder with multiple effective front-line treatment options. However, real-world comparative data on commonly used regimens are limited. We conducted a retrospective cohort study of 348 consecutive, newly diagnosed WM patients treated between 2002 and 2024. Patients received first-line therapy with either bortezomib-dexamethasone-rituximab (BDR, n = 35), Bruton's tyrosine kinase inhibitors (BTKis, n = 57) or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combination of bacteriophage-probiotics alleviates intestinal barrier dysfunction by regulating gut microbiome in a chick model of multidrug-resistant Salmonella infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Taken together, these findings demonstrate that phage-probiotic co-administration not only enhances the clearance of multidrug-resistant Salmonella more effectively than phage treatment alone but also promotes intestinal health, highlighting its potential as an antibiotic-alternatives strategy to improve intestinal health and ensure food safety in poultry production systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluid responsiveness and changes in venous congestion and lung water during volume expansion in critically ill patients: a multicentre observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A fluid challenge worsened venous congestion, assessed by VExUS as well as CVP, in fluid non-responders, while it was not in fluid responders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eradication of Aspiculuris tetraptera in various immunodeficient mouse models using ivermectin: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomic Tuning of Metal-Support Interactions for Pathway-Selective CO<sub>2</sub> Photoreduction on TiO<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photocatalytic CO(2) conversion demands precise control over multielectron reaction pathways to achieve selective solar fuel production. Atomically dispersed Fe and Cu catalysts on TiO(2) direct divergent photoreduction outcomes-CO via Fe and CH(4)/C(2)H(6) via Cu-through modulation of CO intermediate binding. Using in situ diffuse reflectance infrared Fourier transform spectroscopy (DRIFTS), X-ray absorption fine structure (XAFS), and density functional theory (DFT) calculations, this study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of brain iron homeostasis and its influence on cognitive function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings indicate a dynamic interaction between systemic and brain iron homeostasis, which influences BG CBF and attention performance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early outcomes of subcostal four-arm robotic pulmonary resection and mediastinal lymph node dissection for non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the early outcomes of subcostal robot-assisted thoracic surgery (subRATS) for non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC). We conducted a prospective, single-arm cohort study at Seoul National University Bundang Hospital beginning in June 2022 to evaluate the feasibility of subRATS for pulmonary resection in NSCLC. This interim analysis assessed outcomes in consecutive patients from June 2022 to June 2025. The operative times for a subgroup of patients who underwent lobectomy were also analyzed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fucoxanthin Extracted from the Microalgae Phaeodactylum tricornutum Ameliorates Alzheimer's Pathologies with the Reduction of Aβ-Induced NLRP3 Inflammasome Activation in APP/PS1 Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder, one of the most common types of dementia, accompanying severe learning and memory dysfunctions. In AD brains, the misfolded aggregation and deposits of amyloid-β (Aβ) and tau are frequently observed before the cognitive symptom onset; thus, trials for alleviation of these lesions are considered commensurate strategies with AD treatment. Additionally, increasing evidence suggests that misfolded and aggregated proteins induce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Percutaneous modified iliac screw fixation: technique and clinical experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PMIS provides a safe and minimally invasive option for sacropelvic fixation. It avoids the limitations of CIS and S2AI while reducing soft tissue dissection. Although early results are promising, larger studies are needed to validate the effectiveness and broader clinical use of this method.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stable operation of a network-based multi-algorithm earthquake early warning system: the Korea meteorological administration platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rgnef regulates bone mass through the activation of RhoA and Rac1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rho guanine nucleotide exchange factor (Rgnef/p190RhoGEF), a RhoA-specific guanine nucleotide exchange factor, has been implicated in cancer and amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, but little is known about its role in bone. Here we investigate the roles of Rgnef in bone metabolism using Rgnef-deficient and overexpressing mice. Compared with littermate wildtype mice, Rgnef-deficient mice had increased bone mass owing to lower osteolysis and higher osteogenesis, and Rgnef-overexpressing transgenic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of smart patient care robot with enhanced autonomous navigation through path optimization in hospital wards]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A data analytics-driven approach to backorder prediction using federated machine learning in industrial supply chains]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sarcopenic Dysphagia Reconsidered: A Systematic Review of Complex Interactions and Diagnostic Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenic dysphagia is an emerging clinical concept defined as dysphagia resulting from generalized sarcopenia and sarcopenic changes in the muscles involved in swallowing. However, despite growing clinical interest, its diagnostic criteria, pathophysiological boundaries, and causal validity remain insufficiently established. This systematic review aimed to examine how sarcopenic dysphagia has been defined and assessed in the literature and to identify conceptual and methodological gaps. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early age at smoking initiation is associated with elevated cardiovascular disease and mortality risk in a nationwide population-based cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Smoking is a major cause of cardiovascular diseases, including myocardial infarction (MI) and stroke. However, the role of age at smoking initiation in cardiovascular risk has not been fully established. We selected 9,295,979 Korean adults without preexisting cardiovascular diseases who underwent health screening in 2009. The association of age at initiation with incident MI, stroke, MI or stroke, and all-cause mortality was analyzed using Cox proportional hazard models stratified or adjusted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning for predicting functional outcomes in acute ischemic stroke: insights from a nationwide stroke registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurately predicting the prognosis of patients with acute ischemic stroke at discharge remains highly challenging after active treatment. The aim of this retrospective nationwide registry-based study was to identify key predictors associated with favorable outcomes and to develop machine learning models for patient outcome prediction. Analysis of a comprehensive dataset of 40,586 patients revealed younger age (odds ratio [OR]: 0.975; 95% confidence interval [CI]: 0.972-0.977; p < 0.001), lower...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synaptic and intrinsic membrane defects disrupt early neural network dynamics in Down syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Down syndrome, caused by trisomy 21, affects around six million people worldwide and features learning, memory and language deficits. However, the mechanisms underlying trisomy 21 neurophenotypes involving human cortical circuitry are unknown. By characterising developing neural network dynamics and single cell excitability profiles, from synaptic and voltage-dependent ion channel behaviour using an isogenic induced pluripotent stem cell-derived neuronal model, we show that trisomy 21 impairs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to: Optimal dosing and duration of linezolid in multidrug-resistant tuberculosis: methodological and clinical appraisal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Interplay of Endplate Bone Quality, Cage Geometry, and Segmental Biomechanics in Minimally Invasive Transforaminal Lumbar Interbody Fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary Sodium Intake and Prediabetes in Korean Adults: A Nationally Representative Cross-Sectional Analysis of 57,165 Participants (KNHANES 2010-2018)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher dietary sodium intake is independently associated with an increased prevalence of prediabetes in Korean adults. The observed risk threshold and dose-response plateau suggest that sodium moderation, specifically aiming below the 3-4 g/day range, may be a vital strategy for preventing glycemic dysregulation alongside blood pressure control.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D-printable hyaluronic acid/gelatin double-network hydrogels for stretchable and adhesive wound patches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving rapid hemostasis and effective scavenging of reactive oxygen species at wound sites is crucial for designing wound patches to accelerate the skin wound healing process, while considering their tissue biocompatibility and adhesive features. To address these challenges, we propose integrating natural polymer-based double-network hydrogels with multiple functionalities for the 3D printing of wound dressing materials. Natural polymer-based double-network hydrogels comprising oxidized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cellulose nanofibers enable the thermoelastic structuring of agar-based gels mimicking beef intramuscular fat]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent decades, the development of plant-based meat alternatives has been hindered by the lack of fat analogues that can replicate the key thermoelastic properties of animal fat during cooking. This study presents a novel strategy for structurally and thermally reinforcing agar-based emulsion gels by incorporating cellulose nanofibers (CNFs). Emulsion gels containing 0-1 wt% CNFs were compared with beef intramuscular (IM) fat. Increasing the CNF concentration significantly reduced the oil...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tolylfluanid induces mitochondrial dysfunction through excessive ROS generation and inhibits cell growth in bovine mammary epithelial cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tolylfluanid is a phenylsulfamide fungicide commonly used to manage fungal diseases in crops; however, evidence has shown its unintended toxicity in non-target organisms. To elucidate its cellular impact, we investigated how tolylfluanid affects bovine mammary epithelial (MAC-T) cells. The results revealed that exposure to tolylfluanid suppressed MAC-T cell viability, enhanced apoptotic responses, and disrupted 3D spheroid development compared with the control group. The treatment provoked...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cocktail Precursor Approach for Homogeneous ALD InGaO Film Growth Overcoming Limits of Mobility-Reliability Trade-Off in Oxide Semiconductors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crystalline indium gallium oxide (IGO) semiconductors have attracted considerable attention as promising channel materials for high-performance field-effect transistors (FETs) because of their excellent thermal stability and high field-effect mobility. In this study, we report a cocktail precursor strategy based on a 3:1 molar mixture of an In precursor (DMITN) and a Ga precursor (DMGTN) for uniform and efficient atomic layer deposition (ALD) of multicomponent oxide thin films. Thermal analyses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superior localizing and prognostic value of statistical parametric SPECT analysis in temporal lobe epilepsy: A comparative study of ISAS and SISCOM]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ISAS outperforms SISCOM in both localizing accuracy and observer reliability, and its concordance with surgical resection robustly predicts postoperative seizure freedom. These findings support the adoption of ISAS as the first-line SPECT postprocessing technique for presurgical evaluation of TLE.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomy and physiology of strawberry flowers determine fruit set]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Commercial strawberry cultivars are often self-compatible, however most still depend on pollinators to achieve a marketable fruit set. To identify factors influencing fruit development in the absence of pollinators, this study examined the anatomical and physiological characteristics of flowers in four strawberry cultivars. The analyses focused on floral structure, pollen traits, and fruit outcomes. Micro-CT imaging was used to analyze floral morphology. Pollen quantity and viability were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare workers' perspectives on evidence-based infection control in South Korean nursing homes: A qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infection prevention is critical for improving safety and care quality, reducing mortality, and enhancing the quality of life in nursing homes for older adults. These establishments often lack standardized guidelines, and have inconsistent protocols. This study evaluated the Evidence-Based Guidelines for Nursing Home Infection Control in South Korea (ENIK) by examining healthcare workers' (HCWs) experiences. Five focus groups, involving 28 HCWs in total, were analyzed using qualitative content...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Need-Driven Dementia-Compromised Behavior model-based interventions on behavioral and psychological symptoms of dementia: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Need-Driven Dementia-Compromised Behavior model-based interventions alleviated overall behavioral and psychological symptoms of dementia, agitation and depressive symptoms. Subgroup analysis provide evidence supporting interventions that explicitly incorporate the model's core concept and facility-based delivery while suggesting the combination of care system capacity building with individual-level interventions. This study suggests that the model is not merely a theoretical concept...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanism and performance of a p-n Ag<sub>2</sub>O/TiO<sub>2</sub> S-scheme heterojunction for photocatalytic oxidation of gaseous benzene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient photocatalytic degradation of volatile aromatic hydrocarbons, such as benzene, remains a major challenge in photocatalytic air purification due to their highly stable π-conjugated structures and large ring-opening energy barriers. To address this, a series of Ag(2)O/TiO(2) S-scheme heterojunction photocatalysts (denoted as AT-x, where x represents the mass ratio (%) of Ag(2)O to TiO(2)) is synthesized. In the AT-x S-scheme heterojunction, the Ag(2)O acts as the reduction photocatalyst...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reproductive factors and the risk of pelvic organ prolapse in postmenopausal women: A nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Having multiple births and prolonged breastfeeding are key independent risk factors for pelvic organ prolapse in postmenopausal women. Other reproductive and hormonal factors have only minor effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex-specific associations of creatinine and antioxidant biomarkers with lung cancer risk by drinking and smoking behavior: A prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In men, serum creatinine showed a strong inverse association with lung cancer risk under oxidative stress conditions related to smoking and alcohol consumption.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sleep deprivation and epiretinal membrane risk: Machine learning findings from a nation-wide survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sleep deprivation was significantly associated with a 1.25-fold increase in the prevalence of ERM, especially among non-high-risk alcohol consumers and those with diabetes. Weekday sleep deprivation may be a modifiable risk factor for ERM. Prospective studies are warranted to confirm causality and explore the underlying mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic implication of tumor grade in patients with node-negative breast cancer aged ≤ 50 years with 21-gene recurrence scores of 11-25]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A high-grade tumor was associated with increased tumor recurrence in younger node-negative patients with an intermediate RS. These findings support the incorporation of tumor grade into prognostic assessment and treatment decision-making in this group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyperreflective Choroidal Foci and Their Longitudinal Changes Following Treatment for Branched Retinal Vein Occlusion-Associated Macular Edema]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: HCF may dynamically indicate ongoing choroidal activity in BRVO. Their incomplete resolution following treatment correlates with earlier ME recurrence and greater treatment demand, indicating their potential role in guiding retreatment decisions and assessing disease activity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interferometric Evidence of Nonvolatile Anomalous Phase Shifts in Exchange-Spin-Split Josephson Supercurrent Diodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The recent realization of zero-field, polarity-reversible supercurrent rectification in proximity-magnetized Rashba-type Pt Josephson junctions (JJs) enables the development of superconducting logic circuits and cryogenic memory applications. Here, we demonstrate a nonvolatile anomalous phase shift φ(0) directly probed via superconducting quantum interferometry, providing phase-sensitive evidence of spontaneous time-reversal symmetry breaking in these Rashba-type systems. By replacing the Pt...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Central aortic cannulation as a primary strategy in acute type A aortic dissection surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Central cannulation significantly reduced operative duration compared with axillary cannulation. Early mortality was lower in the central cannulation group. The rates of significant neurological dysfunction and procedure-related complications were comparable with those associated with axillary cannulation. Central cannulation can be safely and effectively used as a primary cannulation strategy for ATAAD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Palmitoylation of the human cytomegalovirus tegument protein pp28 facilitates virus release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tegument proteins of human cytomegalovirus (HCMV) play essential roles in viral assembly, coordinating interactions among capsids, membranes, and host-derived components. pp28 (UL99), a dominant tegument protein expressed during late infection, is essential for cytoplasmic envelopment and proper trafficking to the viral assembly compartment (vAC). Here, we identify a critical role for palmitoylation in pp28 function. Using site-directed mutagenesis and acyl-resin assisted capture (acyl-RAC)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does narrow foraminal height adversely affect outcomes of posterior cervical foraminotomy for cervical radiculopathy?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Narrow FH adversely affects clinical outcomes and increases the risk of revision surgery following PCF. Surgeons should consider alternative approaches, such as ACDF, for patients with preoperative FH < 6 mm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrochemical Properties of Interface-Modified Li-Metal All-Solid-State Batteries: Li/LLZTO/LVO Cell]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lithium (Li) metal all-solid-state batteries (ASSBs) were developed with a Li/LLZTO (Li(6).(4)La(3)Zr(1).(4)Ta(0).(6)O(12))/LVO (LiV(3)O(8)) configuration to enhance energy density and safety for electric vehicle applications. To overcome limitations in ionic conductivity and electrode-electrolyte interfacial resistance, we optimized: (1) Li metal anode, (2) anode/solid electrolyte interface, (3) LLZTO solid electrolyte, (4) cathode/solid electrolyte interface, and (5) nonlithiated LVO cathode....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol for necropsy and tissue processing of the common marmoset, Callithrix jacchus, for histopathological analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The common marmoset (Callithrix jacchus) is an important nonhuman primate model in biomedical research, but the lack of a standardized necropsy protocol limits reproducibility and data quality. Here, we present a protocol for necropsy and tissue processing of the common marmoset (Callithrix jacchus). We describe steps for anesthesia, external observation, laparotomy, blood collection, organ sampling, and fixation. We then detail procedures for trimming, tissue processing, and embedding. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiology of Sport Injury Among Korean Male Youth Soccer Players: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prevention strategies should focus on noncontact ankle sprains in Korean youth soccer players. Given the growth spurts experienced by U-15 soccer players, emphasis should be placed on muscle conditioning and balance training to control movement and prevent soccer injuries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circumferential subparaneurial ganglion cyst involving the ulnar nerve at the elbow: illustrative case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Recently, the distribution of subparaneurial ganglion cysts involving the common peroneal and tibial nerves was described based on MRI analysis. Crossover in extreme cases was observed at the sciatic bifurcation through a mechanism comparable to a geyser, enabled by fenestrations in the epi- and paraneurium at the level of the bifurcation. The goal of this study was to investigate whether the geyser theory for crossover holds for other locations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morphological characteristics of choroidal anastomosis as predictors of subsequent rupture in adult moyamoya disease: a longitudinal study using vessel wall imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In ChA-positive hemispheres, a larger LA of the ChA, complex-type ChA, and the presence of ChA-related pseudoaneurysms were significant predictors of subsequent ChA rupture and hemorrhagic stroke, whereas revascularization surgery can reduce the risk of subsequent ChA rupture and hemorrhagic events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Zdhhc22-mCherry BAC transgenic mouse line reveals neuronal expression dynamics in the developing and adult CNS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The DHHC palmitoyltransferase Zdhhc22 is known to play a role in neuronal differentiation, synaptic regulation, and brain development. While transcriptomic data hint at region-specific expression, its exact spatiotemporal and cell-type distribution in the mammalian brain is unclear. For this purpose, we generated a bacterial artificial chromosome (BAC) transgenic mouse line that expresses the mCherry fluorescent reporter driven by the Zdhhc22 promoter. We then analyzed Zdhhc22 expression from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basroparib inhibits YAP-driven cancers by stabilizing angiomotin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Yes-associated protein (YAP) is a key oncogenic effector and a well-established driver of resistance to anticancer therapies, especially in tumors harboring KRAS mutations. Although YAP is clinically relevant, drug-development efforts that directly inhibit its activity have been limited. Here, we show that basroparib-a selective tankyrase (TNKS) inhibitor that suppresses Wnt signaling-attenuates YAP-driven oncogenic programs by stabilizing angiomotin (AMOT), an endogenous negative regulator of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Level Ferulic Acid Production in Engineered Yeast Enables Discovery and Biosynthetic Application of Novel Enzymes from <em>Piper nigrum</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferulic acid (FA), a methoxy-substituted hydroxycinnamic acid, serves as a pivotal precursor for pharmaceuticals and plant natural products, yet its bioproduction faces challenges from competitive byproduct synthesis and inefficient methylation. To address these limitations, we first redirected carbon flux toward FA from fusel and styrenes by knocking out transcriptional activator ARO80 and the FA degradation pathway. Combined with the enhanced cofactor S-adenosylmethionine (SAM) regeneration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Beta-Amyloid Biomarkers on Performance of Digital Mind Mapping Tasks in Alzheimer's Disease Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The study confirms that patients with AD pathology experience difficulties in using their mental lexicon to activate and select appropriate words for retrieval due to damage in the temporal-parietal regions caused by beta-amyloid deposition. This study highlights the potential of digital mind maps as a novel word retrieval task for early differentiation of cognitive impairment in AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure Status and Risk of Cardiovascular Disease in Older Adults Aged 75+ Without Prior Cardiovascular Events: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this large observational cohort, elevated blood pressure (BP) categories were associated with higher risks of stroke and myocardial infarction in adults aged ≥75 years, with the highest risk in uncontrolled hypertension. Stroke risk rose progressively with increasing systolic BP, whereas myocardial infarction demonstrated a U-shaped relationship with diastolic BP. These findings highlight clinically relevant risk patterns in late life and may support future research aimed at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of Lateral Orbital Hollowing With Hyaluronic Acid Filler]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Supraperiosteal HA placement for lateral orbital hollowing restored the lateral contour with high satisfaction and minimal downtime through 6 months. Presenting clinical photographs in a single composite figure enables a clear baseline-to-follow-up comparison. Longer-term follow-up beyond 6 months is needed to better define durability and late events in this region.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Mucilaginibacter aureus</em> sp. nov. and <em>Mucilaginibacter sediminis</em> sp. nov., isolated from wetland soil]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two Gram-stain-negative, non-motile, rod-shaped bacterial strains, designated AW1-3^(T) (strictly aerobic) and AW1-7 ^(T) (facultatively aerobic), both catalase- and oxidase-positive, were isolated from a reed wetland in South Korea. Strain AW1-3^(T) grew at 15-35 °C, pH 6.0-7.0 and in 0.0-0.5% (w/v) NaCl, whereas strain AW1-7^(T) grew at 10-35 °C, pH 6.0-7.0 and in 0-0.5% NaCl. The major fatty acids (>10%) were iso-C(15:0) and summed feature 3 (C(16:1) ω7c and/or C(16 :1) ω6c) in strain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the <em>in vitro</em> urease inhibitory potential, molecular docking and dynamics simulations investigation of mefenamic acid derivatives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This work identifies 2a as a potent, and competitive urease inhibitor. The integrated experimental, ADMET and computational strategy provides a robust molecular blueprint for its activity, positioning it as a promising lead candidate for developing new therapeutic agents against urease-related pathologies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world effectiveness and safety of belantamab mafodotin monotherapy in patients with relapsed/refractory multiple myeloma treated in Europe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Not available.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal Opioid Use and Subsequent Risk of Allergic Diseases in Children: Emulation of Target Trials Using the Korean Nationwide Birth Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative multi-omics stratification and translational evaluation of Treg-targeted combination immunotherapy in breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study identifies Treg-enriched and immunosuppressive breast cancer subtype through integrative multi-omics analysis and demonstrates, through both in-silico and in-vivo approaches, the therapeutic potential of combining Treg-targeted and PD-L1 blockade therapies. These findings highlight Treg-mediated immunosuppression as a key determinant of therapeutic responsiveness, providing a biological rationale for patient stratification and guiding the development of personalized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serial analysis of <em>ESR1</em> mutations in cell-free DNA from hormone receptor-positive, HER2-negative metastatic breast cancer during palliative endocrine therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We observed worse outcomes in patients with persistent bESR1 detection during first-line endocrine therapy and then sustained positive. bESR1 was detected prior to clinical progression in half of patients. Our study suggests the benefit of bESR1 monitoring during palliative endocrine therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Follicle-stimulating hormone linked to cognitive decline and amyloid burden in postmenopausal women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Women have a higher risk of developing Alzheimer's disease (AD) than men, with hormonal changes during menopause being a potential factor. However, the exact relationship between these hormonal changes, cognitive function, and AD pathology is not fully understood. This study investigates the differential associations between serum follicle-stimulating hormone (FSH) and estradiol levels with cognitive function and cerebral amyloid-βeta (Aβ) deposition, quantified using amyloid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative evaluation of three automated urine sediment analyzers excluding cutoff-related trade-offs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Performance comparison of automated urine sediment analyzers is difficult due to cutoff-related trade-offs. In this study, we evaluated and compared UF-5000, UAS800, and Cobas u701 using receiver operating characteristic (ROC) analysis. A total of 774 urine samples were analyzed using manual microscopic examination and microbial culture as the reference test. The area under the ROC curve (ROC-AUC) was compared using DeLong's test. UF-5000, a flow cytometry analyzer, demonstrated significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medication Adjustment After Bariatric and Metabolic Surgery: A Review of Current Evidence and Clinical Practice Trends]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bariatric and metabolic surgery (BMS) is the most effective treatment for severe obesity and its related comorbidities. Rapid metabolic improvement following surgery frequently leads to the reduction or discontinuation of medications for obesity-related comorbidities. However, there are no established guidelines regarding timing or criteria for dose adjustment. A narrative review examined major clinical trials, meta-analyses, and society guidelines relevant to BMS. Evidence from previous and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic and Bariatric Surgery for Class I Obesity (Body Mass Index 30-34.9 kg/m<sup>2</sup>): A Comprehensive Literature Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Class I obesity (body mass index [BMI]: 30-34.9 kg/m²) constitutes a considerable portion of the global obesity burden; however, traditional guidelines for metabolic bariatric surgery (MBS) have historically excluded this population. Recent updates in clinical consensus have expanded surgical eligibility, particularly for patients with obesity-related comorbidities refractory to medical treatment. To synthesize evidence from clinical studies, international guidelines, and expert consensus to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuous Transversus Abdominis Plane Block After Laparoscopic Sleeve Gastrectomy in 50 Consecutive Cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although continuous TAP block did not reduce cumulative opioid consumption, the need for additional opioid and antiemetic injection can be reduced within the postoperative 24 hours.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Kidney Replacement Therapy During Extracorporeal Membrane Oxygenation Support in Terms of Mortality: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: KRT during ECMO is associated with increased mortality, likely due to the severity of illness and complications like infections and bleeding. The optimal timing of KRT initiation remains unclear, and no significant survival benefit was found for early KRT. Further large-scale RCTs are needed to optimize management strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empirical optimization of dual-sgRNA design for in vivo CRISPR/Cas9-mediated exon deletion in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CRISPR/Cas9 has transformed gene editing, enabling precise genetic modifications across species. However, existing sgRNA design prediction models based on in vitro data are difficult to generalize to in vivo contexts. In particular, approaches based on single-sgRNA design require additional filtering of in-frame mutations, which is inefficient in terms of both time and cost. In this study, we developed the first mammalian in vivo-trained prediction model to evaluate the efficiency of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41568097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nine Unrecorded Species of <em>Phanerochaete</em> (Polyporales, Basidiomycota) in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phanerochaete is one of the largest genera of the family Phanerochaetaceae within the order Polyporales, characterized by membranaceous basidiome and ellipsoid to cylindrical basidiospores. As white-rot saprotrophs, Phanerochaete species produce ligninolytic enzymes to degrade lignin and cellulosic materials. Several species have been applied to bioremediation, biopulping, and bioethanol industries due to their enzymatic abilities. While 123 Phanerochaete species have been reported globally,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ergosterol Attenuates Palmitate-Induced Tenocyte Apoptosis Through the Suppression of ER Stress and Myocyte-Derived IL-15/METRNL-Mediated Crosstalk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ergosterol (EG), the main bioactive ingredient in Wolfiporia hoelen, has been shown to suppress inflammation and oxidative stress in various disease models. However, the effects of EG on endoplasmic reticulum (ER) stress and apoptosis in tenocytes in in vitro obesity models have not been studied. Protein expression in tenocytes was assessed by Western blotting. Terminal deoxynucleotidyl transferase dUTP nick-end labeling (TUNEL) staining was performed to distinguish apoptotic cells, and ELISA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Choroidal Vascular Remodeling and Retinal Response After Aflibercept Loading in Diabetic Macular Edema]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Aflibercept treatment induces stromal-dominant choroidal thinning with a consequent increase in CVI. This choroidal remodeling may be associated with the anatomical resolution of DME through mechanisms involving reduction of inflammatory HRF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of single xeno-nucleic acid replacement on the fluorescence of DNA-encapsulated silver nanoclusters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fluorescent properties of DNA/AgNCs are largely governed by the composition of AgNCs, the nucleobase sequence, and the secondary structure of the DNA template. Here, by systematic incorporation of xeno-nucleic acid modifications, we demonstrate the potential of altering the sugar chemistry of the template DNA backbone, as a novel factor in AgNC fluorescence modulation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fully hydrogenated vegetable oil-based non-dairy creamer intake impairs athletic performance in mice: serum metabolomics and intestinal microbiota analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Fully hydrogenated vegetable oil-based non-dairy creamer (FHVO-NDC) is produced through complete hydrogenation of vegetable oil, resulting in a trans fat-free product commonly incorporated into sports foods and performance-oriented beverages. Because diet plays a crucial role in shaping athletic performance, understanding the potential physiological effects of FHVO-NDC is essential for athletes and fitness enthusiasts. However, the combined impact of FHVO-NDC on muscle physiology,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlicensed medical practice as a public health risk: Implications for Korean Medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[APSPGHAN Statement on Endoscopic Variceal Bleeding Hemostasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings provide an evidence-based framework for the management of pediatric variceal bleeding. Individualized care is emphasized while highlighting the pressing need for high-quality pediatric studies to strengthen future recommendations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: High-resolution single-cell RNA sequencing using canFam4 reveals novel immune subsets and checkpoint programs in healthy dogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fimmu.2025.1680437.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tislelizumab efficacy and safety compared to other anti-PD-1s: a network meta-analysis of first-line therapies for unresectable, locally advanced or metastatic esophageal squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Tislelizumab + CT is an effective 1L treatment option for advanced or metastatic ESCC, demonstrating comparable efficacy and safety outcomes relative to existing treatments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Latilactobacillus curvatus</em> DCF0620 and postbiotics derived from soybean germ reduce colitis severity by modulating fibrosis and gut dysbiosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings suggest that L. curvatus DCF0620 and its soybean germ-based postbiotics represent promising therapeutic agents for IBD by demonstrating potent anti-inflammatory, anti-fibrotic, and gut microbiota-modulating effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Step Electrochemical Synthesis of PEDOT-NG Nanoarchitecture via Multifunctional Electrolytes for High-Performance Pseudocapacitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of high-performance pseudocapacitors based on conducting polymers has been severely constrained by fundamental challenges, including poor cycling stability, limited ionic accessibility, and complex multistep synthesis procedures. Here, we demonstrate a revolutionary one-pot electrodeposition approach utilizing lithium nanographenide (LNG) as a multifunctional electrolyte that simultaneously serves as supporting electrolyte, anionic dopant, and structural modifier for the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41567009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fully automated frame selection and region-of-interest placement in 2D shear wave elastography: reduced examination time with comparable reproducibility in diffuse liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Fully automated 2D-SWE markedly reduces examination time while maintaining high reproducibility in liver stiffness assessment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective evaluation of the safety and efficacy of microwave ablation for hepatocellular carcinoma in Korean patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MWA appears to be a safe and effective treatment for early-stage HCC, demonstrating durable tumor control and a low incidence of major complications over 3 years.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive US findings for differentiating between malignant and benign thyroid nodules: Doppler and microvascular imaging according to the TI-RADS and pathologic subtypes of malignancy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CDI and MFI may assist in distinguishing between malignant and benign nodules, and evaluation of nodular vascularity may be tailored to the TI‑RADS category.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supplemental automated breast ultrasound in negative screening mammography: early-stage cancer detection in dense breasts with limited yield in non-dense breasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ABUS identified small, node-negative invasive cancers with likely favorable prognoses but demonstrated limited value in women with non-dense breasts, supporting its personalized use based on breast density and patient preference.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasound-based fat quantification: advancing steatosis assessment in the metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease era]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The association between the consumption of raw Kudoa septempunctata-infected farmed Paralichthys olivaceus and gastrointestinal symptoms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings indicate both an association and a causal relationship between consumption of K. septempunctata-infected farmed P. olivaceus and the onset of gastrointestinal symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Salt Water Drops Slide Faster: Ionic Modulation of Drop Friction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The friction of drops on solid surfaces governs processes in microfluidics, energy devices, and surface engineering. In recent years, it has been established that slide electrification on insulating substrates leads to a substantial increase in drop friction. Here we present experimental evidence suggesting that such spontaneous charging effects impede the motion of drops not only on insulating substrates, but also on conductive substrates coated with nanometer-thin hydrophobic films. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SiO<sub>2</sub>-Infused COFs for PhotoPyro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The therapeutic promise of covalent organic frameworks (COFs) in phototheranostic applications has attracted significant attention due to their tunable porosity and design flexibility. However, their clinical translation remains limited by chemical instability and insufficient performance under physiological conditions. To address these issues, we adopted a post-synthetic modification (PSM) strategy, coating SiO(2) nanoparticles with ultrathin COF layers through Schiff-base condensation of TAPP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends and Characteristics of Corneal Transplantation in South Korea (2021-2023): A Three-Year Analysis of Domestic Survey and Eversight Eye Bank Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Corneal transplantation in South Korea is shifting toward EK, especially DMEK, driven by limited domestic donations and changes in surgical preferences. These findings highlight the importance of enhancing local donation systems and maintaining robust data infrastructure to guide policy and clinical decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The significance of small lymph nodes on CT for advanced poorly cohesive gastric carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between the confusion assessment method for the intensive care unit (CAM-ICU) and prolonged mechanical ventilation following major cardiac surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: An early postoperative positive CAM-ICU assessment was associated with higher risks of PMV, reintubation, ICU readmission, and prolonged ICU stay after major cardiac surgery. Routine CAM-ICU screening may help identify patients at risk of prolonged ventilation and enable timely, targeted interventions to improve postoperative respiratory recovery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Symptom Burden and Palliative Care Needs in Advanced Breast Cancer Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the symptom burden and palliative care needs of Korean women with stage III and IV breast cancer. Using a descriptive cross-sectional design, an online survey was conducted with 132 participants, assessing symptom burden with the Functional Assessment of Cancer Therapy-General and palliative care needs with the Problems and Needs in Palliative Care questionnaire-short version. The results showed that the greatest burden was in social well-being, followed by physical,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facilitating collaboration between public health researchers and policymakers: a scoping review of global practices, barriers and facilitators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings underscore that structured collaboration, particularly when supported by institutional mechanisms, ongoing capacity building and iterative engagement, plays a critical role in increasing the use of research in public health policymaking. By distinguishing co-production as both a deliberate strategy and an emergent outcome, this review offers new insight into how collaborative models can be designed or evolved to strengthen evidence-informed decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Causal analysis of traditional and environmental risk factors for long-term development of type 2 diabetes using a conditional survival Bayesian network: evidence from the Korean Genome and Epidemiology Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commensal microbe-derived butyrate enhances T follicular helper cell function to boost mucosal vaccine efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study underscores the crucial role of the gut microbiota, particularly neomycin-depleted butyrate producing taxa, in regulating PP-Tfh cell function and IgA production. Butyrate emerges as a metabolite linking microbial metabolism to Tfh differentiation and IgA class switching. Together, these findings establish a microbiota-metabolite-Tfh cell axis essential for mucosal immune homeostasis and suggest novel strategies for enhancing vaccine efficacy and protection against enteric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microenvironment-Guided Evolution of ssDNA-SWCNT Probes for Selective Recognition of Aggressive Prostate Cancer Phenotypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite advances in prostate cancer detection, distinguishing indolent from aggressive phenotypes remains challenging. We report a microenvironment-guided strategy for evolving phenotype-specific molecular probes using single-stranded DNA-functionalized single-walled carbon nanotubes (ssDNA-SWCNTs). Our approach employs 3D tumor models that recapitulate complex cancer microenvironments, enabling identification of ssDNA sequences with differential binding properties. We developed two distinct...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41566610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Antiaromatic Ni(II) Norcorroles by Mn Powder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ni(II) norcorroles have garnered significant attention due to their distinct antiaromaticity and stability. However, their conventional synthetic protocol requires the use of unstable Ni(0) complexes, resulting in cumbersome procedures and a limited substrate scope. Herein, we disclose an efficient method for the synthesis of Ni(II) norcorroles using manganese powder. This improved protocol affords Ni(II) norcorroles with heteroaryl and halogenated aryl substituents at the meso positions with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age and sex as risk factors for health-related quality of life outcomes in patients with glioma: a CODAGLIO 2.0 analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with glioma have clinically relevant worse HRQoL compared to the general population. There are statistically but not clinically significant associations between age, sex, and certain HRQoL scales.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond borders: plasmids drive a shared antibiotic resistome in European urban water systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overall, this work provides the first attempt at a holistic description of the UWSs' resistome, its structure, dynamics, and mobility and significantly expands the current knowledge. Video Abstract.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Umbilical cord-derived mesenchymal stromal cells attenuate radiation-induced neuron damage in vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiation-induced brain injury is caused by repeated radiation therapy for brain tumors and leukemia. Effective treatments for radiation-induced brain injury have not been developed. This study aimed to investigate the neuroprotective effects of umbilical cord-derived mesenchymal stromal cells (UC-MSCs) on irradiated neurons. We irradiated fetal mouse cortical neurons followed by coculture with UC-MSCs in vitro. Radiation significantly reduced the number of MAP2-positive mature and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abnormal carnitine concentrations in critical illness associated with compromised outcome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: On ICU-day-6, both low and high free carnitine concentrations associated with delayed ICU-recovery, and excess morbidity and mortality, suggesting a U-shaped relationship.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monitoring patients' symptom improvement in palliative care units using patient-reported outcomes: a multicenter prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare professionals' perspectives on prescribing DOACs to frail older patients; the DOAC-FRAIL questionnaire]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights the complexity of prescribing DOACs to frail older patients. While HCPs take multiple factors into account, a standardized approach to prescribing DOACs in this population remains lacking. In addition, almost half of HCPs expressed a need for guidelines regarding DOAC use in frail older patients. Hence, more research is needed to fill this knowledge gap and guide HCPs in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peptide turnover prediction using transformer architectures on large-scale time-series proteomic data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Remediation of hazardous explosive-contaminated soil at field scale: a data-oriented review of technologies, challenges and recommendations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Explosive contamination in soil from mining, demolition, and defense activities poses serious threats to both environmental and human health. While remediation methods have been evaluated at the laboratory scale, their performance in the field remains a significant concern. This review consolidates field-tested remediation studies and highlights knowledge gaps, emphasizing the need for regulatory alignment and research focused on scalable, low-impact solutions. Statistical analysis via the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic and molecular mechanisms in lung cancer with interstitial pneumonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis (IPF) is associated with an increased risk of lung cancer, with cumulative incidence rates of 3.3% and 15.4% at 1 and 5 years of follow-up, respectively. The prognosis for patients with lung cancer and IPF is worse than that for patients with IPF alone, primarily due to the progression of lung cancer and complications arising after treatment. Epidemiological and molecular studies indicate that IPF and lung cancer share several pathogenic mechanisms, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world clinical utility and challenges of comprehensive genomic profiling for advanced solid tumors in a community health institution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings demonstrate the clinical utility of CGP testing in local medical facilities; however, the high proportion of approved drugs among genomically matched treatments highlights significant barriers to clinical trial participation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical complete response and predictive factors in HER2-positive early breast cancer treated with neoadjuvant chemotherapy aimed at omission of surgery: an exploratory analysis of the JCOG1806 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ER-negativity, an IHC score of 3 + , and a higher histological grade were independent predictors of a cCR. Identifying these features may improve the feasibility and safety of surgery omission for patients with HER2-positive early breast cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Podocyte infolding glomerulopathy in a Japanese girl with systemic lupus erythematosus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Podocyte infolding glomerulopathy is a rare glomerular lesion characterized by microtubular structures and microspheres in the glomerular basement membrane. While most reported cases are associated with autoimmune diseases such as systemic lupus erythematosus, pediatric cases are rarely reported. The patient was a 14-year-old Japanese girl with a 1-year history of proteinuria detected during a school urinary screening program. Five months prior to admission to our department, she was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unexpected Biliary Migration of N-Butyl Cyanoacrylate During Tract Embolization after Portal Vein Embolization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comment on real-world persistence and interpretation of BMD outcomes in denosumab vs. alendronate therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41572007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regional association between PM2.5 exposure and anti-VEGF treatment demand for age-related macular degeneration: a nationwide ecological study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This nationwide analysis revealed a significant association between regional PM(2.5) levels and the use of anti-VEGF intravitreal injections for macular diseases. No such relationship was observed for SO(X), NO(X), or PMD. These findings suggest that PM(2.5) may contribute to the regional demand for AMD treatment, highlighting the need for further investigation into the impact of air pollution on ocular health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mortality comparison between the COVID-19 Omicron variant and influenza among patients with end-stage kidney disease: a nationwide population-based retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this nationwide study, COVID-19 Omicron variant was associated with significantly higher mortality than influenza in hemodialysis patients. Age-stratified analyses showed consistent relative risks but progressively larger absolute risk differences in older patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Translating spatial transcriptomic signatures in adenosquamous carcinoma into bulk prognostic biomarkers in lung adenocarcinoma: a bottom-up approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spatial transcriptomics enables the detection of rare or transitional tumor states not captured by bulk transcriptomics or immunohistochemistry (IHC). However, translating these spatially defined states into clinically relevant biomarkers is challenging, because signals from minor populations are underrepresented or masked in bulk data. Lung adenosquamous carcinoma (ASC), containing intermixed adenocarcinoma and squamous components, provides a model to study lineage transitions and poorly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance evaluation of the BactInsight simplified blood culture system developed for resource-limited settings using a simulated test design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Swallowing Safety in an Older Patient with Tongue and Pharyngeal Morphological Variations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of a novel natural compound that acts on the membrane progestin receptor α (paqr7) from the marine algae Padina]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previously, we identified water-soluble compounds with membrane progestin receptor α (mPRα)-binding activity from the marine algae Padina arborescens. The compounds inhibited fish oocyte maturation. These compounds are potentially novel antagonists of mPR and are of interest as novel inhibitors of the nongenomic pathway of steroids. In this study, a compound with mPRα binding activity was purified from the methanol extract of Padina tarries. The structure of one of the major compounds in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical implications of systolic blood pressure for diabetic retinopathy across HbA1c levels in a Japanese population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell atlas of human lung aging identifies cell type dyssynchrony and increased transcriptional entropy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Age is a major risk factor for lung disease. We characterized the changing cellular, transcriptional, and genomic landscape of human lung aging using single-cell RNA sequencing. We find that lung aging is cell-type dyssynchronous, with alveolar epithelial and endothelial cells exhibiting the greatest transcriptional changes. Among alveolar epithelial cells, aging is associated with a decreased relative proportion of surfactant-expressing SPC^(high) AT2 cells. Among alveolar capillary cells, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating single-cell ATAC-seq atlasing technologies using sequence-to-function modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deciphering the cis-regulatory logic underlying cell type identity remains a key challenge in biology. Single-cell chromatin accessibility (scATAC-seq) atlases enable training of sequence-to-function (S2F) deep learning models to decode enhancer logic. Yet, optimal criteria for constructing training datasets, i.e., the number of cells and ATAC fragments, remain unclear. Moreover, the suitability of different scATAC-seq platforms for such models has not been systematically tested. We introduce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut Microbiota Changes After Hormonal or Surgical Treatment for Endometriosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Hormonal therapy for endometriosis may help not only to control lesions but also to support mental health. Surgical treatment may alter the composition of inflammation-associated gut bacteria; however, these exploratory results from a small cohort should be interpreted with caution. Further studies with larger sample sizes are warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors associated with elevated serum gentamicin levels in hip and knee joints treated with continuous local antibiotic perfusion: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Elevated serum gentamicin levels occurred in a subset of patients treated with CLAP. Elevated serum gentamicin levels may be associated with both treatment-related factors (iMAP pins, gentamicin dose, and CLAP duration) and host-related factors (lower albumin and hemoglobin, renal function, and systemic inflammation). Considering these risk factors may help adjust dosing strategies and contribute to the safe application of CLAP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subtype-specific characteristics and outcomes of liposarcoma: A population-based study using Japan's National Cancer Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Treatment efficacy varies significantly across liposarcoma subtypes, with potential survival benefits of radiotherapy in dedifferentiated subtypes and chemotherapy in pleomorphic subtypes. These findings support subtype-guided treatment approaches and suggest benefits of centralized care for optimal therapy implementation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes of anatomical single-bundle versus double-bundle anterior cruciate ligament reconstruction: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Interventional studies found no significant differences between anatomical SB and DB ACL reconstruction. Observational studies suggested fewer pivot-shift and slightly higher Lysholm scores with DB; however, these findings were susceptible to bias, showed limited clinical relevance, and lacked consistent replication, suggesting that the evidence remains inconclusive.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of cellular characteristics and genome editing responses in chicken primordial germ cell lines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chicken primordial germ cells (cPGCs) hold great potential for genetic modification and germ cell research in chickens. In this study, we evaluated the cellular characteristics of three cPGC lines: cPGC-1, cPGC-2, and cPGC-3. cPGC-1 and cPGC-2 were derived from male chickens, whereas cPGC-3 was derived from a female chicken. We analyzed and compared cell proliferation rates, marker gene expression, and gonadal colonization abilities. Three different cell culture temperatures were assessed (37...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Higher openness and conscientiousness are associated with lower risk of long-term care needs: A 22-year follow-up of community-dwelling older adults in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among older adults living in the community, higher openness and conscientiousness were protective against future LTC needs. These findings highlight the potential role of psychological traits in promoting autonomy and healthy aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The performance and mechanism of sodium carboxymethyl cellulose in promoting the anaerobic ammonium oxidation coupled with Fe (III) reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anaerobic ammonium (NH(4)^(+)-N) oxidation coupled with Fe(III) reduction (Feammox) is a novel promising nitrogen removal pathway, but the unsatisfactory nitrogen removal induced by the low bioavailability of Fe(III) compounds limited its engineering potential. In this study, three easily available exogenous reinforcing substances (ERSs), humic acid (HA), sodium carboxymethyl cellulose (CMC-Na) and sodium sulfite (Na(2)SO(3)), were used to improve Fe(III) bioavailability and Feammox performance....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of Pulpal Sequelae in Cracked Teeth with Reversible Pulpitis using Machine Learning Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ML models demonstrated a predictive accuracy of 74-77%. They could improve diagnostic precision and support timely decision-making for endodontic intervention in the management of cracked teeth with reversible pulpitis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Occurrence, fate and correlation analysis of antibiotics and antibiotic resistance genes (ARGs) in rural domestic wastewater treatment facilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibiotics and antibiotic resistance genes (ARGs) are emerging contaminants of increasing concern in rural wastewater treatment systems. This study examined the occurrence, removal, and ecological risks of 42 antibiotics and related ARGs across the rural facilities utilizing three treatment processes: anaerobic digestion with soil infiltration systems (AD+SIS), anaerobic-anoxic-oxic (A/A/O), and fixed-bed membrane bioreactor coupled with constructed wetlands (FMBR+CW). Eighteen antibiotics were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of Radiologic Morphology in Nodal Spread of Clinical Stage IA Hypometabolic Lung Adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41571027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Palmitic acid induces UCP1-independent mitochondrial depolarization specifcally in brown adipose tissue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brown adipose tissue (BAT) is a major site of non-shivering thermogenesis, where mitochondria generate heat instead of adenosine triphosphate (ATP). The thermogenesis occurs through the activity of uncoupling protein 1 (UCP1) which specifically resides in the mitochondrial inner membrane and dissipates the mitochondrial proton gradient upon activation by long-chain free fatty acids (FFA). Although UCP1-independent proton leak has been reported, the mechanism underlying UCP1-independent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vitro recapitulation of drug metabolite partitioning into the bile and blood using the icHep system consisting of hepatocytes with an induced open-form bile canaliculus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For in vitro studies that predict the safety of systemically circulating drug metabolites, evaluating the formation and biliary excretion of hepatic drug metabolites in human hepatocytes is necessary. However, conventional sandwich-cultured hepatocytes (SCH) form closed bile canaliculi that preclude direct collection of excreted biliary metabolites. Therefore, this study assessed whether primary cultured hepatocytes with an induced open-form bile canaliculus (icHep) provide a suitable system for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative pan-genomics and in vivo validation identify genetic factors important for virulence of Salmonella enterica serovar Gallinarum and serovar Enteritidis in the avian host]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salmonella enterica subspecies enterica serovar Gallinarum biovar Gallinarum (SGa) and Pullorum (SPu) are avian-specific pathogens causing systemic disease, while S. Enteritidis (SEnt) is a broad host range serovar causing gastroenteritis. The genomic mechanisms underlying this difference in host range and pathogenicity remain incompletely understood. Here, we performed a large-scale pan-genome analysis of 5440 poultry-derived genomes (4927 SEnt, 106 SGa, 407 SPu) integrated with functional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical characteristics and severity of primary ciliary dyskinesia caused by large homozygous deletion including exons 1-4 of DRC1: A multicenter retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although the sensitivity of the PICADAR score was low in these patients, most clinical and radiological features of DRC1-related PCD were relatively typical of PCD. Given that DRC1-related PCD appears to worsen with age, early diagnosis and timely intervention are crucial.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding plant cell heterogeneity and dynamics across responses, development, to evolution with single-cell technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-cell technologies are redefining plant cell identity. Traditional classifications based on position, morphology, and a few marker genes yielded static, coarse cell categories. In contrast, single-cell and single-nucleus RNA sequencing reveal hidden cellular heterogeneity and reconstruct developmental trajectories in ostensibly well-characterized plant tissues including vasculature and mesophyll. Environmental cues such as pathogen attack, drought, and wounding generate transient,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Decade of Changes: Investigating Etiologies in Epileptic Spasms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EP4 stimulation promotes cell adhesion and migration via IL-6 signaling in oral squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oral squamous cell carcinoma cell (OSCC) comprises malignant neoplasms arising within the oral cavity. Early-stage detection is associated with favorable prognosis, whereas progression to advanced stages with lymph node metastasis significantly worsens outcomes. We previously reported that the prostaglandin E₂ (PGE₂) receptor EP4 regulates OSCC migration. RNA sequencing reanalysis suggested that EP4 stimulation is strongly associated with cell migration and adhesion, with interleukin-6 (IL-6)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De-escalation strategies for axillary management at primary surgery in early breast cancer: insights and implications for medical oncology practice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The recognition that axillary surgery in early breast cancer primarily serves as a staging tool rather than a curative treatment, along with the shift from axillary lymph node dissection (ALND) to sentinel lymph node biopsy (SLNB) as the standard procedure for clinically node-negative patients, has paved the way for further de-escalation of axillary treatment. This strategy aims to reduce treatment-related morbidity while preserving survival outcomes. Multiple studies have provided compelling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five-year survival of patients with non-small cell lung cancer treated with alkalization therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acidic tumor microenvironments promote malignant progression, immune evasion, and drug resistance. This single-center retrospective cohort study evaluated whether, among patients with stage IV non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) who participated in a pragmatic "alkalization therapy"-defined as a low potential renal acid load diet plus oral sodium bicarbonate and/or potassium/sodium citrate-urinary pH was associated with long-term survival, and whether these associations differed by EGFR/ALK...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-omics analysis reveals ER stress as a main feature in two endothelial cell models of N-linked congenital disorders of glycosylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glycosylation is one of the most important posttranslational modifications. When the glycosylation machinery is affected, this leads to a congenital disorder of glycosylation (CDG). CDG are a class of rare multisystemic diseases that often affect the endoplasmic reticulum (ER). Although vascular complications have been reported in CDG, the contribution of endothelial dysfunction to these phenotypes remains incompletely understood. Here, we evaluated the effect of glycosylation deficiency on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41570364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychological distress among Japanese high school students during the COVID-19 pandemic: An energy landscape analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: By revealing associations between the COVID-19 pandemic and lower levels of psychological distress and healthier mental health states, our work demonstrates the potential of using dynamical systems theory, such as the energy landscape analysis, to interpret health and disease metrics in psychology and psychiatry. This approach may improve mental health surveillance for the next pandemic.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41569975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260123024504&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>