<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 07:46:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dipole-Driven Charge Trapping in Monolayer Janus MoSSe for Ultrathin Nonvolatile Memory Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The continued scaling of flash memory technologies faces challenges such as limited operation speed, poor data retention, and interface defects inherent to conventional three-dimensional architectures. Two-dimensional (2D) materials, with van der Waals interfaces and atomic-scale thickness, offer a promising pathway to overcome these limitations by enabling efficient charge modulation while minimizing surface defects. In this work, a nonvolatile 2D flash memory device is developed employing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multicenter Retrospective Analysis by the Korean Association of Pediatric Surgeons Comparing Laparoscopic and Open Surgical Repair of Congenital Duodenal Obstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Laparoscopic repair can be considered a safe and effective alternative to open surgery for selected patients with CDO, assuming adequate surgical expertise.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Label-Free SERS Fingerprinting of Neuroprotein Conformational Dynamics in Human Saliva]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conformational transitions of neuroproteins are closely associated with neurological disorders and represent key biomarkers for diagnosis and disease monitoring. A reliable and label-free method for detecting and tracking these structural changes is critical for effective clinical application. In this work, a galvanic molecular entrapment (GME) strategy is presented to combine with surface-enhanced Raman scattering (SERS) for localization and label-free detection of neuroproteins. This approach...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of loneliness and perceived social exclusion with donation behavior among community-dwelling individuals aged 40 and over: longitudinal evidence from the nationally representative German Ageing Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Avoiding increases in perceived social exclusion could encourage the decision to donate, an important prosocial behavior, pending further longitudinal evidence. Cross-country comparisons are recommended.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Needling Therapy for Burn Injury and Related Complications: A Scoping Review of Experimental and Clinical Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Needling therapy may be a novel alternative therapeutic intervention for burn injuries and related complications. This scoping review aimed to comprehensively evaluate the evidence status of needling therapy for burns and their complications. Studies on needling therapy for burns and related complications were retrieved from inception to 1st June 2024. Nine databases (MEDLINE, Embase, CENTRAL, CNKI, CiNii, RISS, KISS, DBpia and OASIS) were searched without any language or study-type...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of outpatient treatment engagement following a visit to a specialized emergency department for substance use: A cohort study using high-resolution electronic health records]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Stockholm model for fully integrating specialized substance use disorder care into emergency departments appears to generate high post-acute treatment engagement and highlights the need for (1) targeted interventions for police-initiated admissions and (2) broad aftercare options to better attract treatment-naïve patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-expandable metal stents versus plastic stents for unresectable malignant hilar biliary obstruction: A systematic review and meta-analysis of reconstructed individual patient data from randomized controlled trials with meta-regression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with unresectable MHBO, SEMSs offer superior stent patency and survival compared to PSs, with similar safety and procedural success. These findings reinforce previous guidelines recommending the preferential use of SEMSs for endoscopic palliation in MHBO.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New frontiers and applications of cell-free systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell-free systems (CFS) have emerged as a key platform in the field of synthetic biology. This is used to understand natural biological systems outside living cells. It contains cell extracts from procaryotes, eucaryotes, which provides a controlled environment for complex biological processes that leads to the synthesis of valuable biomolecules. It lacks natural mechanisms, yet it contains all the necessary components, which are required for the synthesis of desired biomolecules. It is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Randomized, Double-Blind, Placebo-Controlled Trial of ID-CBT5101, a Tyndallized <em>Clostridium butyricum</em> Postbiotic, in Adults with Mild-to-Moderate Knee Osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoarthritis (OA) is a common cause of chronic pain and functional impairment in older adults. Evidence suggests a gut-joint axis, where gut dysbiosis and systemic low-grade inflammation may contribute to OA pathogenesis. Postbiotics, which are non-viable microbial products such as heat-killed bacteria, have been proposed as safe and stable alternatives to live probiotics. ID-CBT5101, a tyndallized Clostridium butyricum preparation, reduced inflammation and preserved cartilage in a rat OA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus on the diagnosis of Cushing's disease: a collaborative statement from the Korean Endocrine Society and Japan Endocrine Society]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cushing's disease (CD) is a rare but serious endocrine disorder caused by excessive cortisol secretion due to adrenocorticotropic hormone-secreting pituitary tumors. Despite recent developments in diagnostic criteria and treatment options, CD remains associated with substantial comorbidities and mortality. Early and accurate diagnosis is thus essential. Both the Korean Endocrine Society (KES) and Japan Endocrine Society (JES) guidelines are intended to standardize diagnostic approaches to CD,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Metabolomics and Microbial Profiling in Patients with Irritable Bowel Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study was conducted to identify metabolic and gut microbial changes associated with the pathophysiology of irritable bowel syndrome (IBS) by comparing the plasma/urinary metabolite profiles and gut microbiota composition between healthy controls (HC) and IBS patients. There was no significant difference in overall microbial diversity; however, IBS patients showed relatively higher abundance of Christensenellaceae R-7 group, Clostridium sensu stricto 1, and Negativibacillus. Metabolite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Insights into MltC from <em>Acinetobacter baumannii</em>: Conservation of the Catalytic Residue and Flexibility in Substrate Recognition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lytic transglycosylases (LTs) are key enzymes involved in bacterial peptidoglycan remodeling. Here, we present the crystal structure of MltC from Acinetobacter baumannii (AbMltC), representing the second reported MltC structure after that of Escherichia coli (EcMltC). The AbMltC structure reveals a conserved catalytic residue, E224, equivalent to E217 of EcMltC, which directly participates in glycosidic bond cleavage. Notably, the substrate-binding residue R234, corresponding to R227 of EcMltC,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nitrogen loading fluctuations impact microbial community assembly and functional redundancy in anammox reactors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitrogen loading rate (NLR) fluctuations are common in full-scale anammox systems and can compromise process stability, yet the ecological mechanisms underlying system resilience under disturbed conditions remain insufficiently understood. This study investigated how different intensities of NLR disturbances influence microbial community assembly processes and functional redundancy, and how these ecological responses shape nitrogen removal performance. Two anammox sequencing batch reactors were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune Checkpoint Inhibitor Therapy for Advanced, Unresectable Esophageal Squamous Cell Carcinoma: A Series of Patient-level Meta-analyses From Phase III Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PD-L1 appears to be a useful biomarker in advanced ESCC. Patients with PD-L1 levels of 10 or higher consistently showed survival benefits. For PD-L1 <10, treatment decisions may be less clear; further research on combining PD-L1 with other biomarkers is needed. Patients with PD-L1 <1 showed minimal benefit and should be informed about the limited efficacy of ICIs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating the Role of Executive Function in Brain Responses to Infant Crying Among New Parents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infant crying is a fundamental communication signal that captures caregiver attention and elicits caregiving responses. Executive function (EF) is critical in managing the cognitive and emotional demands of parenting, particularly in processing infant cues. This study explored the relationship between experienced EF difficulties and neural responses to infant crying among biological birthing parents. Participants were pregnant individuals from the RISE project who completed the Behavioral Rating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designing with Li<sub>2</sub>S in Lithium-Sulfur Batteries: From Fundamental Chemistry to Practical Architectures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lithium-sulfur (Li-S) batteries deliver gravimetric energy densities considerably higher than those of conventional lithium-ion systems while relying on low-cost, earth-abundant materials. Despite decades of progress, their commercialization remains hindered by intrinsic challenges such as the insulating nature of sulfur and lithium sulfide (Li(2)S), formation and dissolution of soluble polysulfides, and instability of lithium-metal anodes. Among these, the use of Li(2)S as a pre-lithiated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Thin Stacks: Physics, Materials, and Architectures of Thick Perovskite Light-Emitting Diodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thick light-emitting diodes (LEDs)-here defined as devices in 100 nm to multiple micrometers-are emerging across perovskite platforms. Departing from thin stacks, thick architectures reshuffle optical modes, electrical fields, and recombination statistics. On the physics side, increased emitter-metal separation weakens plasmonic loss and strengthens photon recycling, enabling higher light outcoupling efficiency. Lower current density at the same luminance suppresses emission quenching and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liquid Metal-Architected Thermal Management Materials: Void Engineering for Simultaneous High Thermal Conductivity and Flame Retardancy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermal management materials face fundamental challenges in achieving high thermal conductivity while maintaining flame retardancy, limiting their applications in high-performance electronics. Here, we demonstrate that liquid metal-architected void engineering in silicone composites addresses these challenges through systematic interfacial microstructural control. Mechanochemical encapsulation of aluminum nitride particles with eutectic gallium-indium creates multifunctional core-shell fillers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Metastability in Atomic Layer Deposition: Polymorph and Valence Control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metastable phases characterized by their higher-energy states offer promising functionalities for electronic, catalytic, and energy applications. However, their synthesis is often hindered by high formation energy barriers and thermodynamic constraints. Atomic layer deposition (ALD) has attracted significant interest for a wide range of applications, including semiconductors, advanced electronics, and energy-related applications, owing to its exceptional features, including low-temperature...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lewis Acid-Base Effects on Molecular Structure and Charge Density in Solid Polymer Electrolytes for Solid-State Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solid polymer electrolytes (SPEs) are critical for advancing the safety and performance of solid-state batteries (SSBs). However, challenges such as low ionic conductivity, limited mechanical strength, and narrow electrochemical stability windows hinder their widespread adoption. This study investigates the role of lithium salt formulation, specifically lithium bis(fluorosulfonyl)imide (LiFSI), lithium bis(trifluoromethanesulfonyl)imide (LiTFSI), and a binary mixture of the two, on the molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Sacral Slanting on Coronal Balance and Residual Curve After Lumbar Curve Correction in Adolescent Idiopathic Scoliosis: A 5-Year Follow-up Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignRetrospective cohort study.ObjectivesSacral slanting is defined as the angle between the horizontal line and the upper endplate of the sacrum in the coronal plane. This study evaluated changes in disc wedge angle (DWA) below the lowest instrumented vertebra (LIV) and coronal balance over a 5-year follow-up in patients with adolescent idiopathic scoliosis (AIS) with structural lumbar curve exhibiting sacral slanting.MethodsThe study included 118 patients with AIS and structural lumbar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reconfigurable Vertical Schottky Photodiodes Based on Ferroelectric 2D Semiconductors for Perceptual-Precision, Context-Aware Neuromorphic Vision]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To realize in-memory sensing and computing platforms, it is essential to integrate sensing, computation, and memory functionalities within a single device, enabling energy- and time-efficient vision systems with high perceptual precision. However, achieving such multi-functional processing capability within a compact device structure remains a major challenge. Here, a reconfigurable vertical photodiode based on α-In(2)Se(3) is presented, a ferroelectric 2D semiconductor. Gradual and reversible...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Electronic Radial Effects for Fast Li<sup>+</sup> Transport in Solid-State Electrolytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving high Li^(+) conductivity, near-unity transference numbers, and stable interfaces in solid-state electrolytes remains a major challenge for lithium-metal batteries. Here we introduce a radial-effect design principle: relativistic expansion and spin-orbit coupling of 5d orbitals enhance s-d/p-d hybridization, weaken Li-anion interactions, and lower migration barriers. An entropy-based descriptor, S(d), trained and validated with machine learning across >10,000 oxides, sulfides, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluorine-Free Corrosion-Resistant Electrolyte Design for Enhanced Stability in Lithium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advancing liquid electrolyte design is crucial for overcoming the performance limitations of current battery technologies and enabling next-generation energy storage systems. Among recent developments, localized high-concentration electrolytes (LHCEs) have demonstrated remarkable cycling stability. However, their reliance on fluorinated diluents, which are highly reactive with lithium metal, inevitably leads to severe spontaneous corrosion. This study introduces a fluorine-free,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intracellular mRNA Delivery via Lambda DNA-Based Viscoelastic Mechanoporation in Hyperbolic Microfluidic Channel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intracellular delivery into suspension cells, particularly hard-to-transfect immune cells such as T- and B-lymphocytes, remains challenging. Membrane disruption-based microfluidic methods offer a carrier-free alternative but often depend on high-viscosity buffers, compromising viability and scalability. Here, we introduce a viscoelastic mechanoporation platform using a hyperbolic microfluidic channel and low-viscosity λDNA buffer for the efficient delivery of mRNA and small molecules. The system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Monolithic Ferroelectric-Ionic Duality for Stochastic-Neuromorphic Core Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Learning under uncertainty has become increasingly critical in data-intensive artificial intelligence applications, requiring computing systems that unify deterministic and probabilistic functions. Hardware that combines stable memory with tunable stochasticity is essential for such systems, but achieving this integration within a miniaturized architecture remains significantly challenging due to intrinsic conflicts between precise memory retention and controllable stochastic variability. Here...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population pharmacokinetic modelling of amoxicillin in human breast milk-A contribution from the ConcePTION project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings support the low transfer of amoxicillin into breast milk and align with the absence of adverse effects in breastfed infants, reinforcing its safety during lactation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MA-T Activates Human TRPV4 in the Non-pigmented Ciliary Epithelial Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Matching transformation system (MA-T), an on-demand aqueous chlorine dioxide production solution is utilized in various applications, including antibacterial and cancer therapies. Herein, we focused on the ability of MA-T in oxidizing human transient receptor potential cation channel subfamily V member 4 (hTRPV4), which functions as a redox sensor, using Ca^(2+) imaging and patch-clamp experiments. We found that 10 ppm MA-T activated hTRPV4 in HEK293T cells. Moreover, MA-T induced increase in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pex6 and ubiquitination regulate topological remodeling of the peroxisomal membrane protein Pex14]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pex14 is a membrane peroxin that plays a central role in matrix protein import by mediating the docking of the cytosolic receptor Pex5, which delivers cargo harboring a peroxisome targeting signal 1 (PTS1). We previously reported the crystal structure of the conserved N-terminal domain of Pex14, which harbors the primary binding site for Pex5. However, the mechanistic contribution of this domain to the import process, particularly regarding its membrane orientation, remains unclear. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contribution of organic anion transporting polypeptides to bile acid uptake in the Caco-2 cell monolayer and gastrointestinal tract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The apical sodium-dependent bile acid transporter (ASBT, encoded by SLC10A2) is the sole transporter responsible for bile acid absorption in the human intestinal tract and is a therapeutic target for dyslipidemia. Here, we investigated the mechanisms of bile acid uptake in Caco-2 cells, a widely used in vitro model of intestinal absorption. Initial uptake assays revealed biphasic kinetics in bile acid uptake, suggesting the involvement of multiple transporters. At low substrate concentrations,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Matrix protein SPARC drives pro-inflammatory macrophage polarization through TLR4-MyD88/TRIF signaling in dairy cows with subclinical ketosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Secreted protein acidic and rich in cysteine (SPARC) is a matricellular glycoprotein with important roles in extracellular matrix dynamics and immune-metabolic regulation. Although SPARC has been widely implicated in inflammatory and fibrotic disorders in humans and rodents, its involvement in metabolic diseases of ruminants remains unclear. In this study, we investigated the role of SPARC in macrophage-mediated inflammation in dairy cows with subclinical ketosis (SCK) and explored the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Food-Borne Infections Originating from Turkey but Detected Abroad: A Historical Review and Recommendations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deciphering stiffness-driven changes in colorectal cancer by proteomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor stiffening plays a pivotal role in cancer progression. Increased tumor stiffness, resulting from interactions between cancer cells and their surrounding microenvironment, alters the tumor's mechanical properties and significantly impacts cancer growth and metastasis, the primary cause of cancer-related death. Despite the importance of tumor stiffness, systematic studies exploring its effect on protein dysregulation are limited. In this study, focused on colorectal cancer, we show by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Mobility as a Time-Dependent Exposure Factor and Risk of Fall: A Retrospective Cohort Study of Older Patients with Orthopedic Conditions in a Sub-acute Rehabilitation Setting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Repeated assessments of mobility as a time-dependent exposure factor revealed that fall risk was highest during periods requiring light assistance or supervision and was most frequent during weeks 5-6 of the sub-acute rehabilitation setting. These findings indicate that evaluating mobility only at admission is inadequate for assessing fall risk, underscoring the importance of continuous reassessment throughout the sub-acute rehabilitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative assessment of feature and component profiling workflow for supercritical fluid chromatography - high resolution mass spectrometry analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Supercritical fluid chromatography coupled to high-resolution mass spectrometry (SFCHRMS) is gaining attention for non-target screening (NTS), yet systematic evaluations of data-processing workflows remain scarce. Here, we present the first comprehensive comparison between a component-profile (CP) approach based on Region of Interest analysis combined with Component Detection Algorithm and Multivariate Curve Resolution (ROI-CODA-MCR) and a feature-profile (FP) workflow, MS-DIAL. Using extracted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[iPSC-derived modeling of HLA-lacking hematopoiesis reveals clonal diversity in eltrombopag response in acquired aplastic anemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acquired aplastic anemia (AA) is an immune-mediated bone marrow failure in which cytotoxic T lymphocytes (CTLs) target hematopoietic stem cells (HSCs). Approximately 30% of AA patients develop immune escape clones lacking specific HLA class I alleles (HLA[-]) through loss of heterozygosity in chromosome 6p (6pLOH) or somatic loss-of-function mutations. Eltrombopag (EPAG), a thrombopoietin receptor agonist (TPO-RA), demonstrates clinical efficacy in AA in combination with immunosuppressive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Polysulfide Redox Reaction of Co/Fe Dual-Atom Catalysts Embedded in Metal-Organic Framework-Derived Microporous Carbon Electrode for Lithium-Sulfur Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lithium-sulfur (Li-S) batteries have attracted significant interest owing to their high theoretical energy densities and cost-effectiveness. However, their practical application is hindered by sluggish lithium polysulfide (LiPS) redox kinetics and the shuttle effect, which result in rapid capacity decay and poor rate performance. Herein, a Co-Fe dual-atom catalyst embedded in nitrogen-doped microporous carbon (CoFeDA-CN) is rationally designed to address these limitations. In CoFeDA-CN, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triboelectric Capacitance Supplementation in Energy Storage Composites with Functionalized Carbon Fiber Electrodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structural supercapacitors integrating carbon fiber (CF) electrodes offer promising multifunctionality by combining load-bearing capacity with energy storage. Surface-functionalized CF electrodes paired with electrospun polymeric nanofiber separators can enhance triboelectric performance, while explaining one reason for increased capacitance of structural supercapacitors observed previously under mechanical deformation. Interlayer triboelectric charges from CF/separator interfaces are quantified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and effectiveness of selpercatinib in patients with RET fusion-positive non-small cell lung cancer in real-world clinical practice: a postmarketing study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Real-world data showed selpercatinib to be effective in patients with RET fusion-positive NSCLC in Japan, with a favorable safety profile and no new safety concerns.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor cell invasion of blood vessels predicts poor survival in upper tract urothelial carcinoma following radical nephroureterectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Distinguishing BVI from LymVI provides refined prognostic stratification in UTUC. BVI, alone or combined with LymVI, is strongly associated with adverse survival and increased hematogenous dissemination, while isolated LymVI has limited prognostic impact. Routine pathological subclassification of vascular invasion may improve postoperative risk assessment and guide adjuvant treatment decisions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcome of 50 patients treated with eribulin for soft tissue sarcoma: a single-institute retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Eribulin demonstrated favorable tolerability and durable disease control across diverse patient subgroups, including elderly and comorbid patients who are often ineligible for anthracycline therapy. Although no significant prognostic factors were identified, bi-weekly dosing and two-administration/2-week rest schedules were feasible, with the latter offering the advantage of pegfilgrastim support. These findings support the integration of eribulin into individualized treatment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Investigation of the Temporal Dynamics of Careless Responding Across Different Populations in Experience Sampling Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The experience sampling method (ESM) has become a popular tool in psychology. However, the intensive nature of ESM raises concerns about careless responding, where participants respond without paying sufficient attention. This study investigated the temporal dynamics of carelessness across three common sample types (community, student, clinical). We leveraged four careless responding indicators-response time, within-beep standard deviation, an inconsistency index, and occasion-person...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abnormalities of liver function during critical illness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Liver dysfunction is a frequent yet underrecognized feature of critical illness, affecting up to 20-40% of ICU patients. Even mild abnormalities in liver function tests are associated with increased morbidity, prolonged ICU stay, and higher mortality. Hepatic dysfunction may be the primary reason for ICU admission or develop during the ICU stay. Its clinical presentation is broad, ranging from abnormal liver function tests due to sepsis, drug toxicity, or hypoxia during...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antifouling and pH-Responsive Ultrafiltration Membrane of PAA-co-NH<sub>2</sub>/PEOX-co-NH<sub>2</sub> Multilayer for Protein Purification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Membrane fouling has been a persistent challenge in the protein ultrafiltration process. Stepwise interfacial complexation demonstrates an effective strategy to improve anti-fouling property. The poly(acrylic acid)/poly(2-ethyl-2-oxazoline) (PAA/PEOX) multilayer exhibits excellent anti-fouling property, yet only applied in acid environment (pH < 5). Herein, the amine-crosslinked (PAA-co-NH(2)/PEOX-co-NH(2))(n) membranes are fabricated, which show broadened pH stability (pH 2∼12) upon FT-IR...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laser-Driven Single-Step Synthesis of Monolithic Prelithiated Silicon-Graphene Anodes for Ultrahigh-Performance Zero-Decay Lithium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silicon-based anodes offer a promising alternative to graphite in lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) due to significantly higher energy density. However, their practical application is limited by substantial volume expansion during lithiation, which causes structural instability and continuous formation of the solid electrolyte interphase (SEI), drastically reducing initial coulombic efficiency (ICE) and capacity retention. Strategies such as silicon nanostructuring and integration with conductive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Author Reflections: Suboptimal Nodal Dissection Could Undermine Long-Term Survival in Patients with Non-Small-Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical correlation between plasma biomarker levels and post-transplant complications of allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation in children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Elevated sST2 and REG3α can reflect the occurrence and severity of aGVHD. Acute GVHD, SOS, and TA-TMA can all lead to fluctuations in sST2 and REG3α levels, and warrant further study.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive analysis of CBL and CIPK gene families in Magnolia biondii and functional characterization of MbCBL4 under salt stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We identified the characteristics of CBL and CIPK families of Magnolia biondii and the MbCBL4-overexpressed Arabidopsis plants conferred salt tolerance. Calcineurin B-like protein (CBLs) and CBL-interacting protein kinase (CIPKs) are important components of the Ca²⁺-mediated signal pathway. These proteins play a key role in plant growth, development, and response to environmental stress. Magnolia biondii is a woody plant valued for ornamental and medicinal uses and is frequently exposed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sensitive and selective detection of microRNA using hyperbranched rolling circle amplification based on symmetric dumbbell-type probe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Examining the changes in microRNA expression in vivo enhances the understanding of their tumor-associated functions and facilitates clinical assays based on their roles as disease markers. However, due to the low abundance and high homology, their detection remains challenging. Herein, we developed an exponential amplification method by combining a symmetric dumbbell-type probe (SDTP) and toehold-initiated hyperbranched rolling circle amplification (HRCA) to obtain high sensitivity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Homogenize Strain Distribution via Molecular Network Engineering for Mechanically Reliable Flexible Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flexible perovskite solar cells (FPSCs) suffer from strain localization-induced mechanical degradation, primarily due to heterogeneous strain distribution at grain boundaries. Herein, we propose a molecular engineering approach involving a crosslinked Methacrylic anhydride (MA) to construct a 3D crosslinking network within perovskite films. This molecular-scale network effectively redistributes localized strain into a more homogeneous pattern, as indicated by reduced strain variance and a lower...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic Insights Into the Estrogen-Like Effects of Selenium-Enriched Armillaria on Anti-Osteoporosis in Ovariectomized Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Selenium (Se) is an essential trace element in bone metabolism. Armillaria (AM) has the ability to enrich Se and exhibits the potential for treating osteoporosis. The aim of this study was to evaluate the effect of Se-enriched Armillaria (AM-Se) on osteoporosis in ovariectomized rats. AM-Se was prepared by adding sodium selenite to the liquid fermentation medium of AM. Forty 8-week-old female Sprague-Dawley rats were randomly divided into five groups as follows: (1) Sham operation group (SHAM),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The environmental exposome in heart failure risk and progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Environmental exposures have a crucial role in the incidence and progression of heart failure (HF) by exacerbating genetic predisposition and other pathophysiological mechanisms. The exposome - encompassing pollution, climate and the urban environment - and the biological responses to these factors shape cardiovascular health in complex ways. Air, noise and light pollution, exposure to toxic metals, and extremes of temperature adversely affect HF outcomes. Social determinants of health,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease and steatohepatitis-associated hepatocarcinoma preclinical models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) encompasses liver steatosis and metabolic dysfunction-associated steatohepatitis (MASH), which can result in fibrosis and/or cirrhosis and increase the risk of hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC). The latest Clinical Practice Guidelines acknowledge the importance of systemic metabolic dysfunction as a driver of hepatic lipid accumulation and disease progression. To ensure translational relevance of preclinical models, they need to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[α-synuclein triggers NCOA4-FTH1-mediated ferroptosis of oligodendrocyte in multiple system atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiple system atrophy (MSA) is a fatal neurodegenerative synucleinopathy characterized by the accumulation of α-synuclein in oligodendrocytes, forming glial cytoplasmic inclusions. Although iron dysregulation and ferroptosis, an iron-dependent form of regulated cell death, have been implicated in neurodegeneration, their specific role in MSA oligodendrocytes remains unknown. We investigated ferroptosis pathways in postmortem brain tissues from patients with MSA, Parkinson's disease (PD), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IGD: a multi-omics database for Ipomoea pes-caprae genomic and biological research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[omnideconv: a unifying framework for using and benchmarking single-cell-informed deconvolution of bulk RNA-seq data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study highlights the strengths, limitations, and complementarity of state-of-the-art tools, shedding light on how different data characteristics and confounders impact deconvolution performance. We provide the scientific community with an ecosystem of tools and resources, omnideconv, simplifying the application, benchmarking, and optimization of deconvolution methods.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High levels of circulating miR-19a-3p in patients with metastatic HER2 + breast cancer are associated with a favorable prognosis and anti-tumor immune responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Trastuzumab, combined with chemotherapy, is the current standard treatment for both metastatic and early-stage HER2-positive (HER2 +) breast cancer. One of the mechanisms of action of trastuzumab is antibody-dependent cellular cytotoxicity (ADCC), which involves engaging FcγRIIIA (CD16) on natural killer (NK) cells. A competent immune system and properly functioning NK cells are crucial for effective ADCC, as they can influence favorable clinical outcomes. Resistance to trastuzumab...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transporters, an important but poorly studied area of Toxoplasma gondii]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Membrane transporters play a vital role in the obligate intracellular parasite Toxoplasma gondii, mediating the acquisition of nutrients from host cells, the regulation of ion gradients, and the maintenance of metabolic homeostasis. Despite their central importance for parasite survival, pathogenesis, and drug resistance, the majority of T. gondii transporters remain poorly characterized. Key unresolved questions include the mechanisms underlying purine nucleotide transport across the plasma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An integrative clinical and bioinformatic analysis identifies MicroRNAs as biomarkers of ischemic stroke severity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Identifying reliable circulating biomarkers is crucial for improving the diagnosis and risk stratification of patients with ischemic stroke. In this study, we evaluated several whole-blood circulating miRNAs (miR-106b-5p, miR-16-5p, miR-15b-5p, let-7e-5p, and miR-125a-3p/-5p) to determine their diagnostic and disease severity in acute ischemic stroke (AIS). Sixty AIS patients and thirty age- and sex-matched controls were included. Whole-blood miRNAs were quantified at admission and on day 7....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of glucagon-like peptide-1 receptor agonists on heart rate in non-diabetic individuals with overweight or obesity: a systematic review and pairwise and network meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GLP-1RAs were associated with the increasing of HR in patients with overweight or obesity. Orforglipron 36 mg was associated with the most pronounced increase, and tirzepatide 5 mg the least.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of candidate microRNA biomarkers of endometriosis in different bodily fluids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrachromosomal insertion as a diagnostic challenge: a hidden structural rearrangement causing recurrent duplication and deletion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This case highlights the potential of intrachromosomal insertions, although balanced in carriers, to cause recurrent segmental duplications or deletions in offspring. Comprehensive analysis using FISH and long-read sequencing is essential for accurate diagnosis, appropriate genetic counseling, and informed reproductive decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced methane emissions in transgenic rice genotypes are associated with altered rhizosphere microbial hydrogen cycling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rice paddies significantly contribute to atmospheric methane (CH(4)). Here, we show that two independent rice genotypes overexpressing genes for PLANT PEPTIDES CONTAINING SULFATED TYROSINE (PSY) reduce cumulative CH(4) emissions by 38% (PSY1) and 58% (PSY2) over 70 days of growth compared with controls. Genome-resolved metatranscriptomic data from PSY rhizosphere soils reveal lower ratios of gene activities for (mostly hydrogenotrophic) CH(4) production versus consumption, decreased activity of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes of alveolar bone and gingival tissues in modified vs. conventional periodontally accelerated osteogenic orthodontics: a 5-year retrospective analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In terms of long-term outcomes, the modified method demonstrates superior performance in alveolar bone and gingival augmentation, outperforming the mainstream method.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported outcomes after long-term period of niraparib maintenance in platinum-sensitive recurrent ovarian cancer: a prospective, multicenter cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PRO-based surveillance showed satisfactory QOL and stable symptom control in PSROC after long-term period of niraparib maintenance, regardless of BRCA status. This real-world research highlights the significance of long-term usage of niraparib and PROs in PSROC management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing classification accuracy in medical datasets using a hybrid distance and cluster refinement-based K-means clustering method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning methods, especially the K_Means clustering method, have demonstrated potential in analyzing medical data by facilitating pattern detection. However, the classic K_Means algorithm suffers from two major limitations: (1) its reliance on a single, often suboptimal distance metric (typically Euclidean), and (2) the lack of a mechanism to refine clusters post-assignment, which can lead to poor cohesion and misgrouping. To address these challenges, this paper proposes a novel enhanced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal dynamics of tumor-associated neutrophils: bridging the gap between cancer progression and immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative assessment of graves' ophthalmopathy activity using <sup>99m</sup>Tc-DTPA SPECT/CT orbital imaging: a feasibility study with multiple indicators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In summary, this study confirms that quantitative indices from orbital ^(99m)Tc-DTPA SPECT/CT, particularly SUV(mean)-3D, effectively quantify EOMs inflammatory activity in GO. Parameters derived using CT-based 3D VOI delineation (SUV(mean)-3D and SUV(max)-3D) demonstrated superior reliability over traditional methods. Among all indices, SUV(mean)-3D demonstrated superior diagnostic efficacy (AUC = 0.887) for differentiating active from inactive disease. These indices provide an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interest in HIV pre-exposure prophylaxis use and associated factors among people who inject drugs in Iran: a nationwide survey in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the effectiveness of pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) in reducing HIV incidence, this intervention is inaccessible in Iran. We examined the interest in using PrEP and associated factors among people who inject drugs (PWID) in 2023 using data from 2,174 PWID. The main outcome was interest in using PrEP, which was divided into three categories: interest in using PrEP under any circumstances, interest in using PrEP if provided for free, and no interest in using PrEP. We found that 37.9% of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phytochemical Insights into <em>Panax</em> Genus Metabolites: Evidence-Based Fatigue Intervention via Ethnopharmacological and Biomedical Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditional Chinese Medicine (TCM) has a longstanding history in the treatment of fatigue-related conditions, and is increasingly recognized as a foundation for novel therapeutic approaches. The Panax genus, extensively utilized in the fundamental TCM principles to enhance vitality, modulate immune function, and stimulate Yang energy, is a key resource in managing both physiological and pathological fatigue. This study provides a comprehensive synthesis of recent advancements in plant-derived...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient conductive hearing loss as a notable and rare manifestation of preeclampsia: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Transient conductive hearing loss due to SOM is a rare manifestation of preeclampsia, likely driven by hypertension-induced increased vascular permeability and altered fluid dynamics. Severe proteinuria may exacerbate systemic fluid imbalance, contributing to middle ear effusion. Early recognition via audiometric and tympanometric evaluation, exclusion of alternative etiologies, and targeted management (e.g. fluid overload reduction) can ensure prompt recovery and improve maternal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterogeneous response to efgartigimod in real-world experience with myasthenia gravis: Predictors and treatment strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efgartigimod is an established therapy for acetylcholine receptor antibody-positive generalized myasthenia gravis, yet real-world data on long-term overall responsiveness, response patterns, steroid-sparing effects, bridging therapy use, and predictors of benefit remain limited. In this multicenter retrospective study, we evaluated 46 patients treated across seven tertiary centers between April 2022 and March 2025, collecting demographic, clinical, therapeutic, and outcome data. Patients...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving resilience monitoring in non-stationary systems via a robust data-chunking algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Histone H3.3 phosphorylation facilitates H3K9me3-heterochromatin formation during retrotransposon silencing and X-chromosome inactivation via H3.3K27me3-CBX7-KAP1 axis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The conserved histone variant H3.3 plays pivotal roles in heterochromatin formation and retrotransposon silencing. However, the molecular mechanism underlying H3.3-primed heterochromatin regulation remains elusive. Here, we demonstrate that H3.3-specific Ser31 phosphorylation and Lys27 trimethylation synergistically promote H3K9me3-heterochromatin formation. Mechanistically, polycomb protein chromobox homolog 7 (CBX7) preferentially binds Ser31-phosphorylated H3.3K27me3 nucleosomes and then...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of effective precipitation region on the glacier mass balance across the inner Tibetan Plateau]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neoadjuvant chemotherapy plus cadonilimab followed by extra-fascial hysterectomy for International Federation of Gynecology and Obstetrics stage IB2 cervical cancer: a prospective, multi-center, single-arm, phase 2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Radical hysterectomy remains the standard treatment for stage IB2 cervical carcinoma but is often accompanied by considerable peri-operative and long-term complications that impair quality of life. The increasing emphasis on functional preservation has prompted exploration of less extensive surgical options, whereas neoadjuvant chemoimmunotherapy may induce tumor downstaging, enabling more conservative surgery without compromising oncologic safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41582028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers in Irritable Bowel Syndrome: Rationale and Practical Use]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Irritable bowel syndrome (IBS) is currently diagnosed based on symptoms and limited diagnostic testing, highlighting the need for noninvasive biomarkers and personalized therapies. Emerging blood-based biomarkers such as cytolethal distending toxin B and antivinculin antibodies, DNA methylation profiles, and intestinal permeability measures, along with stool-based microbiome and metabolite markers, show promise in distinguishing IBS, and its bowel habit subtypes, from other gastrointestinal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging Tissue and Blood Biomarkers for Eosinophilic Esophagitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eosinophilic esophagitis is a chronic, immune-mediated condition traditionally diagnosed and monitored through sedated endoscopy with biopsy. This invasive method, while essential, poses challenges for routine care. This article summarizes current research on noninvasive and minimally invasive biomarkers spanning blood, tissue, and esophageal sampling methods that aim to improve diagnostic accuracy, monitor disease activity, and guide personalized treatment. While no biomarker is yet validated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[American Dental Association and American Academy of Oral and Maxillofacial Radiology patient selection for dental radiography and cone-beam computed tomography: Clinical recommendations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND PRACTICAL IMPLICATIONS: Clinicians should base imaging decisions on the patient's medical and dental histories, clinical examination findings, disease risk assessment, and the presence of specific clinical conditions. When used appropriately, radiographic imaging contributes to dental treatment decisions and results in optimal patient care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of a competitive endogenous RNA regulatory network for intramuscular fat content in Laiwu pig based on whole transcriptome analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intramuscular fat (IMF) content is an important factor for meat quality evaluation, which varies between species, and mainly involves the number and size of intramuscular adipocytes. However, the potential mechanism has not been well elucidated. In this study, the whole transcriptomic data of longissimus dorsi muscle from Laiwu pigs (LW, fatty type) and Duroc×Landrace×Yorkshire pigs (DLY, lean type) were collected and an in-depth analysis was conducted. Through differentially expressed analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Influenza Epidemic Trends Based on a Large-scale Claims Database and National Infectious Disease Surveillance in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Claims data such as those from JMDCdb may be useful for retrospective examination of influenza trends. Moreover, a detailed analysis of the number of cases reported per sentinel suggested the potential to propose threshold values that enable earlier prediction of epidemics than conventional criteria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cohort Profile: The Tokyo Adolescent Mental Health Study (TAMHS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Tokyo Adolescent Mental Health Study (TAMHS) is an ongoing, school-based longitudinal cohort designed to elucidate the developmental trajectories of mental health among adolescents in Japan and to inform evidence-based strategies for promoting adolescent well-being. Since its inception in 2009, TAMHS has annually tracked adolescents aged 12-18 from a Tokyo secondary school known for its tradition of enrolling twins and triplets. Participants are followed for up to six years. As of 2024,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phenotypic impact on coat color and uterine development in mice carrying a missense mutation associated with bovine White Heifer Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[White Heifer Disease (WHD) is a congenital reproductive abnormality, especially in white female offspring in certain breeds of cattle like Belgian Blue. The roan locus was reported to affect coat color and fertility. It was suggested that a missense mutation (Ala218Asp) in the transmembrane domain of Kit ligand (KITL) gene was responsible for WHD. Here we generated two types of knock-in (KI) mice to reproduce the missense KITL mutation using pigmented agouti ICR mice. KI mice carrying compound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Titanium hypersensitivity in dental implants: A systematic review of updated clinical evidence and diagnostic strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite the limited evidence, current data indicate that titanium hypersensitivity is rare but clinically relevant. Titanium micro-particles often originating from early mechanical wear may act as immunological co-factors in susceptible patients, underscoring the need for standardized and sensitive diagnostic protocols to support early and accurate identification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Program personnel perspectives and outcomes of the Minneapolis Addiction Recovery Initiative (MARI) Safe Station program: A fire station-based substance use deflection program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preliminary findings highlight MARI Safe Station's ability to provide accessible, equitable addiction recovery services and reduce stigma, while identifying areas for continued improvement as the program evolves.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The stress-activated kinase p38 mediates non-canonical activation of Src and tyrosine phosphorylation of the adapter protein TAB1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Src is a non-receptor tyrosine kinase that is overexpressed and highly activated in many cancers and is one of the key factors contributing to malignant transformation. According to current concepts, Src activity relies on tyrosine phosphorylation and phospho(p) Y419 in the activation loop is often regarded as a marker of its activation. However, recent studies have shown that pY419 may contribute to substrate selection. Therefore, the mechanisms underlying Src activation other than classical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering an orthogonal ubiquitin transfer cascade with Ring E3 RNF38 by phage display to reveal its regulation of nuclear transport]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ring E3 ubiquitin (UB) ligases rely on signature Ring domains for mediating UB transfer to substrate proteins. The large number of Ring E3s and their weak association with substrates pose a significant challenge in identifying the substrates of individual E3s, thereby hindering the elucidation of their biological functions. Here, we utilized phage display to engineer an "orthogonal UB transfer" (OUT) cascade with Ring E3 RNF38, enabling the exclusive transfer of an engineered UB (xUB) to its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling tumor progression in heterogeneous microenvironments: A cellular automata approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding how microenvironmental heterogeneity influences tumor progression is essential for advancing both cancer biology and therapeutic strategies. In this study, we develop a cellular automata (CA) model to simulate tumor growth under varying microenvironmental conditions and genetic mutation rates, addressing a gap in existing studies that rarely integrate these two factors to explain tumor dynamics. The model explicitly incorporates the cellular heterogeneity of stem and non-stem...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of accelerometer-measured rest-activity rhythm patterns and parameters with cardiovascular and all-cause mortality in older adults: Population-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RAR patterns and parameters were significantly associated with cardiovascular and all-cause mortality in older adults. Early identification and intervention for adverse RAR patterns may help improve long-term health outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Depressive symptoms status and nighttime sleep duration in relation to cognitive performance in Chinese elderly: Insights from a large cross-sectional inquiry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study clarifies the sleep-depression-cognition interplay in older Chinese adults, providing an empirical basis for targeted interventions (optimizing sleep to 6-7.9 h/night, alleviating depression) to reduce cognitive impairment risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nicotinamide-based Sirtuin 2 inhibitors as anti-HCMV agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human cytomegalovirus (HCMV) is a prevalent herpesvirus pathogen and remains a significant cause for mortality and morbidity in immunocompromised individuals and newborns. Like all viruses, HCMV uses host cellular proteins to facilitate virus replication and spread. Sirtuin 2 (SIRT2) is an NAD^(+)-dependent deacetylase with a variety of substrates, including α-tubulin, where acetylation can alter function and stability. We have previously developed small molecule inhibitors targeting SIRT2 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into substrate binding, domain swapping and heat resistance of a hyperthermostable archaeal AIR synthetase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The enzyme 5-aminoimidazole ribonucleotide synthetase (AIR synthetase, AIRS, known also as PurM) catalyzes the fifth step in the de novo purine biosynthetic pathway: the ATP-dependent conversion of formylglycinamidine ribonucleotide (FGAM) to aminoimidazole ribonucleotide (AIR). AIRS belongs to the PurM superfamily, sharing ATPase domains. In this study, we employed hyperthermostable AIRS from Pyrococcus abyssi (Pa) and Pyrococcus horikoshii (pH), members of the thermophilic archaeal genus known...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting the WWP2-ASPP2 axis overcomes cisplatin resistance by inhibiting the mevalonate pathway in TP53-mutant bladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cisplatin resistance remains a major challenge in bladder cancer. Although the tumor suppressor ASPP2 is a critical co-factor for TP53-mediated apoptosis, its role in metabolic reprogramming and cisplatin response remains unclear. This study aimed to delineate the mechanism by which ASPP2 regulates cisplatin sensitivity through metabolic reprogramming. We first assessed the clinical significance of ASPP2 using patient tissues and public databases, finding that its downregulation in bladder...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic flame retardancy of condensed phases: Performance and mechanism of polyester fibres co-modified with silicon-doped carbon quantum dots and sodium lignosulphate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyester fiber (POLY) materials are highly flammable due to their hydrocarbon content and high heat release. Although lignin-based flame retardant of sodium lignosulphonate (Sodi) is highly attractive due to their renewable nature and low toxicity, their application is limited by poor dispersion in POLY and the formation of fragile, porous char layers. Carbon quantum dots (CQDs) can promote the compatible and facilitate carbonization of Sodi. In this study, a kind of silicon-doped carbon...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Analysis of Daily 10 Hz and Accelerated Theta Burst Transcranial Magnetic Stimulation on Suicidality in Treatment Resistant Depression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and challenges in enzymatic rubber degradation: Exploring genetic, molecular, and biotechnological aspects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rubber waste is one of the most persistent solid wastes of our times, mostly represented by end-of-life tires. While the biological origin of natural rubber makes it biodegradable, many tire components are not, and they make enzymatic attack by microorganisms extremely difficult. Despite the great multi-enzymatic catabolic capacity of various bacteria and fungi, there are currently no organisms or enzymes capable of effectively degrading vulcanized tire waste. However, biotechnological advances...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potential of traditional Chinese medicine-antibiotic combinations in combating multidrug-resistant organisms: Advances, mechanisms, and clinical implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TCM-antibiotic combinations have promising clinical application value for addressing MDROs infections. By integrating the multi-target actions of TCM with the rapid bactericidal effects of antibiotics, this approach offers a synergistic solution that enhances clinical outcomes and mitigates the emergence of resistance. Future research should focus on translating these findings into clinical practice through rigorous mechanistic studies and well-designed clinical trials, ultimately...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Core Experiences in Gastropsychology Fellowship Training]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Advances in Targeting Regions of Interest for In Situ Cryo-Electron Tomography of Cellular Architecture]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cryogenic electron tomography (cryo-ET) enables in situ structural analysis of macromolecular assemblies within their native cellular environments, spanning more than four orders of magnitude in spatial scale, from micrometre-level cellular context accessed through correlative imaging to near-sub-nanometre resolution achieved through subtomogram averaging (STA). This review summarises recent advances in mapping cellular architecture, encompassing membrane-bound organelles, cytoskeletal networks,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Synthetic Anticoagulant Octaparin Attenuates Renal Ischemia-Reperfusion Injury via DC-SIGN/NF-κB Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Octaparin exerts multifaceted renoprotective effects in IRI by modulating DC-SIGN/NF-κB signaling. Its ability to simultaneously suppress thromboinflammation, oxidative stress, and apoptosis-without the risks associated with conventional heparins-represents a transformative therapeutic strategy for AKI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Standardized Invasive Protocol for the Investigation of Patients with Presumed Coronary Microvascular and Vasomotor Dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As previously discussed in the preceding companion papers, there are complicated theoretical and practical issues that hinder progress in the evaluation and treatment of patients with coronary microvascular and vasomotor dysfunction. Solving this problem will require intellectual flexibility, but the invasive assessment requires a practical standardized protocol to minimize variations between participating sites. In this third companion paper, we review the indications and develop a standardized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and Evaluation of an Automated Robotic System for Full Crown Preparation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study developed an automated robotic system for crown preparation that demonstrated superior accuracy and shorter operation time compared with the guide approach.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct transmission of SFTSV from dogs to humans: Molecular confirmation and risk assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides the first molecular confirmation of direct SFTSV transmission from dogs to humans, identifying bloody stools and saliva as high-risk transmission sources. These findings underscore the importance of including dogs in SFTSV surveillance systems and implementing protective measures when handling sick pets in endemic areas.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Testing effects of paced breathing on plasma Aβ and brain perivascular spaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging is the strongest known risk factor for Alzheimer's disease (AD), and elevated plasma amyloid-β (Aβ) levels in healthy adults are associated with increased AD risk. Aging is also associated with autonomic imbalance, characterized by increased sympathetic and decreased parasympathetic activity. In our previous randomized clinical trial, we found that four weeks of daily slow-paced breathing designed to enhance parasympathetic activity reduced plasma Aβ42 and Aβ40 levels in younger and older...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Measles Vaccine Associated Febrile Seizures among Children 6-59 months old in a Federally Qualified Health System, 2008-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 15-year retrospective cohort study of 53,830 children 6-59 months old in a Federally Qualified Health System identified 10 febrile seizures 7-14 days after measles vaccination (incidence rate 2.05 [95% CI 0.98, 3.77] per 100,000 person-days); all had concurrent illnesses and co-administered vaccines. To date, no child has developed epilepsy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mismatch between oxygen delivery and consumption in the cerebral watershed during subacute global hypoperfusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hemodynamically significant carotid artery stenosis is a common clinical condition that can lead to chronic cerebral hypoperfusion. Despite the well-recognized pivotal role of pial collaterals in maintaining cerebral perfusion during focal arterial occlusions, regulation of microvascular blood flow and oxygenation in the cerebral watershed "pial-collateral territory" during chronic hypoperfusion remains unexplored. To answer this question, we applied 2-photon microscopy and Doppler optical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applications of machine learning-based quantitative structure activity relationship (ML-QSAR) models in environmental science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the exponential growth of cheminformatics data and the increasing complexity of chemical space in environmental domains, traditional quantitative structure-activity relationship (QSAR) approaches-constrained by predefined functional assumptions-are encountering significant limitations. There is an urgent need to transition toward a model-free, data-adaptive, and knowledge-integrated modeling paradigm. This review systematically examines the development and application of Machine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal P2X7R and Myelin PET Reveal Distinct Neuroinflammatory and White Matter Signatures Compared with TSPO PET and DTI-MRI in the TgF344-AD rat model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emerging evidence links glial activation, particularly microglia, to Alzheimer's disease (AD) progression. While TSPO PET (positron emission tomography) imaging detects neuroinflammation, its limitations drive interest in alternative targets like the P2X7 receptor. Myelin loss, potentially tied to chronic inflammation, is increasingly recognized as a key hallmark in AD, though the timing and relationship between neuroinflammation and demyelination remain poorly understood. We conducted a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized Repetitive Transcranial Magnetic Stimulation Reduces Frontal EEG Complexity in Patients with Obsessive-Compulsive Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: OCD is characterized by increased frontal neural complexity as indexed by multiple entropy- and complexity-based EEG measures. Individualized rTMS modulated these abnormalities, supporting frontal EEG complexity as a promising objective biomarker of neuromodulatory effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LUNG TRANSPLANTATION AFTER PROLONGED TA-NRP IN COMBINED HEART-LUNG PROCUREMENT FROM CONTROLLED DCD DONORS IN ITALY]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thoraco-abdominal normothermic regional perfusion(TA-NRP) is an emerging strategy for heart recovery in controlled donation after circulatory death(cDCD). Its impact on lung graft retrieval remains debated, especially regarding the duration of TA-NRP. This is particularly relevant in Italy, where the world's longest mandatory stand-off period(20 minutes) leads to prolonged TA-NRP for heart assessment. This study evaluates the impact of TA-NRP on lung transplant(LT) outcomes in a nationwide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel cerebrovascular disease blood biomarkers identified by targeted-proteomics in a high risk Native American population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We have identified altered blood biomarkers related to CVD in NAON for risk-stratification of CVD-related complications. Further study of these biomarkers may complement existing clinical risk factors for prevention, diagnosis, and therapy in CVD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changing Landscape in Stage, Treatment and Survival of Gastric Cancer in China 1998-2022: Insights of 40,158 patients from the National Gastric Cancer Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: From 1998 to 2022, the proportion of patients diagnosed with early-stage gastric cancer in China gradually increased, and treatment strategies changed substantially over time, accompanied by a modest improvement in the 5-year OS rate. The disparities in stage distribution and survival outcomes between China and Japan highlight the need to further improve early detection of gastric cancer and to develop more effective treatment modalities for patients with stage III disease in China.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Botrychium ternatum, the Hmong medicinal flora, improves acetaminophen-induced hepatic injury by inhibiting the abnormal activation of the B cell receptor signaling pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In summary, BT demonstrates substantial hepatoprotective effects, potentially by suppressing the BCR signaling pathway, with kaempferitrin identified as a critical bioactive component targeting LYN kinase.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Dynamics of Quinolone and Macrolide Resistance in Hospital Wastewater: Insights from Kathmandu Valley, Nepal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: HWW is a significant AMR reservoir, emphasizing improved wastewater treatment and antibiotic stewardship to mitigate resistance dissemination.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colorectal Cancer T Stage, Size at Diagnosis and Presentation 2017-2023: An Analysis Using VA Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Interruptions in care following the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic had measurable consequences among U.S. Veterans through the end of 2023. Among those diagnosed, median size was larger and more presented with bowel obstruction. This may be because decreased screening activity combined with lower healthcare utilization changed the distribution of cancer size at diagnosis to be larger - underlining the importance of encouraging engagement or re-engagement of Veterans in colorectal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Emotional States on Bilingual Adaptive Control Across Different Switching Frequency Contexts: An ERP Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emotional states influence how bilinguals adapt their language control strategies in different contexts. The Adaptive Control Hypothesis (ACH) posits that bilinguals adjust control mechanisms based on contextual demands, yet the role of emotional states in this process remains unclear. This study examines how emotional states (positive, negative, and neutral) modulate bilingual control by manipulating contextual control demands through language-switching frequencies (25%, 50%, 75%) in a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transplantation of Mitochondria isolated from iPSC-MSCs mitigates doxorubicin-induced cardiomyopathy by inhibiting cardiomyocyte senescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Transplantation of mitochondria isolated from iPSC-MSCs improved cardiac function in a mouse model of DIC by alleviating cardiomyocyte senescence via improved metabolic function. This may offer a novel therapeutic strategy for DIC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insulin-like Growth Factor 2 mRNA-binding Protein 2 Regulates PINK1 Expression through m<sup>6</sup>A Pathway to Promote Mitophagy in BMSCs Alleviating Postmenopausal Osteoporosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The senescence and altered differentiation potential of bone marrow mesenchymal stem cells (BMSCs) contribute to the pathogenesis of postmenopausal osteoporosis (PMOP). Insulin-like growth factor 2 mRNA-binding protein (IMP2) has been demonstrated to regulate BMSCs. However, its specific mechanistic actions remain unclear, particularly due to the lack of concrete evidence within the ovariectomy (OVX) in vivo microenvironment. In this study, we utilized Cre-LoxP technology to achieve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardamonin attenuates osteoporosis progression and promotes osteogenic differentiation of bone mesenchymal stem cells by upregulating TCF4 expression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CAR attenuates bone loss in an OVX-induced mouse model of osteoporosis and promotes osteogenic differentiation of hBMSCs via increasing TCF4 expression, indicating the therapeutic potential of CAR in osteoporosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oligodendrocytes at the Crossroads: Central Players and Interactive Partners in White Matter Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[White matter degeneration in aging drives cognitive and motor decline. Oligodendrocytes (OLs) and their precursors are central to this process. Their intrinsic aging, marked by differentiation failure, metabolic and mitochondrial deficits, and transcriptional epigenetic dysregulation, causes myelin thinning and axonal support loss. Degeneration is amplified by dysfunctional crosstalk: microglia clear debris poorly and turn inflammatory; astrocytes disrupt lipid balance and secrete inflammatory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of cytokines in cytokine release syndrome (CRS) after CAR T cell therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) T cell therapy has transformed the treatment landscape for hematological malignancies. However, cytokine release syndrome (CRS) remains a common and potentially severe toxicity, significantly affecting patient safety and requiring intensive clinical management. This review provides a focused synthesis on the role of cytokines in CRS after CAR T cell therapy, integrating recent mechanistic insights with clinical implications. We delineate the cellular and molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light-promoted engineered bacterial DNase I therapeutic intervention to enable potent cancer photoimmunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacteria are emerging as a promising tool for targeted cancer therapy due to their innate tumor-homing ability, high mobility, and capacity to rapidly colonize in the tumor microenvironment (TME). However, bacterial cancer therapy (BCT) alone has not proven fully effective. Herein, we present an innovative bio-therapeutic system, TEPy@VNP-D, which integrates genetically engineered Salmonella typhimurium VNP20009 carrying humanized DNase I toxin plasmids (VNP-D) with an aggregation-induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolated Intermediate Cuneiform Dislocation: A Case Report on the Surgical Considerations for a Rare Injury of the Foot]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this report a rare case of isolated dorsal dislocation of the intermediate cuneiform in a 32-year-old woman following a low-energy injury is presented. The patient sustained a direct medial-to-lateral midfoot crush injury. Imaging revealed dorsal dislocation of the intermediate cuneiform with associated plantar avulsion fractures, indicating ligamentous instability. Closed reduction under general anaesthesia was unsuccessful due to soft tissue interpositioning. Open reduction and internal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multimodal Neuro-Demographic Signature for Immuno-Metabolic Depression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our analysis shows that IMD is characterized by a distinct, multimodal neuro-demographic signature involving cortico-limbic circuitry. This signature demonstrates high specificity for unraveling MDD heterogeneity and is clinically linked to anhedonia, supporting the potential for biologically-informed patient stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practical method for endothelial glycocalyx imaging in formalin-fixed, paraffin-embedded tissues in vascular pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The endothelial glycocalyx (eGCX), a delicate carbohydrate-rich layer coating the vascular endothelium, critically regulates vascular homeostasis, controlling permeability, thrombosis, and inflammation. Despite its fundamental importance, assessing the morphology of the eGCX remains technically challenging because of its fragile structure, which collapses during conventional fixation. Existing visualization methods require complex preparation, expensive equipment, and fresh tissues, severely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of sleep duration and nocturnal oxygenation with OCT-derived retinal arterial structure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sleep duration and nocturnal oxygen desaturation showed distinct associations with retinal arterial characteristics. OCT-based vascular metrics may serve as noninvasive indicators of sleep-related microvascular alterations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disrupted resting-state amygdala connectivity dynamics in major depressive disorder with suicidal ideation: Implications for emotional dysregulation and suicide risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight heightened temporal instability of the AN and associated excessive anxious mood in MDD, while the diminished dominance of the amygdala-DMN-RN coupling indicates impairments in self-referential and reward processing in MDD patients with SI. Overall, disruptions in amygdala-based network dynamics may implicate neurobiological substrates underlying emotional dysregulation and elevated suicide risk in MDD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[6-Mercaptopurine vs. Mycophenolate Mofetil in Autoimmune Hepatitis and Azathioprine Intolerance: A Multicenter Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both 6-MP and MMF were capable of maintaining biochemical response in patients with AIH who were intolerant to AZA, with no clear evidence of inferiority of either treatment. While MMF was generally better tolerated, 6-MP may present a safe and effective treatment option in women of reproductive age. In addition, therapy with 6-MP enables clinicians to monitor drug metabolite levels, titrate dosages, and monitor adherence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Xiaoyaosan and isoliquiritigenin remodel depression-associated chromatin 3D structure and phase separation of NF-κB1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Xiaoyaosan (XYS) is a classical traditional prescription with well-documented antidepressant effects. However, the active components and molecular mechanisms to alleviate depression remain unclear. In this study, using chronic social defeat stress (CSDS) and lipopolysaccharide (LPS)-induced depression models, we found that XYS and its key ingredient isoliquiritigenin (ILG) not only significantly improved depressive-like behaviors in mice but also exerted dual regulatory effects at the cellular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of AI Multi-model Responses and Evaluations for PEP Guidelines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-acting cabotegravir and rilpivirine in people with HIV and obesity: Real-world outcomes from the RELATIVITY cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this real-world cohort, LAI CAB + RPV was safe and effective in PWH with obesity, with comparable VF rates, tolerability, and adherence to participants without obesity. These findings support the use of LAI CAB + RPV across diverse PWH populations, including those with a BMI ≥ 30 kg/m², and highlight its feasibility in PWH with multiple comorbidities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time for resistance: New tools and strategies for microglia replacement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrokinetic mobilization of PFAS in soils: Linking head group and chain length to remediation efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PFAS pose significant remediation challenges due to their chemical stability, structural diversity, and strong affinity for soil components. These properties complicate their mobilization from contaminated soils and necessitate compound-specific treatment approaches. Five PFAS compounds (PFBA, PFOA, PFDA, PFOS, and FOSA) were selected to investigate the influence of molecular structure, representing variations in chain length and head group. Electrokinetic (EK) remediation and hydraulic gradient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibody responses to SARS-CoV-2 vaccine in nursing home residents support a Bi-annual update schedule]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The immunologic findings in this cohort of NHR align with the existing real-world clinical effectiveness data in older individuals and support the CDC recommendation of a bi-annual vaccination to reduce severe COVID-19 outcomes in persons age 65 and older.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acetylation-mediated fluconazole inactivation: A novel antifungal resistance mechanism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antifungal resistance is considered a global health threat. However, enzymatic inactivation of antifungals, a common mechanism seen in antibacterial resistance, has not yet been described in fungi. From a One Health perspective, this study demonstrates that Cryptococcus deuterogattii and C. neoformans, the leading agents of cryptococcosis, enzymatically inactivate fluconazole. Agrochemicals induce the overexpression of genes that code for acetyltransferases, specifically GCN5 and NAT10. These...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasmonic bimetallic Au-Ag nanoclusters embedded in covalent organic frameworks as efficient photocatalysts for simultaneous nizatidine degradation and H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub> evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Covalent organic frameworks (COFs) demonstrate great potential as photocatalysts for the remediation of organic pollutants; however, their efficiency is often limited by the factor of rapid electron-hole recombination. In response to this challenge, we anchor ultrasmall (∼2.5 nm) bimetallic Au-Ag nanoclusters within the porous architecture of a nitrogen-rich COFs scaffold. The nitrogenated frameworks not only provide a high surface area and abundant active sites but also facilitate electron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Mode Ventilation Promotes Diaphragm Function Recovery in Rats With Ventilator-Induced Diaphragmatic Dysfunction by Upregulating Insulin-Like Growth Factor-1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DMV is beneficial for diaphragm function recovery. And IGF-1 plays an important role in DMV to enhance diaphragm mass and strength of VIDD rats, which may promote protein synthesis and muscle differentiation through activating Akt/mTOR signaling pathway.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular marker development for salt tolerance in cowpea: insights from genome-wide association analysis at the early vegetative stage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study identified efficient marker combinations consisting of two significant SNPs associated with salt tolerance in cowpea, providing genomic insights and candidate frameworks for future validation and breeding applications. Salt stress is a major abiotic factor that severely reduces crop productivity, particularly in arid and semi-arid regions. Its effects are further exacerbated by climate change and the continuous buildup of salts in the soil. Although cowpea (Vigna unguiculata L.) is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41581103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of signal decomposition methods for regional sea level trend estimation: a case study of the Korean peninsula]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Regional sea level rise (SLR) analysis requires robust methods capable of capturing temporal variations beyond simple linear trends. The Korean Peninsula, surrounded by three distinct seas with diverse oceanographic characteristics, provides an ideal testbed for evaluating different methodological approaches to SLR trend estimation. This study compares three analytical methods-Complete Ensemble Empirical Mode Decomposition with Adaptive Noise (CEEMDAN), Ensemble Empirical Mode Decomposition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New beam hardened data correction and its application to artifact reduction in CT images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41579111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Grounded in physical modeling and analytical approximation, this study presents a mathematical formulation for estimating the mean energy corresponding to beam-hardened projection data and develops a correction method that effectively mitigates beam-hardening artifacts. The results highlight the potential of the proposed mean energy-based correction as a practical and computationally efficient solution for improving CT image quality. However, as this study primarily focused on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41579111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of serum-free medium supplemented with microalgal extract using response surface methodology for human fibroblast culture]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41578323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41578323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260126024629&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive associations between brain functional connectivity, motor abilities, and executive function development in early childhood: a longitudinal machine learning study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of unmet healthcare needs among women with disabilities: evidence from a national cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Women with disabilities experience high rates of unmet healthcare needs. Limitations in daily living due to physical disability, low socioeconomic status (SES), and mental health vulnerability emerged as major factors underlying unmet healthcare needs among women with disabilities. Integrated policies addressing financial barriers, healthcare accessibility, and women's health are needed to meet the unique needs of women with disabilities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics and treatment outcomes for presumed congenital superior oblique palsy in adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In adults with presumed congenital SOP, diverse clinical manifestations were observed. The angle of deviation, duction and version patterns, and treatment outcomes were not associated with the presence of SO hypoplasia on MRI. Despite the diversity in clinical features, treatment outcomes remained favorable.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aortoesophageal fistula as a late-onset complication of infected aortic arch aneurysm caused by Salmonella enterica serotype Choleraesuis: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-Invasive electrophysiological monitoring of cardiac organoids using 3D-Net-assisted microelectrodes array platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multidisciplinary approaches for the prevention and management of capsular contracture: a review of clinical, pharmacological, and biomaterial-based strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Capsular contracture (CC) is the most frequent complication associated with silicone-based breast implant surgery and often leads to multiple revision surgeries. The implantation of a foreign object triggers the formation of a fibrous capsule around the silicone implant. Over time, excessive and uncontrollable fibrosis leads to capsule thickening and contraction, resulting in severe pain, discomfort, and implant distortion, all hallmarks of CC. Various strategies have been proposed to prevent or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Updated data from IMbrave050: Adjuvant atezolizumab plus bevacizumab for high-risk hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this updated analysis, the initial RFS benefit seen with atezolizumab plus bevacizumab vs active surveillance was not sustained and OS remained immature. The safety profile of atezolizumab plus bevacizumab remained manageable and consistent with that of each agent and the underlying disease. Overall, the benefit-risk profile does not support atezolizumab plus bevacizumab as adjuvant therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuro-immune, metabolic, and oxidative pathways in depression due to hypothyroidism and Hashimoto's thyroiditis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings indicate that depression due to hypothyroidism is largely influenced by abnormalities in thyroid hormones, thyroid-stimulating hormone, metabolic pathways, and diminished antioxidant defenses. The observed results may be explained by the established impact of these hormones and biomarkers on cerebral functions, resulting in major depressive disorder.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41580036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Burden of chronic respiratory disease in Asia, 1990-2023: a systematic analysis for the Global Burden of Disease Study 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41579872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Chronic respiratory diseases are an important global issue, particularly in Asia, where burden patterns vary widely across countries. With more than half the world's population living in Asia, understanding the national and regional burden of chronic respiratory diseases is essential; however, research on this area remains inadequate. We aimed to investigate the burden of chronic respiratory diseases in Asia at national and regional levels, and to identify key risk factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41579872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260126024628&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>