<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 19:20:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Record Open-Circuit Voltage in Perovskite/PERC Tandem Solar Cells via Novel a-Si Interlayer Passivation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monolithic perovskite/silicon tandem (PST) solar cells are rapidly emerging as next-generation solar cells with significant potential for commercialization. This study presents a proof of concept for a silicon diffused junction-based PST cell, utilizing a passivated emitter rear contact (PERC) cell with a low-temperature (<200 °C) laser-fired contact process to minimize thermal damage. By introducing amorphous silicon to the emitter surface of PERC bottom cell, the open circuit voltage (V(oc))...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, Korea University, POSTECH, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrinsic and Extrinsic Determinants of Stability in Spiro-OMeTAD-Based Hole-Transporting Layers in Perovskite Solar Cells: Mechanistic Insights and Strategic Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spiro-OMeTAD has remained the benchmark hole-transporting material (HTM) in state-of-the-art perovskite solar cells, owing to its favorable energy level alignment and excellent interfacial compatibility. However, its practical implementation is critically hindered by the intrinsic instabilities introduced by conventional dopants such as lithium bis(trifluoromethanesulfonyl)imide (LiTFSI) and 4-tert-butylpyridine (tBP). While these dopants enhance electrical conductivity, they concurrently...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving HER2 Diagnostics with Digital Real-Time PCR for Ultrafast, Precise Prediction of Anti-HER2 Therapy Response in Patients with Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While human epidermal growth factor receptor (HER2) has emerged as a tumor-agnostic biomarker, standard HER2 testing for anti-HER2 therapies using immunohistochemistry (IHC) and in situ hybridization (ISH) assays remains subjective, time-consuming, and often inaccurate. To address these limitations, an ultrafast and precise HER2 testing method is developed using Lab-On-An-Array (LOAA) digital real-time PCR (drPCR), a fully automated digital PCR enabling real-time absolute quantification. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Analysis of Vehicles for the Regeneration of Mouse Endometrial Damage Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates the superior regenerative potential of an SIS-based EMSC patch over direct EMSC injection for endometrial repair. The findings suggest that scaffold-assisted cell therapy could be a promising approach for treating endometrial damage-related infertility. Further studies are required to optimize this strategy for clinical applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anharmonic Phonon Scattering Triggering Multi-ion Migration in Oxide-Based Superionic Conductors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The thermodynamic equilibrium assumption often invoked in modeling ion migration in solid-state materials remains insufficient to capture the true migration behavior of Li ions, particularly in less-crystalline superionic conductors that exhibit anomalously high Li ion conductivity. Such materials challenge classical frameworks and necessitate a lattice dynamics-based perspective that explicitly accounts for nonequilibrium phonon interactions and transient structural responses. Here, we uncover...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bifunctionally Driven Organic Photonic Conversion Devices Facilitated by Minimalistic Synthesis-Based Interfacial Energetic Alignment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bifunctional integration of indoor organic photovoltaics (OPVs) and photodetectors (OPDs) faces fundamental challenges because of incompatible interfacial thermodynamics: indoor OPVs require unimpeded charge extraction under low-light conditions (200-1000 lx), whereas OPDs require stringent suppression of noise current. Conventional hole transport layers (HTLs) fail to satisfy these opposing charge-dynamic requirements concurrently with commercial practicality (large-area uniformity,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling NiO<sub><em>x</em></sub>/Perovskite Interfaces: Charge Transport and Device Performance in Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[NiO(x) is a p-type semiconductor widely used as a hole transport material in perovskite solar cells (PSCs), yet the impact of fabrication methods on its interfacial properties and the underlying mechanisms remains unclear. This study investigates how the fabrication process─nanoparticle precursor (NP NiO(x)) and sputtering deposition (SP NiO(x))─and interfacial space charge effects influence charge transport and device performance in NiO(x)/perovskite systems. SP NiO(x) exhibits a higher...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between residential greenness and allergic diseases among adolescents in South Korea: A nationwide representative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Residential greenness was associated with a reduced prevalence of allergic diseases among Korean adolescents, with stronger protective associations observed among middle school students and those from higher-income households. These findings highlight the need to improve equitable access to green spaces for all adolescents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between body composition and hospitalization in patients undergoing maintenance hemodialysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Body composition is closely associated with hospitalization in patients undergoing MHD. Efforts to maintain euvolemic status and active interventions such as nutritional support and rehabilitation therapy may be essential to preserve a favorable body composition in this vulnerable population. Geriatr Gerontol Int 2025; ••: ••-••.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DynG: a dynamic scaling factor for thermographic stomatal conductance estimation under changing environmental conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermal imaging is a key plant phenotyping and monitoring technique but faces major bottlenecks in accurately and efficiently inferring stomatal conductance (g(sw)) from leaf temperature. The conductance index (I(g)) was previously proposed to estimate g(sw) from thermography by linking temperature differences between real and artificial leaves (ALs) based on the leaf energy balance. However, I(g) is highly sensitive to environmental fluctuations, hampering interpretation and reducing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter on 'Long-Term Dynamic Changes of Alanine Aminotransferase Levels Are Associated With Liver-Related Events in Nucleos(t)ide Analogue-Treated Chronic Hepatitis B Patients in China']]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social value of active seniors' behavior in the inner beauty market: A systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Involvement in the inner beauty market enhances active seniors' economic independence, social relationships, and holistic health. These findings support its role in promoting successful aging. Geriatr Gerontol Int 2025; ••: ••-••.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complementary Interventions Using Technology for Individuals With Infertility Using Assisted Reproductive Technology: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global rise in infertility highlights the need for personalized informational and psychological support. Digital health technology offers a promising avenue; however, knowledge gaps remain regarding optimal delivery methods, outcomes, and limitations. This scoping review synthesizes recent evidence on complementary interventions using technology for individuals with infertility undergoing reproductive technology-assisted interventions and evaluates their effectiveness and limitations. Seven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EXPRESS: Exacerbation of paclitaxel-induced neuropathic pain behaviors in breast tumor-bearing mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Paclitaxel-induced neuropathic pain model in breast tumor-bearing female MMTV-PyMT mice may be a useful animal model for investigating the analgesic effects and underlying mechanisms for CINP in breast cancer patients as well as the interplay between CINP development and cancer progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Regulating Hydrogel Actuators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Self-regulating hydrogels represent the next generation in the development of soft materials with active, adaptive, autonomous, and intelligent behavior inspired by sophisticated biological systems. Nature provides exemplary demonstrations of such self-regulating behaviors, including muscle tissue's precise biochemical and mechanical feedback mechanisms, and coordinated cellular chemotaxis driven by dynamic biochemical signaling. Building upon these natural examples, self-regulating hydrogels...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tactile force sensor based on a modified acoustic reflection principle for intraoperative tumor localization in minimally invasive surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The study introduces an acoustic-based tactile force sensor that supports surgeons in ensuring patient safety in MIS. Additionally, the sensor is proven to be a practical integration, and it can enable surgeons to detect the tumor's position and relative size during intraoperative surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A systematic review on volumetric analysis in orbital MRI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Accurate interpretation of volumetric data requires careful consideration of technical variables. Standardization of acquisition protocols, validated segmentation methods, and automated volumetry approaches are essential for enhancing reproducibility and clinical applicability. This systematic review provides a comprehensive framework for future research in orbital MRI volumetry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing the Diagnostic Performance of Repeated Endoscopic Ultrasound-Guided Tissue Acquisition Combined with Surrogate Repeated Endoscopic Retrograde Pancreatography for Small Pancreatic Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Repeated EUS-TA and ERP showed good diagnostic sensitivity for small pancreatic cancers ≤ 10 mm. When malignancy is suspected but not confirmed by a single procedure, repeating both may be an option in selected cases. Performing EUS-TA and ERP at least twice may be reasonable when small pancreatic cancer is suspected.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cooling-induced brushite crystallization in urine as a predictive risk marker for calcium kidney stone recurrence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kidney stones have a high recurrence rate-10% within 5 years and 50% within 10. Crystalluria reflects the urinary physicochemical environment and may serve as a recurrence marker, but key crystals like brushite are rarely detected under ambient conditions. This study aimed to identify novel recurrence markers by inducing crystallization through urine cooling and analyzing crystal composition. The analyzed urine samples from 164 stone formers, including first-time stone formers (FSF, n = 77) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Invasive Interventions and Risk Factors for Early Critical Events in Multiple System Atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiple system atrophy (MSA) is a progressive, adult-onset neurodegenerative disorder involving autonomic failure, cerebellar ataxia, and parkinsonism. Patients often require invasive interventions, such as gastrostomy or tracheostomy, and sudden death is common. This study aimed to elucidate patterns of invasive treatment and identify risk factors for tracheostomy or sudden death within 5 years of onset. In total, 214 patients diagnosed with MSA between November 2014 and October 2024 across 66...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the need for multimodal care in anorexia and cachexia patients with advanced cancer referred to palliative care: a secondary analysis of a multicenter survey in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The nine components were associated with NISs, anxiety, and distress. They were useful in evaluating needs for multimodal care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combination chemotherapy for older patients with unresectable biliary tract cancer: a prospective observational study using propensity-score matched analysis (JON2104-B)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GEM + CDDP + S-1 was associated with longer PFS without additional toxicity than GEM + CDDP for fit older patients. However, the OS for both were not statistically different. The efficacies of GEM + CDDP and gemcitabine for vulnerable older patients did not also differ significantly. These findings highlight the importance of vulnerability in patients with aBTC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Operando Evaluation of the Electrochemically Active Area in a Solid Oxide Fuel Cell Porous Electrode by Micro X-ray Absorption Spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An operando X-ray absorption spectroscopic technique, which enables us to measure X-ray absorption spectra with a position resolution of submicrometers at increased temperatures while controlling atmospheres and passing an electrical current through the specimen, was developed. By applying this technique, the electrochemically active area in a porous La(0.6)Sr(0.4)CoO(3-δ) electrode for a solid oxide fuel cell (SOFC) was experimentally and directly evaluated for the first time. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visualizing Molecular-Scale 3D Distributions of Ionic Liquids in Electric Double-Layer Capacitor by 3D Scanning Force Microscopy with Variable Tip/Sample Bias Voltages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atomic force microscopy (AFM) imaging of ionic liquid (IL) distribution in electric double-layer (EDL) devices has been actively explored to understand the origin of their excellent performance. However, this has been impeded by insufficient resolution or a poor understanding of the mechanisms of 3D IL imaging. Here, we overcome these difficulties using 3D scanning force microscopy (3D-SFM) with variable tip/sample bias voltages for visualizing 3D N,N-diethyl-N-methyl-N-(2-methoxyethyl)ammonium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Points-Based Health Incentive Program and Subsequent Health and Well-Being in Japan: An Outcome-Wide Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The points-program has the potential to promote not only the immediate outcomes it targets but also other domains of health and well-being outcomes through increased social interaction and healthy behaviors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomechanics of manual-bent versus patient-specific mandibular implants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The patient-specific mandibular reconstruction plate (PSMRP) has gained prominence for its precise adaptation to mandibular contours and reported enhanced mechanical reliability compared to the manual-bent mandibular reconstruction plate (MBMRP). Despite this, a biomechanical comparison between MBMRP and PSMRP is essential for informed clinical decision-making and advancing the field of mandibular reconstruction. Thereupon, biomechanical behavior was compared between two reconstructed mandibles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling Materials Synthesis Mechanisms Using <em>In Situ</em> Transmission Electron Microscopy and Neutron Scattering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving precise control of materials synthesis is a cornerstone of modern manufacturing, driving efficiency, functionality, and device innovation. This review examines the roles of in situ transmission electron microscopy (TEM) and neutron scattering (NS) in advancing our understanding of these processes. In situ TEM offers atomic-scale insights into nucleation, growth, and phase transitions, while NS provides an analysis of reaction pathways, phase evolution, and structural transformations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating discriminatory requests and refusals of healthcare workers: A Canadian-based inpatient hospital algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundHealthcare workers are increasingly subject to violence, aggression, and discriminatory requests from patients and families, reflecting broader societal biases within healthcare settings. In response, some institutions have developed policies and decision-making tools to guide leaders in addressing these situations ethically, consistently, and in accordance with human rights obligations.AimThis paper describes the revision of a previously published Caregiver Preference Algorithm to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thorough Physiological Assessment in Non-Culprit Vessels of Patients with Acute Myocardial Infarction: Is It a Required Action?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The prognosis of NCVs in AMI patients correlated with Angio-FFR but not with Angio-IMR, indicating it is epicardial vessel occlusion rather than microcirculatory dysfunction, predominantly leading to additional adverse prognosis. Compared to Angio-FFR, measuring Angio-IMR could be of limited necessity and clinical value in the management of NCVs among AMI patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical invasiveness, reoperation, and preoperative depression are predictive of super-utilization in adult spinal deformity surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ASD patients with depression who undergo more complex or revision spinal surgical procedures are more likely to be super-utilizers. Identifying likely super-utilizers within the ASD population may enable targeted interventions and preoperative planning to reduce unnecessary costs, while improving patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combinations of intrinsic capacity and frailty and their associations with self-rated health in community-dwelling older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNA-binding proteins and glycoRNAs: a new frontier on the cell surface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[European survey on metabolic and cardiovascular risk in Cushing syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Cushing's syndrome (CS) is associated with increased metabolic and cardiovascular (CV) risk factors and morbidities. Evidence-based guidelines for the management of these issues in active or remitted CS are not available, so best practice is derived from guidelines developed for the general population. We aimed to evaluate the awareness and practice variation for CV comorbidities of CS across Reference Centres (RCs) of the European Reference Network on Rare Endocrine Conditions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global research trends in endoscopic breast surgery: a bibliometric analysis from 1994 to 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endoscopic breast surgery (EBS) is designed to reduce surgical trauma and optimize cosmetic outcomes through inconspicuous incisions. However, a comprehensive understanding of the evolution of research focus in EBS is lacking. This study aimed to analyze global publication trends, academic impacts, and evolving research directions in the field of EBS. The Web of Science Core Collection database was searched for publications related to EBS from database inception to December 31, 2024....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neurotoxic and some systemic effects of cadmium oxide nanoparticles following their subchronic intranasal administration to rats: experimental data analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrial emissions of cadmium, which is used in various industries, and formation of cadmium nanoparticles during high-temperature technological processes aggravate the problem of chemical pollution. Insufficient understanding of the toxic impact of cadmium nanoparticles, coupled with the serious multisystem toxicity of this metal, necessitate expansion of knowledge about their potential toxic effects. We assessed the response of female outbred albino rats to subchronic exposure to cadmium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence-assisted assessment of metabolic response to tebentafusp in metastatic uveal melanoma: a long axial field-of-view [<sup>18</sup>F]FDG PET/CT study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI-assisted whole-body quantification of [1⁸F]FDG PET/CT and PERCIST-based response assessment are feasible and hold prognostic significance in tebentafusp-treated mUM. TMTV and TLG may serve as non-invasive imaging biomarkers for risk stratification and treatment monitoring in this malignancy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported efficacy of adjunctive brexpiprazole in major depressive disorder in a phase 4, open-label, interventional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patient-reported diary data revealed early and sustained improvements in depressive symptom severity during 8 weeks of adjunctive brexpiprazole treatment. 'Word of the day' may be an effective qualitative tool for future trials.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxidatively Induced Reductive N<sub>2</sub> Binding: A Dinickel-Bridging Bent N<sub>2</sub> Radical Anion and Its Redox-Triggered N<sub>2</sub> Release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitrogenase accumulates reducing equivalents in hydrides and couples H(2) elimination to the reductive binding of N(2) at a di-iron edge of its FeMo cofactor (FeMoco). Here, we describe that oxidation of a pyrazolato-based dinickel(II) dihydride complex K[L(Ni-H)(2)] (1^(K)), either electrochemically or chemically using H^(+) or ferrocenium, triggers H(2) elimination and binding of N(2) in a constrained and extremely bent bridging mode in [LNi(2)(μ(1,2)-N(2))] (3^(N2)). Spectroscopic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dad's Diet Shapes the Future: How Paternal Nutrition Impacts Placental Development and Childhood Metabolic Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early-life programming is a major determinant of lifelong metabolic health, yet current preventive strategies focus almost exclusively on maternal factors. Emerging experimental and preclinical data reveal that a father's diet before conception, particularly high-fat intake, also shapes offspring physiology. Here, we synthesize the latest evidence on how such diets remodel the sperm epigenome during two discrete windows of vulnerability: (i) testicular spermatogenesis, via DNA methylation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Common network related to hyperkinetic seizures revealed by functional lesion network mapping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: This study aims to determine whether the anatomically heterogeneous lesions that cause hyperkinetic seizures (HKS) are connected to a common functional network.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes of epilepsy surgery: A 25-year experience from a tertiary referral center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Despite pharmacological advances in epilepsy treatment, one-third of patients remain pharmacoresistant and may require surgery. Despite extensive literature on epilepsy surgery, studies with follow-ups longer than 5 years are rare. Our goal was to analyze the outcomes of patients undergoing epilepsy surgery at our center, with a minimum follow-up of 15 years.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solid-State Quantum Coherence From a High-Spin Donor-Acceptor Conjugated Polymer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Molecular spin systems that can be chemically tuned, coherently controlled, and readily integrated within devices remain central to the realization of emerging quantum technologies. Organic high-spin materials are prime candidates owing to their similarity in electronic structure to leading solid-state defect-based systems, light element composition, and the potential for entanglement and qubit operations mediated through spin-spin exchange. However, the inherent instability of these species...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Trauma-Informed Messaging Among Women Experiencing Intimate Partner Violence with Adverse Childhood Experience-Related Comorbidities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trauma-informed communication has shown promise in healthcare settings for supporting individuals affected by adverse childhood experiences (ACEs), yet its application in public health messaging remains underexplored. Given the strong link between ACEs and intimate partner violence victimization (IPVV), this study designed and tested a trauma-informed, text-based message aimed at promoting trauma understanding and positive behavioral intentions among women experiencing IPVV with self-reported...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Team-Based Ordering Workflows on Ambulatory Physician EHR Time, Order Volume, and Visit Volume]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Team-based ordering rates are relatively low, and new adoption of team-based ordering was not associated with physicians' time spent ordering or in the EHR overall. Teamwork may facilitate substantial increases in both order and visit volume, but a greater level of team-based ordering may be required to realize EHR time savings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outpatient and Inpatient Management of Infants and Children With Eczema Herpeticum Diagnosed in the Emergency Department]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this cohort, oral acyclovir outpatient management was not followed by disease progression or serious complications. These findings support that some mild EH cases may be managed without hospitalization, but further prospective studies are needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fractures are Highly Correlated with Bone Density and Inversely Correlated with Bone Turnover Markers in Autosomal Dominant Osteopetrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autosomal Dominant Osteopetrosis (ADO) is a rare, osteosclerotic disorder usually caused by missense variants in the CLCN7 gene, resulting in impaired osteoclastic bone resorption. Penetrance is incomplete and disease severity varies widely, even among relatives within the same family. Although ADO can cause visual loss, osteonecrosis, osteomyelitis, and bone marrow failure, the most common complication of ADO is fracture. We are conducting a natural history study to characterize disease...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gluten-free journeys: an evaluation of online travel health information for patients living with coeliac disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coeliac disease is a widely prevalent chronic condition, which presents potential challenges during international travel. Our analysis of information provided by national coeliac disease organisations points to the need to make more comprehensive and standardised travel health advice available online to people living with coeliac disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Target-Triggered Self-Assembly of Peptides with Silver Nanoparticles for Electrochemical Biosensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peptides have great potential in the design and fabrication of biosensors because of their high specificity, multifunctionality, and relatively low cost. In this paper, we report an electrochemical biosensor leveraging multifunctional peptides and silver nanoparticles for integrated target recognition, self-assembly, and signal output. As a proof of concept, we chose granzyme B (GrB) as a model target. Specifically, when the target is present, the recognition peptide is cleaved, and the assembly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Remote Blood Collection for Telomere Length Measurement: Assessing the Impact of Sample Characteristics and Handling on DNA Quality and Assay Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We established that whole blood collected remotely in BD Microtainers can provide a valid sample source for qPCR TL measurement. We also outline important logistical considerations related to sample collection and handling and provide recommendations for researchers who want to use this method.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of PM<sub>2.5</sub> Exposure on Birthweight: Racial and Ethnic Disparities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides evidence that associations of prenatal PM(2.5) exposure with reductions in birthweight varied among infants at the lowest, middle and highest percentiles of the conditional birthweight distribution; further, these associations varied by maternal race/ethnicity and neighbourhood racial/ethnic composition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outlook on zero/ultrashort echo time techniques in functional MRI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Since its introduction more than 30 years ago, the blood oxygenation level-dependent (BOLD) contrast remains the most widely used method for functional MRI (fMRI) in humans and animal models. The BOLD contrast is typically acquired with echo planar imaging (EPI) to obtain sensitization of the signal during the echo time (TE) to dynamic changes in deoxyhemoglobin content, while achieving high spatiotemporal resolution and full brain coverage. However, EPI-based fMRI also faces multiple...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amorphous Silica Induced Loose CeO<sub>2</sub> Clusters with Isolated Pt Atoms for Efficient Reverse-Water Gas Shift Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pt-based catalysts exhibit extraordinary potential in reverse-water gas shift (RWGS) reactions, but often fail to possess a high reaction rate and high durability at the same time under high temperature. Herein, we designed a SiO(2)-induced loose CeO(2) as an effective capture for Pt atoms. The abundant surface O vacancies in the loose CeO(2) can trigger significant electron transfer from Pt to CeO(2) and play a crucial role in stabilizing Pt atoms, therefore, largely improving its thermal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing Electrocatalytic Coupling of Carbon Dioxide and Methanol for High-Efficiency Formic Acid Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The coupling of electrocatalytic CO(2) reduction (ECR) and methanol oxidation reaction (MOR) presents a promising strategy for simultaneous cogeneration of formic acid (FA) at both cathode and anode. However, sluggish kinetics, low selectivity and efficiency hinder practical application. Herein, we demonstrate an integrated ECR||MOR system employing CuBi cathode and NiCo anode for energy-efficient FA cogeneration. The CuBi alloy achieves high Faradaic efficiencies (FE > 90%) for FA generation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Controlling the Organization and Differentiation of Human Neural Stem Cells on Hilbert Microcapillary Scaffolds Fabricated via Two-Photon Lithography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[3D scaffold architecture is critical for directing human neural stem cell (hNSC) fate and spatial organization. In this study, two-photon lithography (TPL) is used to fabricate microcapillary scaffolds based on the Hilbert space-filling curve as biomimetic basement membrane structures for guiding hippocampal-derived hNSC differentiation. The scaffolds feature 80 µm lumens with porous ellipsoidal membranes suspended above the substrate to provide topographical cues and permit nutrient diffusion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid epigenome unveils parental genetic divergence shaping salt-tolerant heterosis in Brassica napus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heterosis holds great potential for improving yield, quality, and environmental adaptability in crop breeding, which suggests that hybrids can exhibit better performance in adapting to extreme environments. However, the epigenetic mechanisms of salt-tolerant heterosis in allopolyploid crop Brassica napus (AACC, 2n = 38), particularly chromatin accessibility, remain largely unexplored. We investigated the dynamics of chromatin accessibility and transcriptional reprogramming during a time course...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Central Neurophysiological Alterations in Dystrophic mdx Mice Correlate With Reduced Hippocampal Levels of the Endogenous NMDA Receptor Ligand D-Aspartate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patients with Duchenne muscular dystrophy (DMD) may experience neurobehavioral and cognitive concerns, including psychiatric symptoms, due to the absence of full-length dystrophin (Dp427), frequently accompanied by deficiencies in shorter isoforms. The lack of dystrophin affects neurophysiological processes from the uterine phase, impacting neural circuitry in brain regions such as the prefrontal cortex, hippocampus, and cerebellum. This leads to reduced inhibitory GABAergic transmission and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship Between State Policies Targeting Unethical Treatment Practices and Opioid-Related Outcomes: An Event Study Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The passage of state laws targeting patient brokering is not associated with significant changes in opioid-related outcomes. Additional resources may be needed to accompany implementation and enforcement efforts before desired policy effects are realized.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare Expenditures Associated With Implementing an External Facilitation Program to Increase the Prescribing of Medications Used for the Treatment of Opioid Use Disorder Among Veterans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Veterans at intervention sites with an OUD history had higher outpatient psychiatric-related costs, which could be explained by increased access to optimal mental health services at VHA. Improving access to OUD treatment at VA may lead to more coordinated and comprehensive treatment of both OUD and other associated mental health and physical comorbidities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Animal fluency as a specific indicator of aphasia in dementia screening: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating the Potential Effects of 6PPDQ on Clear Cell Renal Cell Carcinoma via Network Toxicology and Molecular Docking Analysis With In Vitro Experimental Validation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[N-(1,3-Dimethylbutyl)-N'-phenyl-p-phenylenediamine-quinone (6PPDQ), as a recently identified environmental toxicant, has garnered significant attention because of its widespread detection in ecosystems and human habitats. Emerging evidence highlights its potential detrimental effects on various organs. However, its carcinogenic potential remains poorly understood, particularly its role in clear cell renal cell carcinoma (ccRCC). This study seeks to elucidate the molecular mechanisms underlying...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Language Functional Connectivity Alterations During Resting State in Brain Arteriovenous Malformation Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Three factors may contribute to maintaining intact language function in AVM patients, including the weakened inhibitory effect from the left dominant cerebral hemisphere over the right cerebral hemisphere leading to activation of the potential language functions of the right cerebral hemisphere (inter-cerebral connection reorganization), the functional upregulation of the cerebral language areas by cerebellar language-related brain regions via ACC (cerebrocerebellar connection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic architecture of the S-locus supergene revealed in a tetraploid distylous species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heterostyly is a polymorphic floral adaptation controlled by supergenes. The molecular basis of distyly has been investigated in diploid species from several unrelated families, but information is lacking for polyploid systems. Here, we address this knowledge gap in Schizomussaenda henryi, a tetraploid distylous species of Rubiaceae, the family with the greatest number of heterostylous species. Using chromosome-level genome assemblies and transcriptome profiling, we characterized its tetraploid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abdominal simultaneous 3D water T<sub>1</sub> and T<sub>2</sub> mapping using a free-breathing Cartesian acquisition with spiral profile ordering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed Look-Locker-based method using CASPR enables efficient, flexible, and simultaneous w T 1 $$ \mathrm{w}{T}_1 $$ and w T 2 $$ \mathrm{w}{T}_2 $$ mapping at isotropic resolution in a fixed scan time during free breathing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recombinant Allergy Vaccine-Induced Transmission of Maternal Allergen-Specific Neutralizing IgG]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chromosomal Abnormalities in Couples Experiencing Recurrent Implantation Failure in West of Iran: A Case-Control Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Chromosomal abnormalities significantly contribute to RIF. Therefore, it is imperative to conduct cytogenetic screening for both partners before initiating any assisted reproductive technology procedures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic Profiling Reveals a Glycolytic Shift and an IRG1/Itaconate/NF2L2 Axis Regulating Neurotoxic Oxidative Stress in Inflammatory Microglia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polar metabolic profiling, as well as bioenergetic assays, were used to characterize microglial responses to lipopolysaccharide, which induces a pro-inflammatory state, and interleukin-4, which is associated with an anti-inflammatory phenotype. BV2 microglial cells and primary microglia were used for these investigations. Results revealed that lipopolysaccharide-treated microglia exhibited an increased aerobic glycolytic activity measured by extracellular flux analysis, accompanied by increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plectin affects cell viscoelasticity at small and large deformations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plectin is a giant protein of the plakin family that crosslinks the cytoskeleton of mammalian cells. It is expressed in virtually all tissues and its dysfunction is associated with various diseases such as skin blistering. There is evidence that plectin regulates the mechanical integrity of the cytoskeleton in diverse cell and tissue types. However, it is unknown how plectin modulates the mechanical response of cells depending on the frequency and amplitude of mechanical loading. Here we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PEDUNCLE LENGTH 1 regulates wheat peduncle elongation through brassinosteroid signaling pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study identifies TaPL1, a MADS-box transcription factor underlying the QFiriti-6B QTL, as a key regulator of peduncle elongation in wheat. TaPL1 enhances brassinosteroid signaling through direct suppression of TaBKI1, and its loss-of-function alleles exhibit reduced plant height and peduncle length, but increased grain weight, offering valuable targets for yield improvement in wheat breeding.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive Value of Early Nursing Scores on 90-Day Outcomes in Intracerebral Hemorrhage Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND Multiple factors impact the prognosis of intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH). This study aimed to evaluate prognosis at 90 days after ICH in 561 patients using the numerical rating scale (NRS), the Braden scale, the Morse fall risk scale (MFS), and the enhanced modified early warning (MEW) scale. MATERIAL AND METHODS A retrospective study was performed among 561 patients with ICH diagnosed in our hospital. The primary outcome was the 90-day prognostic status, classified as poor or good....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Food Insecurity-Related Stigma Among Adults in the United States: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectiveTo characterize individual- and structural-level stigma associated with government (ie, SNAP, WIC) and emergency food program (ie, food banks, pantries, cupboards, soup kitchens) utilization in the US.Data Source5 databases (PubMed, PsychINFO, Web of Science, CINAHL, Sociological Abstracts) were searched in June 2024.Study Inclusion and Exclusion CriteriaIncluded peer-reviewed articles (January 2004 - June 2024), in the US, in English, original research or systematic reviews, and report...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microvascular Occlusion and Postrecanalization Hyperperfusion in a Swine Model of Acute Ischemic Stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Focal cerebral ischemia and reperfusion result in a substantial presence of microclots, which occurs alongside hyperperfusion in this swine model of recanalized acute ischemic stroke. These platelet microclots extend beyond the ischemic area. The density of microclots within the ischemic region increased with prolonged ischemia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Inflammatory and Cardiovascular Proteomics Biomarkers With Indices of Heart Rate Variability in the General Population: KORA S4/FF4 Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identified novel circulating proteins associated with heart rate variability indices. These proteins could improve our understanding of the pathophysiology underlying cardiac autonomic nervous dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid Diagnosis and Subtyping of Hermansky-Pudlak Syndrome With Flow Cytometry Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The diagnostic approaches for Hermansky-Pudlak Syndrome (HPS) include genetic sequencing, immunoblotting, electron microscopy (EM), and flow cytometry with mepacrine staining. However, these methods are often impractical for routine clinical use due to high cost, technical complexity, and limited availability. In this study, we evaluated dense granules (DGs) function in HPS mouse models using flow cytometry with mepacrine and FluoZin-3 staining. We then developed a standardized, practical flow...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Death and Access to Health Care Among Individuals Incarcerated in US State Prisons From 2001 to 2019]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cardiovascular disease is an important cause of death among individuals incarcerated in state prisons. A large number of individuals who died from cardiovascular disease, did not receive medical treatment during their incarceration, with racial disparities in carceral care provision. Strategies to ensure quality and equitable cardiovascular care for this population are needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondrial Complex Member VdNuo1 Recruits Superoxide Dismutases VdSOD2/4 to Maintain Superoxide Anion Homeostasis During Pathogenesis in Verticillium dahliae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During oxidative phosphorylation, the leaked electrons generate superoxide anions to attack the mitochondrial inner membrane and impair mitochondrial activity. Three superoxide dismutases (SODs) are secreted to degrade host superoxide anions in Verticillium dahliae. However, the roles of mitochondrial SODs (mtSODs) in superoxide anion detoxification and in virulence are unknown in this fungus. We had previously shown that complex I VdNuo1 subunit mediates multiple biological functions and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between endothelial inflammatory markers and cerebral small vessel disease in a community-based population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Endothelial inflammation, especially VCAM-1, was associated with presence of CSVD and higher CSVD burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disordered Inverse Photonic Beads Assembled From Linear Block Copolymers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structurally colored colloids, or photonic pigments, offer a sustainable alternative to conventional dyes, yet existing systems are constrained by limited morphologies and complex synthesis. In particular, achieving angle-independent color typically relies on disordered inverse architectures formed from synthetically demanding bottlebrush block copolymers (BCPs), hindering scalability and functional diversity. Here, we report a conceptually distinct strategy to assemble three-dimensional inverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four novel species of the genus Aquimarina isolated from marine sponges: Aquimarina callyspongiae sp. nov., Aquimarina mycalae sp. nov., Aquimarina discodermiae sp. nov., and Aquimarina penaris sp. nov]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Four Gram-stain-negative, strictly aerobic, catalase- and oxidase-positive bacterial strains, designated 2201CG5-10^(T), 2201CG14-23^(T), 2201CG1-2-11^(T), and 2304DJ70-9^(T) were isolated from marine sponges collected in the Republic of Korea. Phylogenetic analyses based on 16S rRNA gene and whole-genome sequences revealed that these strains represent a distinct phyletic lineage within the genus Aquimarina. Based on the whole-genome sequence comparisons, the closest phylogenetic relatives of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unusual Ferromagnetic Band Evolution and High Curie Temperature in Monolayer 1T-CrTe<sub>2</sub> on Bilayer Graphene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[2D van der Waals ferromagnets hold immense promise for spintronic applications due to their controllability and versatility. Despite their significance, the realization and in-depth characterization of ferromagnetic materials in atomically thin single layers, close to the true 2D limit, has been scarce. Here, a successful synthesis of monolayer (ML) 1T-CrTe(2) is reported on a bilayer graphene (BLG) substrate via molecular beam epitaxy. Using angle-resolved photoemission spectroscopy and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, POSTECH, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A history-dependent approach for accurate initial condition estimation in epidemic models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mathematical modeling is a powerful tool for understanding and predicting complex dynamical systems, ranging from gene regulatory networks to population-level dynamics. However, model predictions are highly sensitive to initial conditions, which are often unknown. In infectious disease models, for instance, the initial number of exposed individuals (E) at the time the model simulation starts is frequently unknown. This initial condition has often been estimated using an unrealistic,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bandgap-Engineered Graphene Quantum Dot Photosensitizers for Tunable Light Spectrum-Activated NO<sub>2</sub> Sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Visible-light activation is highly desirable for gas sensors due to its energy-efficient operation and broad accessibility. Photocatalysis offers a promising strategy for visible-light activation; however, a limited understanding of the band engineering-mediated activation process restricts the rational design of photocatalysts for gas sensors. In this work, we systematically investigate the impact of band tuning in photocatalysts on the nitrogen dioxide (NO(2)) sensing performance of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum: "Development of a diamagnetic loop in KAIMIR" [Rev. Sci. Instrum. 95, 073501 (2024)]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathogen sharing in the digital age: The unfinished agenda of the WHO pandemic agreement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regioselective Hydroamidation of α,β-Unsaturated Esters Enabled by Lewis Acid/Iron Relay Catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving precise regioselectivity in the hydroamination of alkenes is in high demand yet remains a longstanding challenge, particularly when electronically competing β-substituents are present. Here, we report a dual boron/iron catalytic system that enables the unprecedented hydroamidation of α,β-unsaturated esters to exclusively access α-amidated esters under mild conditions. The strategy harnesses the Lewis acidity of B(C(6)F(5))(3) to rapidly generate reactive silyl ketene acetal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune checkpoint inhibitors in gynecologic oncology: Current status and perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) have transformed cancer treatment by leveraging the immune system's capacity to fight gynecologic cancer. This review summarizes the current status and future perspectives of ICIs in the treatment of cervical, endometrial, and ovarian cancers and rare tumors. ICIs have demonstrated significant efficacy in tumors with high tumor mutational burden and immune markers such as PD-L1 expression and microsatellite instability. In cervical cancer, the integration of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alternating vertical nystagmus associated with Wernicke encephalopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Syllable-based speech characteristics as potential biomarker for differential diagnosis of Parkinson's disease, multiple system atrophy, and cerebellar ataxia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Speech disorders differ between Parkinson's disease (PD) and multiple system atrophy (MSA), but studies focusing on group differences based on syllables or including cerebellar ataxia (CA) are lacking until now. This cross-sectional study aimed to analyze syllable-based speech characteristics in patients with PD, MSA, and CA, as well as healthy controls, to determine their diagnostic utility. Speech samples were collected from 68 PD, 52 MSA, 23 CA, and 70 healthy controls. Participants performed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Novel mechanism whereby metformin improves glucose homeostasis: TXNIP-GLUT1 axis modulation enhances intestinal glucotonic effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut microbial production of imidazole propionate drives Parkinson's pathologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parkinson's disease (PD) is characterized by the selective degeneration of midbrain dopaminergic neurons and aggregation of α-synuclein. Emerging evidence implicates the gut microbiome in PD, with microbial metabolites proposed as potential pathological mediators. However, the specific microbes and metabolites involved, and whether gut-derived metabolites can reach the brain to directly induce neurodegeneration, remain unclear. Here we show that elevated levels of Streptococcus mutans (S....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A phase 2 randomized, placebo-controlled study on the efficacy and safety of AR1001, a phosphodiesterase-5 inhibitor, in patients with mild-to-moderate Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AR1001 was safe and well tolerated. Although primary efficacy endpoints were not met after 26 weeks of treatment, participants receiving 30 mg AR1001 showed favorable changes in AD-related plasma biomarkers compared to placebo.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparation of high-purity 1,3-distearoyl-2-oleoylglycerol (StOSt) via a two-step enzymatic interesterification combined with two-step solvent fractionation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-purity 1,3-distearoyl-2-oleoylglycerol (StOSt) was produced from high-oleic sunflower oil and ethyl stearate via a two-step enzymatic interesterification combined with a two-step solvent fractionation. Lipozyme RM IM (Rhizomucor miehei) was employed as a biocatalyst and the reaction was conducted in a packed-bed reactor. Molecular distillation was used to remove fatty acid ethyl esters from the reaction mixtures after enzymatic reactions. The optimum conditions were a temperature of 55 °C,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expandable Cage in Minimally Invasive Transforaminal Lumbar Interbody Fusion: Comparative Data with Static Cage from Single Institution, Single Surgeon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Minimally invasive transforaminal lumbar interbody fusion (MIS-TLIF) is widely adopted for the treatment of lumbar degenerative disease. Expandable cages are now increasingly used in MIS-TLIF to facilitate disc height restoration in narrow spaces. Despite theoretical advantages, the clinical and radiologic outcomes of expandable cage compared to static cage remain controversial.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Broadening PEth testing for alcohol exposure in the Asia-Pacific region]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Contributing Factors of Illicit Drug Use Among Youth Aged 18-24 in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The high prevalence of prescription drug and inhalant use among South Korean youths suggests that the perception that the country is drug-free is inaccurate and emphasizes the need for targeted intervention strategies. Effective prevention measures should include community education regarding drug risks, early detection of at-risk individuals, and enhanced access to tailored treatment alternatives.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How family structure shapes adolescent mental health under financial hardship?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The association between adolescent mental health and financial hardship appears shaped by family context, with distinct patterns of psychiatric vulnerability and resilience across family structures. Tailored post-pandemic recovery efforts should account for both economic conditions and family dynamics in addressing adolescent mental health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of high-flow nasal oxygen therapy on esophageal pressure and cardiovascular function in healthy, anesthetized, spontaneously breathing dogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: High-flow nasal oxygen therapy increased esophageal pressure without cardiovascular compromise in healthy, anesthetized, spontaneously breathing dogs. Additionally, HFNOT reduced the respiratory rate without altering arterial blood gas values.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ready, set, but no go: Skin fat comes preloaded with waiting precursors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fat depots across the body dynamically tune their sizes in response to nutrient demands and nonmetabolic cues. Writing in Cell Stem Cell, Rivera-Gonzalez et al.¹ report that skin fat, notable for its ability to rapidly expand, harbors molecularly distinct precursors, primed for proliferation and differentiation into mature adipocytes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-washing using a Soxhlet apparatus improves the mechanical properties and biocompatibility of 3D printing resin in contaminated solvent]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photopolymerization-based 3D printing is widely used in dental manufacturing due to its precision and customizability. However, printed resin specimens require effective post-washing to remove unpolymerized resin, which is a critical step that affects both their mechanical properties and biocompatibility. A conventional ultrasonic bath may fail to achieve effective post-washing due to solvent contamination by the residual resin, resulting in incomplete cleaning and possible redeposition. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of AlphaFold3 prediction for post-translational modification, oligomeric assembly, and quenchable metal binding of fluorescent proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Green fluorescent proteins (GFPs) are optical markers that are widely used in molecular and cell biology studies to track the location and function of biomolecules. Elucidating their structures will facilitate further engineering of these fluorescent proteins (FPs) to enhance their properties. AlphaFold3 (AF3) is a recently developed prediction tool that exhibits higher accuracy compared with other prediction tools, particularly in predicting protein-ligand interactions with state-of-the-art...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluorescence-guided tumor resection with a cathepsin B-activatable, EGFR-targeted probe and a dual-mode surgical exoscope]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluorescence-guided surgery enhances surgical precision by enabling real-time tumor visualization. Here, we developed a cathepsin B-activatable imaging probe conjugated to the EGFR-targeting antibody cetuximab (Cetux-CB probe) for fluorescence-guided resection of triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC). The probe consists of a cathepsin B-sensitive peptide linker, a near-infrared fluorophore (Flamma™ Fluors 749), and a quencher (qFlamma Black01), enabling enzymatic activation following...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To fuse or not to fuse: surgical strategies for recurrent lumbar disc herniation from a 16-nation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Significant differences existed between spine surgeons in the surgical treatment of recurrent LDH. Intra- and intergroup variations were observed, reflecting the lack of consensus in the literature and the challenge of adapting differences in habits and training to the few existing guidelines.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of On-Current and Reliability in InGaZnO Thin-Film Transistors for Synaptic Circuit Applications through Gate Insulator Stack Engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A nanometer-scale multilayer gate insulator (GI) engineering strategy is introduced to simultaneously enhance the on-current and bias stability of amorphous InGaZnO thin-film transistors (a-IGZO TFTs). Atomic layer deposition supercycle modifications employ alternating layers of Al(2)O(3), TiO(2), and SiO(2) to optimize the gate-oxide stack. Each GI material is strategically selected for complementary functionalities: Al(2)O(3) improves the interfacial quality at both the GI/semiconductor and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation of Fully Automated AI-Integrated System for Body Composition Assessment on Computed Tomography for Opportunistic Sarcopenia Screening: Multicenter Prospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Implementation of the fully automated AI-integrated system significantly enhanced opportunistic sarcopenia screening, achieving excellent technical success and high segmentation accuracy without manual intervention. This system has the potential to transform routine health check-ups by providing rapid and accurate assessments of body composition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermodynamically Coupled Three-Enzyme Cascade Converts Styrene to Cinnamic Acid, l-Phenylalanine, and Phenylpyruvate via CO<sub>2</sub> Fixation without External Energy Cofactors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the development of a cofactor-free CO(2) fixation platform based on a three-enzyme cascade comprising Aspergillus niger ferulic acid decarboxylase (AnFDC), Anabaena variabilis phenylalanine ammonia-lyase (AvPAL), and Proteus mirabilis l-amino acid deaminase (PmLAAD). Unlike canonical ATP- or NADPH-dependent CO(2) assimilation pathways, this system uses a prFMN-dependent carboxylation mechanism, enabling efficient CO(2) incorporation under ambient conditions without energy-intensive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeepGAM: An interpretable deep neural network using generalized additive model for depression diagnosis: Data from the heart and soul study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks have achieved significant performance breakthroughs across a range of tasks. For diagnosing depression, there has been increasing attention on estimating depression status from personal medical data. However, the neural networks often act as black boxes, making it difficult to discern the individual effects of each input component. To alleviate this problem, we proposed a deep-learning-based generalized additive model called DeepGAM to improve the interpretability of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A domain key-based secure SOME/IP protocol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the introduction of Advanced Driver Assistance Systems (ADAS), modern vehicles are equipped with numerous sensors, significantly increasing data communication within the in-vehicle network. However, the limited bandwidth of the Controller Area Network (CAN) poses challenges for high-speed sensor data transmission. To address this, automotive ethernet is emerging as a replacement for CAN, enabling the efficient transmission of large volumes of data, such as from cameras and LiDAR. Supporting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Remimazolam Preserves Oxygen Reserve and Improves Sedation Safety Compared to Propofol in Endoscopic Retrograde Cholangiopancreatography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Remimazolam effectively preserved the oxygen reserve compared with propofol, lowering the risk of hypoxia during sedation. Remimazolam was also associated with more favorable recovery profiles for patients undergoing ERCP, making it a safe and preferred sedative for this procedure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The spatial dynamics of urban vegetation and housing prices: Insights from pre- and post-pandemic Chicago using OLS and MGWR models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the spatial dynamics of urban vegetation and its impact on housing prices in Chicago, analyzing data from both pre- and post-COVID-19 periods. Employing Ordinary Least Squares (OLS) and Multiscale Geographically Weighted Regression (MGWR) models, we assess how the effects of green spaces on property values vary across different neighborhoods. The OLS model generally indicates a positive correlation between increased vegetation and housing prices. In contrast, the MGWR model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends In Reported Outcomes For Growth Hormone Therapy In Children With Growth Hormone Deficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results of this systematic review allow the development of a core outcome set that is recommended for routine use in all children receiving rhGH for childhood GHD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of prior online gaming experience on the migration of offline gamblers to online gambling platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of online gambling platforms has heightened concerns over their potential to intensify problematic gambling behaviors. While previous research has examined various risk factors, the influence of prior online gaming experience on gambling transitions remains underexplored. This study investigates whether and how engagement with online gaming facilitates the migration from offline to online gambling. Using survey data from 742 adults in South Korea, the analysis demonstrates that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of a grief programme for sudden bereavement: A logotherapy approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As traditional Koreans tend to avoid talking about death, this study purposed to help university students overcome the grief caused by death by using their inner strength through logotherapy. This study aimed to evaluate the effectiveness of a sudden bereavement programme using a randomized controlled pretest-posttest experimental design. Participants were 48 university students recruited online and randomly assigned to either the experimental or the no-treatment control group. The experimental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suffering in silence - Clinical nurses' miscarriage experience in South Korea: A qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Globally, despite the existence of policies intended to protect pregnant clinical nurses, many continue to face various risks during pregnancy, and inadequate support systems contribute to an increased risk of miscarriage. Particularly in South Korea, the miscarriage experiences of clinical nurses have yet to be thoroughly explored. Therefore, this study aimed to explore the experiences of clinical nurses following miscarriage within the context of their professional roles. A qualitative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of Lateral Pelvic Lymph Node Dissection Following Neoadjuvant Chemoradiation Therapy in Rectal Cancer: A Multicenter Retrospective Study (KROG 22-09)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LPLND did not significantly reduce pelvic recurrence or improve survival in patients treated with nCRT. However, LPLND may benefit patients with post-nCRT LPLN LSA ≥ 5 mm, suggesting that patient selection is crucial.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validated intraoperative bleeding severity scale (VIBe) for hemostasis assessment in lumbar spinal fusion: a prospective, randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: VIBe is a reliable and reproducible tool for intraoperative bleeding assessment in lumbar spine fusion. Active hemostatic agents were effective, and the addition of passive agents offered no measurable advantage.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to the Letter to the Editor: Preoperative prediction of microvascular invasion in ICCA-how far can gadoxetate MRI go?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterostructure nanodisks for multicolor polariton lasers with controllable whispering-gallery modes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Highly efficient optoelectronic devices of ultrasmall sizes are demanded as building blocks of next-generation integrated circuits, where tunable color enhances the feasibility of various applications. Here, we realize tunable multicolor nanolasers using disk-shaped axial heterostructures composed of III-nitride materials (GaN/InGaN/GaN), leveraging the optical confinement effect and active waveguiding. In heterostructure nanodisks, the development of exciton-polariton induces unique features...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40911051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association and Prognostic Implications of "No-Reflow Phenomenon" and Hypercoagulability in Patients With ST-Segment Elevation Myocardial Infarction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrated a close relationship between heightened thrombogenicity (assessed by TEG P-FCS) with "no-reflow phenomenon," and their additive prognostic implications after primary PCI in STEMI patients. Effective control of clot strength may reduce the risk of "no-reflow phenomenon" and improve clinical outcomes in these patients. (Gyeongsang National University Hospital Registry [GNUH]; NCT04650529).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing Frailty in Cardiology: Identifying Barriers Faced by Cardiologists and Health Care Professionals in Asia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Distinct barriers to frailty implementation exist at multiple levels, including gaps in provider expertise, insufficient support, and resource constraints that limit adequate frailty care provision. To address the diverse needs of stakeholders, a comprehensive implementation strategy leveraging interdisciplinary cardiogeriatric team resources and involving nurses could improve frailty care in cardiology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unravelling the genetic architecture of inflammatory bowel disease multiplex families with rare and common variant polygenic risk scores]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multiplex IBD families show diverse genetic architecture, with almost half showing a high burden of common and/or rare risk variants. While genetic predispositions to smoking influences IBD risk in sporadic cases, it provides limited insights into familial IBD. These findings highlight the genetic complexity within multiplex families and the need for tailored research approaches such as risk stratification and genetic screening strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of A/T/N Biomarkers: Comparing Plasma and Imaging Modalities in Alzheimer Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Imaging biomarkers, particularly tau PET, show superior prognostic accuracy compared with plasma biomarkers, whereas plasma biomarkers offer advantages in combination models through neurodegeneration markers. These findings underscore the complementary roles of plasma and imaging biomarkers and emphasize the need for tailored strategies for prognostic modeling in AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of second-line chemotherapy regimens in advanced biliary tract cancer: a systematic review, meta-analysis, and population-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FOLFIRINOX demonstrates numerically favorable outcomes compared to current second-line regimens for advanced BTC, with manageable toxicities. These findings suggest FOLFIRINOX as a potential second-line option, warranting further prospective validation and patient selection refinement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Homotopy reservoir computing: Harnessing chaos for computation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reservoir computing (RC) has traditionally relied on tuning systems toward the edge of chaos to optimize their computational capability. In contrast, we propose a novel method that starts from a fully chaotic system and systematically tames it into a trainable reservoir using homotopy. Our approach constructs adaptive reservoirs whose internal dynamics evolve in real time with the input, yielding a new class of computational models: Homotopy Reservoir Computing (Homotopy RC). We demonstrate the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Entropy-Enhancing Strategy Enables Highly Efficient Pt Utilization for High-Temperature H<sub>2</sub>O-CO<sub>2</sub> Coelectrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coelectrolysis of H(2)O and CO(2) using high-temperature solid oxide cells offers a highly efficient solution for converting greenhouse gases into valuable fuels and chemicals. Although Pt is an effective catalyst for this reaction, its high cost has limited its usage. Herein, we present that Pt-containing alloy catalysts with increased entropy exhibit high Pt utilization efficiency, catalytic performance, and thermal stability. Ab initio molecular dynamics and density functional theory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence-Driven Automated Design of Anterior and Posterior Crowns Under Diverse Occlusal Scenarios]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Occlusal scenarios influenced the surface deviation and quality of auto-generated anterior and posterior crown designs. DL software produced higher-quality molar designs than CA software.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive Dentition Intrusion in Hyperdivergent Patients Using Temporary Skeletal Anchorage Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyperdivergent skeletal Class II malocclusion is largely genetically determined and poses significant challenges in orthodontic treatment, particularly due to compromised facial aesthetics, reduced bite force and airway narrowing. Traditionally, orthognathic surgery has been the standard treatment for correcting such skeletal discrepancies. However, the advent of temporary skeletal anchorage devices (TSADs) has expanded the possibilities for orthodontic camouflage by allowing effective vertical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying Distinct Symptom Clusters in Older Adults Living With HIV in the United States: A Latent Class Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the number of older people living with HIV (PLWH) continues to grow, many experience a high symptom burden that negatively affects quality of life. Identifying symptom subgroups can help inform targeted interventions. Our study explored symptom patterns among older PLWH and their associations with self-rated health. Participants (≥50 years) completed surveys on demographics, symptoms, and self-rated health. The latent class analysis identified symptom occurrence-based subgroups, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Abscess Formation Within Craniofacial Fibrous Dysplasia of the Maxilla]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fibrous dysplasia, a rare skeletal disorder marked by replacement of normal bone with fibrous tissue and disorganized woven bone, most commonly affects the craniofacial region. Although craniofacial fibrous dysplasia (CFD) typically progresses slowly and remains asymptomatic, it can occasionally give rise to complications. The authors report a unique case of an intralesional abscess within maxillary CFD in an 88-year-old man presenting with acute facial pain and swelling. Computed tomography...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stacking the Risks: Fatal Consequences of Anabolic Steroid Misuse and Stacked Substance Use in FAERS Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AAS misuse, especially through high-risk stacking, significantly elevates the risk of serious health outcomes, particularly in younger individuals. Public health interventions-including targeted outreach, harm reduction, and enhanced healthcare provider awareness training-are necessary to educate on and mitigate these risks.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing metal-organic frameworks and covalent organic frameworks for photocatalytic CO<sub>2</sub> reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Increasing atmospheric carbon dioxide concentration necessitates innovative approaches to transform CO(2) into valuable compounds utilizing solar energy. The photocatalytic CO(2) reduction reaction (PC CRR) offers a sustainable solution, yet wide band gaps, rapid electron-hole recombination, and poor CO(2) adsorption capacity limit traditional metal oxide semiconductors for the PC CRR. This review systematically evaluates recent engineering advances in metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Utility of Salivary Steroid Profiling for the Differential Diagnosis of Adrenal Diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Salivary steroid profiling holds promise as a non-invasive tool for the diagnosis of adrenal diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alternative Surveillance Improves Outcomes by Detecting Early-Stage Hepatocellular Carcinoma in Chronic Hepatitis B Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CT/MRI-based alternative surveillance led to earlier HCC detection and improved post-diagnosis survival, particularly in high-risk CHB patients, supporting its potential role as an alternative to ultrasound in selected populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-Derived Organoids from Multiple Sites of a Single Tumor Recapitulates Intratumoral Heterogeneity in Patients with Gastric Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Intratumoral heterogeneity poses challenges for PDO-based models, highlighting the need for comprehensive assessment. Despite their limitations, PDOs offer valuable insights into precision medicine for patients with gastric cancer, aiding in the development of therapeutic strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking Ring-Opening Polymerization of Glycidyl Propargyl Ether via Lewis Pair Organocatalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alkyne groups provide exceptional versatility for functionalization in macromolecular systems. However, the controlled anionic ring-opening polymerization (AROP) of epoxide monomers bearing terminal alkynes remains challenging due to the lability of alkynes under strongly basic conditions. Herein, we present a controlled AROP of glycidyl propargyl ether enabled by Lewis pair organocatalysis, employing a phosphazene base and triethylborane. This catalytic system suppresses undesired interactions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Buffering brain aging: education moderates language impairment in Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Having more years of education is associated with buffering the effects of accelerated brain aging on language ability in PD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40910106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A real-world safety evaluation of new oral anticoagulants in elderly patients: evidence from the Adverse Drug Reaction Monitoring Center of Henan Province]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40909877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Attention should be paid to the clinical use of NOACs in elderly patients, and pharmacovigilance should be strengthened, and the implementation of individualised medication regimen should be used to promote clinical safety and rational drug use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40909877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From abstract painting to action painting: rethinking embodied simulation in aesthetic experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40909395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40909395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From greens to safety: Exploring the relationship between outdoor neighborhood conditions, neighborly bonds, and social integration among public housing residents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to examine the relationship between outdoor environmental quality, trust in neighbors, and social integration among residents of public rental housing in Seoul, South Korea. It also investigates how neighborly relationships moderate this association. The study uses data from the 2016-2021 Seoul Public Rental Housing Panel Survey (SPRHPS) and applies individual fixed effects models to examine how outdoor environmental quality affects trust in neighbors. It also explores the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cellular expansion of hepatocellular carcinoma organoids using decellularized liver scaffolds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The DLS collagen framework facilitates the proliferation of HCC organoids. Thus, cultivating HCC organoids within a DLS appears to represent an effective method for rapid cell expansion, although it was ineffective for HepG2 cells and liver organoids. Further studies are required to validate the biological and oncological equivalence between seeded HCC organoids and those rapidly expanded within a DLS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic and prognostic performance of <em>PAK1</em> methylation in patients with hepatocellular carcinoma undergoing liver transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These data suggest that PAK1 methylation is not a clinically useful biomarker for HCC in LT recipients. New DNA methylation biomarkers are required for early diagnosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forensic analysis and evaluation of file-wiping applications in Android OS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anti-forensics refers to techniques designed to obstruct the discovery of evidence in digital forensic investigations. File-wiping is one of the anti-forensic techniques that make data recovery impossible by overwriting data with specific patterns. This technique poses significant challenges to investigators. Our study evaluates the effectiveness of file-wiping applications on the Android OS from the anti-forensic perspective. We selected six applications from the Google Play Store that support...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distributed Response to Distributed Intervening: Making Sense of Public Digitalization Through Digital Support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Communication and interaction with public authorities and healthcare professionals in Denmark primarily go through digital self-service platforms, requiring diverse skills and device access. In this article, we describe how senior citizens in Denmark handle and make sense of public digitalization through different forms of digital support. Through an ethnographic study of community-led initiatives of digital support, we highlight how senior citizens find socio-technical ways of managing digital...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40913150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating the pitfalls of pulmonary function testing in chronic lung allograft dysfunction and chronic pulmonary graft-versus-host disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The genomics of discrete polymorphisms maintained by disruptive selection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Disruptive selection can lead to the evolution of discrete morphs. We show that particular genetic architectures, in terms of dominance, epistasis, and linkage, are likely to evolve to produce discrete morphs under disruptive selection. Recent genomic studies have revealed that causative mutations tend to cluster, sometimes as a result of chromosomal rearrangements, but we still know little about the molecular mechanisms of dominance and epistasis. Although disruptive selection can also lead to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tracking phase transitions of tactoids in sulfated cellulose nanocrystals using second harmonic generation microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cellulose nanocrystals (CNCs) have emerged as promising candidates for chiroptical functional materials due to their ability to form cholesteric liquid crystals with tunable periodicity. The quality of the final cholesteric phase is influenced by the nucleation, growth and coalescence mechanism of the initial droplets, known as tactoids. Current research focuses on understanding the size and morphological transformations of these tactoids, to gain deeper insights into their dynamic behavior and,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resolving In Situ Exposure Dynamics in a Chemically Amplified EUV Photoresist Using Table-Top EUV Photoemission Spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extreme ultraviolet (EUV) lithography has revolutionized the high-volume manufacturing of nanoscale components. The use of EUV light leads to ionization-driven chemistry in the imaging materials of lithography, the photoresists. The complex interplay of ionization, generation of primary/secondary electrons, and the subsequent chemical mechanisms that lead to image formation in photoresists has been notoriously difficult to study. This is in particular true for the radiochemical transformations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of baseline PINP on the BMD increase with romosozumab, teriparatide, and denosumab in treatment-naïve primary osteoporosis: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ROMO demonstrated robust increases in both LS and TH BMD across all PINP levels. TPTD led to increases in LS BMD comparable to those with ROMO in the low PINP group. DMAb led to increases in both LS and TH BMD comparable to those with ROMO in the high PINP group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes in patients with chronic limb-threatening ischemia with or without hyperpolypharmacy after revascularization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912636/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Hyperpolypharmacy in patients with CLTI after revascularization was negatively associated with overall survival, freedom from cardiovascular death, and limb salvage.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912636/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electro-assisted microalgae cultivation, harvesting, and recovery of high-value products: A review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrotechnology has recently emerged as an eco-friendly method for enhancing microalgal processes. Electric fields can be applied to microalgae at different stages to improve their biomass productivity, high-value products (HVPs) content, harvesting efficiency, and cell disruption for biomolecule recovery. Incorporating them into microalgal processes can significantly contribute to achieving a circular bioeconomy. This review discusses the application of electric field-based techniques for the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aspergillus and Host-Pathogen Interaction: Focus on treatment-relevant aspects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Invasive aspergillosis (IA) remains a major cause of morbidity and mortality in immunocompromised individuals, with an expanding spectrum of at-risk populations, particularly in the intensive care settings. Despite advances in antifungal pharmacotherapy, treatment outcomes remain suboptimal, and the rise of antifungal resistance highlights the need for adjunctive therapy that leverage host immune mechanisms. The pathogenesis of IA is primarily driven by impaired or dysregulated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between serum vitamin D metabolite levels and cognitive function in community-dwelling older adults: A cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sex-based differences in vitamin D-cognition associations may reflect disparities in vitamin D levels and hormonal effects, such as estrogen-enhancing and testosterone-suppressing metabolism. 1,25(OH)(2)D(3), VMR, and 3-epi-25(OH)D(3) may be more sensitive than total 25(OH)D.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40912362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250906152050&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>