<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 07:41:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Additive Manufactured Programmable Scaffold Sensor Based on Triply Periodic Minimal Surfaces for Broad-Spectrum Pressure Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40922074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250909034145&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving both high sensitivity and a wide detection range in flexible pressure sensors poses a challenge due to their inherent trade-off. Although porous structures offer promising solutions, conventional methods (templating, foaming, and freeze-drying) fail to precisely control cavity dimensions, spatial arrangement, and 3D morphology, which are crucial for sensing performance. Here, we propose a scalable fabrication strategy that integrates triply periodic minimal surface (TPMS)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40922074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250909034145&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerebrospinal fluid draining lymphatics in health and disease: advances and controversies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The meninges, consisting of the dura, arachnoid and pia mater that surround the brain and spinal cord, have been recognized from the earliest anatomical studies. First identified in 1787, lymphatic vessels in the dura are now receiving greater attention as their contribution to cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) clearance in diverse neurological conditions is being investigated. New methods have increased the understanding of dural lymphatics, but much is still being learned about their heterogeneity,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrathin Amorphous Boron Nitride Films and Their Functional Integration in Lithium Metal Anodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultrathin amorphous materials are promising counterparts to 2D crystalline materials, yet their properties and functionalities remain poorly understood. Amorphous boron nitride (aBN) has attracted attention for its ultralow dielectric constant and superior manufacturability compared with hexagonal boron nitride. Here, we demonstrate wafer-scale growth of ultrathin aBN films with exceptional thickness and composition uniformity using capacitively coupled plasma-chemical vapor deposition (CCP-CVD)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When automation hits jobs: Entrepreneurship as an alternative career path]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the relationship between occupational automation risks and workers' transitions to entrepreneurship using data from the Current Population Survey. We find that employees facing automation-related job displacement are inclined to shift toward unincorporated entrepreneurship, emphasizing entrepreneurship as a viable alternative career path. Noteworthy variations emerge when examining specific automation technologies, revealing a positive association between industrial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compartment-specific adaptive responses and dysregulation under NQO1 deficiency in diabetic kidney disease: A transcriptomic GSEA-based investigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic kidney disease (DKD) involves oxidative stress-driven damage to glomeruli (Gloms) and proximal convoluted tubules (PCT). NAD(P)H: quinone oxidoreductase 1 (NQO1) regulates redox balance, but its compartment-specific role remains unclear. Streptozotocin (STZ)-induced hyperglycemia increased albuminuria and foot process effacement, with NQO1 KO (NKO) mice exhibiting greater podocyte injury than WT, indicating exacerbated glomerular damage. To investigate the underlying mechanisms, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3-O-acetylrubiarbonol B preferentially targets EGFR and MET over rubiarbonol B to inhibit NSCLC cell growth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) is one of the leading causes of cancer-related deaths, remaining a significant challenge in terms of early detection, effective treatment, and improving patient survival rates. In this study, we investigated the anticancer mechanism of rubiarbonol B (Ru-B) and its derivative 3-O-acetylrubiarbonol B (ARu-B), a pentacyclic terpenoid in gefitinib (GEF)-sensitive and -resistant NSCLC HCC827 cells. Concentration- and time-dependent cytotoxicity was observed for both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[rev-Gelatin: A Gelatin with Reverse Thermo-Responsive Behavior Inspired by Candy and Ice Cubes Phase Dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional gelatin's gel-to-sol transition upon heating restricts its utility in biomedical applications that benefit from a gel state at physiological temperatures such as Pluronic F127 and poly(NIPAAm). Herein, we present "rev-Gelatin", a gelatin engineered with reverse thermo-responsive properties that undergoes a sol-to-gel transition as temperature rises from ambient to body temperature. Inspired by the phase dynamics of common materials like candy and ice cubes, whose surfaces soften or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and safety of combining pharmacopuncture therapy and acupotomy for treating patients with degenerative lumbar spinal stenosis: A pragmatic, assessor-blinded, randomized, controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compared to CKMT alone, CKMT+PA offers significant improvements in pain relief, functional capacity, and quality of life in patients with degenerative LSS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comparative Analysis of Molecular Epidemiology and Antibiotic Resistance in Group B Streptococcus Isolated From Invasive and Noninvasive Adult Cases in Daejeon, South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: This study aims to determine the molecular features and antimicrobial resistance of Streptococcus agalactiae (Group B streptococcus, GBS) causing invasive and noninvasive infections in Korean adults. Methods: Sequence type (ST), capsular serotype, pilus island typing, and antimicrobial susceptibility were analyzed for GBS isolates obtained at a hospital laboratory that processed the primary clinical specimens collected from Korean adults between 2021 and 2024. Results: Among the 90...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moderating role of triglycerides in the relationship between amyloid-β, hippocampal atrophy, and cognitive decline in mild cognitive impairment and early Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The role of triglycerides in Alzheimer's disease dementia (ADD) progression remains unclear. This study aimed to investigate how triglyceride levels influence the relationship between amyloid-beta (Aβ) deposition, hippocampal atrophy, and cognitive decline in individuals with mild cognitive impairment (MCI) and early-stage ADD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2'-Fucosyllactose mitigates cognitive deficits in Alzheimer models: targeting amyloid pathology, oxidative stress, and synaptic plasticity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: 2'-FL improved cognitive performance in 5xFAD mice, reduced Aβ plaque deposition and pro-inflammatory cytokine levels in vivo, and mitigated oxidative stress and synaptic dysfunction in cellular models. These findings indicate that 2'-FL modulates multiple pathological features relevant to AD in preclinical models.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Development of a nitrate‑responsive whole‑cell biosensor based on engineered probiotic <em>Saccharomyces boulardii</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1007/s10068-025-01850-x.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endolysin-based biocontrol strategies against <em>Listeria monocytogenes</em> in food: A comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Listeria monocytogenes poses significant challenges in the food industry due to its resistance in harsh environments and its ability to form biofilms. Endolysins represent a promising solution for controlling L. monocytogenes in the food industry, with potential applications during both production and storage. This review discusses various endolysins that effectively inhibit L. monocytogenes, emphasizing their optimal conditions and potential uses in food products. When used in combination with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of combined treatment with <em>Curcuma longa</em> extract, curcumin, or bisdemethoxycurcumin and UVA on imiquimod-induced psoriasis-like lesions in BALB/c mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The combination of Curcuma longa extract and its active compounds, curcumin and bisdemethoxycurcumin, as photosensitizers with ultraviolet A (UVA) light has potential in alleviating psoriasis. This study evaluated their therapeutic effects on psoriasis-like lesions induced via imiquimod application in BALB/c mice. Treatments with Curcuma longa extract, curcumin, or bisdemethoxycurcumin combined with UVA (TUVA, CUVA, and BUVA, respectively) were administered. All treatments improved abnormal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effect of Hydrogen Peroxide With Different Concentration on the Color and Surface Microhardness of the Resin Bracket]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: HP application at concentrations of > 8.7% and < 17.5% is effective in whitening discolored resin brackets while not deteriorating the SBS, surface hardness, and microstructure. Dental clinicians can safely use HP within the recommended range to achieve effective esthetic outcomes without compromising bracket performance and durability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laser-Induced Photothermal Conversion to Hemispherical MoS<sub>2</sub> Enabling Non-Contact Self-Powering Image Sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Molybdenum disulfide (MoS(2)) has recently emerged as a promising material for the development of triboelectric nanogenerators (TENGs) owing to its inherently negative triboelectric properties when paired with polymeric layers, along with its notable transparency and mechanical flexibility. However, MoS(2)-based TENGs operating in the contact-separation mode encounter critical limitations, including mechanical wear and limited triboelectric performance, particularly within the constraints of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide Survey on Endoscopic Papillectomy for Ampullary Adenoma: Current Practices and Variability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although general clinical practices appear standardized, significant variability remains in specific procedural and post-procedural approaches. These findings highlight the need for refined guidelines to support a more consistent and comprehensive approach to EP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analgesic effects of transversus abdominis plane and quadratus lumborum blocks are not clinically meaningful for laparoscopic nephrectomy: systematic review and network meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: While TAP and QL blocks demonstrated a significant analgesic effect compared to systemic analgesia, the clinical relevance of this benefit may be limited.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of criteria for evaluating competency-based curriculum in medical schools using the Delphi hierarchy process method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study developed an evaluation model and valid evaluation criteria specifically designed for the curricula of Korean medical schools. These were created based on expert consensus, which adds to the strength and relevance of the proposed framework. The establishment of valid evaluation criteria is expected to enhance evaluation practices, promote educational quality, and support the continuous improvement of medical education.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endothelial to mesenchymal transition: a central mechanism in diabetes-induced vascular pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetes mellitus is a major global health concern associated with micro-and macrovascular complications. Among the diverse mechanisms that contribute to vascular dysfunction in diabetes, endothelial to mesenchymal transition (EndMT) has emerged as a key pathological process. EndMT involves the loss of endothelial cell characteristics and the acquisition of mesenchymal features, resulting in impaired endothelial function, increased fibrosis, and inflammation. In addition to findings from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unmet clinical need in patients with acute kidney injury and acute kidney disease: insights from a Korean multicenter cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40922042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40922042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking Chronic Kidney Disease Epidemiology Collaboration equations in the Korean population: from race-based to region-based estimation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40922041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40922041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Discovery of genes positively modulating treatment effect using potential outcome framework and Bayesian update]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40922030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40922030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polygenic scores for psychiatric traits mediate the impact of multigenerational history for depression on offspring psychopathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A family history of depression is a well-documented risk factor for offspring psychopathology. However, the genetic mechanisms underlying the intergenerational transmission of depression remain unclear. We used genetic, family history, and diagnostic data from 11,875 9-10 year-old children from the Adolescent Brain Cognitive Development study. We estimated and investigated the children's polygenic scores (PGSs) for 30 distinct traits and their association with a family history of depression...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor antigen PRAME promotes melanoma growth by inactivating p53 through the SIRT1-DBC1 axis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preferentially expressed antigen in melanoma (PRAME), which is highly expressed in melanoma, is associated with tumor progression and malignancy. Notably, melanoma cells often exhibit inactivation of the tumor suppressor p53 despite carrying the wild-type p53 gene. Here, we investigated the functional interplay between PRAME and p53. Consistent with our analysis of human databases, PRAME overexpression promoted melanoma cell proliferation. Conversely, PRAME downregulation produced the opposite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A versatile toolkit for drug metabolism studies with GNPS2: from drug development to clinical monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolism is a fundamental process that shapes the pharmacological and toxicological profiles of drugs, making metabolite identification and analysis critical in drug development and biological research. Global Natural Products Social Networking (GNPS) is a community-driven infrastructure for mass spectrometry data analysis, storage and knowledge dissemination. GNPS2 is an improved version of the platform offering higher processing speeds, improved data analysis tools and a more intuitive user...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for Progression to Frequent Exacerbators in Stable Patients with COPD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among stable COPD patients, older age, decreased lung function, increased eosinophil counts, and use of ICS-containing inhalers were associated with progression to frequent exacerbators.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delineating coronary epicardial stenosis status from microvascular dysfunction using pressure-drop coefficient from multicenter ILIAS registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The established diagnostic cut-off values of CDP can differentiate between the concomitant ES and MVD, improving the functional assessment of CAD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deciphering natural and anthropogenic sources in estuarine sediment organic matter using multi-spectroscopic fingerprinting coupled with receptor modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Identifying the sources of sedimentary organic matter (OM) is essential for understanding pollution dynamics and guiding effective management in estuarine environments. This study proposes a novel and transferable source tracking framework that integrates Fourier transform infrared (FTIR) and fluorescence spectroscopy with a principal component analysis-absolute principal component score-multiple linear regression (PCA-APCS-MLR) receptor model to apportion OM sources in surface sediments across...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-related differences in the step-to-step control of foot placement during prolonged walking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Walking is essential for maintaining independence and quality of life, yet aging may impair the neuromuscular function required for stable gait over time. This study sought to quantify age-related differences in step-to-step control during prolonged walking using detrended fluctuation analysis (DFA). We hypothesized that step-to-step changes in step length and step width would exhibit reduced temporal persistence over time, with more pronounced effects in older than in younger adults. 15 younger...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quality indicator survey of clinical practice guidelines for esophagogastric junction cancer 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clinical practice guidelines for esophagogastric junction cancer (EGJ GLs) were published in 2023. In order to evaluate how EGJ GLs have been adopted into clinical practice worldwide and to identify any outstanding clinical questions to be addressed in the next edition, this survey was conducted. An electronic questionnaire was developed. The questionnaire comprised 16 questions designed to assess the adoption of the guideline. Responses were collected online. The survey was conducted by the EGJ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvent-Directed Self-Assembly of Sorafenib into Spherical Particles for Enhanced Anticancer Efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sorafenib, a clinically approved multityrosine kinase inhibitor, exhibits poor aqueous solubility, which limits its bioavailability and therapeutic efficacy. In this study, we introduce a solvent-directed self-assembly strategy to modulate the nanostructure of sorafenib without the use of external carriers or complex formulation techniques. In pure water, sorafenib forms large lamellar aggregates, whereas in 30% methanol-water mixtures, it self-assembles into uniform spherical particles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-Driven quality assurance in mammography: Enhancing quality control efficiency through automated phantom image evaluation in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed deep learning model accurately assessed mammography phantom images according to guideline criteria and achieved expert-level performance. By automating the evaluation process, the model can improve scoring consistency and significantly enhance the efficiency and scalability of quality control workflows.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Normative serum cortisol levels in second and third trimesters and their associated factors: A prospective cohort study from Sri Lanka]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The pregnant women in rural Sri Lanka reported a low mean serum cortisol level, which gradually increased with the POG. Significantly higher mean serum cortisol was associated with primi-gravidity, history of miscarriage, pre-pregnancy BMI, and POG at cortisol test, but not psychological factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-modal virtual reality system for tinnitus treatment methods and validation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Virtual reality (VR) has been utilized in clinical treatment because it can efficiently simulate situations that are difficult to control in the real world. In this study, we evaluated the efficacy of VR in patients with chronic subjective tinnitus. We assessed the clinical effectiveness based on electroencephalogram (EEG) analysis and questionnaire responses after patients participated in a 6-8-week VR-based tinnitus relief program. The intervention involved removing tinnitus avatars in the VR,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Versatile Usability of Lateral Crural Strut Graft for Correction of Various Nasal Tip Deformity in Secondary Rhinoplasty in Asians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In Asian patients, LCSG using autogenous cartilage would be a useful and versatile option for various types of nasal tip deformities in secondary rhinoplasty, which can effectively improve tip cosmesis, symmetry, external valve function, and can also lengthen the contracted nose.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Condensation of the Golgi Apparatus Activates YAP1 to Promote Gastric Cancer Progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alterations in the structure of the Golgi apparatus play a pivotal role in cancer progression and invasion. A better understanding of how Golgi morphology regulates the metastatic potential of cancer cells could help identify potential treatment strategies. In this study, we investigated how specific structural variations in the Golgi, particularly fragmentation and condensation, influence the malignancy of gastric cancer using human cell lines, xenograft mouse models, and human patient tissue...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum Ferritin and Iron-Related Biomarkers in Relation to Breast Cancer Risk by Menopausal Status: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: An inverse association between serum ferritin levels and breast cancer risk was observed in premenopausal women, with a similar but non-significant trend in postmenopausal women.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Bondable and Strain-Durable Electroceuticals Using Self-Healing and Stretchable Conducting Nanocomposite Trilayer for Effective Vagus Nerve Stimulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vagus nerve stimulation (VNS) is a promising therapy for neurological and inflammatory disorders across multiple organ systems. However, conventional rigid interfaces fail to accommodate dynamic mechanical environments, leading to mechanical mismatches, tissue irritation, and unstable long-term interfaces. Although soft neural interfaces address these limitations, maintaining mechanical durability and stable electrical performance remains challenging. Herein, we introduce a self-bondable and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SEPTIN9 locally activates the RhoGEF ARHGEF18 to promote early stages of mitochondrial fission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondria continually undergo fission to maintain their network and health. Nascent fission sites are marked by the ER, which facilitates actin polymerization to drive calcium flux into the mitochondrion and constrict the inner mitochondrial membrane. Septins are a major eukaryotic cytoskeleton component that forms filaments that can both directly and indirectly modulate other cytoskeleton components, including actin. Septins have been implicated in mitochondrial fission; however, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging electrostatic screening and ion transport in lithium salt-doped ionic liquids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alkali salt-doped ionic liquids are emerging as promising electrolyte systems for energy applications, owing to their excellent interfacial stability. To address their limited ionic conductivity, various strategies have been proposed, including modifying the ion solvation environment and enhancing the transport of selected ions (e.g., Li+). Despite the pivotal role of electrostatic interactions in determining key physicochemical properties, their influence on ion transport in such systems has...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immersed Halide Perovskite-Based Electrochemical Cells for Stable Solar Water Splitting: Achievements, Opportunities, and Prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently, halide perovskite materials have attracted significant research interest in photoelectrochemical cells as promising photoabsorbers due to their superior optoelectronic properties. However, their instability under environmental conditions remains a major obstacle to the development of stable water-splitting devices. This review thoroughly examines the growing array of encapsulation strategies that have accelerated the integration of perovskite materials into water-splitting systems. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lanthanum-Induced Gradient Fields in Asymmetric Heterointerface Catalysts for Enhanced Oxygen Electrocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-nitrogen-carbon (M-N-C) catalysts display considerable potential as cost-effective alternatives to noble metals in oxygen electrocatalysis. However, uncontrolled atomic migration and random structural rearrangement during pyrolysis often lead to disordered coordination environments and sparse active sites, fundamentally limiting their intrinsic catalytic activities and long-term durability. Herein, a novel strategy is reported for use in directionally regulating atomic migration pathways...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Image of "Power of Woman (Weibermacht)" and Plastic Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Northern Renaissance motif of Weibermacht-the "power of woman"-depicted female beauty as a destabilizing force capable of undermining male authority, intellect, and divine order. These visual allegories, featuring figures such as Phyllis, Judith, and Delilah, warned of the dangers inherent in seductive appearance. Far from neutral, beauty was rendered as morally volatile, triggering cultural anxiety through its capacity to challenge patriarchal norms. This essay traces the legacy of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Biomaterial Delivery of Hypoxia-Conditioned Extracellular Vesicles (EVs) as a Therapeutic Platform for Traumatic Brain Injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traumatic Brain Injury (TBI) is a common and debilitating injury, causing long-lasting neurological deficits. Current therapeies for recovery remain inadequate, undersing the urgent need for innovative interventions. In this study, a novel therapeutic approach is introduced that delivers extracellular vesicles (EVs) derived from human-induced pluripotent stem cell-derived neural progenitor cells (hiPSC-NPCs) with a gelatin-based injectable bioorthogonal hydrogel (BIOGEL). The hiPSC-NPCs are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cation Dehydration by Surface-Grafted Phenyl Groups for Enhanced C<sub>2+</sub> Production in Cu-Catalyzed Electrochemical CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The challenge to produce multicarbon (C(2+)) products in high current densities in the electrochemical reduction of carbon dioxide (CO(2)RR) has motivated intense research. However, the ability of solvated cations to tune and activate water for C(2+) production in the CO(2)RR has been overlooked. In this study, we report the incorporation of a covalently grown layer of functionalized phenyl groups on the Cu surface that leads to a 7-fold increase in ethylene production (to -530 mA cm^(-2)) and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and safety of herbal medicine on treatment of dysmenorrhea: An analysis of a multicenter, prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Herbal decoction group significantly decreased the intensity and duration of menstrual pain and analgesic dosage. These findings suggest that herbal decoction may be a safe and effective personalized treatment option for dysmenorrhea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Traditional Korean and Western medicine use after industrial accidents: A hurdle model analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Between 2018 and 2023, adjusted KM utilization remained unchanged, whereas WM visits declined. KM use was positively linked to being female and having occupational diseases. WM visits tended to rise with greater medical severity yet decreased as socioeconomic conditions improved. Still, the rise in total KM claims under WCI indicates a growing demand for conservative, pain-relieving musculoskeletal care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shared decision-making for early-stage breast cancer treatment: An evolutionary concept analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings provide a comprehensive conceptual framework to guide the development of detailed SDM guidelines tailored for early-stage breast cancer patients. Enhanced understanding of SDM can support nurses and healthcare professionals in facilitating collaborative and optimal decision-making processes within oncology care. Furthermore, this study lays the groundwork for developing measurement tools and disease-specific interventions to advance SDM implementation in early-stage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Job Experiences, Stakeholder Expectations, and Policy Challenges of Early-Career Social Workers in Hospice and Palliative Care: A Qualitative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides valuable foundational data and clinical preparation guidelines for early-career social workers entering the hospice and palliative care field. Furthermore, it offers evidence supporting the policy and institutional changes essential for the continued development of hospice and palliative care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spiritual Well-Being and Care Burden among Families of Patients with Terminal Cancer: Is Emotional Distress a Crucial Thing?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among family caregivers of patients with cancer, spiritual well-being reflects their care burden, in which emotional distress may play an important role.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Emergency Nurses' Life-Sustaining Treatment Withdrawal Knowledge, Role Perception, and Job Stress on Providing End-of-Life Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Despite the challenging environment of the emergency department, nurses who recognize their important role in the process of life-sustaining treatment withdrawal are more likely to provide high-quality EOL care. The perception of nurses' roles is especially influential on psychological care performance, and alternative approaches may be necessary for spiritual care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging artificial intelligence and machine learning in kinase inhibitor development: advances, challenges, and future prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein kinases are central regulators of cell signaling and play pivotal roles in a wide array of diseases, most notably cancer and autoimmune disorders. The clinical success of kinase inhibitors-such as imatinib and osimertinib-has firmly established kinases as valuable drug targets. However, the development of selective, potent inhibitors remains challenging due to the conserved nature of the ATP-binding site, off-target effects, resistance mutations, and patient-specific variability. Recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fit accuracy of complete crowns fabricated by generative artificial intelligence design: a comparative clinical study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The fit accuracy of crowns fabricated using generative artificial intelligence was equivalent to those produced using the manual-input computer design method when the margins were well defined. While marginal and occlusal discrepancies were within clinically acceptable range, careful attention must be given to automated design outcomes, considering various tooth preparation shapes, anatomical structures, and clinical variations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fatal yellow fever among captive non-human primates in southern Colombia, 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This report presents the first evidence of natural YFV infection in C. albifrons, A. fusciceps, and L. lagotricha under managed care conditions. The presence of YFV in endangered and vulnerable NHPs has critical implications for conservation and public health. Epizootic surveillance protocols must expand beyond Alouatta spp. to include a broader range of species and captive populations. Reinforced vector control, biosafety measures, and One Health-based interventions are urgently...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Role of Short-Chain Fatty Acid-Producing Gut Microbiota and Gut Microbial Dynamics in Patients with Hepatocellular Carcinoma Receiving Chemoembolization: A Prospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Specific SCFA-producing bacteria, such as Roseburia cecicola and Dialister_uc, were associated with treatment response and survival after TACE in patients with HCC, suggesting a potential prognostic role of the gut microbiome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural interaction explainable AI predicts drug response across cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Personalized treatment selection is crucial for cancer patients due to the high variability in drug response. While actionable mutations can increasingly inform treatment decisions, most therapies still rely on population-based approaches. Here, we introduce neural interaction explainable AI (NeurixAI), an explainable and highly scalable deep learning framework that models drug-gene interactions and identifies transcriptomic patterns linked with drug response. Trained on data from 546 646 drug...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ground Reaction Force Estimation via Time-aware Knowledge Distillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human gait analysis with wearable sensors has been widely used in various applications, such as daily life healthcare, rehabilitation, physical therapy, and clinical diagnostics and monitoring. In particular, ground reaction force (GRF) provides critical information about how the body interacts with the ground during locomotion. Although instrumented treadmills have been widely used as the gold standard for measuring GRF during walking, their lack of portability and high cost make them...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Model-based prediction of nanoparticle and dissolved form ratios using total concentration data: a case study of SNB-101]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Irinotecan (CPT-11), a topoisomerase I inhibitor, serves as a prodrug for SN-38, its active metabolite with significantly higher cytotoxic potency. Despite its clinical efficacy, irinotecan's therapeutic potential is limited by low fraction of conversion to SN-38, inefficient tumor targeting, and dose-limiting toxicities such as diarrhea and neutropenia. Nanoparticle-based formulations, such as SNB-101, offer a promising solution by encapsulating irinotecan and SN-38, enhancing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Application of probiotic bacteria in ginsenoside bioconversion and enhancing its health‑promoting benefits: a review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1007/s10068-024-01734-6.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Allium cepa</em> L. (onion) peel alleviates collagen and epinephrine-induced thrombosis in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thrombosis is a leading cause of cardiovascular diseases, driven by platelet aggregation, endothelial activation, and vascular occlusion. While Allium cepa L. (onion) is known for its health benefits, the antithrombotic potential of its peel remains underexplored. This study investigates the effects of Allium cepa L. peel extract (APE) in a rat model of collagen and epinephrine (CE)-induced thrombosis. High-performance liquid chromatography confirmed that APE contains high levels of quercetin, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety assessment of potential probiotic lactic acid bacteria strains <em>Pediococcus acidilactici</em> SY21 and <em>Pediococcus acidilactici</em> SY22]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pediococcus acidilactici SY21 and Pediococcus acidilactici SY22 exhibit anti-inflammatory activity; however, their safety has not been evaluated. The suitability as probiotic strains were evaluated by using phenotypic and genotypic analyses. Indole production, urease activity, mucin degradation, bile salt hydrolase activity, β-hemolysis, and gelatin liquefaction activity were not found. The minimum inhibitory concentrations of the nine antibiotics tested were below the cut-off values recommended...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ingredient-dependent water mobility and physicochemical properties of model tomato ketchup in relation to serum separation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study was performed to evaluate the effects of added ingredients such as modified starch (MS), xanthan gum (XG), sugar, (SU), salt (SA), and vinegar (VIN) on the water mobility and physicochemical properties of model tomato ketchup and to investigate the correlation between the obtained variables and serum separation. The type and concentration of ingredients added to the tomato paste (TP) had significant effects on experimental variables, including the serum separation rate, water...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved longevity and <em>in vivo</em> performance of neurotransmitter detection using 30 µm cone-shaped carbon fiber microelectrode]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fast Scan Cyclic Voltammetry (FSCV) is a widely used electrochemical technique to detect rapid extracellular dopamine transients in vivo. It employs carbon fiber microelectrodes (CFMEs), but conventional 7 µm diameter CFMEs often suffer from limited mechanical durability and reduced lifespan, hindering their use in chronic monitoring. To improve mechanical robustness and long-term functionality, we fabricated 30 µm diameter CFMEs and modified their geometry via electrochemical etching to form...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming Waste to Innovation: Sustainable Piezoelectric Properties of Pb(Ti <sub>0.52</sub> Zr <sub>0.48</sub> )O <sub>3</sub> with Recycled β‑PbO Massicot]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present an indigenous approach to enhancing the properties of Pb-(Zr(0.52)Ti(0.48))-O(3) by synthesizing it from β-PbO obtained from spent lead-acid batteries. Initially, β-PbO, orthorhombic massicot, was produced by two-step heating, and 99.9% lead powder was derived from recovered lead-acid batteries at 700 °C. The synthesized β-PbO was thoroughly analyzed using X-ray diffraction, field emission scanning electron microscopy, Fourier-transform infrared spectroscopy, X-ray...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Thermally Stable Ionic Liquid-Based Composite Polymer Electrolytes Enabled by In Situ Polymerization for Lithium-Ion Rechargeable Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Commercial lithium-ion batteries using organic solvent-based liquid electrolytes (LEs) face safety issues, including risks of fire and explosion. As a safer alternative, solid-state electrolytes are being extensively explored to replace these organic solvent-based LEs. Among various solid electrolyte options, polymer electrolytes offer advantages such as flexibility and ease of processing. However, they present challenges like low ionic conductivity at room temperature and reduced stability at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of an identity test for COVID-19 mRNA vaccines using SARS-CoV-2 NAT standard]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the development of messenger ribonucleic acid (mRNA) vaccines for the infectious novel coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2), further research on test methods is required to ensure their quality as well as rapid and effective approval for release to the market. During the current national lot release testing, identity tests cannot be conducted on other products using primers, probes, and in-house reference materials provided by the manufacturer and specific to one vaccine, because their sequences...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of data breach on IT investment at neighboring hospitals: Evidence from California Hospitals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Data breaches involving hacking/IT incidents at a neighboring hospital could nudge a hospital toward increased IT capital investment. This may result from neighboring hospitals acknowledging the need to take preventive measures. Hospitals should be strategically encouraged to reinforce cybersecurity capacity to minimize loss from future attacks.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation into the Therapeutic Efficacy and Inflammatory Modulatory Effects of the Combined Use of 0.01% Atropine Eye Drops and Orthokeratology Lenses in the Management of Myopia Among Adolescent Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The combination of 0.01% atropine eye drops with orthokeratology lenses is more effective than orthokeratology alone in controlling myopia progression and mitigating ocular surface inflammation in adolescents, without increasing adverse effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Urban Green Space and Acute Exacerbations of COPD in Korea: A Nationwide Study Using the NHIS-NSC Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Greater urban green space coverage may be associated with reduced AE-COPD risk. However, results should be interpreted with cautiously given model limitations and exploratory nature of subgroup findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human opsin restoration by histone methylation using methyltransferase fusion protein SETD7-dCas9]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epigenetic modulation enables precise gene regulation without altering DNA sequences. While histone acetylation has been widely utilized for gene activation, the therapeutic potential of histone methylation remains underexplored. In this study, we developed a new epigenetic activator by fusing the histone methyltransferase SETD7 to deactivated Cas9 (dCas9). The optimized SETD7-dCas9 fusion protein successfully induced H3K4 mono-methylation and activated transcription at multiple target loci. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research on ways to attract foreign patients to a Korean medicine clinic: a retrospective 2024 case study from Seoul]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This study aimed to analyze the clinical characteristics and treatment patterns of foreign patients visiting a single Korean medicine clinic to identify strategies for improving TKM-based medical tourism in South Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of electroacupuncture on restoration of traumatic vertebral compression fracture: two case studies and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vertebral compression fractures (VCFs) cause severe pain and functional impairments. Conventional treatments, including medication and vertebral augmentation, have limited efficacy and safety. Electroacupuncture (EA), which combines acupuncture with electrical stimulation, is a promising but under-studied approach for VCF management. This case report with a literature review presents two cases of traumatic VCF that were successfully treated with EA as well as a literature review on this topic....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pediatric Atopic Dermatitis Exhibits Distinctive Patterns in JAK/STAT Pathway Activation and CD6-ALCAM Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pediatric atopic dermatitis (AD) shows distinct clinical characteristics compared to adult AD, suggesting unique inflammatory profiles that may influence disease prognosis and treatment response. We aimed to identify unique immune signatures of pediatric AD and investigate the differences between pediatric and adult AD patients. Nine pediatric (6-16 years) and 12 adult (20-60 years) were enrolled. PBMCs were collected from AD patients and age- and sex-matched healthy controls (HCs)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct T Cell Dysregulation Reflects Disease Severity and Progression in Infantile Epileptic Spasms Syndrome and Lennox-Gastaut Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developmental and epileptic encephalopathies (DEEs), including Infantile Epileptic Spasms Syndrome (IESS) and Lennox-Gastaut Syndrome (LGS), are severe pediatric conditions characterized by profound developmental delays and treatment-resistant epilepsy. Although steroid therapies provide some clinical benefits, the underlying immunological mechanisms remain poorly understood. In this study, we performed comprehensive immune profiling using multi-parametric flow cytometry on PBMCs from IESS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spectrum of therapeutic options in hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is a prevalent cancer with high mortality rates globally. This review explores various HCC treatments, including surgical resection, liver transplantation, local ablation, and systemic therapies. With advancements in surgical techniques, local therapies, and immunotherapy, the treatment paradigm for HCC is rapidly evolving. Surgical resection remains the preferred first-line treatment for localized HCC with preserved liver function, offering significant survival...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reliability and validity of applying Kirkpatrick model for evaluating exercise rehabilitation program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to evaluate the reliability and validity of the Kirkpatrick four-level questionnaire-comprising reaction (R), learning (L), behavior (B), and results (Res)-in the context of an exercise rehabilitation program. A total of 141 university students, aged 21 to 25, participated in a 15-week exercise rehabilitation program. Intrarater reliability was assessed using the intraclass correlation coefficient (ICC) in a pre-posttest setup and analyzed through Bland-Altman plots. Convergent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In silico framework about prediction of collagen-derived matrikine generation and its ligand function binding to integrin [Formula: see text] for malignancy of colon cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colon cancer accounts for the second leading cause of cancer-associated death worldwide. Since the metastasis contributes to its malignancy, targeting the extracellular matrix (ECM) remodeling is critical for its therapy. Most research had focused on the native form of the structural ECM proteins, termed core matrisomes, to find out the relationship of the TME to colon cancer progression. This study computationally predicted the generation and function of their bioactive fragments, termed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cancer-metastasis-on-a-chip reveals efficacy of bevacizumab and siRNA in overcoming carboplatin resistance in SKOV3 ovarian cancer within a fibrotic metastatic microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microfluidic platforms have emerged as powerful tools for investigating complex interactions between cells and their microenvironment. Conventional in vitro cancer models often fail to accurately replicate the complexities of the in vivo tumor microenvironment. In contrast, cancer-metastasis-on-a-chip models integrate the benefits of three-dimensional cell cultures with microfluidic technology, providing more physiologically relevant platforms for studying cancer biology and improving precision...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-Temperature Photocrystallization of Atomic Layer Deposition-Processed Tin Oxide for Highly Efficient and Flexible Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atomic layer deposition (ALD) enables an excellent surface coverage and uniformity in the preparation of large-area metal-oxide thin films. In particular, ALD-processed SnO(2) has demonstrated great potential as an electron transport layer in flexible perovskite solar cells (PSCs) and tandem modules. However, the poor electrical conductivities and surface wettabilities of amorphous SnO(2) remain critical challenges for commercialization. In this study, a low-temperature and rapid crystallization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surface Reconstruction in Quasi-2D Perovskite Films Treated with Cesium Halide Nanocrystals: Halide Exchange or Phase Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The formation of heterostructure interfaces from quantum dots (or nanocrystals) and lower-dimensional (2D or quasi-2D) materials enables interfacial and optoelectronic property tuning. However, this strategy has not been sufficiently characterized, for example, the application of cesium halide nanocrystals to quasi-2D perovskite structures is underexplored, and the mechanisms of the resulting structural modifications and specific nanocrystal roles are not fully understood. Herein, the effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perovskite Quantum Dot-Enhanced Silicon Photodetectors for High-Performance Infrared Sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infrared photodetectors are crucial for autonomous driving, providing reliable object detection under challenging lighting conditions. However, conventional silicon-based devices are limited in their responsivity beyond 1100 nm. Here, a scallop-structured silicon photodetector integrated with tin-substituted perovskite quantum dots (PQDs) that effectively extends infrared detection is demonstrated. The scallop nanowire design creates resonant light trapping, while the PQD layer enhances charge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term impact of growth hormone therapy on mortality and type 2 diabetes in Prader-Willi syndrome: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GHT was not a direct predictor of mortality in PWS, which was instead influenced by comorbidities. However, its prolonged use was linked to increased T2DM. These findings support individualized risk assessment and metabolic monitoring in patients with PWS receiving GHT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SKKU, SNU, Yonsei University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-Effectiveness of Obesity Treatments: Glucagon-Like Peptide-1 Receptor Agonists, Endoscopic Sleeve Gastroplasty, and Metabolic/Bariatric Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity represents a major global health challenge, requiring interventions that are both effective and economically sustainable. This review examines the cost-effectiveness of commonly discussed treatment options: glucagon-like peptide-1 receptor agonists (GLP-1 RAs), endoscopic sleeve gastroplasty (ESG), and metabolic/bariatric surgery (MBS). We synthesized evidence from published clinical studies and economic analyses, comparing incremental cost-effectiveness ratios (ICERs) and cost per...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amino Acid Metabolite Profiling for Predicting and Understanding the Metabolic Effects of Metabolic and Bariatric Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic and bariatric surgery induces metabolic benefits beyond weight loss, including improved insulin sensitivity, type 2 diabetes (T2D) remission, and reduced inflammation. Recent metabolomics research highlights amino acid metabolites-branched-chain amino acids, aromatic amino acids, and tryptophan-derived compounds-as key biomarkers for predicting surgical outcomes. Elevated preoperative levels of isoleucine, phenylalanine, levodopa, and 3-hydroxyanthranilic acid are associated with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bariatric Surgery in Patients With Prader-Willi Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prader-Willi Syndrome (PWS) is a genetic disorder characterized by insatiable hyperphagia, resulting in severe, early-onset obesity that is often refractory to conventional management. The associated comorbidities and reduced life expectancy in PWS present a significant therapeutic challenge. This review synthesizes the existing literature on the controversial role, outcomes, and complexities of bariatric surgery in patients with PWS. In recent decades, bariatric surgical techniques have evolved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obesity and Venous Thromboembolism: Mechanisms, Clinical Implications, and Prevention Strategies With a Focus on Bariatric Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Venous thromboembolism (VTE), comprising deep vein thrombosis (DVT) and pulmonary thromboembolism (PTE), constitutes a significant global health concern due to its substantial morbidity and mortality, especially among hospitalized and surgical individuals. DVT commonly presents in the lower extremities with symptoms such as calf pain, swelling potentially spreading to the ankle and foot, localized warmth, and skin discoloration. PTE, arising from acute pulmonary artery obstruction by a thrombus,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Significance of Early Postoperative Weight Loss in Bariatric Surgery: A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early postoperative weight loss (EWL) after bariatric surgery is a critical as a powerful predictor of long-term weight loss and metabolic outcomes. This narrative review shows evidence from recent studies examining the biological, behavioral, and clinical implications of EWL in patients undergoing various bariatric procedures. We discuss the hormonal and metabolic adaptations that occur in the first months after surgery, the psychosocial and behavioral factors influencing postoperative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ECG-GraphNet: Advanced arrhythmia classification based on graph convolutional networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our novel approach and comprehensive analysis underscore the potential advantages of ECG-GraphNet in clinical diagnosis and monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hand-Assisted Laparoscopic Colectomy for Complicated Colorectal Disease in Emergency Settings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HAL appears to be a feasible option in emergency colectomy for ASA I-III patients and may be beneficial in specific surgical practice contexts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibacterial and anticancer activity of multifunctional iron-based magnetic nanoparticles against urinary tract infection and cystitis-related bacterial strains and bladder cancer cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FCF NPs effectively induce cancer cell death, show excellent photodynamic anticancer efficacy against BC cells, and exhibit potent antibacterial activity against uropathogenic bacterial strains via PDT, exhibiting high potential for application in versatile imaging-based diagnostics and therapeutics in BC treatment and urinary tract infection management. However, prior to their clinical application, in vivo studies using animal models are required to validate these biological and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subsidence reduction effect of transforaminal lumbar interbody fusion (TLIF) with upper and lower open windows modified with lattice structure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cage subsidence is a common complication following transforaminal lumbar interbody fusion (TLIF) that can lead to poor clinical outcomes, including recurrent pain and segmental instability. Conventional TLIF cage designs often fail to distribute stress evenly, increasing the risk of endplate damage and subsequent subsidence. This study aims to evaluate the effect of a modified TLIF cage with upper and lower open windows (lattice structure) in reducing cage subsidence in patients with lumbar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unobtrusive continuous hemodynamic monitoring method using processed heart sound signals in patients undergoing surgery: a proof of concept study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heart sounds provide essential information about cardiac function; however, their clinical meaning and potential for minimally invasive hemodynamic monitoring in real world clinical settings remain underexplored. This study assessed relationships between heart sound indices and hemodynamic parameters during liver transplant surgery. Data from 80 liver transplant recipients were analyzed across five procedural phases (approximately 1,680k cardiac beats). The heart sound indices (S1 amplitude, S2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abnormal theta- and gamma-band cortical activities during visuospatial attention in idiopathic REM sleep behavior disorder patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose: Idiopathic rapid eye movement (REM) sleep behavior disorder (iRBD) is a sleep disorder considered to be a prodromal stage of neurodegeneration disease and is often accompanied by cognitive impairments. The purpose of this study was to investigate spatiotemporal characteristics of abnormal oscillatory cortical activity associated with dysfunction of visuospatial attention in iRBD based on an explainable machine learning approach. Methods: EEGs were recorded from 49 iRBD patients and 49...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dendritic Cells Induce Clec5a-mediated Immune Modulation in MPTP-induced Parkinson's Disease Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that Clec5a plays a critical role in the immunomodulatory function of tolDCs. The administration of Clec5a-expressing DCs effectively reduced neuroinflammation and protected dopaminergic neurons in an MPTP-induced PD model. Therefore, Clec5a-expressing tolDCs may demonstrate therapeutic potential by managing PD symptoms by suppressing inflammatory responses associated with neurodegeneration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut microbial metabolites link dietary history to appetite regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All metazoan guts harbor commensal communities, from a dozen bacterial species in Drosophila to hundreds in humans. Here, we condition flies with diets containing varying levels of protein and sugar to investigate the impact of dietary history on the interaction between commensal gut bacteria and feeding adaptation in Drosophila. We find that appetite increases with dietary protein, dependent on total gut bacteria content, and enhanced by a drug that promotes the growth of short-chain fatty acid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of undifferentiated carcinoma of the salivary gland: clinicopathological and immunohistochemical analyses in comparison with lymphoepithelial carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study proposes reclassifying these poorly differentiated or high-grade salivary gland carcinomas as UDC based on their indeterminate differentiation and IHC profiles. This may lead to a clearer diagnostic category and enhance our understanding of these high-grade tumors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variation in mitotic counting and risk classification practices for gastrointestinal stromal tumors: a survey of pathologists in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative outcomes of excision and active surveillance for cervical intraepithelial neoplasia 2 in women under 35: a single institutional retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: There was no significant difference between the excisional procedure and active surveillance in terms of achieving normalized cytology from CIN 2. Active surveillance is a feasible option for managing CIN 2 in women under 35 years of age.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating the impact of hyperbilirubinemia on cognitive dysfunction in adult zebrafish: an in vivo model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Transient bilirubin elevation alone was sufficient to impair cognition and disrupt BBB function in adult zebrafish, even in the absence of overt liver damage or systemic inflammation. Although inflammation is more pronounced during liver injury, bilirubin itself may exert direct neurovascular effects. These results support considering bilirubin levels as a modifiable risk factor for perioperative neurocognitive dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Donor-derived cell-free DNA in solid organ transplantation: analytical considerations, diagnostic performance, and clinical interpretation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Donor-derived cell-free DNA (dd-cfDNA) has emerged as a valuable noninvasive biomarker for detecting allograft injury in solid organ transplantation. It is released into the bloodstream from the transplanted organ as a result of cell injury and immune activation, with baseline levels influenced by organ type, tissue turnover, and posttransplant physiological changes. Several analytical platforms are available, including quantitative polymerase chain reaction (PCR), digital droplet PCR, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urinary mRNA biomarkers for the noninvasive diagnosis of calcineurin inhibitor toxicity in kidney transplant recipients with graft dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Urinary mRNA levels of LTF, NNMT, and HIF1A may serve as useful biomarkers for identifying CNI toxicity in kidney transplant recipients with graft dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adiponectin as a Predictor of Metabolic Dysfunction-Associated Steatotic Liver Disease and Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease: A 17-Year Korean Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Different adiponectin levels revealed distinct risks. This study emphasizes adiponectin's potential as a predictive indicator of MASLD and NAFLD, stressing the need for further investigation across diverse demographic groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[APC/C-CDH1 suppresses AROS-mediated protection against DNA damage-induced senescence by ubiquitination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anaphase-promoting complex/cyclosome (APC/C) regulates the cell cycle by destruction of target proteins ubiquitination. However, understanding the control of APC/C has remained elusive. We identify APC2, the catalytic core subunit of APC/C, as a binding partner of active regulator of SIRT1 (AROS). Subsequent immunoprecipitation assays confirm the interaction in vivo. We reveal that AROS competes with APC11 for APC2 binding, thereby impeding the destruction of Cyclin B1. By contrast, the APC/C...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional analysis of secreted tissue inhibitor of metalloproteinases-1 from adult human neural stem cells (ahNSCs) for regeneration and neuroprotection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The adult human neural stem cell (ahNSC)-conditioned medium (CM) contains various secreted factors that promote tissue repair and neuroprotection. This study aimed to identify the key secreted proteins in ahNSC-CM and investigate the role of tissue inhibitor of metalloproteinases-1 (TIMP-1) in wound healing, angiogenesis, and neuroprotection against oxygenglucose deprivation. Cytokine array and liquid chromatography- tandem mass spectrometry analysis of ahNSC-CM revealed that monocyte...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cdk1-dependent lamin aggregation underlies oxidative stress-induced nuclear shape abnormalities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Altered nuclear morphology, one of the characteristics of cancer cells, is often indicative of tumor prognosis. While reactive oxygen species (ROS) are known to induce nuclear morphology changes, mechanisms underlying these effects remain elusive, particularly regarding nuclear assembly. We hypothesized that mitotic cells might exhibit increased susceptibility to ROSinduced nuclear deformation due to the dynamic nature of nuclear envelope during mitosis, i.e., disassembly and reassembly....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New insights to B cell tolerance involving the mechanosensitive ion channel Piezo1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[B cell tolerance is critical for preventing autoimmunity, yet the mechanisms by which B cells discriminate self from non-self antigens remain incompletely understood. While early findings emphasize the role of classical antigen-mediated BCR signaling strength by varying antigen formats, emerging evidence highlights the importance of mechanical cues during antigen recognition. This review explores how mechanosensitive ion channels, particularly Piezo1, contribute to B cell activation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in single-cell bioinformatics for inferring higher-order chromatin contact maps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA, a large molecule located in the nucleus, carries essential genetic information, including gene loci and cis-regulatory elements. Despite its extensive length, DNA is compactly stored within the limited space of the nucleus due to its hierarchical three-dimensional (3D) organization. In this structure, DNA is organized into territories known as topologically associated domains (TADs). Within each TAD, numerous chromatin loops link promoters and enhancers across the genome. These loops and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment Persistence After Major Cardiovascular Events in Psoriasis: A Retrospective Cohort Study Comparing Biologic, Systemic, and Phototherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patients with psoriasis experience significantly higher cardiovascular morbidity compared to the general population. Although certain psoriasis treatments may confer cardioprotective effects, current clinical guidelines addressing treatment continuation following major adverse cardiovascular events (MACE) are lacking. Therefore, we conducted a retrospective cohort study using Korean health insurance data (January 2008-October 2021) to examine treatment modifications after MACE in patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Physical Activity on Medical Expenses among Individuals with Obesity in Korea: Insights from a Nationwide Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this nationwide study of individuals with obesity, lower physical activity levels were associated with increased medical expenses. Consistently engaging in physical activity might significantly lower medical expenses, particularly among elderly people and individuals with comorbidities. These findings highlight the importance of promoting This is a PDF file of an article accepted, but it is not yet the definitive version of record. sustained physical activity as a strategy for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustaining Progress of the Journal of Korean Neurosurgical Society Amidst the Crisis in Korean Healthcare System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The 2024 Journal Citation Reports (JCR) reveal that the impact factor (IF) for the Journal of Korean Neurosurgical Society (JKNS) has risen to 1.7, an increase from 1.4 in 2023. Meanwhile, Republic of Korea has been in turmoil in healthcare system since February 2024, provoked by government's sudden and drastic policy to increase medical school admissions. This situation has profoundly impacted medical research activities, in addition to clinical practice. There is concern about whether the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of intravenous administration of high-dose selenium for preventing chemotherapy-induced peripheral neuropathy in gastric cancer patients receiving adjuvant oxaliplatin and capecitabine after gastrectomy: a retrospective pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High-dose intravenous selenium appears to be a safe and potentially effective intervention for reducing paresthesia associated with oxaliplatin-based chemotherapy. Further large-scale prospective studies are warranted to validate these findings and establish optimal dosing guidelines.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40916401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sign-reversed anomalous Nernst effect with matched Seebeck coefficient in lanthanide-iron alloys for the direct sensing of heat flux]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heat flux sensors based on the anomalous Nernst effect (ANE) have emerged as a promising solution for achieving thin and flexible designs. ANE-based heat flux sensors typically employ thermopile structures composed of two ANE materials with opposite signs, connected in series to enhance sensing performance. However, a mismatch in the Seebeck coefficient between the two ANE materials causes a considerable offset voltage due to the Seebeck effect (SE) under oblique heat flux. This parasitic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Survey on sampling conditioned brain images and imaging measures with generative models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Generative models have become innovative tools across various domains, including neuroscience, where they enable the synthesis of realistic brain imaging data that captures complex anatomical and functional patterns. These models, such as Variational Autoencoders (VAEs), Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs), and diffusion models, leverage deep learning to generate high-quality brain images while maintaining biological and clinical relevance. These models address critical challenges in brain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of Crohn's-disease-associated anal canal cancer with p53-positive dysplasia: suggesting insights to stepwise carcinogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crohn's-disease-associated colorectal cancer, where chronic inflammation increases the risk of cancer development, is less common than other types of colorectal cancer. Pathological analyses of Crohn's-disease-associated colorectal cancer are limited. Herein, we present a case of Crohn's disease-associated colorectal cancer, suggesting stepwise carcinogenesis from the chronic inflammatory mucosa. A man in his 40s had a 28-year history of Crohn's disease with perianal involvement for over 20...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of renal effects between sacubitril/valsartan and thiazide diuretics among patients with uncontrolled hypertension and chronic kidney disease in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compared to the addition of thiazide diuretics, the transition to sacubitril/valsartan resulted in greater BP reduction and more favorable changes in uric acid, HbA(1c), and eGFR in patients with CKD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-sequential prediction of postoperative complications after gastric cancer surgery using machine learning: a multicenter cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Hour-based ML models incorporating comprehensive perioperative data predict post-gastric cancer surgery complications with high accuracy and time-sequential capability, potentially aiding clinical decision-making and improving outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of automatic staplers for renal artery division in laparoscopic donor nephrectomy: impact of vessel diameter on hemostatic outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Automatic staplers are effective for renal artery management in laparoscopic donor nephrectomy; however, when used on smaller arteries, supplemental hemostatic measures may be required. Advancing stapler technology and careful device selection are crucial for improving surgical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An electrochemiluminescence device powered by streaming potential for the detection of amines in flowing solution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The research and implementation of portable and low-cost analytical devices that possess high reproducibility and ease of operation is still a challenging task, and a growing field of importance, within the analytical research. Herein, we report the concept, design and optimization of a microfluidic device based on electrochemiluminescence (ECL) detection that can be potentially operated without electricity for analytical purposes. The device functions exploiting the concept of streaming...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic value of leaflet coaptation gap in transcatheter edge-to-edge repair for functional mitral regurgitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CG was associated with less MR reduction but with no clear difference in adverse clinical outcomes after TEER. Similar outcomes between residual MR grade 2+ and ≤1+ in CG patients highlight the importance of procedural endpoint in anatomically challenging cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of concomitant methotrexate and predictors of remission in Janus kinase inhibitor therapy for rheumatoid arthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Concomitant MTX provided potential advantages in terms of early disease control in JAK inhibitor therapy for RA, particularly in patients with active disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the genetic basis of medication-related osteonecrosis of the jaw: A systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Medication-related osteonecrosis of the jaw (MRONJ) is an adverse event often associated with the use of antiresorptive drugs. This systematic review aims to identify genes and their polymorphisms associated with the risk of developing MRONJ in patients with oncological or skeletal-related diseases treated with antiresorptive drugs. A systematic literature review was conducted in accordance with PRISMA guidelines. Three electronic databases (PubMed, Scopus, and Web of Science) were searched for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and magnitude of perceived dual-task difficulties in people with multiple sclerosis: an international study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DT difficulties were already perceived in almost half of the mildly disabled patients and increased with disability severity. The DTQ, DTSL, and DIDA-Q show discriminative ability, with the highest AUC and ES observed in DIDA-Q. The DTQ, DTSL, and DIDA-Q can clearly be used in pwMS for clinical and research purposes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rostro-caudal TMS mapping of immediate transcranial evoked potentials reveals a pericentral crescendo-decrescendo pattern]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: We recently demonstrated that single-pulse TMS of the primary sensorimotor hand area (SM1(HAND)) elicits an immediate transcranial evoked potential (iTEP). This iTEP response appears within 2-8 ms post-TMS, featuring high-frequency peaks superimposed on a slow positive wave. Here, we used a linear TMS-EEG mapping approach to characterize the rostro-caudal iTEP expression and compared it to that of motor-evoked potentials (MEPs).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residual Hindfoot Valgus Alignment Detected by True Mechanical Axis Is Associated with Poorer Clinical Outcomes after Total Knee Arthroplasty: The Role of Ankle Osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ankle OA was significantly associated with residual hindfoot valgus alignment based on HTC. Although ankle OA did not directly affect clinical outcomes, residual valgus alignment and older age were independently associated with worse postoperative WOMAC scores.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amorphous MoS<sub>3</sub> Derived from (NH<sub>4</sub>)<sub>2</sub>MoS<sub>4</sub>: Structural Insights and Applications in All-Solid-State Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amorphous molybdenum polysulfides (a-MoS(x)) have attracted considerable attention because of their unique physical and chemical properties, which enable their use in a wide range of applications including energy-storage materials. Among various synthesis methods, thermal decomposition provides an effective route for synthesizing a-MoS(x). In particular, amorphous molybdenum trisulfide (a-MoS(3)) prepared via thermal decomposition has emerged as a promising active material for energy-storage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Lemborexant-Based Sleep Medication Formulary on Benzodiazepine Reduction and Clinical Outcomes: A Single-Center Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Benzodiazepine and non-benzodiazepine hypnotics (Z-drugs) are known risk factors for adverse events, including delirium and falls. Although formularies are intended to promote appropriate prescribing, few comprehensive studies have assessed their clinical impact in the context of sleep medications. This study aimed to evaluate changes in hypnotic prescribing patterns and associated clinical outcomes following the implementation of a sleep medication formulary. A psychiatric liaison team...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationship between triceps surae muscle-tendon morphology and shear modulus across passive ankle range of motion in cerebral palsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alterations in skeletal muscle morphology and composition are critical factors in cerebral palsy (CP), including changes in passive stiffness and in belly and fascicle lengths. In this study, we quantified the relative contributions of muscle and tendon to passive stiffness across the ankle range of motion in individuals with CP and typically developing (TD) peers. We also investigated morphological factors underlying increased muscle stiffness. Twelve individuals with CP and 12 age-matched TD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the effectiveness of ChemoNurse: A mobile chemotherapy drug guide for cancer nurses - A randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The ChemoNurse mobile application significantly improved cancer nurses' knowledge and professional attitudes regarding chemotherapy administration. These findings highlight the potential of mobile technologies as effective, scalable tools for enhancing clinical competence and supporting safe, evidence-based cancer nursing practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Natural Inhibitors Against Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome Coronavirus 2 Main Protease From Three Vietnamese Bryophytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Erythrodontium julaceum, Marchantia polymorpha, and Plagiochila bantamensis are widely distributed bryophytes in Vietnam. However, comprehensive chemical and biological data on their composition remain limited. Bio-guided isolation based on severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) M^(pro) inhibition was applied to these species, resulting in the identification of 23 metabolites. Compound P8 is a new natural compound. Subsequently, the SARS-CoV-2 M^(pro) inhibition of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40921028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protective Role of Apelin in a Mouse Model of Post-Intensive Care Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Post-Intensive Care Syndrome (PICS) is a serious condition involving physical weakness, depression, and cognitive impairment that develop during or after an intensive care unit (ICU) stay, often resulting in long-term declines in quality of life. Patients with acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS) and severe COVID-19 are at particularly high risk, yet the molecular mechanisms underlying PICS remain poorly understood. Here, we identify impaired Apelin-APJ signaling as a potential contributor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes following off-Pump coronary artery bypass grafting using only three in situ arterial grafts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: OPCAB using only in situ skeletonized BITA and rGEA grafts achieved excellent early angiographic patency and long-term outcomes, suggesting that applying our criteria for rGEA use might help improve the long-term outcomes of CABG.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Published Population Pharmacokinetic Models of Imatinib Perform Poorly on TDM Data from Pediatric Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Current models fail to accurately predict imatinib plasma concentrations in our real-world dataset, especially for children. Future pharmacokinetic studies should focus on developing better models for pediatric populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recurrence associated with 2-year visual acuity after subretinal tissue plasminogen activator for submacular hemorrhage in neovascular age-related macular degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study suggests that recurrence was a robust determinant of poor 2-year BCVA after vitrectomy with subretinal tPA injection for SMH complicating nAMD and that subretinal tPA injection was effective in most cases, without recurrence. Our findings highlight the importance of establishing methods for preventing and controlling recurrence to maintain long-term BCVA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Timing of surgery and outcomes in patients with congenital pulmonary airway malformation: a national inpatient database study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In-hospital mortality and morbidity were comparable among the different timings of surgery for CPAM. Preoperative bacterial pneumonia and thoracoscopic surgery could be risk factors for long duration of anesthesia but not for long hospital stay.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40920238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reassignment of the vibronic structure in the absorption spectrum of carbon cluster anion C6- exhibiting fast radiative cooling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Linear carbon cluster anions, such as C6-, have been considered to be promising candidate interstellar molecules. Recent experiments have demonstrated that in a collision-free vacuum environment, C6- exhibits fast radiative cooling from its highly vibrationally excited states through inverse internal conversion (IIC). Since IIC is driven by vibronic coupling, the understanding of vibronic structures of C6- is of theoretical significance. Here, we utilize time-dependent density functional theory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ball Milling Approaches for Biomass-Derived Nanocarbon in Advanced Sustainable Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The synthesis of biomass-derived nanocarbons via ball milling has emerged as an innovative, sustainable, and cost-effective strategy in the field of nanotechnology. This review comprehensively explores the principles, mechanisms, and process parameters that influence the production of high-quality nanocarbons from biomass using ball milling. This process efficiently transforms biomass residues into nanoscale carbon, including graphene, carbon nanotubes, and nanofibers, with tunable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EUS-Guided Gallbladder Drainage Using a Lumen-Apposing Metal Stent for Acute Cholecystitis in a High-Risk Elderly Patient]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Binder-Free Nickel Borate/Nickel Hydroxide Bifunctional Catalyst for Coupled Nitrate Reduction and Glycerol Oxidation Toward Sustainable Ammonia Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The accumulation of nitrate (NO(3)^(-)) from agricultural runoff poses a growing threat to ecosystems and public health. Converting nitrate into ammonia (NH(3)) through the electrochemical nitrate reduction reaction (NO(3)RR) offers a promising strategy to mitigate environmental contamination while creating a sustainable circular route to fertilizer production. However, achieving high NH(3) production and energy efficiency remains challenging. Here, we report a binder-free mixed-phase nickel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multimodal Observational Case-Control Study Exploring Gut Microbiota-Hippocampus Alterations in Individuals With High Positive Schizotypy From the General Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our results suggest a potential relationship between aberrant gut microbial composition and hippocampal alterations in people with positive schizotypy from the general population. Our findings inform future large-scale research that further explores specific mechanisms of gut microbiome-hippocampus interactions in psychosis and the potential of tailored microbial interventions targeting hippocampal-mediated symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peginterferon-alpha-2a add-on to treatment with siRNA JNJ-73763989 in virologically suppressed chronic hepatitis B: The phase II PENGUIN study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Treatment with JNJ-3989 ± bersacapavir + NA and PegIFN-α2a was generally well tolerated. Most patients had pronounced HBsAg reductions from baseline, no additional benefit from PegIFN-α2a, and did not achieve functional cure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40919077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging HER2 Targeting Immunotherapy for Cholangiocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cholangiocarcinoma (CCA) is a fatal bile duct malignancy. CCA is intrinsically resistant to standard chemotherapy, responds poorly to it, and has a poor prognosis. Effective treatments for cholangiocarcinoma remain elusive, and a breakthrough in CCA treatment is still awaited. The human epidermal growth factor receptor 2 (HER2) plays an oncogenic role by promoting an aggressive cancer phenotype through multiple pathways. While HER2 has shown increasing potential as an effective target for breast...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ECM-Preserving Decellularization of Dermis via Subtle Cell Membrane Disruption Induced by Subcritical Dimethyl Ether]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decellularized tissues are used as biomaterials for transplantation. Many decellularized tissues in clinical applications are prepared using surfactants; however, we have developed a new decellularization method that uses subcritical dimethyl ether (DME) instead of surfactants. Subcritical DME perfusion is usually used for lipid extraction; therefore, by perfusing tissues with subcritical DME, phospholipid cell membranes may be destroyed. DME vaporizes at room temperature and pressure,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biological Evaluation of Cleavable Linkers in Exatecan-Based Antibody-Drug Conjugates: A Comparative Study of DXd and Exo-Linker Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs) represent a transformative class of cancer therapies that combine the specificity of monoclonal antibodies with the cytotoxicity of potent drug payloads. This study presents the development and evaluation of a novel linker platform designed to enhance ADC stability and pharmacokinetics by addressing the limitations associated with traditional cleavable linkers. Using trastuzumab conjugated with a payload linker consisting of this platform and exo-EVC-Exatecan...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metal-organic framework-injectable hydrogel hybrid scaffolds promote accelerated angiogenesis for <em>in vivo</em> tissue engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The application of nanoscale metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) in tissue engineering is receiving increased attention. As three-dimensional scaffolding materials that provide an appropriate extracellular microenvironment supporting the survival, proliferation, and organization of cells play a key role in vivo tissue engineering, hybridization of nanoscale MOFs with bulk hydrogels has led to the development of nanoscale MOF-combined hydrogels. However, development of nanoscale MOF-combined hydrogel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural representations of visual statistical learning based on temporal duration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Time perception is an essential aspect of daily life, and transitional probabilities can be learned based on temporal durations that are independent of individual objects. Previous studies on temporal and spatial visual statistical learning (VSL) have shown that the hippocampus and lateral occipital cortex are engaged in learning visual regularities. However, it remains unclear whether VSL on temporal duration unlinked to object identity is represented in brain regions involved in VSL and object...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robust backup support technique with dual guide extension catheters: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Guide extension catheters are specially designed for percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI) to enhance backup support of the guide catheter by providing coaxial alignment, thereby allowing deep intubation of the catheter. We have developed an innovative auxiliary support technique utilizing a dual guide extension catheter system, designed to enhance safety and facilitate deep coronary artery access.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leukocyte recruitment in flavivirus-induced encephalitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flaviviruses are capable of causing a myriad of diseases in humans, including viral encephalitis. This condition involves complex interactions between the virus, resident cells of the central nervous system and leukocytes recruited to the brain. We reviewed the mechanisms underlying leukocyte recruitment during flavivirus-induced encephalitis with a focus on the role of various chemoattractants and adhesion molecules. We discuss how these molecules orchestrate the migration of peripheral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40918112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut dysbiosis is linked to severe steatosis and enhances its diagnostic performance in MASLD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Gut microbiota composition and dysbiosis (defined as Bact2-enterotype) are distinctly associated with steatosis severity in MASLD/MetS. Patient stratification by microbiota composition enhances the diagnostic classification of severe steatosis in MASLD, suggesting a potential for personalised interventions in patients with microbiota dysbiosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acceptability and efficacy of a smartphone application intervention for mental health care based on interpersonal psychotherapy for improving depression symptoms in prenatal women: Protocol for a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Perinatal depression is a predominant and serious condition that adversely affects prenatal and postpartum women and their children. Prenatal depression is a notable predictor of postpartum depression, highlighting the need for mental health care during pregnancy. Therefore, we developed an innovative smartphone application based on interpersonal psychotherapy (IPT) to improve depressive symptoms in women in the perinatal period (i.e., from pregnancy through the first year...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40917811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250909034144&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>