<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:45:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systemic control of HNF1B-driven redox homeostasis by N6-adenosine methylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transcription factors are key regulators of gene expression and play essential roles in various diseases, yet their lack of small-molecule binding pockets makes them difficult to target with drugs. Internal RNA modifications, such as N6-methyladenosine, are widespread in mammalian cells, but how m6A-encoded epitranscriptomic information influences transcription factor activity and cellular function remains incompletely understood. Here, we demonstrate that m6A methylation directly regulates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Directed evolution on compact landing pads yields highly efficient recombinases for large DNA integration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Site-specific DNA recombinases are powerful tools for genome engineering. The recent convergence of DNA recombinase-mediated technology with prime editing has established a promising new frontier for large-scale genomic integration. However, this strategy has limitations, including low intrinsic catalytic efficiency of DNA recombination enzymes and inefficiency of their long DNA landing pad insertions. To overcome these challenges, we developed a novel directed evolution strategy using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protein structure-informed bacteriophage genome annotation with Phold]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacteriophage (phage) genome annotation is essential for understanding their functional potential and suitability for use as therapeutic agents. Here, we introduce Phold, an annotation framework utilizing protein structural information that combines the ProstT5 protein language model and structural alignment tool Foldseek. Phold assigns annotations using a database of over 1.36 million predicted phage protein structures with high-quality functional labels. Benchmarking reveals that Phold...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure and function of the RNA polymerase complex of Borna disease virus, a nuclear-replicating non-segmented negative-strand RNA virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Borna disease virus 1 (BoDV-1) is a non-segmented negative-strand (NNS) RNA virus that uniquely replicates in the nucleus of mammalian host cells, in contrast to most NNS RNA viruses that replicate in the cytoplasm. The mechanisms underlying nuclear replication of BoDV-1 and related bornaviruses with their RNA-dependent RNA polymerase (RdRp) complexes remain poorly understood. Here, we report the 2.8 Å cryo-EM structure of the BoDV-1 RdRp complex, comprising the large (L) protein and tetrameric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Mobility and Health-Related Quality of Life Between Hemiarthroplasty and Total Hip Arthroplasty for Femoral Neck Fractures in the Elderly: A Post Hoc Analysis of a Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: THA may yield a higher probability of independent mobility recovery and better postoperative HRQoL than HA in elderly patients with FNFs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERK phosphorylates HNRNPF to promote the proliferation and suppress the differentiation of embryonic stem cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mitogen-activated extracellular signal-regulated kinase/extracellular signal-regulated kinase (MEK/ERK) signaling plays a dual role in regulating the self-renewal and differentiation of embryonic stem cells (ESCs). How MEK/ERK promotes ESC self-renewal remains elusive, while the mechanisms for MEK/ERK to stimulate ESC differentiation have been investigated extensively. Here, we demonstrated that ERK2 phosphorylates heterogenous nuclear ribonucleoprotein F (HNRNPF) on Ser346 and Tyr356....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Specific killing and resensitization of pathogenic Escherichia coli strains carrying blaCTX-M-15 β-lactamase using targeted-antibacterial-plasmids (TAPs)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Targeted-Antibacterial-Plasmids (TAPs) offer a precise approach to combat multidrug-resistant bacteria by selectively removing resistant strains while preserving commensals. Here, we assess TAPs that deliver CRISPR/Cas systems via conjugation to kill or resensitize extended-spectrum β-lactamase (ESBL)-producing Escherichia coli carrying the blaCTX-M-15 gene. We systematically tested multiple variables in the TAP approach, including two commensal E. coli donors, three distinct helper plasmids...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Division of labor in trypanosome RNA processing and export through expanded Mex67 paralogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In animals and fungi, bulk messenger RNA (mRNA) export to the cytoplasm is mediated by the Mex67/Mtr2 (NXF1/NXT1) heterodimer and driven by an ATP-dependent remodeling machinery on the cytoplasmic side of nuclear pore complexes, the exclusive gateways of nucleocytoplasmic transport. Uniquely, we show that trypanosomes have three distinct Mex67 paralogs (TbMex67, TbMex67b, and TbMex67L); each having a different non-redundant role in ribosomal RNA (rRNA) processing and mRNA export. Specifically,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microenvironment-aware spatial modeling for accurate inference of cell identity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spatial omics technologies enable the simultaneous measurement of molecular features within their spatial context, providing unprecedented insights into cellular organization and tissue architecture. The advent of single-cell resolution platforms has further enhanced our ability to uncover microenvironment-dependent cell states. While numerous computational methods have been developed for spatial omics analysis, most focus on spatial domain detection rather than on resolving cell identities....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond DNA binding: single C2H2 zinc fingers with adjacent β-strands mediate dimerization in Drosophila transcription factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[C2H2 proteins, characterized by DNA-binding C2H2-type zinc finger domains, constitute the largest group of transcription factors. In addition to binding DNA, C2H2 domains can mediate protein-protein interactions, facilitating the oligomerization of C2H2 proteins. In this study, we identified eight C2H2 proteins in the Drosophila genome that feature a unique single C2H2 domain containing a conserved "CGxΦ" motif. Yeast two-hybrid assays, size-exclusion chromatography coupled with multi-angle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SCALE: unsupervised multiscale domain identification in spatial omics data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-cell spatial transcriptomics enables precise mapping of cellular states and functional domains within their native tissue environment. These functional domains often exist at multiple spatial scales, with larger domains encompassing smaller ones, reflecting the hierarchical organization of biological systems. However, the identification of these functional domain hierarchies has been largely unexplored due to the lack of suitable computational methods. In this work, we present SCALE, an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laying hen responses to balanced protein reduction on performance, egg quality, nitrogen balance, and fat and mineral utilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The effect of graded reductions in balanced crude protein (CP) on hen productive performance, egg quality, nitrogen balance, abdominal fat deposition, tibia traits, and relative economic outcomes from 26 to 44 weeks of age (WOA) was investigated. A total of 252 26-week-old Hy-Line Brown hens were housed in enriched cages (7 birds/cage) and randomly allocated to 1 of 4 different dietary CP levels of iso-energetic diets with 9 replicates per treatment. The trial was conducted over two phases of 26...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary toxicity of polymethyl methacrylate nanoplastics via intratracheal intubation in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plastics, ubiquitous in daily life and industry, are released into the environment in substantial quantities. Instead of complete biodegradation, plastic waste fragments into smaller particles, accumulating as nanoplastics (NPs; < 1 μm). Humans are exposed to NPs through inhalation and ingestion of contaminated water and food, which can induce cytotoxicity through physical and chemical pathways. Polymethyl methacrylate (PMMA), commonly used in implants and artificial bones, has been identified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ferroelectric switching of interfacial dipoles in α-RuCl<sub>3</sub>/graphene heterostructure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate electrically switchable, non-volatile dipoles in graphene/thin hBN/α-RuCl(3)alpha-RuCl3 heterostructures, stabilized purely by interfacial charge transfer across an atomically thin dielectric barrier. This mechanism requires no sliding or twisting to explicitly break inversion symmetry and produces robust ferroelectric-like hysteresis loops that emerge prominently near 30 K. Systematic measurements under strong in-plane and out-of-plane magnetic fields reveal negligible effects on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sirt6 deficiency in mast cells promotes adipose fibroinflammation in obesity through galectin-3 signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mast cells (MCs) play a key role in obesity and insulin resistance, though the mechanisms driving adipose dysfunction remain unclear. We find that Sirt6 expression in MCs decreases with obesity in both male mice and humans. Selective depletion of Sirt6 in MCs worsens inflammation, fibrosis, and metabolic dysfunction in diet-induced obesity. Adoptive transfer of MC-deficient KitW-sh/W-sh mice with Sirt6-deficient MCs leads to greater weight gain on a high-fat diet compared to transfer with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cesium-Promoted Nickel-Ceria Anodes for Enhanced Stability and Performance in Low-Temperature Solid Oxide Fuel Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solid oxide fuel cells (SOFCs) are a promising energy technology, but their performance is limited by high operating temperatures and material degradation. While significant research has focused on improving anode stability at high temperatures, less attention has been given to low-temperature (≤450 °C) performance, where the anode's role becomes more critical. This study investigates the effect of a cesium-based promoter, introduced as a CsNO(3) aqueous solution or powder onto gadolinium-doped...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cervical Spinal Meningeal Enhancement on Magnetic Resonance Imaging in Healthy Dogs: Characteristics of Enhancement Patterns and the Effect of Acquisition Time]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Meningeal enhancement on magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) is commonly associated with pathological conditions, including inflammation, neoplasia, or ischemia. However, short and thin segments of contrast enhancement are considered normal in the brain meninges, but studies on spinal meningeal enhancement in dogs are limited. This prospective, exploratory study aimed to determine the presence and characteristics of cervical spinal meningeal enhancement in healthy dogs as well as the impact of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tailoring Interfacial Oxygen Vacancy-Mediated Ordering in Ternary Pt<sub>3</sub>(Co,Mn)<sub>1</sub> Intermetallic Nanoparticles for Enhanced Oxygen Reduction Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The sluggish kinetics and limited durability of the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) at the cathode remain a major barrier to the widespread deployment of proton exchange membrane fuel cells (PEMFCs). Here, we introduce a low-temperature interfacial engineering strategy to construct ternary L1(2)-ordered Pt(3)(Co,Mn)(1) intermetallic nanoparticles. A conformal MnO shell on Pt(3)Co(1) cores not only suppresses particle coalescence but also undergoes redox activation to generate interfacial oxygen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to: Molecular identification of severe fever with thrombocytopenia syndrome virus in deer ked: implications for disease transmission (One Health, volume 21, article number 101107)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1016/j.onehlt.2025.101107.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A one health approach to prioritizing emerging zoonotic diseases (EZDs) in northern Vietnam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Rabies, avian influenza and Streptococcus suis were the three most prioritized diseases across the two provinces. This list can serve as a foundation for strengthening one health collaboration for disease prevention and control in these targeted provinces.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-output, web-based risk assessment system for cesarean section due to dystocia: integration of logistic regression and risk scoring models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This dual-output, user-friendly, and admission-based web system enhances interpretability and supports personalized counseling and evidence-based decision-making. Specifically designed for Korean women, it enables the early identification of high-risk cases and may help reduce unnecessary operative interventions. Therefore, further multicenter studies are warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Ideal Surface Reveals How Active It Is and Why It Degrades: SrTi<sub>0.5</sub>Fe<sub>0.5</sub>O<sub>3-δ</sub> Model Thin Film with Atomically Flat Terraces─A Case Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface cation segregation, specifically strontium (Sr), has been identified as a primary factor contributing to the performance degradation of perovskite-based oxide electrodes used in various energy conversion devices. However, due to the complex chemistry and structure of the perovskite oxide surfaces, the mechanisms behind surface segregation and its impact on electrode activity are only partially understood. Moreover, this phenomenon occurs during perovskite synthesis, further complicating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standardizing vaginal microbial profiling: evaluating swab materials, storage conditions, and host DNA depletion strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of TYR gene variants associated with white coat color in Hanwoo cattle using whole-genome sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights significant genomic differences between White and Brown Hanwoo populations, including reduced genetic diversity in White Hanwoo due to potential inbreeding. In addition, it confirms the TYR gene as a critical determinant of coat color through the identification of a functionally relevant missense variant. These findings provide valuable insights for Hanwoo breeding and conservation strategies and lay the foundation for further functional studies on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive transcriptomic and functional characterization of protoplast regeneration in Angelica gigas Nakai]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research trends in hospital information systems in Korea: a topic modeling analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to analyze research papers related to Hospital Information Systems (HIS), including Electronic Health Record and Electronic Medical Record (EMR), in South Korea over three decades. The research explores frequently used terms and concepts in HIS research, examines how these reflect key focus areas, and investigates the evolution of research trends. This study employed text preprocessing, text network analysis, and a large language model (LLM)-based topic modeling approach. Network...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brain-infiltrating CD8 T cells retain functional activity to protect against acute Zika virus infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Zika virus (ZIKV) infection can cause severe neurological complications, yet the role of CD8^(+) T cells in controlling viral pathogenesis in the brain remains unclear. Using Ifnar1^(-)/^(-) mice, which lack type I interferon signaling, we demonstrate that ZIKV infection triggers significant infiltration of CD8^(+) T cells into the brain, accompanied by neurological defects. ZIKV-experienced CD8^(+) T cells exhibit enhanced cytotoxic potential, and adoptive transfer of these cells improves...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of metal-semiconductor interface treatments and absorber structure on the performance and reliability of uni-traveling-carrier photodiodes (UTC-PDs)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The effects of absorber structure-controlled by adjusting the thickness ratio of doped and undoped InGaAs layers-and metal-semiconductor interface treatment methods were investigated in waveguide-type UTC-PDs. Ultraviolet-ozone (UVO) and ammonia solution cleaning of the InGaAs surface improved the interface quality in terms of contact resistivity and bias-temperature stability. Nevertheless, devices cleaned using buffered oxide etchant (BOE) exhibited higher photoresponsivity and superior...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Advances in Therapeutic Approaches for Knee Osteoarthritis: a Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Knee osteoarthritis (KOA) is a progressive and chronic musculoskeletal condition that continues to be the leading cause of disability worldwide. Conventional treatment approaches for the management of KOA largely focus on symptom alleviation rather than halting or reversing disease progression. However, recent advancements have highlighted the integrated interplay of mechanical stress, inflammation, cellular senescence, and chondrocyte dysfunction in the progression of KOA, in turn prompting new...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding the full chemical catalytic cycle of class I PHA synthase: A QM/MM metadynamics perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The accumulation of plastic waste continues to pose a significant threat to ecosystems, driven by inefficient recycling processes and inadequate waste management. Polyhydroxyalkanoates (PHAs) have emerged as promising biodegradable alternatives, owing to their ability to degrade under various environmental conditions and modulable material properties, which enable broad applicability. Despite these advantages, the detailed molecular mechanisms of PHA biosynthesis-particularly those of the key...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Negative Capacitance in Hf<sub>0.5</sub>Zr<sub>0.5</sub>O<sub>2</sub> for Low-Power and Reliable Charge Trap Flash Memory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Charge trap flash (CTF) memory has emerged as a key solution for high-density nonvolatile memory. However, the high operating voltage of CTF memory leads to critical reliability issues, such as cell-to-cell interference and dielectric breakdown, limiting further pitch size scaling in 3D architectures. Here, we report a negative capacitance charge trap flash (NC-CTF) memory that exhibits remarkable operation efficiency by using the NC-induced capacitance boosting effect of Hf(0.5)Zr(0.5)O(2)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodality imaging in hypertrophic cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy (HCM) is a myocardial disorder characterized by unexplained myocardial hypertrophy. Although the diagnosis of HCM is traditionally based on increased left ventricular (LV) wall thickness, contemporary management requires a comprehensive multimodality imaging approach to accurately define disease phenotype, assess functional consequences, and guide risk stratification. Transthoracic echocardiography remains the first-line imaging modality, providing real-time...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cultural adaptation and psychometric validation of the Korean version of the Intensive care unit Dignified Care Questionnaire (IDCQ)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biogenic iron oxide nanoparticles synthesized using Trichoderma spp.: A sustainable approach for fusarium wilt management in tomato]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fusarium wilt caused by Fusarium oxysporum poses a significant threat to tomato cultivation worldwide and requiring the development of sustainable and effective control measures. This study explored the potential of biologically synthesized iron oxide nanoparticles (IONPs) as an eco-friendly alternative to conventional fungicides and evaluated their antifungal efficacy along with plant health impact. The IONPs were synthesized using Trichoderma spp. metabolites and characterized using multiple...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effectiveness and safety of combining platelet-rich plasma with cartilage tympanoplasty type 1 to treat tympanic membrane perforations: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The autologous PRP application during cartilage tympanoplasty type 1 leads to higher success rates and greater hearing improvement, and also increases the success rate during all follow-up periods.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Author Reflections: Reconsidering the Role of Preoperative Biopsy in Early Stage Lung Cancer: It Could Be a Risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colorectal microenvironment determines the prognosis of colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here we aimed to evaluate the feasibility of distinguishing colorectal microenvironments that support cancer cell growth from those that do not. We hypothesized that patients whose non-tumor-bearing tissue (NBT) obtained from the furthest margins of resected cancer specimens resembled the tumor had a poorer prognosis. Patients with colorectal cancer were divided into groups with tumor-supportive (TSM) or healthy microenvironments using bulk RNA sequencing data from 273 paired NBT and tumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global, regional, and national burden of chronic respiratory diseases and impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, 1990-2023: a Global Burden of Disease study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic respiratory diseases, including chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD), asthma, pneumoconiosis, interstitial lung disease (ILD) and pulmonary sarcoidosis, are major global causes of mortality and morbidity. Although the COVID-19 pandemic has influenced acute respiratory health, its impact on chronic respiratory conditions remains unclear. We estimated the global, regional and national burden of chronic respiratory diseases from 1990 to 2023, including risk factors, and evaluated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of recovery grade in Bell's palsy using machine learning models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While most cases of Bell's palsy resolve successfully, some patients do not fully recover despite medical treatment. Various tools have been developed to assess the status of facial nerve palsy (FNP), enhance prognostic accuracy, and guide early rehabilitation or more intensive therapies. However, existing evaluation tools often struggle with accurately predicting moderate cases of FNP. Recently, machine learning algorithms have shown promise in predicting clinical outcomes across various...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A-site dependent metastable polar phases from polarization compatible octahedral rotations in perovskite AZrO<sub>3</sub> (A = Ca, Sr)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the electronic structures and ferroelectric properties of perovskite CaZrO(3) and SrZrO(3) using first-principles density functional theory. Both materials are in the non-polar Pnma space group with [Formula: see text] octahedral rotation pattern. However, in the absence of the octahedral rotation, a polar instability exists for both materials, which is suppressed as the magnitude of the [Formula: see text] octahedral rotation increases. This suggests that metastable polar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[6-Gingerol alleviates high glucose-induced inflammation and cytotoxicity in THP-1 cells by inhibiting TLR4 signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LC2767 alleviates LPS-induced liver injury and fibrosis by regulating FXR expression, NF-κB activation, and gut microbiota]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevated neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio and the incidence of autoimmune diseases: evidence from a large prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We prospectively assessed the association between neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio (NLR) and incident autoimmune disease risk using data from 430,347 UK Biobank participants recruited between 2006 and 2010. The NLR was calculated by dividing neutrophil counts by lymphocyte counts and categorized into quartiles. Cox regression models estimated hazard ratios (HRs) for per quartile increase of (1) a composite of 39 types of autoimmune diseases, (2) each specific autoimmune diseases, applying a 2-year...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Dataset Showing a Century of Evolution in the Complexity of the United States Legal Code]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As societies confront increasingly complex regulatory demands in domains such as digital governance, climate policy, and public health, there is a pressing need to understand how legal systems evolve, where they concentrate regulatory attention, and how their institutional architectures shape capacity for adaptation. Yet, the long-term structural dynamics of law remain empirically underexplored. Here, we provide a quantitative analysis of the United States Code (U.S. Code), the primary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and risk factors for intra-anesthetic hyperglycemia in 400 nondiabetic dogs: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND CLINICAL RELEVANCE: Intra-anesthetic hyperglycemia occurred in nondiabetic dogs, with specific risk factors identified: elevated preanesthetic fasting glucose, ASA status ≥ 3, medetomidine use, surgery, intra-anesthetic hypothermia, dopamine and norepinephrine use. Patients with these risk factors may be predisposed to hyperglycemia, highlighting the importance of intra-anesthetic glucose monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiological Approach to Splenomegaly: Etiologies, Pathophysiologies, and Diagnostic Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The spleen is frequently referred to as the "silent and forgotten" organ of the abdomen by clinicians and radiologists, primarily because of the secondary nature of most splenic pathologies and their relative rarity compared with hepatic diseases. Nevertheless, the term splenomegaly frequently appears in radiological reports. Although it is often reported in the context of a known underlying cause, it is also commonly used as a purely descriptive term without reference to the underlying...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Access and Reimbursement for Artificial Intelligence in Radiology in Mongolia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Network Radiology as a New Paradigm in Radiology Practice: Recent Insights From Integrated Health Systems in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data-driven life-stage classification for companion dogs and cats using age-specific diagnosis patterns in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Age-specific diagnosis patterns support four practical life stages for dogs and cats in South Korea. These boundaries can inform evidence-based preventive examination schedules, animal health policy, and pet insurance product design.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to Commentary on "Effects of Deep Learning-Based Reconstruction on the Quality of Accelerated Contrast-Enhanced Neck MRI"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Impact of Radiologic and Pathologic Features on the Development of Progressive Pulmonary Fibrosis in Patients With Interstitial Lung Disease Other Than Idiopathic Pulmonary Fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Traction bronchiectasis on CT was a significant predictor of PPF, while radiologic and symptomatic progression and older age were associated with poorer survival in patients with ILD other than IPF. These findings indicate that careful radiological evaluation and symptom monitoring may help to predict disease progression and outcomes in patients with non-IPF ILD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potential Role of Imaging in the Evaluation of Adiposity and Approval of Anti-Obesity Drugs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global increase in obesity highlights the need for accurate tools to assess body composition and monitor treatment efficacy. Traditional metrics, including body mass index and waist circumference, offer limited precision for fat quantification. Imaging-based techniques capable of visualizing internal structures are increasingly being recognized for their ability to provide comprehensive fat assessment. This review outlines the principles, strengths, and limitations of key modalities,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Outcomes of No-Touch Radiofrequency Ablation Versus Tumor-Puncture Microwave Ablation for Small Hepatocellular Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: NT-RFA showed superior local tumor control compared to MWA, despite greater procedural complexity and longer ablation times.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coronary CT Angiography-Derived Fractional Flow Reserve in Asia and the United States: 2025 Status Update]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coronary CT-derived fractional flow reserve (CT-FFR) is a noninvasive alternative to invasive FFR for assessing the hemodynamic significance of coronary artery stenosis. CT-FFR uses routinely acquired coronary CT angiography (CCTA) with artificial intelligence and computational fluid dynamics to estimate pressure gradients, thereby supporting clinical decision-making without procedural risk. Adoption and implementation vary widely across regions. In Asia, South Korea exclusively uses HeartMedi+,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening Outcomes of Supplemental Automated Breast Ultrasound in Women With Nondense Breasts Undergoing Mammography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Supplemental ABUS improved cancer detection and sensitivity in women with nondense breasts, with the benefits primarily observed in those with scattered fibroglandular density.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Access and Reimbursement for Artificial Intelligence in Radiology: A Korean Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of BARC-defined Bleeding in East Asian Acute Myocardial Infarction Patients: Evidence from Multicentre Registries in Korea and Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Bleeding Academic Research Consortium (BARC) classification was proposed to standardize bleeding endpoint definitions and reports in cardiovascular clinical trials. However, its prognostic value has not been fully validated in East Asian patients with acute myocardial infarction (AMI) who have a higher bleeding risk than Western populations do.We analyzed bleeding events (types 2 or 3) based on the BARC classification in 13,657 patients with AMI (mean age 64.9 ± 12.7 years) from nationwide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Viral Transduction for T Cell Engineering in Immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Viral transduction of primary T cells enables stable genetic engineering for research and immunotherapy, supporting both transgene overexpression and gene deletion. Although the overall workflow can be similar to transduction in other mammalian cell lines, primary T cell culture imposes distinct requirements such as cell-state-dependent nuances shaped by T cell activation and proliferation which can make it challenging to obtain a sufficient number of genetically engineered T cells. This article...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intolerance of uncertainty modulates amygdala habituation to emotional faces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[People differ widely in how they perceive uncertain situations as stressful and threatening. Intolerance of uncertainty (IU) captures these individual differences while operating as a transdiagnostic and transsituational risk factor. In the present study, we investigated how individual differences in the sensitivity to uncertainty, rather than broader anxious traits, influence the temporal dynamics of amygdala habituation to emotional faces. Eighty-five human participants (18 males) completed an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is cubital tunnel obliteration a safe and effective procedure for cubital tunnel syndrome? A case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cubital tunnel obliteration seems to be a safe and reliable surgical option for treating CuTS and its short-term outcome was favorable for both idiopathic and secondary CuTS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput identification of geographical origins of rubies using hyperspectral visible and fluorescence spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explored hyperspectral (HS) visible and fluorescence spectroscopy as a high-throughput analytical tool for discrimination of rubies originating from Myanmar (MM), Mozambique (MZ), and Thailand (TH). Rubies are a variety of the mineral corundum (Al(2)O(3)), and their color is mainly related to Cr and Fe. In this study, multiple rubies were loaded onto a carbon-coated plate and measured under a HS camera for high-throughput analysis. The absorption peaks around 420 nm and 558 nm were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Excessive smartphone use among multicultural adolescents in South Korea: Vulnerable groups and associated risk factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multicultural adolescents reported higher smartphone use than their non-multicultural peers with patterns varying by cultural and socioeconomic factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A green approach to PFAS remediation: Mechanochemical degradation with natural piezoelectric tourmaline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perfluorooctane sulfonic acid (PFOS) and perfluorobutane sulfonic acid (PFBS) are among the most frequently detected per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS) in the environment owing to their prevalence and high stability, raising serious concerns regarding their toxicity and long-term persistence. This study proposes a promising approach for the degradation of PFOS and PFBS using a mechanochemical degradation (MCD) technique, employing tourmaline (TM). A comprehensive suite of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First-line lenvatinib plus pembrolizumab versus chemotherapy for advanced endometrial cancer: 1-Year follow-up after final analysis of the ENGOT-en9/LEAP-001 phase 3 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The mismatch repair-proficient, all-comer, and mismatch repair-deficient populations continued to demonstrate antitumor activity for lenvatinib+pembrolizumab after an additional year of follow-up. These results should be interpreted with caution due to the exploratory nature of the analysis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pressure-Induced Structural, Mechanical, and Optoelectronic Tunability in Fluorinated Two-Dimensional Hybrid Perovskite (FPMA)<sub>2</sub>PbI<sub>4</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a systematic high-pressure investigation of fluorinated two-dimensional hybrid perovskite (FPMA)(2)PbI(4), combining in situ synchrotron powder X-ray diffraction (HP-PXRD), photoluminescence spectroscopy (HP-PL), and first-principles density functional theory (DFT) simulations. Under hydrostatic compression to 5.54 (±0.4) GPa, HP-PXRD exhibits anisotropic lattice contraction (a/a(o) = 4.54%, b/b(o) = 3.35%, c/c(o) = 9.79%), leading to an isothermal bulk modulus of 15.6 (±1.3) GPa (K(0)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Humanizing Donor Terminology in Anatomical and Clinical Research: Best Ethical Practice in Anatomy (BEPA) Consensus Statement From the Universal Anatomical Organization (UAO)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anatomical education and research are built on the generosity of individuals who donate their bodies to advance science. However, the terminology traditionally used to describe these individuals-"specimens," "cadavers," or "cadaveric specimens"-risks objectifying the donor and obscuring their humanity. This paper examines the historical roots of depersonalized language, its persistence in contemporary research, and the ethical implications of its continuing use. Drawing on comparisons with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Suicide in Individuals with Atherosclerotic Cardiovascular Disease: A Nationwide Population-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Individuals with ASCVD have increased risks of suicide. Our findings suggest the importance of screening and preventing suicidal ideation in individuals with ASCVD to improve prognosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Efficacy of Opioid-Free and Opioid-Sparing Anesthesia in Dogs Undergoing Dental Procedures: A Prospective Study of Perioperative Analgesia and Hemodynamic Stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This prospective, randomized, and blinded clinical trial aimed to compare opioid-free anesthesia (OFA) and opioid-sparing anesthesia (OSA) protocols for perioperative analgesia and hemodynamic stability in 60 healthy dogs undergoing dental procedures, including extractions and endodontic treatments. All dogs received intramuscular medetomidine (10 µg/kg) as premedication, followed by intraoperative constant rate infusions according to group assignment: OFA1 (ketamine 0.6 mg/kg/hr), OFA2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of overall survival in advanced biliary tract cancer in the phase 3 TOPAZ-1 study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inclusion of intracranial volume as a covariate feature improves MRI-based Alzheimer's disease classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Structural MRI-based regional volumes are widely used for Alzheimer's disease (AD) classification, but inter-individual variability in intracranial volume (ICV) introduces confounding. Traditional adjustment methods use region-of-interest (ROI)/ICV ratios or residual adjustment during pre-processing, yet no consensus exists on the optimal method. This study tests whether explicitly including ICV as a covariate (ROI + ICV) improves classification compared with ratio, residual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term experience with growth hormone therapy in pediatric growth disorders: an analysis of the LG growth study data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multidimensional analysis of smartphone overuse in insomnia: Integrating digital phenotyping with clinical assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND AIMS: This study aimed to identify the differences in characteristics between high- and low-risk smartphone users among individuals with insomnia symptoms using digital phenotyping and clinical assessments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Body Fatness With Hypertension, Dyslipidemia, and Myocardial Infarction in a Multinational Pooled Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This analysis revealed a positive association of dual-energy X-ray absorptiometry-measured body fat parameters with CVDs for individuals in a specific BMI group. The findings highlight a need for policy changes to include directly measured body fatness in assessing CVD risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complete revascularization timing in ST-segment elevation myocardial infarction and multivessel disease with heart failure: the OPTION-STEMI trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In the OPTION-STEMI trial, among patients with STEMI and multi-vessel disease who were not in cardiogenic shock, immediate complete revascularization was not non-inferior compared with staged complete revascularization. However, subgroup analysis suggests that the worse outcomes with immediate complete revascularization may be limited to patients with heart failure at admission. Further studies are required to demonstrate the non-inferiority of immediate complete revascularization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence, Co-occurrence, and Prognostic Implications of S Modifiers in the Korean National Lung Cancer Screening Program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background The documentation of clinically significant incidental findings (S modifiers) in low-dose CT lung cancer screening varies among radiologists. Although the Korean National Lung Cancer Screening Program adopted structured reporting for seven standardized S modifiers, the prognostic value of standardized S modifiers has not been evaluated comprehensively. Purpose To evaluate the implementation of structured reporting for prespecified S modifiers by analyzing their prevalence, mortality...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patulin Biodegradation by Rhodosporidiobolus ruineniae and Meyerozyma guilliermondii Isolated From Fruits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patulin (PAT) is a toxic secondary metabolite produced by certain species of Penicillium and Aspergillus on pome fruits. In this study, we isolated Rhodosporidiobolus ruineniae (R. ruineniae) and Meyerozyma guilliermondii (M. guilliermondii) from a peach and an apple as candidates for PAT degradation, respectively, and investigated the effects of three key parameters (incubation time and temperature, and initial PAT concentration) on PAT removal rates, and the mechanism involved in PAT...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exercise and Forest Therapy Programs for Improving Cognitive Function and Physical Health in Older Adults With Mild Cognitive Impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iatrogenic vascular injury during retrograde intramedullary nailing of a distal femur fracture: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a case of iatrogenic injury to the lateral circumflex femoral artery following distal femoral nailing in a 72-year-old patient. Postoperatively, progressive thigh swelling developed, but initial contrast-enhanced computed tomography (CT) showed no evidence of vascular injury. The arterial injury was subsequently identified on a follow-up contrast-enhanced CT scan and was successfully treated with angiographic microcoil embolization. This case underscores the critical importance of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From trauma surgery to acute care surgery: a 4-year observational study at a single trauma center in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The transition from the trauma surgery model to the ACS model successfully increased the efficiency of trauma and emergency general surgery within the level II low-volume environment, accomplishing without reducing the existing trauma caseload. These findings support the adoption of ACS in similar emergency medical institutions and offer insights relevant for national policy development concerning emergency general surgery in Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Venous phase extravasation on computed tomography is a red flag sign in critical/severe pelvic injuries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Venous phase extravasation was associated with higher transfusion requirements, cardiac arrest incidence, and mortality compared to arterial extravasation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thirteen-year trend analysis of orbital blowout fractures: shifts in mechanisms and ocular sequelae across two Korean trauma centers (2011-2023)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Between 2011 and 2023, the Korean OBF landscape shifted from violent assault to accidental mechanisms, accompanied by a marked decline in preoperative ocular motility impairment. Assault mechanism and male sex remain strong risk indicators, while center-based differences appear largely explained by temporal composition. Public health efforts that reduce violence may therefore translate directly into better functional status at initial presentation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhaled amikacin as a preventive strategy against ventilator-associated pneumonia in a trauma intensive care unit: early evidence from a single-center retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prophylactic inhaled amikacin neither prevented nor increased IVAC and VAP risk in mechanically ventilated trauma patients, suggesting no meaningful impact on VAP outcomes in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Formation of an endometrial epithelial monolayer in a microfluidic device with human tissue-derived endometrial organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The endometrium is the uterine lining that supports implantation and pregnancy. Existing in vitro systems only partly capture epithelial structure and function. We built a microfluidic model of the human endometrial epithelium using patient-derived organoids and defined a parameterized device and ECM conditions that yield a stable, polarized monolayer on chip. We specify the geometry, surface treatments, and collagen-based hydrogel or coating conditions, and we link these parameters to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum: Correction of Text in the Article "Complications of Nasopharyngeal Swabs and Safe Procedures for COVID-19 Testing Based on Anatomical Knowledge"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This corrects the article on p. e88 in vol. 37, PMID: 35315599.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing an Active Vaccine Safety Surveillance System Using Large Scale Databases in Korea: Lessons and Scalable Insights for Global Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vaccines are highly effective, but rare or delayed adverse events following immunization (AEFIs) require post-licensure surveillance beyond clinical trials. Korea lacks a comprehensive, active, database-based framework, yet key assets exist: nationwide claims databases (National Health Insurance Service/Health Insurance Review and Assessment Service), the national immunization registry (Korea Disease Control and Prevention Agency's Immunization Registry Information System) for National...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the Performance of Basic Local Government Initiatives in Suicide Prevention: Insights From Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: There are notable disparities in suicide prevention performance among Korea's basic local governments. Customized strategies that reflect local capacities and contexts are essential to reduce these gaps and improve overall effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suicidal Ideation Among Patients With Breast Cancer: A Comparison of Patient Health Questionnaire-9 Item 9 and Columbia-Suicide Severity Rating Scale]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although PHQ-9 item 9 may have limited utility in detecting active suicidal ideation among patients with breast cancer, it may serve as a valuable screening tool for identifying those at risk of having thoughts of suicide accompanied by wish for death.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beneficial Effects and Factors Associated With Provision of Breast Milk at Neonatal Intensive Care Unit Discharge to Very Low Birth Weight Infants: A Nationwide Cohort Study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Breast milk provision to VLBW infants at NICU discharge in Korea was comparable to that in other countries. This nationwide study highlights the critical role of breast milk in promoting the neurodevelopment of VLBW infants. Future efforts should focus on identifying the barriers to breast milk provision to improve health outcomes in vulnerable populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors of Complications in Patients With Persistent or Long-Standing Persistent Atrial Fibrillation/Atrial Flutter Who Underwent Electrical Cardioversion: A Multicenter Cardioversion Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Female sex and a history of SSE were the most important risk factors of complications in patients with persistent or long-standing persistent AF/AFL who underwent ECV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expert Consensus Study on the Redesign of the Sexually Transmitted Infection Surveillance System in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although a consensus was not reached in some of the surveys in this study, it involved the collection of various expert opinions. Therefore, policies should be promoted with a prioritized focus on items with high agreement, but items for which no consensus was reached need to be reviewed in greater depth through additional research and investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequential Mediation by Maternal Weight Gain and Late Blood Metal Concentration in the Association Between Heavy Metal Exposure in Early Pregnancy and Fetal Growth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The effect of Pb exposure in early pregnancy on birthweight was mediated by GWG and Pb exposures during late pregnancy. When assessing the impact of heavy metal exposure on birthweight, it is important to note that GWG and late heavy metal levels act as mediators, rather than confounders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Handgrip Strength in Korean Youth and Young Adults: Reference Values and Their Associations with Metabolic Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We established age- and sex-specific aCHGS reference values among Korean youth and young adults, demonstrating effectiveness in predicting MS risk. These standards may serve as a practical clinical tool to identify individuals at increased risk of MS early in development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physical Implementation of Reinforcement Learning via a Signal Summation Process in a Dual-Input Synaptic Transistor: Photoinduced Dipole Inversion of Au(I) Complex with Charge Traps of cPVP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence (AI) has driven research beyond software into hardware innovation. To improve computational efficiency, AI accelerators integrating large numbers of transistors have been developed, yet this approach remains constrained by scaling and thermal limitations of silicon technology. Synaptic transistors, specialized for analog and parallel computation, have emerged as promising alternatives. Nevertheless, simply replacing silicon transistors offers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Topical Carrier-Free Delivery of Finasteride and Peptides for Enhanced Hair Growth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Finasteride is widely used to treat androgenetic alopecia; however, concerns regarding systemic side effects limit its long-term use. Here, we developed a peptide-based, carrier-free topical delivery system that enhances hair growth while minimizing systemic exposure to finasteride. The system employs a skin- and cell-penetrating peptide with intrinsic anti-inflammatory activity as both the delivery vehicle and a therapeutic component. Upon coassembly with finasteride via a compositionally tuned...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the Korean Version of the Pediatric Eating Assessment Tool-10 (K-PEDI-EAT-10) with Correlation to Videofluoroscopic Swallowing Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The K-Pedi-EAT-10 is a reliable, valid, and non-invasive tool for screening pediatric dysphagia. Its strong psychometric performance supports its potential use for the early identification and timely intervention of children at risk for dysphagia in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Intensity Interval Training Enhances Cardiovascular and Functional Outcomes Compared With Moderate-Intensity Continuous Training in Higher-Functioning Chronic Stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In higher-functioning chronic stroke survivors, HIIT was superior to MICT for cardiovascular fitness and functional mobility under a matched exposure; lipid changes occurred within HIIT only without between-group effects. These findings support incorporating HIIT into stroke rehabilitation programs to enhance recovery outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global Overview of Acquired Upper Limb Amputation Epidemiology: A Systematic Review of Prevalence, Incidence, Level, and Etiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Upper limb amputation leads to significant physical and psychosocial burden; however, it remains underrepresented in global epidemiological and rehabilitation studies. This study aimed to systematically review the global epidemiological data on upper limb amputation, focusing on its prevalence, incidence, anatomical levels, and etiology. According to the PRISMA (Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses) guidelines, a comprehensive literature search was conducted using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors of failed electrical cardioversion in patients with persistent or long-standing persistent atrial fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Longer AF duration, history of HF, and increased LAVI were strongly associated with failed ECV in patients with persistent or long-standing persistent AF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of the Chemical Properties, Photostability, and Antioxidant Activity of Turmeric Oleoresin by Propylene Glycol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Curcuminoids from turmeric exhibit beneficial health effects. However, their practical application is limited because of poor stability and solubility. The present study investigated the effects of propylene glycol (PG), a common food additive, on the chemical properties, photostability, and antioxidant activity of turmeric oleoresin (TO). PG significantly improved the solubility and dispersion stability in aqueous solutions (P<0.05). PG at 20%－30% concentration effectively prevented pigment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gastroprotective Effects of <em>Artemisia annua</em> L., on an Hydrochloric Acid/Ethanol-Induced Acute Gastritis Model via Anti-Oxidative and Anti-Inflammatory Activities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SPB-201, a water extract of Artemisia annua L., was investigated for its gastroprotective effects against hydrochloric acid/ethanol-induced gastric mucosal injury in rats and oxidative stress-induced damage in gastric cell models, with a focus on the mechanisms underlying its antioxidant and anti-inflammatory activity. Sprague-Dawley rats pretreated with SPB-201 (50 mg/kg) showed significantly reduced gastric lesion areas, improved histological architecture, modestly decreased gastric acid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of Oral Antidiabetic Drugs in Metabolic Dysfunction-Associated Steatotic Liver Disease: A Nationwide Target Trial Emulation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with concurrent T2DM and MASLD, SGLT2 inhibitors demonstrated better cardiovascular outcomes compared to other OADs. These findings suggest that SGLT2 inhibitors may be the preferred OAD choice for cardiovascular risk reduction in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply: Mean Nocturnal Baseline Impedance in Gastroesophageal Reflux Disease: Considerations on the Study by Lee et al]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Loss of Inspiratory Augmentation as a Predictive Factor for the Development of Gastroesophageal Reflux Disease After Peroral Endoscopic Myotomy in Patients With Achalasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: : Loss of inspiratory augmentation may predict GERD after POEM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in Esophageal Transit Scintigraphy After Peroral Endoscopic Myotomy in Patients With Achalasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: : Patients with achalasia who received POEM showed improved not only manometric LES parameters but also esophageal transit. Analysis of the radiation curve's time-to-peak showed that improved retention in the upper portion is an indicator of symptoms improvement in patients who underwent POEM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanding the Physiological Role of the Endoluminal Functional Lumen Imaging Probe From the Esophagus to Pediatric Pylorus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Mean Basal Esophagogastric Junction Pressure a Simpler and More Reliable Marker for Gastroesophageal Reflux Disease Barrier Function?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequence-Defined Polysulfates via S(VI)-Fluoride Exchange Iterative Exponential Growth (SuFEx IEG)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the high reactivity, modularity, and orthogonality of the S(VI)-fluoride exchange (SuFEx) reaction, a new addition to click chemistry, we report here the SuFEx iterative exponential growth (SuFEx IEG) method for synthesizing uniform polymers and block copolymers (BCPs) with molecular weights up to 21 kDa. The key step in SuFEx IEG was the on-demand, orthogonal activation of the pair of functional groups, the SuFEx-inactive tetrahydropyranyl and imidazylate groups, into SuFEx-active...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Recyclable Triangular Phenanthrenequinone (TPQ) Catalyst-in-a-Teabag System for Biomimetic Aerobic Oxidation of Benzylamines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An insoluble triangular phenanthrenequinone (TPQ) catalyst was developed and applied in a reusable "catalyst-in-a-teabag" system for the aerobic oxidation of benzylamines. Encapsulation of TPQ in a permeable PTFE pouch enabled efficient aerobic oxidation under mild conditions, affording imine products in excellent yields and easy catalyst recovery. The TPQ catalyst exhibited high reusability with full activity restoration after acid-alcohol reactivation, providing a practical and sustainable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OsCML17 a pollen-expressed calmodulin-like protein regulates pollen germination and tube growth in rice (Oryza sativa)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rice pollen-specific calmodulin-like protein OsCML17 contributes to fertilization by regulating pollen germination and pollen tube elongation, and is localized to the endoplasmic reticulum and plasma membrane. In angiosperms, successful fertilization relies on the precise growth of the pollen tube growth. Calcium ion (Ca^(2+)) regulates various physiological responses and plays a critical role in pollen germination and pollen tube growth. Calmodulin-like proteins (CMLs), which consist of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical impact of disease stability on exacerbation and mortality in COPD: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Disease stability was associated with a lower risk of exacerbation and mortality, suggesting its potential role as a treatment target and outcome measure for COPD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41492099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PD-L1 mRNA expression correlates with tumor growth rate in giant cell tumor of bone: a volumetric MRI analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher PD-L1 mRNA expression correlated with accelerated tumor growth in extremity GCTB. These exploratory findings suggest PD-L1 may serve as a potential biomarker of tumor aggressiveness, warranting validation in larger cohorts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal deep learning approaches for improving polygenic risk scores with imaging data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enhancing the predictive accuracy of polygenic risk scores (PRS) can be achieved by incorporating imaging data, which captures disease-related phenotypic variations. This study aimed to evaluate the predictive performance of PRS, image-derived deep learning scores (IDS), imaging-derived phenotypes (IDPs), and clinical covariates. Additionally, IDP-proxy genetic scores (IGSs) were developed as substitutes for IDPs in cases where imaging data are unavailable. The study assessed the predictive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasound-Based Classification of Infraorbital Fat and Groove Patterns: Clinical Implications for Safer Filler Injection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pre-injection ultrasound evaluation provides critical insights into fat positioning and vascular structures, supporting safer and more individualized injection strategies. The proposed classification offers a clinically useful framework for personalized infraorbital filler treatments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reframing learning interactions: transforming professional identity among students of traditional Korean medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The insights gained from traditional Korean medical education have valuable implications for global medical education. By revealing the general principles and culturally specific dynamics of professional identity formation, this study contributes to a deeper understanding of how identity is shaped within pluralistic medical education environments, in which diverse medical paradigms, learning experiences, and cultural values intersect.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microwave synthesis of new naproxen analogues for chronic inflammation and their gastro-protective effect in post-operative model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the present study, novel naproxen analogues (NS9-NS12) were synthesized under microwave irradiation and characterized by ¹H NMR, ^(13)C NMR, and HR-ESI-MS advanced spectroscopic techniques. Their analgesic, anti-inflammatory and gastro-protective activities were evaluated in postoperative and chronic inflammatory pain models. Analgesic activity was determined by Eddy Hot plate and Acetic-induced Writhing tests using dose of 30 mg/kg (b.wt), while anti-inflammatory activity was determined by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variations in survival outcomes of infants born at 22-23 weeks' gestation by neonatal intensive care quality level in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Survival outcomes for infants born at 22-23 weeks' gestation vary widely across neonatal units. This national, prospective cohort study evaluated 919 infants born at 22-23 weeks' gestation in South Korea between 2013 and 2022, using Korean Neonatal Network data. Infants were categorized based on the level of neonatal care: 785 in lower-level centers (Group A) and 134 in higher-level centers (Group B). Survival was significantly higher in Group B (64.9%) compared to Group A (29.3%) (P < 0.0001)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accuracy of AI-based raman spectroscopy in the diagnosis of gastric cancer: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric cancer (GC) remains a significant global health challenge with high mortality rates, often due to late-stage diagnosis. We hypothesize that Raman spectroscopy (RS) (a modern minimally invasive technique that uses light to analyze the molecular composition of tissue, generating a unique "fingerprint" that reveals biochemical details, distinguishing between normal and diseased tissues.) when combined with Machine learning (ML) would provide accurate and expedite approach of detecting GC....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adaptive Immunity and Alzheimer's Disease: Dual Roles in Neurodegeneration and Neuroprotection with Therapeutic Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder defined by amyloid-β (Aβ) plaques, tau hyperphosphorylation, and neuroinflammation. Although earlier work emphasized brain-resident glia (microglia and astrocytes), recent studies highlight adaptive immune cells, particularly T and B lymphocytes, as modulators of AD pathology. This review synthesizes animal and human findings from 2022-2025 to provide updated insights into the multifaceted roles and therapeutic potential of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing Cancer Immunotherapy: Chimeric Antigen Receptor (CAR)-T Cell Engineering through Novel Screening Methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer immunotherapy represents a paradigm-shifting achievement in oncology. Particularly, chimeric antigen receptor (CAR)-T cell therapy utilizing genetically engineered T cells has produced remarkable clinical responses in hematological malignancies. However, significant challenges still remain including limited efficacy in solid tumors and critical safety concerns. The functionality of CAR-T cells depends on their synthetic receptor, CAR, which redirects T cell specificity and enhances...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41490986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260107024453&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ocean Carbon Dioxide Removal and Storage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ocean, Earth's largest carbon reservoir, exerts a central role over atmospheric CO(2) through its capacity to store carbon primarily as bicarbonate ions. Direct observations indicate that the global ocean has a net carbon uptake of 2.6-3.0 petagrams of carbon annually, representing nearly 30% of anthropogenic CO(2) emissions. This review examines two principal domains of oceanic carbon cycling. The first concerns the natural uptake and storage of anthropogenic CO(2), with emphasis on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crossover control: A key to unlocking genetic diversity in plant breeding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During meiosis, crossovers between homologous chromosomes generate genetic diversity but are limited in number, widely spaced by interference, and biased toward gene-rich euchromatin while suppressed in pericentromeric heterochromatin. This constrained crossover patterning restricts the genetic variation available for plant breeding. Recent studies have identified key crossover regulators-including the anti-crossover helicases FANCM and RECQ4, the pro-crossover factor HEI10, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41491601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two types of Wechsler Adult Intelligence Scale (WAIS) index discrepancies are associated with insufficient weight reduction after sleeve gastrectomy in adult patients with obesity: a retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results show that the existence of WAIS index score discrepancies between the PRI/WMI and PSI is associated with insufficient weight reduction after LSG in patients with obesity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of nocturnal desaturation and hypercapnia using accelerometer-integrated pulse oximetry: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among individuals with suspected sleep-related breathing disorders, accelerometer-integrated pulse oximetry may serve as a valuable tool to distinguish nocturnal desaturation episodes caused by exertion from those due to sleep-related hypoventilation. These findings suggest that accelerometer-integrated pulse oximetry could offer a feasible screening method for detecting sleep-related hypoventilation in outpatient settings lacking access to PtcCO(2) monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of late recurrences after hepatectomy for perihilar cholangiocarcinoma: a single-center cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The presence of pathological perineural invasion is significantly associated with late recurrence of pCCA. This finding provides significant insights for the long-term follow-up and managemant of pCCA patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preoperative stool scale is a risk factor for anastomotic leakage after minimally invasive low anterior resection for rectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reciprocity between p63 and p21 via TNFα/NF-κB signaling in p63-positive salivary duct adenocarcinoma cell]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of the rs17822931 (538G &gt; A, G180R) in the ABCC11 gene with risk of middle ear cholesteatoma in older adults: a hospital-based case-control study at Heidelberg University Hospital, Germany]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings from a German cohort replicate the association between the rs17822931 (538G > A, G180R) polymorphism in the ABCC11 gene and cholesteatoma risk in a non-Japanese population, suggesting a broader role of rs17822931 across ethnicities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RE: Response to the readers' comments on our guidelines: Executive summary of the guidelines for prescribing opioid analgesics for chronic non-cancer pain (third edition) by the Japan Society of Pain Clinicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of Loco-Regional Recurrence after Pulmonary Non-Anatomical Metastasectomy: A Multicentre Retrospective Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Loco-regional recurrence after pulmonary metastasectomy seems to be correlated with primary tumour histology and number of metastases. Further studies are needed to clarify the role of size-adjusted margin parameters in preventing recurrence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Renal limited sarcoidosis presenting with non-caseating granulomatous interstitial nephritis in the absence of extrarenal manifestations: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Renal limited sarcoidosis is an exceptionally rare condition characterized by non-caseating granulomas confined solely to the kidneys, without involvement of other organs. Its diagnosis is challenging because of the absence of systemic manifestations. We present a case of a 74-year-old woman with a history of type 2 diabetes mellitus, papillary thyroid carcinoma, and osteoporosis, who showed progressive renal dysfunction. Laboratory findings revealed elevated serum creatinine and urinary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a novel intestinal ultrasound score for predicting endoscopic activity of ileocecal ulcers in intestinal Behçet's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We developed and preliminarily validated a novel ultrasonographic score for intestinal BD to identify endoscopically active disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Severity-Dependent Contributions of Knee Adduction Moment Lever Arm Components and Associated Gait Variables in Medial Knee Osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The characteristics of the contributions of the lever arm components and related gait variables were revealed in Early-mild and Severe OA. These findings may inform gait strategies to reduce KAM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multifocal rosette-forming glioneuronal tumor-like low-grade glioneuronal tumor with dysembryoplastic neuroepithelial tumor features associated with drug-resistant epilepsy: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rosette-forming glioneuronal tumors (RGNTs) are rare, World Health Organization grade 1 tumors that typically arise around the fourth ventricle. However, cerebral hemisphere RGNTs have recently been reported, with some exhibiting clinical features resembling low-grade epilepsy-associated tumor (LEAT). We report a case of multifocal RGNT in a patient with drug-refractory epilepsy. A 14-year-old woman was incidentally found to have multifocal brain tumor involving the left temporal lobe and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative molecular profiles of distinct tumor components in recurrent tentorial meningioma after stereotactic radiosurgery: a case report implicating acquired aggressive alterations associated with WHO grade progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Meningiomas, the most common primary benign intracranial tumors, may recur and, in some cases, undergo WHO grade progression, acquiring more aggressive clinical behavior. The molecular mechanisms underlying such progression, particularly following stereotactic radiosurgery (SRS), remain poorly understood. We report a 70-year-old woman with a gradually enlarging tentorial meningioma treated with SRS as primary therapy. The irradiated lesion remained stable on serial MRI for 30 months following...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Histologically indolent but widely disseminated diffuse midline glioma H3K27-altered revealed by autopsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of N-butyl-2-cyanoacrylate-based middle meningeal artery embolization for preventing recurrence of chronic subdural hematoma in patients aged 65 years and older]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the efficacy and safety of N-butyl-2-cyanoacrylate (NBCA)-based middle meningeal artery embolization (MMAE) in preventing recurrence of chronic subdural hematoma (CSDH) in elderly patients. We retrospectively analyzed 221 patients aged ≥ 65 years who underwent burr hole surgery (BHS) with or without adjunctive MMAE between April 2023 and March 2025. Clinical, radiological, and perioperative variables were assessed, with the primary outcome being 90-day recurrence requiring...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Calcium ions play a critical role in calcification of Corynebacterium matruchotii]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lipocalin-2 upregulation in hypoxic murine osteocytes enhances RANKL-induced osteoclastogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteocytes regulate bone remodeling by interacting with osteoblasts and osteoclasts. Hypoxia influences osteocyte function and has been linked to increased osteoclastogenesis in pathological conditions such as orthodontic tooth movement (OTM) and bone metabolic diseases; however, the molecular mechanisms underlying these effects remain unclear. This study aimed to identify hypoxia-responsive genes in osteocytes and investigate their effects on osteoclastogenesis. Transcriptome analysis of murine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41495150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Hepatocyte Membrane-Based Culture System Recapitulating the Physiological Microenvironment of Hepatic Stellate Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liver fibrosis is a progressive disease primarily driven by the activation of hepatic stellate cells (HSCs). Understanding the mechanisms regulating HSC activation requires an in vitro model that accurately recapitulates the hepatic microenvironment. In vivo, quiescent HSCs form direct contact with hepatocytes (Heps) through fine dendritic processes known as spines, which are essential for maintaining liver architecture and homeostasis. However, conventional extracellular matrix (ECM)-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of lipopolysaccharide on energy metabolism and immune cell activation in different microglia model systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microglia, the brain's resident immune cells, constantly monitor their environment for signs of tissue damage or pathogens. Upon activation by stimuli like lipopolysaccharide (LPS), microglia undergo metabolic changes and release pro-inflammatory mediators. However, variations between human and rodent microglia, as well as differences between in vitro and in vivo conditions, likely influence microglial cellular functions and their responses to stimulation. In the present study, we compared...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Latitude and the effects of blue-blocking glasses in bipolar disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Numerical modeling of dissolved mercury dynamics and transformation in sea water in Minamata Bay, Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mercury pollution in Minamata Bay has remained a persistent environmental issue since the discovery of Minamata disease. In this study, hydrodynamic simulations were performed using Delft3D FLOW, and a mercury transformation model was developed with the OPEN PLCT module of the WAQ system. A precipitation-related freshwater inputs module was incorporated to capture the direct impact of precipitation on the water surface. The simulated concentrations of total dissolved mercury (THg) were generally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rare ABCA7 mutations in Alzheimer's disease and cerebral amyloid angiopathy pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rare mutations in the ATP binding cassette subfamily A member 7 (ABCA7) gene are known risk factors for Alzheimer's disease (AD). Genetic sequencing in 1372 Belgian patients previously revealed rare ABCA7 mutations in 102 carriers, 58 with a premature termination codon mutation (PTC) and 44 with a missense mutation. Among carriers, 14 received post-mortem examination. Here, we reviewed and report the demographics, clinicopathological phenotypes, and diagnoses of identified ABCA7 mutation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining the Factor Structure of Objective Health Literacy and Numeracy Scales: Large-Scale Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that scales of objective health literacy have at least three latent constructs (ie, conceptual knowledge, numeracy, and synthesis) and that disease specificity is not psychometrically prominent. Each factor has some overlap with subjective health literacy, but overall, subjective and objective health literacy should be interpreted as independent constructs, given the small-to-modest correlations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41494165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cholestasis-reducing effects of bezafibrate on survivors of biliary atresia with native livers: A prospective phase II trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: BZF decreased cholestasis markers in survivors of BA with native livers, indicating its potential as an alternative to delayed liver transplantation for this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simultaneous detection of elements and molecules using laser ablation-ICP-MS/MS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Detections of elements and molecules in coffee beans were carried out using single ICP-MS/MS coupled with a laser ablation sampling technique. For elemental analysis, laser-induced sample particles were introduced into the ICP, where the elements were ionized as M⁺ through the hard ionisation achieved in the high-temperature and atmospheric-pressure plasma (ICP). For molecular analysis, volatile organic compounds (VOCs) which were released from the solid material through laser-induced sample...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic factors influencing outcomes of allogeneic HCT for AML with monosomal karyotype]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monosomal karyotype (MK) comprises chromosomal abnormalities defined as either one single autosomal monosomy with structural abnormalities (MK1) or two or more distinct autosomal monosomies (MK2). MK is a predictive factor for extremely poor prognosis in patients with acute myeloid leukemia (AML), and not all patients are eligible for allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplantation (HCT). Using registry data from the Japan Society for Transplantation and Cellular Therapy, we retrospectively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A phase I/II study of tagraxofusp in Japanese patients with blastic plasmacytoid dendritic cell neoplasm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tagraxofusp (TAG), a first-in-class CD123-targeted therapy, is a recombinant fusion protein of human interleukin-3 conjugated to a truncated diphtheria toxin payload. Blastic plasmacytoid dendritic cell neoplasm (BPDCN) is an aggressive orphan hematologic cancer with a poor prognosis, and is derived from plasmacytoid dendritic cells that overexpress interleukin-3 receptor subunit alpha (IL3RA or CD123). This open-label phase I/II study evaluated the efficacy and safety of TAG in 11 Japanese...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Belantamab mafodotin, pomalidomide, and dexamethasone in Japanese patients with RRMM in the phase 3 DREAMM-8 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The phase 3 DREAMM-8 (NCT04484623) trial assessed belantamab mafodotin + pomalidomide + dexamethasone (BPd) vs bortezomib + Pd (PVd) in lenalidomide-exposed patients with relapsed/refractory multiple myeloma (RRMM) and ≥ 1 prior therapy. Here, we present findings from Japanese patients (data cutoff: 27-May-24). The primary endpoint was progression-free survival (PFS). Secondary endpoints included overall response rate (ORR), duration of response (DoR), and safety. Overall, 21 patients were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relapsing peritoneal dialysis‑associated peritonitis caused by Pseudomonas oryzihabitans with concurrent tunnel infection: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41493712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260107024452&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>