<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:22:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying biomechanical and neurophysiological risk factors for postoperative neurologic deterioration in OPLL surgery: A study using ROC curve and path analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The ∆OPLL(C5-C6) occupying area ratio appears to be a strong predictor of PMD and PSD in cervical OPLL surgery, potentially influencing outcomes primarily through neurophysiological changes. To help mitigate postoperative neurological complications, continuous neurophysiological monitoring and targeted biomechanical assessments may be beneficial components of the surgical planning process.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring FPUT thermalization with Toda integrals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We assess the ergodic properties of the Fermi-Pasta-Ulam-Tsingou-α model for generic initial conditions using a Toda integral. It serves as an adiabatic invariant for the system and a suitable observable to measure its equilibrium time. Over this time scale, the onset of action diffusion results in ergodic temporal fluctuations. We compare this time scale with the inverse of the maximum Lyapunov exponent λ and its saturation time, which are systematically shorter. The Toda integral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility on diverse biochars as supplementary cementitious materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the feasibility of using Korean-produced biochar derived from wood (WB), rice husk (HB), and poultry manure (MB) as a cement replacement in mortar. The physicochemical and microstructural characteristics of each biochar were analyzed, and mortar specimens containing 5% biochar were tested for flow and compressive strength. WB and HB showed favorable particle sizes and large specific surface areas, enhancing internal curing and filler effects, which resulted in up to 29%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integration of TLR7/8 agonists into lipid nanoparticles enhances antigen-specific immune responses to N1-methyl-Ψ-modified mRNA-LNP vaccines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bypassing Nonlocal Phenomena in Metals Using Phonon-Polaritons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electromagnetic design relies on an accurate understanding of light-matter interactions yet often overlooks electronic length scales. Under extreme confinement, this omission can lead to nonclassical effects such as nonlocal response. Here, we use mid-infrared phonon-polaritons in hexagonal boron nitride (hBN) screened by monocrystalline gold flakes to push the limits of nanolight confinement unobstructed by nonlocal phenomena, even when the polariton phase velocity approaches the Fermi...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physics-informed neural networks for programmable origami metamaterials with controlled deployment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Origami-inspired structures provide unprecedented opportunities for creating lightweight, deployable systems with programmable mechanical responses. However, their design remains challenging due to complex nonlinear mechanics, multistability, and the need for precise control of deployment forces. Here, we present a physics-informed neural network (PINN) framework for both forward prediction and inverse design of conical Kresling origami (CKO) without requiring pre-collected training data. By...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DNA extraction from a maize (<em>Zea mays</em> L.) seed without damaging germination ability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA extraction with reliable purity and concentration is essential for most of the molecular genetics studies. Extracting DNA from young leaves in seedling stage is advantageous because it causes less damage to remaining plant which can be further used for phenotypic analysis. DNA extraction from seeds is even more advantageous in terms of saving time, labor, space, and cost for germination. Maize is one of the most important food and feed sources and provides great materials for genetic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design, Synthesis, and Antiviral Activity of 8‑Aza Fluoroneplanocin Derivatives Targeting SAH Hydrolase and Viral RdRp]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA viruses such as SARS-CoV-2 and dengue virus pose global health threats, highlighting the urgent need for broad-spectrum antivirals with improved safety. We synthesized 8-aza Fluoroneplanocin derivatives designed to reduce cytotoxicity while maintaining antiviral potency. Among them, compound 3a, bearing an 8-aza adenine base, exhibited its potential broad-spectrum activity against SARS-CoV-2 (EC(50) = 12.2 μM) and dengue virus (E(50) = 37.4 μM), with no detectable cytotoxicity (CC(50) > 100...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Extraction Optimization and HPLC-based Quality Evaluation of Thiophenes from <em>Tagetes erecta</em> Roots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tagetes erecta L. is widely studied for its flower-derived lutein, which is known for promoting eye health. However, its roots contain uniquely thiophenes-absent from the flowers and leaves-which exhibit valuable bioactivity. Our recent study has reported on patent applications related to their efficacy in modulating benign prostatic hyperplasia, underscoring their pharmaceutical and functional potential. Despite this, no optimized extraction or quality evaluation of thiophene-rich T. erecta...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioengineered Extracellular Vesicles in Emerging Cancer Vaccine Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amid the evolving landscape of immunotherapy, the pursuit of safer, more precise, and broadly applicable vaccine platforms has intensified. While conventional technologies-such as lipid nanoparticle-based mRNA systems-achieved unprecedented success in infectious disease prophylaxis, their limitations in safety and durability have prompted the search for alternatives to address more complex immunological challenges, particularly in oncology. Within this context, extracellular vesicle (EV)-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning-Assisted Prediction of State of Health in Lithium Metal Batteries with Electrochemical Impedance Spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical impedance spectroscopy (EIS) offers a nondestructive means of diagnosis for the battery's state of health (SoH). However, traditional equivalent circuit-based approaches-relying on extensive modeling and fitting of complex EIS data such as real and imaginary impedance components, phase shift, and frequency-are time-consuming and heavily dependent on expert interpretation, which can compromise reliability. In this context, artificial intelligence-based models present a faster and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Growth of Platinum Monosulfide Nanoparticles on MXene via Single-Source Precursor for Enhanced Hydrogen Evolution Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[2D Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXene offers high electrical conductivity and a large surface area, making it attractive for electrocatalysis. However, its intrinsic hydrogen evolution reaction (HER) activity remains poor due to the lack of active catalytic sites. To activate the otherwise inert surface, platinum monosulfide (PtS) nanoparticles are synthesized directly on Ti(3)C(2)T(x) nanosheets via thermal decomposition of a single-source precursor, Pt(dmampS)(2), in a solution-based process. This direct...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Quantum Dot Photovoltaic Efficiency Through Defect Passivation and Triplet Energy Transfer with 9-Anthracenecarboxylic Acid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256207/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A dual-functional electron transport layer (ETL) is reported for PbS colloidal quantum dot (CQD) photovoltaics by incorporating 9-anthracenecarboxylic acid (ACA) into a zinc oxide (ZnO) matrix. Despite its favorable electron transport characteristics and appropriate band alignment, intrinsic defects in ZnO, such as oxygen vacancies, remain a limiting factor in device performance. The carboxylate functional group of ACA effectively passivates these defects, thereby reducing trap-assisted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256207/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metal Nanodot Array via Thin Oil Layer-Assisted Dropwise Solid-State Dewetting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precise control of metal nanodot arrays is crucial for optimizing their plasmonic, catalytic, and photonic properties. Fabrication methods for homogeneous nanodots generally rely on complex processes, such as lithography or layer-by-layer assembly. Recently, nanodot array fabrication via metal deposition, e.g., sputtering and thermal evaporation, has received attention due to its simplicity and scalability. However, structures produced by deposition are often inhomogeneous and suffer from size...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Giant Small-Molecule Donors With Controlled Backbone Planarity Afford High-Performance and Photostable Organic Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High power conversion efficiency (PCE) and long-term stability are critical requirements for the commercialization of organic solar cells (OSCs). Small-molecule donors (SMDs) are promising due to easy purification and excellent batch-to-batch reproducibility, but they suffer from poor morphological stability associated with their fast diffusion kinetics. Here, new giant small-molecule donors (GSMDs) are designed that combine increased molecular sizes with excellent optoelectronic properties,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visible Light-Driven Heterojunction Array Based on Type-I In<sub>2</sub>S<sub>3</sub>/In<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub> for Selective Multi-Gas Discrimination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Visible light-activated chemoresistive gas sensors offer a promising solution for minimizing power consumption, preventing material degradation, and enabling room temperature operation. However, their lower photon energy compared to UV light results in slower recovery and reduced sensitivity to NO(2), while detecting gases like volatile organic compounds and amines remains challenging. This work presents a visible light-driven gas sensor array based on type-I In(2)S(3)/In(2)O(3) heterostructure....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical coherence tomography-guided stent optimization for complex coronary lesions: the OCCUPI trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The current study identifies long lesions or small-vessel disease as the determinants of stent optimization following OCT guidance, with the achievement of stent optimization significantly associated with improved clinical outcomes. Stent expansion, apposition, and edge dissection, the three key components of the OCCUPI-OCT criteria, were highly predictive of favourable clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[c-Abl Kinase Targets Tight Junction Protein ZO-2 in Regulation of Cell Migration and Morphology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[c-Abl is a non-receptor tyrosine kinase involved in the regulation of cell migration and morphogenesis, but the underlying mechanism remains unclear. Here, we report the identification of tight junction protein ZO-2 as a bona fide substrate of c-Abl. We show that c-Abl directly binds to and phosphorylates the C-terminus of ZO-2. In addition, c-Abl stimulates the activity of JAK1, which subsequently phosphorylates the N-terminus of ZO-2. Using the RNAi-mediated knockdown/rescue strategy, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the missing middle in osseointegration: meso-scale topography between macro design and microroughness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Meso-scale topography offers a powerful yet underutilized strategy to enhance osseointegration. Future implant designs should adopt an integrative, hierarchical approach that combines microroughness with meso-scale structuring to achieve synergistic improvements in cellular behavior, mechanical stability, and early healing. This strategy aligns with the hierarchical organization of natural bone and holds the potential to overcome longstanding biological bottlenecks in implant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated remediation approach of pharmaceutical wastewater using <em>Pistia stratiotes</em> and its toxicity analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this research, biologically synthesized iron oxide(Fe(2)O(3)) nanoparticles and phytoremediation studies(Pistia stratiotes) were used to treat the pharmaceutical effluents. This study evaluated the effectiveness of phytoremediation and Fe(2)O(3)-based adsorption for treating pharmaceutical effluents. The biologically synthesized iron oxide nanoparticle was characterized through UV-DRS, FTIR, and SEM-EDAX. The size of Fe(2)O(3) ranged from 400-500nm. Phytoremediation achieved a maximum removal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multifunctional microfluidic bioelectronic suture for accelerated healing and wound monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sutures, owing to their mechanical stability and proximity to wound edges, are the most commonly used wound healing tools. However, conventional sutures are largely passive and functionally limited. Emerging fiber technologies can impart functionality to suture structures, and sutures capable of sensing or modulation have been developed. Nevertheless, a monolithic suture that integrates sensing, electrical stimulation, and controlled drug delivery within a single architecture has not been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic changes of natural killer cell immunophenotypes and receptors according to the mortality in the intra-abdominal murine sepsis model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The sustained impairment of NK cell phenotype is associated with lethal outcomes in sepsis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic factors in gastric cancer survivors comparing Cox proportional hazards and machine learning using a Korean National cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subwavelength grating-assisted silicon nitride edge coupler with relaxed alignment tolerance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose and realize a silicon nitride (SiN) edge coupler with enhanced alignment tolerance, achieved through the integration of a subwavelength grating (SWG) structure. The incident optical mode is guided from the SWG tri-tip to the main waveguide via two adiabatic transitions through intermediate bridge waveguides. The SWG tri-tip, composed of three laterally arranged SWG waveguides, provides a broader horizontal optical input region than a single-tip design, enhancing horizontal alignment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world persistence and compliance of denosumab versus alendronate among postmenopausal women with osteoporosis in Asia-Pacific]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Postmenopausal women with osteoporosis were more likely to be persistent and compliant with denosumab, compared with weekly oral alendronate.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Information-theoretic entropy and topological descriptor analysis of tin oxide (SnO₂) for structural and property prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent years, topological descriptors have emerged as powerful tools for exploring the structural complexity and physico-chemical behavior of molecular networks. While extensive studies have been devoted to nanostructures and dendrimer systems, the mathematical modeling of tin oxide (SnO₂)-a material of high importance in sensing, catalysis, and nanotechnology-remains largely unexplored. Motivated by this gap, we develop and compute some important topological descriptors of the graph...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RECAP-seq: restriction enzyme-based CpG-methylated fragment amplification for early cancer detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aberrant DNA methylation drives cancer development, yet current screening methods require substantial resources for targeted enrichment across multiple CpG-rich regions. Early cancer detection in cell-free DNA (cfDNA) presents additional challenges due to low circulating tumor DNA fractions (0.01-10%) that dilute cancer-specific signals. To address these limitations, we developed Restriction Enzyme-based CpG-methylated fragment AmPlification sequencing (RECAP-seq) to selectively enrich...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compact machine learning model for perioperative stroke prediction prior to surgery: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perioperative stroke significantly impacts postoperative outcomes. Current risk stratification methods for perioperative stroke prediction lack accuracy and practicality. We aimed to develop a machine learning (ML) model that improves both accuracy and usability for predicting perioperative strokes. Data from 36,502 patients at Seoul National University Hospital (SNUH) were utilized to develop and internally validate. An external validation was conducted using data from 404 patients at Boramae...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical and esthetic properties of denture base resins in relation to thermocycling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the shear bond strength (SBS), flexural strength, and color stability of three denture base resins (DBRs)-heat-polymerized (HEA), cold-polymerized (COL), and 3D-printed (TDP)-before and after thermocycling. SBS was evaluated after bonding COL to each DBR. Flexural strength was measured via three-point bending, and color stability with a colorimeter. Half of the specimens underwent 10,000 thermocycles to simulate aging. TDP (9.91 MPa) showed significantly lower SBS than HEA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amino acid metabolites as potential circulating biomarkers for sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenia, characterized by the loss of muscle mass and strength, is a multifactorial disorder, including metabolic disturbance. Plasma amino acids (AAs) regulate muscle protein synthesis and breakdown. This study evaluated plasma AA metabolites as potential biomarkers for sarcopenia using metabolomic analysis. We assessed 31 AA metabo lites in an age-matched discovery cohort (72 men, 36 women with sarcopenia; 72 and 36 controls) and a validation cohort (36 men, 46 women with sarcopenia; 128...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interface identification in micro-LED repair applications via depth profiling using femtosecond laser-induced breakdown spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The commercialization of micro light-emitting diode (micro-LED) display technology depends on the efficient transfer of millions of individual micro-LEDs onto display panels with high spatial precision and yield. However, the extremely high pixel density in 4 K and 8 K displays poses a significant challenge for defect-free transfer. To maintain display quality and ensure production viability, it is crucial to develop effective strategies for repairing defective chips. While conventional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redirecting microglia phenotype via inhibition of NFAT1 ameliorates deficits in mouse model of synucleinopathies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The abnormal deposition of α-synuclein (α-syn) and neuroinflammation are key features of synucleinopathies. We recently demonstrated that leucine-rich repeat kinase 2 (LRRK2) and nuclear factor of activated T cells 1 (NFAT1) modulate the neurotoxic inflammation in synucleinopathies mediated by microglia. Therefore, we hypothesized that targeting NFAT1 might ameliorate the microglial neurotoxicity in synucleinopathies. Here we utilized 11R-VIVIT, an NFAT1 inhibitory peptide, in in vivo, ex vivo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct crosstalk between GPCRs and ion channels via G proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent years, cryo-electron microscopy structures of ion channels in complex with G proteins have been resolved, providing insights into the molecular mechanisms underlying the crosstalk between G protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs) and ion channels. Downstream signaling initiated by GPCR activation can indirectly modulate ion channel activity. Alternatively, the direct binding of Gα or Gβγ subunits to ion channels can directly regulate their ion conduction activity. Recent cryo-electron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RPS24 microexon isoform as a novel biomarker for estrogen receptor-positive breast cancer progression and therapeutic resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alternative splicing significantly contributes to gene expression heterogeneity and disease progression, yet analyzing its dynamics in short genetic regions such as microexons remains challenging. Here we identified notable variations in ribosomal protein S24 (RPS24) splicing patterns across breast cancer subtypes and investigated this novel regulatory mechanism. To overcome the complexity of analyzing three consecutive microexons (3 bp, 18 bp and 22 bp), we developed a specialized approach...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNA-associated glycoconjugates highlight potential ambiguities in glycoRNA analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A recent ground-breaking study suggested that small RNA from mammalian cells can undergo N-glycan modifications (termed glycoRNA)¹. The discovery relied upon a metabolic glycan labeling strategy in combination with commonly used phase-separation-based RNA isolation. Following the reported procedure, here we likewise identify an N-glycosylated species in the RNA fraction. However, our results suggest that the reported RNase sensitivity of the glycosylated species depends on the specific RNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A survey on large language models in biology and chemistry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is reshaping biomedical research by providing scalable computational frameworks suited to the complexity of biological systems. Central to this revolution are bio/chemical language models, including large language models, which are reconceptualizing molecular structures as a form of 'language' amenable to advanced computational techniques. Here we critically examine the role of these models in biology and chemistry, tracing their evolution from molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SIRT3-IDH2 axis is a target of dietary fructose: implication of IDH2 as a key player in dietary carcinogen toxicity in mice colon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent epidemiological studies have shown that dietary fructose intake is associated with an increased risk of colorectal cancer, yet its specific molecular mechanisms in colon carcinogenesis remain underexplored. Here we investigate the molecular mechanisms by which dietary fructose contributes to colon carcinogenesis, focusing on the role of mitochondrial NADP^(+)-dependent isocitrate dehydrogenase 2 (IDH2). Using an unbiased multiomics approach (transcriptomics and proteomics), liver and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide health claims analysis of phenothiazine-associated retinopathy risk in chlorpromazine and perphenazine users]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We conducted a nationwide, retrospective cohort study to quantify the risk of phenothiazine-associated retinopathy among new users of chlorpromazine (n = 35,955) and perphenazine (n = 224,790) in South Korea between January 1, 2015, and December 31, 2023. Adults without prior phenothiazine prescriptions or retinopathy who received at least one week of either drug were identified in the Health Insurance Review and Assessment database. We compared incidence rates of overall retinopathy,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting dual-specificity phosphatase 23 to overcome chemoresistance and stem cell-like behavior in non-small cell lung cancer cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coevolutionary signals in multiple sequence alignments improve virulence factor prediction with an MSA Transformer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Identification of virulence factors (VFs) is critical for expanding our knowledge on bacterial pathogenesis and also for developing targeted strategies for the prevention and treatment of related infectious diseases. Understanding virulence factors requires to consider coevolutionary information, as it reveals the evolutionary interdependencies between amino acid residues, which can provide some biological insights into their functional and structural roles in bacterial pathogenicity. Previous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epigenome-wide profiling of trisomy 18 specific DNA methylation signatures in first-trimester chorionic villi]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: To our knowledge, this is the first comprehensive MC-seq-based analysis of T18-specific DNA methylation patterns in first-trimester chorionic villi. These findings suggest that DNA methylation changes may represent downstream consequences of chromosomal imbalance in T18 and provide a foundation for future investigations into its pathophysiology and the development of epigenetic biomarkers for early non-invasive detection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Star-branched polymer donors enabling high-performance organic solar cells with superior flexibility and intrinsic stretchability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emerging wearable electronics are anticipated to leverage the flexibility and stretchability of organic solar cells (OSCs). However, achieving a balance between power conversion efficiency (PCE) and mechanical robustness remains challenging, as the molecular structural modifications required for enhanced flexibility of photovoltaic materials typically compromise charge transport and extraction. Herein, we design and synthesize three star-branched polymer donors (SPDs: S1, S2, and S3) by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The "Picasso faces" of diabetic kidney disease - how the art of phenotyping and molecular biomarkers is transforming clinical nephrology: an observational study in patients with type 2 diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ACE, AIP, and the miRNAs hsa-miR-126-3p and hsa-miR-423-5p may support DKD phenotyping and kidney function prediction. Incorporating these markers into clinical models could enable the implementation of individualized nephroprotective strategies in patients with T2DM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluorescence Modulation Behavior of Quantum Dots under Alternating Electric Fields and Applications in Logic and Neuromorphic Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The triode, an electronic device that facilitates signal amplification or switching, has significantly contributed to signal amplification, advanced electronic technology research, practical problem-solving, and overall scientific and technological progress. This work develops a novel triode, namely a fluorescent triode, featuring a sandwich-like electrode/insulator/quantum dots/electrode architecture. It is demonstrated that compared to traditional DC voltage-based fluorescence modulation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel Blood-Based Test for Colorectal Cancer Detection Using Cell-Free DNA Fragmentomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This cfDNA-based blood test demonstrated high diagnostic accuracy for CRC and acceptable performance for AA. Its consistent performance across clinical subgroups suggests its potential as an effective noninvasive CRC screening tool.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Managing the move: HIV and coping for men moving to Johannesburg]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Men in South Africa are disproportionately underrepresented in HIV care, and men who migrate face challenges using HIV services. Positive coping skills are critical for effective healthcare decision-making, yet little is known how men's HIV status and mobility-related stressors affect their coping strategies. Johannesburg is home to ∼5 million people who have relocated from elsewhere, mostly men. From February-April 2024, we conducted a cross-sectional survey among men who moved to Johannesburg,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frailty is Linked to Lower Subjective Life Expectancy in Korean Middle-Aged and Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While Socioemotional Selectivity Theory suggests that individuals perceive their remaining time as limited with age, this perception may vary with health. This study examined differences in subjective life expectancy (SLE) between frail and non-frail middle-aged and older adults in South Korea across age groups. A cross-sectional sample was drawn from Wave 1 of the Korean Longitudinal Study of Aging. Propensity score matching produced two comparable groups (749 frail and 749 non-frail) with no...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Ultra-High Dose-Rate Radiotherapy (FLASH-RT) on the Hematopoietic and Immune Systems: An Animal Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultra-high dose-rate radiotherapy, also known as FLASH radiotherapy (FLASH-RT), reduces radiation-induced damage in several organs. This study aimed to compare the effects of FLASH-RT and conventional dose-rate radiotherapy (CONV-RT) at 3 Gy and 5 Gy of total-body irradiation (TBI) on the survival of the hematopoietic system, peripheral blood cells, and immune-related responses. C57BL/6N male mice were divided into controls (0 Gy), FLASH-RT (109 Gy/s), and CONV-RT (0.067 Gy/s) groups. FLASH-RT...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Focused Extracorporeal Shock Wave Therapy for Hemiplegic Shoulder Pain: A Randomized Crossover Pilot Study in Stroke Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results suggest that the application of F-ESWT in patients with stroke could alleviate HSP. However, further studies are required to confirm this benefit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting alcohol use disorder risk in firefighters using a multimodal deep learning model: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Firefighters constitute a high-risk occupational cohort for alcohol use disorder (AUD) due to chronic trauma exposure, yet traditional screening methodologies relying on self-report instruments remain compromised by systematic underreporting attributable to occupational stigma and career preservation concerns. This cross-sectional investigation developed and validated a multimodal deep learning framework integrating T1-weighted structural magnetic resonance imaging with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of home training program to improve health and physical fitness of individuals with spinal cord injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Home training using Thera-Band is feasible for persons with SCI to manage obesity and improve cardiopulmonary function, muscle strength, and endurance. It can facilitate the maintenance of physical activity in individuals with SCI who have limited mobility and access to training facilities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ataluren-Induced Functional Restoration of Neurofibromin in Fibroblasts From Neurofibromatosis Type 1 Patients With Nonsense Mutations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neurofibromatosis Type 1 (NF1) is an autosomal dominant genetic disorder caused by heterogeneous mutations in the tumor suppressor gene NF1. Neurofibromin, encoded by NF1, predominantly acts as a negative regulator of the RAS-MEK signaling pathway. Up to 30% of NF1 patients harbor nonsense mutations (NS) that introduce premature termination codons (PTCs). Ataluren is a well-characterized small molecule that acts as a nonsense suppressor by enhancing the ribosomal readthrough of PTCs. Here, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Challenging diagnosis of groove pancreatitis with severe gastric outlet obstruction: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this case of GP, pancreatoduodenectomy safely treated severe gastric outlet obstruction when a cancer diagnosis could not be excluded.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early pleuroparenchymal fibroelastosis mimicking lung malignancy: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Histopathology is essential for distinguishing PPFE from malignancy. Early diagnosis allows individualized therapy to slow progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transition Metal Nitrides: Multifunctional Catalysts and Energy Materials with Tailorable Architectures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transition metal nitrides (TMNs) exhibit notable multifunctionality due to their superior physicochemical and catalytic attributes. This review delineates their crystal architectures, thermodynamic robustness, and inherent merits such as enhanced catalytic activity, sintering resistance, and operational selectivity. Density functional theory analyses have illuminated their electronic, optical, vibrational, plasmonic, mechanical, and morphological characteristics. TMNs, including mono-, bi-, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Observation of Intrinsic Spin-Layer Coupling and Robust Valley Polarization in Bilayer MoS<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, direct evidence of intrinsic spin-layer coupling in bilayer MoS(2) through polarization-resolved photoluminescence measurements on fully suspended samples is presented. By eliminating substrate-induced symmetry breaking, such as electrostatic potential gradients and unintentional strain, the intrinsic valley dynamics of bilayer MoS(2) is isolated. The results reveal that the degree of circular polarization (DoCP) in bilayers remains significantly higher than that of monolayers across the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Room-Temperature Collective Quantum Emission Mediated by Wannier-Mott Excitons in CsPbBr<sub>3</sub> Nanowires]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Room-temperature collective quantum emission (RT-CQE), enabled by many-body interactions and phase-synchronized dipole oscillations, offers a promising path for scalable quantum photonics. Here, superfluorescence (SF) is demonstrated in CsPbBr(3) perovskite nanowires (NWs), facilitated by Wannier-Mott excitons with spatially delocalized wavefunctions and strong dipole-dipole interactions. The intrinsic quasi-1D geometry and occasional bundling promote preferential dipole alignment along the NW...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Evaluation of a Novel Dual-Mode Radiofrequency Device for Facial Laxity: A Case Series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The DENSITY dual-mode RF system is a safe, well-tolerated, and effective non-invasive option for treating facial skin laxity in individuals with darker skin tones. It offers a compelling alternative for single-session rejuvenation with minimal recovery time and high patient satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative validation of automated perfusion analysis software for ischemic penumbra estimation and EVT decision-making]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: JLK PWI demonstrates high technical and clinical concordance with RAPID, supporting its use as a reliable alternative for MRI-based perfusion analysis in acute stroke care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A rare PBX1 variant identified in adulthood: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Abnormalities in PBX1 represent a monogenic cause of congenital anomalies of the kidney and urinary tract (CAKUT). However, their phenotypic heterogeneity poses a challenge for timely detection, particularly in the absence of overt anomalies in the kidney and urinary tract. Here, we present a 28-year-old male diagnosed with a rare PBX1 nonsense variant identified during the evaluation of early-onset chronic kidney disease. As part of the initial workup for decreased renal function and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeepAttNet: deep neural network incorporating cross-attention mechanism for subject-independent mental stress detection in passive brain-computer interfaces using bilateral ear-EEG]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed rest-versus-rest paradigm and DeepAttNet enabled robust, subject-independent mental stress detection with a fairly high accuracy using only two-channel EEG recordings. This approach is expected to offer a practical solution for continuous stress monitoring, potentially advancing passive BCI applications outside laboratory settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using large language models for clinical staging of colorectal cancer from imaging reports: a pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study confirms that LLM-based NLP, with proper prompt engineering, can accurately extract clinical stages from CRC imaging reports, particularly in English-only contexts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive value of aortoiliac calcification of deceased donors for chronicity score of allograft baseline biopsies and graft outcomes in kidney transplantation: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Aortoiliac calcification in deceased donors is associated with older donor age, higher KDPI scores, and increased incidences of diabetes mellitus and TA. Although it correlated with donor-related risk factors known to influence graft outcomes, it did not independently predict graft function or survival. Therefore, its role in donor selection appears limited and warrants further validation through larger prospective studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyglycolic acid-cyanoacrylate complex for prevention of major intestinal anastomotic leakage in a rat model: an experimental animal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: No significant differences were observed in the macroscopic intra-abdominal findings or intraluminal bursting pressure between the groups. The only difference in PCC group was enhanced fibroblast activation at moderate levels compare to the control group. Further research is warranted to optimize material combinations and validate efficacy in larger preclinical and clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-port <em>versus</em> multiport robotic surgery in head and neck procedures: the emergence of a new platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accuracy comparison of direct Sanger sequencing, immunohistochemistry, and droplet digital polymerase chain reaction in detecting <em>BRAF</em> mutations in papillary thyroid carcinoma: a retrospective diagnostic accuracy study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: IHC and ddPCR demonstrated superior sensitivity compared to SS for detecting BRAF^(V600E) mutations in PTC. These findings support the use of IHC and ddPCR as more reliable alternatives to SS in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Y-shaped trivalent aptamer for targeted visualization and tracking of reprogrammed astrocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite extensive research into the diverse transformations and functions of astrocytes, conventional fluorescence immunohistochemistry for their distinct identification remains challenging and time-consuming, primarily due to the lack of cell surface binders specific to these glial cells. To address this limitation, we developed a specific and straightforward imaging strategy for primary astrocytes using cell surface-targeting aptamers. We identified a novel anti-astrocyte DNA aptamer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physically programmed vegan leather emulating the mechanical and sensory characteristics of animal leather from once-discarded gluten]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The production of animal-derived leather raises substantial environmental and ethical concerns, prompting the search for sustainable alternatives. However, most synthetic leathers are not biodegradable and fail to replicate the tactile and mechanical properties of natural hide, while bio-based films often exhibit poor toughness/elongation and hydration sensitivity. Here, we report a chemical toughener-free process that transforms wheat gluten-a widely available but underutilized plant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biodegradable Adhesive Systems for Bio-Integrated Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biodegradable adhesives, unlike their traditional counterparts, are engineered to bond to biological tissues while naturally degraded over time, thereby eliminating the need for removal procedures and reducing the risk of chronic inflammation. These unique features are particularly suitable for temporary biomedical applications such as wound closure, internal sealing, or integration with electronics for active/passive functions. The adhesive performance arises from the strategic combination of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiscale Engineering of Ion-Conducting Gels for Sustainable Bioelectronic Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ion-conducting gels are indispensable for bioelectronics, offering softness, high ionic conductivity, and biocompatibility. Nevertheless, sustaining robust performance under physiological conditions demands moving beyond isolated material or device innovations to a unified, multiscale design approach. At the material level, advances in polymer network engineering enable precise tuning of ion mobility, retention, and electrochemical stability, while simultaneously imparting mechanical toughness,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of glucagon-like peptide 1 receptor agonists across all health outcomes in type 2 diabetes: An umbrella review and evidence map of randomised controlled trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this study, GLP-1RAs were associated with cardiovascular, renal, and metabolic benefits in type 2 diabetes without increasing cancer risk, though gastrointestinal adverse events were common. Our findings support the clinical use of GLP-1RAs, with attention to individual risk profiles and treatment tolerability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Approach for Upcycling Textile Waste for Simultaneous Energy Recovery and Li-ion Battery Electrode Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing volume of textile waste, driven by fast fashion, presents significant environmental and economic challenges owing to limited recycling and high landfilling rates. This study introduces a sustainable upcycling strategy that converts denim waste (textile waste surrogate) into functional carbon materials for lithium-ion battery (LIB) anodes, using pyrolysis followed by KOH activation. The pyrolysis process yielded 13 wt% gas, 63 wt% liquid, and 24 wt% solid residues. The activated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Degradation Behavior of Co<sub>3</sub>O<sub>4</sub> Spinel OER Catalyst Under Dynamic Operation and Thermally Driven Healing in Alkaline Water Electrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Green hydrogen production suffers from the intermittent nature of renewable energy resources, which accelerates the degradation of electrocatalysts in water electrolyzers. Therefore, it is crucial to minimize the catalyst degradation under dynamic operating conditions. This study investigated the degradation behavior of an oxygen evolution reaction catalyst under two types of dynamic operation via controlling the voltage range, elapsed time at high voltage, and power fluctuation frequency....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expert Consensus Statement on the Disease Burden and Vaccination for Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV) Infection in Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) is a leading cause of acute respiratory infection in adults, with higher morbidity and mortality in older adults and those with COPD or asthma. Despite the burden, disease awareness remains low and treatment is limited to supportive care. Recent advances have led to the approval of multiple vaccines and updated guideline recommendations. We reviewed current literature, surveillance data, and international guidelines to assess the burden of RSV in adults and to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Very High Dose Immunoglobulin Treatment for Chronic Inflammatory Demyelinating Polyneuropathy: A Multicentre UK Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Very high dose immunoglobulin may be partially effective in a minority of subjects with CIDP. Subjects treated with very high dose immunoglobulin may have greater pre-treatment disability, be more likely to have another autoimmune disease, have worse post-treatment outcomes, and take longer to reach maximal improvement, than subjects on lower doses. Concurrent autoimmune disease may increase immunoglobulin-induced thromboembolic risk. Earlier consideration of alternative therapies...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Air-pollution-vulnerable industries and the prevalence of diabetic retinopathy: a county-level study in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the relationship between employment in industries vulnerable to air pollutant exposure and the county-level prevalence of diabetic retinopathy (DR) in the United States. A cross-sectional dataset of 3,127 counties was assembled by integrating 2020 emissions data for seven major ambient pollutants (NOₓ, PM₂.₅, PM₁₀, CO, NH₃, SO₂, and VOCs) with 2021 modeled DR prevalence estimates and 2020 workforce composition indicators from nationally representative datasets. Spatial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthetic Neuromelanin Particles for Metal-Free Photocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuromelanin, a brain pigment comprising a pheomelanin core encased in a eumelanin shell, offers a unique bioinspired blueprint for functional nanomaterials. Here, synthetic neuromelanin particles (NMPs) with tunable shell thicknesses are reported, prepared via co-polymerization of dopamine and L-cysteine under alkaline oxidative conditions. Electron microscopy and spectroscopy reveal a core-shell nanostructure in which sulfur-rich, spin-active pheomelanin cores are progressively shielded by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NanoBRET-Based Biosensor for High-Throughput Screening of RAB11A-FIP2 Interaction Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein-protein interactions (PPIs) are critical regulators of cellular processes and represent promising therapeutic targets. However, existing drug discovery approaches for PPI targeting, such as surface plasmon resonance, have inherent limitations, including their inability to fully recapitulate the cellular environment. To address these challenges, we developed a NanoBRET-based RAB11A activation biosensor that utilizes bioluminescence resonance energy transfer (BRET) to detect PPIs in live...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of ECPR initiation time and age on survival in out-of-hospital cardiac arrest patients: on the measurement and meaning of ECPR initiation time: author's reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated endoscopic image quality assessment for robust colorectal lesion detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does experience translate? A multicenter evaluation of the learning curve in single-port robotic prostatectomy based on prior multiport proficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-port robot-assisted radical prostatectomy (SP-RARP) offers potential benefits over multiport RARP (MP-RARP), including fewer incisions and reduced postoperative pain. However, the influence of prior MP-RARP experience on early SP-RARP learning curves remains unclear. We retrospectively analyzed 622 consecutive SP-RARP cases performed by four surgeons with differing MP-RARP caseloads (> 1,000, > 400, > 200, and > 100) across multiple centers. The primary endpoint of this study was the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sealing stretchable electronics through a viscoplastic surface effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization and benchmarking of complete 4D transverse phase space for high-intensity ion beams using novel virtual pepper-pot technique]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precise and fast measurement of transverse beam properties is essential for understanding and optimizing particle beams. In this study, a multi-diagnostic approach is employed for high-dimensional transverse phase space reconstruction of high-intensity ion beams. This includes conventional single-slit scanning and the standard pepper-pot technique. In addition to these methods, a novel diagnostic tool called the Virtual Pepper-Pot (VPP), has been developed and implemented for the first time in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasmon-Driven Dimerization Reveals the Propagation Length of Surface Plasmon Polaritons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface plasmon polaritons (SPPs) propagate along metal-dielectric interfaces for tens of micrometers, converting light into confined electromagnetic waves. When an SPP encounters a nanoscale impeder, a part of its energy converts to localized surface plasmons (LSPs); this local conversion and energy loss are characterized by its 1/e decay distance, called the propagation length. Albeit powerful, conventional optical methods that probe radiative energy decay provide an incomplete picture of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hiatal Hernia-Related Esophageal Varices Misdiagnosed as Cancer: Salvaged With Clipping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 61-year-old man presented with hematemesis following a biopsy of a distal esophageal lesion initially suspected to be malignancy. Emergency endoscopy revealed tortuous submucosal vessels with active bleeding at the biopsy site. Band ligation failed due to poor suction, and hemostasis was successfully achieved using hemoclips. Imaging showed no evidence of cirrhosis or portal hypertension, but a large hiatal hernia compressing the distal esophagus was noted. At 2-week follow-up, 2 hemoclips...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Causal Relationship between Potential Shift and Molecular Structure in Concentrated Electrolytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the origin of potential shifts in concentrated electrolytes is crucial for the design of stable and high-energy-density lithium-metal batteries. In our previous work, we identified a strong correlation between experimental electrode potential and Li^(+)-anion interactions, suggesting the importance of intermolecular structure beyond conventional molecular properties. In this study, we revisit this issue from the perspective of causal discovery. We applied the Linear Non-Gaussian...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing contaminant leaching from concrete in water storage tanks using non-target screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Concrete is widely used for drinking water storage, yet it can leach organic compounds that may affect water quality. In response to the EU Drinking Water Directive (2021), all materials in contact with drinking water, including concrete, must be approved before installation by 2027. This study used non-target screening to support this process by analyzing chemical leaching from concrete. The three tested concrete types released similar compounds, mainly polyethylene glycols (PEGs), with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A tungsten-based solar absorber with a strip-combined starfish structure with high photothermal conversion efficiency and low radiative heat loss]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose a tungsten-based broadband resonator capable of achieving near-perfect solar absorption with suppressed radiative heat loss. Across the entire solar radiation spectrum, the absorber exhibits a spectrally integrated total solar absorptance of 95%. Taking into account the thermal emission under an operating temperature of 100 °C, the photothermal conversion efficiency remains as high as 92-93%. Using particle swarm optimization, the initial square-based structure is transformed into...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electron Donor-Acceptor (EDA) Complex Formation via Spatial Control of Donor-Acceptor Interactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electron donor-acceptor (EDA) complexes are of fundamental importance and practical utility in photoactive molecules, including fluorescence probes and photoredox catalysts. However, the design guidelines for developing efficient intramolecular EDA complexes are still underdeveloped. In this study, we systematically investigate the linker structures between an indole electron donor and a dinitrobenzene electron acceptor within single-molecule EDA complexes to optimize their relative positions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel lytic phages improve the antibiofilm activity of dalbavancin, daptomycin, and fosfomycin against vancomycin-resistant enterococci]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Periprosthetic joint infections (PJI) caused by Enterococcus spp., especially vancomycin-resistant strains (VRE), are challenging to treat due to biofilm tolerance and limited antibiotic options. Bacteriophages offer a promising adjunct through targeted and biofilm-disrupting activity. This study evaluated two novel lytic phages, alone and combined with last-line antibiotics, for their ability to eradicate VRE biofilms in vitro. Two novel lytic phages, CUB-FM (E. faecium) and CUB-FS (E....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pressure-dependent structure of neat liquid methanol, CH3OH: Molecular dynamics simulations with various united atom-type potentials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Molecular dynamics computer simulations have been conducted on neat liquid methanol, using three different "united atom" (three site) interatomic potentials: TraPPE [Chen et al., J. Phys. Chem. B 105, 3093 (2001)], UAM-I [García-Melgarejo et al., J. Mol. Liq. 323, 114576 (2021)], and OPLS/2016 [D. Gonzalez-Salgado and C. Vega, J. Chem. Phys. 145, 034508 (2016)]. The effects of pressure, between 1 bar and 6 kbar, have been evaluated on total scattering structure factors, partial radial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of three novel loci involved in reduced seed-shattering behaviour of an aus rice cultivar, Oryza sativa Kasalath]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reduced seed shattering is a key yield-improving trait selected during the domestication of the Asian rice, Oryza sativa, from its wild ancestor, O. rufipogon. Three quantitative trait loci, qSH1, sh4, and qSH3, are reported to be involved in the reduced seed-shattering behaviour of cultivated rice. Genotyping surveys of these loci have shown that the sh4 mutation is conserved in all cultivars, whereas the qSH1 mutation is only observed in some japonica cultivars. Furthermore, the qSH3 mutation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic impact of leuprorelin acetate on spinal and bulbar muscular atrophy: pre- and post-marketing observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although leuprorelin acetate, a luteinizing hormone-releasing hormone agonist, has been approved based on short-term clinical trials conducted in Japan, its long-term efficacy on physical function remains unclear. We aimed to evaluate the long-term therapeutic efficacy of leuprorelin acetate using real-world clinical data through a self-controlled trend-shift analysis. The analysis included 91 genetically confirmed patients with spinal and bulbar muscular atrophy, with follow-up data collected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors associated with period of sick leave after gynecologic cancer treatment: a prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with gynecologic cancer requiring long-term treatment required the most time to return to work.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for postoperative swallowing dysfunction in elderly patients undergoing gastrointestinal cancer surgery: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Swallowing function declines transiently after gastrointestinal cancer surgery in elderly patients. Older age, sarcopenia, MMSE ≤ 23, and preoperative Fujishima Grade 8 are independent predictors of postoperative swallowing dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world short-term outcomes after distal pancreatectomy with en bloc celiac axis resection using the National clinical database of Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although specific mortality risk factors could not be identified, the low mortality rate suggests that DP-CAR is safely performed in Japanese practice. Future efforts should focus on achieving zero DP-CAR-associated mortality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A robust decision framework for vertical farming using integrated objective weighting and distance driven ranking approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vertical Farming Techniques cultivates plants without soil, leading to greater productivity and profit. This unconventional farming technique requires minimal resources while producing high-quality yields. This study offers a comprehensive analysis of these methods, including hydroponics, aquaponics, aeroponics and fogponics. The quantification of uncertainty and ambiguity is done by employing the q-rung picture fuzzy set. This study introduces a novel hybrid Logarithmic percentage change-driven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrective osteotomy for malunited distal radius fracture using an augmented reality (AR) osteotomy guide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tooth loss, dental prosthesis use, and cause-specific mortality in older Japanese adults: a 7-year cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Poor oral health, particularly tooth loss, is associated with increased risk of all-cause mortality. However, the impact of dental prosthesis use on these associations remains unclear. This study evaluated the relationship between the number of remaining teeth, dental prosthesis use, and mortality from specific causes using seven-year follow-up data from the Japan Gerontological Evaluation Study (JAGES). All-cause mortality and ten cause-specific mortality outcomes were assessed. The number of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In-depth 3D exploration of autosomal dominant polycystic kidney disease through light sheet fluorescence microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autosomal Dominant Polycystic Kidney Disease (ADPKD) is the most prevalent genetic kidney disorder. Animal preclinical studies are one of the main tools to study this disease, often through either 2D histology imaging for high-resolution analysis or CT or MRI for full kidney segmentation. As an alternative to these modalities, we propose the use of Light Sheet Fluorescence Microscopy (LSFM) for high-resolution 3D imaging of healthy and ADPKD-induced mouse kidneys, enabling a detailed volumetric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Production of offspring via the transplantation of frozen germ cells from Tokyo bitterling, a fish on the brink of extinction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many freshwater fish face extinctions due to habitat destruction and overfishing. Bitterlings, which lay their eggs in the gill chambers of freshwater mussels, are in steep decline worldwide, along with mussels, owing to the concreting and siltation of riverbeds. In particular, Tokyo bitterling is listed as "endangered" on the Red List and is on the verge of extinction. Although in situ and ex situ conservation efforts are underway, their effectiveness is limited. Here, we developed a method for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary and oral factors associated with eating slowly and chewing well: a National web-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several studies have investigated manner of eating, such as "eating slowly" or "chewing well," to prevent being overweight and obese. In Japan, one of the goals of the "Basic Act on Shokuiku" (Food and Nutrition Education), is "to increase the number of people who eat slowly and chew their food well." Therefore, this cross-sectional study aimed to clarify the factors associated with eating slowly and chewing well. Survey forms were randomly distributed to national-based monitors from an online...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TORC2 inactivation promotes heterochromatin formation in rDNA and prolongs viability of quiescent fission yeast cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A large amount of the energy produced by glucose is consumed in the biogenesis of ribosomes, the cellular machinery for protein synthesis. Recent studies suggest that a low-calorie diet and the suppression of ribosome biogenesis can extend lifespan. However, the molecular mechanisms underlying these phenomena remain elusive. Here, we demonstrate that TORC2 (TOR complex 2) promotes ribosomal RNA (rRNA) transcription by facilitating the association of Paf1C (RNA polymerase II-associated factor 1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disease-specific alterations of the enteric nervous system in precancerous colonic mucosa and their implications for mucin regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The dynamics of enteric glial cells (EGCs), the most prevalent cell type of the enteric nervous system (ENS), remain to be fully elucidated. Here, we analyzed the number and spatial distribution of Sox10 + mucosal EGCs in the human lower gastrointestinal tract. In the histologically normal mucosa, an average of 3.5 EGCs were present in each intercrypt region, with a higher concentration near the crypt base. Sex and anatomical location significantly influenced EGC numbers, while aging altered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First imported cases of MPXV Clade Ib from Goma, Democratic Republic of the Congo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Given the expansion of regional mpox outbreaks and populations considered at-risk, these findings underscore how mpox case investigations and community messaging should include considerations for non-sexual human-human transmission of Clade Ib that includes children <15 years.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41258006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacist follow-up of patients prescribed nirmatrelvir/ritonavir: a single-center retrospective analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment with L-type amino acid transporter 1 inhibitor JPH203 enhances protein synthesis in C2C12 myotubes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Excessive muscle protein synthesis causes skeletal muscle hypertrophy. Essential amino acids are substrates for muscle proteins and stimulate muscle protein synthesis. Several essential amino acids are taken up into muscle cells through L-type amino acid transporter 1 (LAT1). However, LAT1 may influence protein synthesis in an amino acid uptake-independent manner. Here, we investigated the effects of LAT1 inhibition on protein synthesis in C2C12 myotubes and the associated mechanisms. JPH203 (50...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complex dissociation following maternal suicide attempt in a 17-year-old female: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case highlights a rare presentation of dissociative amnesia with stupor and conversion disorder. The diagnosis was initially challenging owing to amnesia masking the stressor. Careful exclusion of organic causes and thorough psychological assessment were key. This case underscores the importance of identifying underlying trauma in complex dissociative presentations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between anthropometric indices and body fat for identifying excess body fat in elementary school children: a population-based cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that BMI and degree of obesity are strongly associated with body fat percentage across the 85th, 90th, and 95th percentiles and that obesity classifications based on BMI as well as degree of obesity align closely with those based on body fat percentage.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infrared thermography for detecting compensatory load in people with haemophilia: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Temperature increases occurred in areas beyond the painful area, suggesting strain even in asymptomatic regions. People with haemophilia experiencing pain may require careful monitoring and treatment of surrounding areas. Our findings could aid in diagnosing haemorrhage and local inflammation while informing treatment decisions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of an electronic library in forensic psychiatric wards: a survey of its actual use by forensic inpatients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The prevalence of depression and anxiety and associated factors among school-going adolescents in poverty and conflict-affected settings in Uganda]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A substantial proportion of school-going adolescents in Uganda report at least moderate symptoms of depression and anxiety. Government and public sector agencies should re-evaluate their strategies at both family and school levels, particularly in underserved settings. Schools can serve as platforms for screening-and-referral pathways and group-based psychosocial programs, while the health system should strengthen capacity for co-occurring conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking category selectivity: insights from the macaque inferior temporal cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ritchie et al. argue that the traditional framework of category selectivity has limited value for understanding the organization of the ventral visual stream and propose shifting focus toward behavioral relevance and examining vision under naturalistic task conditions. While I agree with many of their points, I expand on their discussion of category selectivity, as well as the drivers of ventral stream organization, from a nonhuman primate perspective.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct observation of an ionic cobalt complex electron mediator <em>via operando</em> X-ray absorption spectroscopy in photocatalytic Z-scheme CO<sub>2</sub> reduction with (CuGa)<sub>0.3</sub>Zn<sub>1.4</sub>S<sub>2</sub> and BiVO<sub>4</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Real-time Co(II)/Co(III) redox state transitions of cobalt complex electron mediators during aqueous Z-scheme CO(2) reduction with oxide and sulfide photocatalysts were directly observed by operando X-ray absorption spectroscopy. This approach provides a general framework for advancing mechanistic understanding of ionic redox mediator-driven artificial photosynthesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Multifaceted Ganzfeld at the Crossroad Between Visual Perception and Consciousness: Behavioral, Neural and Qualitative Aspects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A Ganzfeld is a homogeneous visual field, devoid of any focal points. Such a stimulus has been used by researchers to study perceptual phenomena in the absence of changes in sensory structure. Others have used it to study altered states of consciousness (ASCs). Until now, these different facets have been studied separately with little attention for the emotional subjective experience. This study aimed to elucidate the perceptual, phenomenal, and emotional experience of the multifaceted Ganzfeld...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A chimeric RNA consisting of siRNA and aptamer for inhibiting dengue virus replication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silencing viruses by chimeric RNAs, wherein small interfering RNAs (siRNAs) targeting viral RNAs are conjugated with RNA aptamers specific to viral envelope proteins, is a promising treatment for viral infection diseases; however, practical evaluations are apparently lacking. Here, we present a chimeric RNA comprises siRNA and RNA aptamer, both of which target all four serotypes of dengue virus (DENV), for suppressing DENV replication. The siRNA targeting consensus sequences in the 3'-UTR of all...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reversible temperature-induced shape transition of Pt nanoparticles supported on Al<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Supported platinum catalysts are widely used in industry for hydrogenation reactions. The variations of the electronic and geometric properties of Pt nanoparticles due to temperature can greatly affect their reactivity. In this work, we use in situ X-ray absorption spectroscopy and environmental transmission electron microscopy to study the effect of H(2) and temperature on the shape and electronic properties of 1.8 nm average diameter Pt nanoparticles supported on Al(2)O(3). We utilize actively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of the sucrose concentrations and incubation periods on in vitro pollen germination and pollen tube growth in three rice cultivars]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-quality pollen grains are essential for artificial cross pollination and grain production. The optimization of culture conditions for in vitro pollen germination is useful for evaluating pollen quality. However, there is limited information on in vitro pollen germination system for rice (Oryza sativa L.). Therefore, this study aimed to develop an efficient pollen germination system for rice and determine the optimal incubation period, incubation temperature, and sucrose concentration. Three...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Free <em>N</em>-glycans occurring in plant extracellular fluid or cytosol interact with an auxin, indole-3-acetic acid: Putative biofunction of free <em>N</em>-glycans in plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two types of free N-glycans (FNGs), high mannose type (HMT) and plant complex type (PTC), occur ubiquitously in plants, the former mainly in the cytoplasm and the latter in the vacuole or extracellular fluid. It has been hypothesized that these plant FNGs have auxin-like activity that promotes fruit ripening based on the experimental results of adding FNGs to plant tissues; however, the postulated biological functions have not been proven at this time. In this study, using fluorescence analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide association study identifies candidate genes contributing to flowering time variation in <em>Lotus japonicus</em> in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flowering time is an important factor in plant fitness and local adaptation. Genome-wide association (GWA) studies have allowed the identification of candidate genes in certain plant species for various traits, including flowering time. Lotus japonicus is widely found throughout the Japanese archipelago. To obtain flowering time data with more prominent difference as more suitable indicator of environmental adaptation, flowering time data were collected for 132 wild accessions originating from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxylipin KODA enhances the early growth of rice (<em>Oryza sativa</em> L.) under low-temperature stress at night to simulate a natural temperature condition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[α-Ketol octadecadienoic acid (KODA), an oxylipin, has stimulatory effects on flowering, rooting, and resistance to pathogens. It also increases the yield of rice, Oryza sativa L. Here we examined the effects of KODA on the early growth of rice under various temperature conditions. KODA was applied by imbibing seeds in 1 µM KODA solution overnight. KODA treatment did not promote the growth at 25°C or 28°C, which are appropriate temperatures for rice cultivation. At a constant temperature of 15°C,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward the commercialization of recombinant pharmaceuticals expressed in plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent developments have shown that the production of recombinant proteins in plants is more useful than in microbial, insect, or mammalian cell-based expression systems in terms of cost-effectiveness, scalability, safety, and sustainability. Furthermore, transient expression systems in plants may be superior to stable transgenic plants in terms of cost, yield, environmental impact, and regulation compliance. Recombinant proteins, such as enzymes, growth factors, scaffolds, and antibodies are in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41257068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current Usage of Extracorporeal Photopheresis in Solid Organ Transplantations in Europe: A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solid organ transplantation (SOT) faces significant challenges in managing allograft rejection, with current immunosuppressive therapies often associated with substantial adverse effects. Extracorporeal photopheresis (ECP) has emerged as a promising adjunctive treatment for rejection prevention and management in heart and lung transplants, with growing evidence supporting its use in kidney and liver transplants. Despite this, the availability of ECP and its place in standard treatment pathway is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current roles of colonoscopy in minimally invasive colorectal surgery: Preoperative guidance, intraoperative colonoscopy, and combined endoscopic-laparoscopic surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colonoscopy is a cornerstone in the detection and diagnosis of colorectal tumors, playing a critical role in both screening and clinical evaluation. More recently, its utility has expanded to therapeutic guidance, particularly with the advent of minimally invasive surgical techniques. Preoperative tattoo marking is commonly used for tumor localization; however, it poses challenges such as intraperitoneal ink scattering and difficulty in defining dissection planes in the lower rectum. To address...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case report of rare right intraventricular thrombus: a diagnostic and anticoagulation management challenge]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Antiphospholipid syndrome (APS) is a rare autoimmune disorder characterized by an increased risk for both arterial and venous thrombosis. This case of a right intraventricular thrombus mimicking a cardiac tumour highlights the complexities of anticoagulation management in APS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41256192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mid-to long-term outcomes and CT-assessed radiolucency with cemented single-peg glenoid component for anatomic total shoulder arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The cemented single-peg glenoid component for aTSA showed 100 % implant survival at mid-to long-term follow-up. Radiolucency was associated with larger CSA and superior humeral head subluxation but was not associated with worse clinical outcomes. CT assessment using both axial and coronal planes was a useful method for providing a more accurate evaluation of radiolucency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-based design of a sequence-specific RNA probe that mimics the kink-turn motif]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The technology for sequence-specific detection of RNA is in high demand in the medical field as well as in basic research in life sciences. Various methods for detecting RNA have been developed so far, but all of them are designed based solely on the rules of base complementarity, which leads to the false detection of unrelated RNAs with very similar sequences. In this study, we challenged the biomimetics approach at the molecular level to develop a sequence-specific RNA probe by mimicking a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Water-ethanol separation with Janus tip charged carbon nanotubes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ethanol is an important industrial substance, serving both as a solvent and fuel. In particular, from the perspective of producing bioethanol as an alternative fuel, there is a need for methods that can separate water and ethanol with lower energy consumption. Using molecular dynamics simulations, we investigate the selectivity for water and ethanol molecules with Janus tip charged carbon nanotubes (CNTs), where one tip is positively charged and the other negatively charged. These charges...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cyclic Tetraindoles With a Cyclooctatetraene Core: Controlling Planarity and Antiaromatic Character via N-Alkylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyclooctatetraene (COT), a representative 4n π-electronic system, typically exhibits nonaromatic character in highly twisted structures, but planarization significantly alters its electronic properties, increasing antiaromaticity. Therefore, investigations on the structure-property relationships of COT derivatives are essential for the development of future functional materials. In this study, we have developed a series of cyclic tetraindoles possessing a central COT ring. The degree of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI in Healthcare: Identity Threat or Opportunity? Insights From Medical Specialists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent years, artificial intelligence (AI) has gradually permeated the medical sector, bringing about multifaceted changes in healthcare practices. Existing studies demonstrate significant gains of AI for clinical application in terms of performance and innovation. While this literature largely emphasizes technological advancements, it often overlooks AI's human and professional implications. AI may not replace humans in the near future due to ethical, legal, and technical constraints, but it...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Composition to Ionic Conductivity: Machine Learning-Guided Discovery and Experimental Validation of Argyrodite-Type Lithium-Ion Electrolytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The discovery of solid-state electrolytes (SSEs) with high lithium-ion conductivities is critical for advancing all-solid-state batteries. However, prior efforts have largely focused on structure-driven design. This study presents a composition-based machine learning framework, Elements-To-Ionics (E2I), for the accurate prediction and optimization of the ionic conductivities of argyrodite-type SSEs using only their elemental compositions. Guided by these predictions, a series of Si-Sn, Ge-Si,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41255030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating morphology and genetics to resolve the first reptilian liolopid life cycle in Africa, <em>Paraharmotrema karinganiense</em> (Digenea: Liolopidae)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To enhance patient care ownership: A baseline cross-sectional study on pediatric training]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Shiftwork, mental well-being, and PCO might be positively related to one another. A feeling of accomplishment, or a sense of meaning in work, can be a target of intervention to enhance PCO while promoting trainees' well-being.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Organophotoredox-Catalyzed Trifluoromethylative Cyclization of Alkenoic Thioesters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the visible-light-induced trifluoromethylative cyclization of alkenoic thioesters, enabling the synthesis of CF(3)-substituted sulfur heterocycles without metals. Organophotocatalysts promote efficient radical cyclization with a broad substrate scope and high diastereoselectivity. Mechanistic studies indicate an oxidative quenching pathway initiated by photocatalyst-reagent interactions, and theoretical calculations reveal that the conformational bias of the carbocation intermediate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive long-read sequencing system to assess DNA methylation at differentially methylated regions and imprinting-disorder-related genes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We established a T-LRS system targeting all ID-related regions, defined standard MI ranges in CpGs on each parental allele, and demonstrated the usefulness of T-LRS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reverse translational research of transient magnetic resonance imaging hyperintensity following intracranial stem cell therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that the transient FLAIR hyperintensity observed following intracerebral stem cell therapy is primarily attributed to transient glial cell activation, resulting in increased AQP4 expression and transient brain water influx. Additional mechanisms, including vesicle-mediated transport, secretion, synaptic activity, and lipid signaling, also contribute to the transient FLAIR hyperintensity signals and may play a role in the manifestation of clinical symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Renal transcriptome-wide analyses in association with kidney black carbon load]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Here, we identified genes and pathways associated with real-life kidney BC particle load, indicating alterations in gene expression involved in assembly and maintenance of primary cilia, the anti-inflammatory properties of the innate immune system, and DNA damage-related pathways. These findings highlight the need for public health measures to reduce exposure and protect kidney health in at-risk populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical efficacy of sitafloxacin-containing regimens for Mycobacterium avium complex pulmonary disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Controversial efficacy of antithrombin followed by recombinant thrombomodulin administration in patients with sepsis-induced disseminated intravascular coagulation: an analysis of postmarketing surveillance data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: efficacy of rTM administration following AT supplementation in patients with sepsis-induced DIC is controversial, and the evidence is restricted to decreasing mortality rates in patients with JAAM-defined DIC scores >6 and SOFA scores>9. However, further studies are needed to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondria transplantation mitigates attenuation of muscle fiber regeneration by evoked contractions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rest is generally required for full muscle regeneration after an injury; however, rehabilitative activity is often used after injury to attempt a faster recovery. While rehabilitative activity can enhance muscle regeneration, there is also a risk that returning to vigorous muscle contractions too early after sustaining an injury, could reinjure the muscle, and negatively impact full muscle regeneration. It is not known whether MT added to rehabilitative muscle activity would speed regeneration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Therapeutics of Staying]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Remembrance of Professor Zelig Eshhar: <em>A Life Committed to CAR-T</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital cognitive behavior therapy to reduce perinatal anxiety symptoms: perceptions of implementation barriers and facilitators among providers serving historically marginalized communities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While clinicians and service providers viewed digital CBT-specifically Daylight-as acceptable and beneficial for increasing access among marginalized perinatal populations, critical implementation considerations emerged during the focus groups. Addressing these factors through tailored strategies and culturally relevant adaptations is essential for successful implementation, particularly when scaled to healthcare settings. Future research should further explore these issues to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure in Adolescence and Atherosclerosis in Middle Age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this population-based cohort study, higher BP levels in adolescence were associated with a dose-dependent higher risk for atherosclerosis in middle age, particularly for severe coronary atherosclerosis. Excess risks of atherosclerosis were even evident in the elevated BP range in adolescence as defined by the 2025 ACC/AHA and 2024 ESC BP guidelines.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of carboplatin schedule on pCR in a modified KEYNOTE-522 regimen with dose-dense AC for triple negative breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this single-center analysis, every three-week carboplatin dosing followed by ddAC in a modified KEYNOTE-522 regimen provides higher pCR rates at the time of surgery. Patients who received weekly carboplatin dosing experienced more iHSR. These findings strongly warrant additional studies to determine the relationship of carboplatin dosing to TNBC outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Ambulatory Specialty Model-Imitation or Innovation?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recommendations from the IFCC Working Group on Laboratory Errors and Patient Safety for the Global Adoption of an Essential Quality Indicators Panel in Laboratory Medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The proposed essential QI panel provides a standardized and feasible framework to support its integration into national comparison programs and the IFCC MQI platform. Its implementation will facilitate data consolidation, strengthen the development of national and global quality specifications, and contribute to continuous improvement in patient safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor cell-specific loss of GPX4 reprograms triacylglycerol metabolism to escape ferroptosis and impair antitumor immunity in NSCLC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glutathione peroxidase 4 (GPX4) is a master regulator of ferroptosis, a process that has been proposed as a potential therapeutic strategy for cancer. Here we have unexpectedly found that inducible knockout of GPX4 in tumor cells significantly promotes non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) progression in the autochthonous Kras LSL-G12D/+ Lkb1 fl/fl (KL) and Kras LSL-G12D/+ Tp53 fl/fl (KP) mouse models, whereas inducible overexpression of GPX4 in tumor cells exerts the opposite effect....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Review of Early-Onset Gastrointestinal Cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lung Cancer Deaths Prevented and Life-Years Gained From Lung Cancer Screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41259039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119142220&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>