<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:40:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Astrocytic monoamine oxidase B (MAOB)-gamma-aminobutyric acid (GABA) axis as a molecular brake on repair following spinal cord injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroregeneration and remyelination rarely occur in the adult mammalian brain and spinal cord following central nervous system (CNS) injury. The glial scar has been proposed as a major contributor to this failure in the regenerative process. However, its underlying molecular and cellular mechanisms remain unclear. Here, we report that monoamine oxidase B (MAOB)-dependent excessive γ-aminobutyric acid (GABA) release from reactive astrocytes suppresses the CNS repair system by reducing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, POSTECH, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The WHO pandemic agreement: why countries will not use compulsory licensing - and how to fix it]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma Exosomes from Viral Hemorrhagic Septicemia Virus-Infected Olive Flounder (Paralichthys olivaceus): Proteomic Insights and Wound Healing Effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles (EVs) or their sub types, such as exosomes are valuable nano-biomolecules for immunotherapeutic, drug delivery, and diagnostic purposes. Freshwater and marine fish, including olive flounder (Paralichthys olivaceus), are highly susceptible to the contagious Viral hemorrhagic septicemia virus (VHSV). In this study, we aimed to determine how infection alters the biological responses by analyzing the proteomic profiles of plasma-derived exosomes from phosphate buffered saline...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Threshold-based analysis of eutrophication dynamics in a semi-enclosed bay: The dominant role of dissolved inorganic nitrogen in Masan Bay, South Korea (2010-2015)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eutrophication in semi-enclosed coastal systems remains a persistent concern due to restricted water circulation and continuous nutrient inputs. To better characterize nutrient-driven water quality degradation, we applied a threshold-based analysis to seasonal monitoring data collected from Masan Bay, South Korea, between 2010 and 2015. Eutrophication status was assessed using a composite Eutrophication Index (EI) integrating chemical oxygen demand (COD), dissolved inorganic nitrogen (DIN), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of Co/Co<sub>2</sub>N<sub>0.67</sub> nanoparticles embedded S and N-doped carbon from a cobalt-complex as a bifunctional Electrocatalyst for ORR and OER]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advancing impactful, economical, and durable Co-based bifunctional electrocatalysts for the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) and oxygen evolution reaction (OER) has been crucial in developing sustainable energy technologies. In this work, Co and Co(2)N(0.67) nanoparticles (NPs)-incorporated S, N-doped carbon catalysts (Co/Co(2)N(0.67)/SNC) were prepared via direct pyrolysis of the CoDATT complex, exhibiting high bifunctional electrocatalytic performance for ORR and OER. The complex precursor,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strong Magnon-Phonon Coupling in the Kagome Antiferromagnets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Magnon-phonon hybridization in ordered materials is a crucial phenomenon with significant implications for spintronics, magnonics, and quantum materials research. We present direct experimental evidence and theoretical insights into magnon-phonon coupling in Mn_{3}Ge, a kagome antiferromagnet with noncollinear spin order. Using inelastic x-ray scattering and ab initio modeling, we uncover strong hybridization between planar spin fluctuations and transverse optical phonons, resulting in a large...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioadaptive liquid-infused multifunctional fibers for long-term neural recording via BDNF stabilization and enhanced neural interaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brain-computer interfaces (BCIs) enable direct communication between the brain and computers. However, their long-term functionality remains limited due to signal degradation caused by acute insertion trauma, chronic foreign body reaction (FBR), and biofouling at the device-tissue interface. To address these challenges, we introduce a multifunctional surface modification strategy called targeting-specific interaction and blocking nonspecific adhesion (TAB) coating for flexible fiber, achieving a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Evaluations of a Mixed Extract of <em>Salvia Miltiorrhiza Bunge</em> and <em>Paeonia Lactiflora</em> Pall. (USCP-GVH-014): A 12 Weeks Clinical Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salvia miltiorrhiza Bunge and Paeonia lactiflora Pall. are traditionally used to manage cardiovascular health. However, clinical evidence evaluating standardized extracts for specific cardiovascular benefits is still evolving. This study aimed to evaluate its efficacy and safety of a mixed extract of S. miltiorrhiza Bunge and P. lactiflora Pall. (USCP-GVH-014) for improving cardiovascular function in adults with early-stage vascular health decline. This 12-week, single-center, single-arm,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Replication stress-induced nuclear hypertrophy alters chromatin topology and impacts cancer cell fitness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microscopic examination of biopsy tissues remains essential for cancer diagnosis, despite advancements in sequencing technologies. Alterations in nuclear size or the nuclear-to-cytoplasmic ratio are hallmark features of cancer cells and often correlate with disease progression. However, the mechanisms underlying nuclear size abnormalities and their impact on tumor progression remain unclear. In this study, we demonstrate that nuclear hypertrophy occurs in response to enhanced DNA replication...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wafer-scale integration of monolayer MoS<sub>2</sub><em>via</em> residue-free support layer etching and angular strain suppression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A crack-free and residue-free transfer technique for large-area, atomically-thin 2D transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDCs) such as MoS(2) and WS(2) is critical for their integration into next-generation electronic devices, either as channel materials replacing silicon or as back-end-of-line (BEOL) components in 3D-integrated nano-systems on CMOS platforms. However, cracks are frequently observed during the debonding of TMDCs from their growth substrates, and polymer or metal residues are often...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of <em>Streptococcus mitis</em> subsp. <em>carlssonii</em> isolated from human vagina: prevalence, phenotypic, and genomic insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The genus Streptococcus is a heterogenous group of commensal and pathogenic bacteria. Members of this genus are classified into two major groups, the pyogenic group and the viridans group streptococci (VGS). VGS are frequently found as normal members of the human microbiome and are regarded as commensals. In this work, we characterized a VGS strain isolated from the vaginal swab sample of a Korean patient diagnosed with endometrial cancer. Phylogenetic, phenotypic, and genome-based analyses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polystyrene particles induces asthma-like Th2-mediated lung injury through IL-33 secretion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plastics, particularly polystyrene (PS), are extensively used worldwide, especially in disposable packaging, which contributes to environmental pollution by generating microplastic particles. Herein, we investigated the pulmonary toxic effects of PS microplastics, focusing on airway inflammation and immune response. PS microplastic (50 nm to 1 μm) exposure was more likely to cause a severe pulmonary inflammatory response, particularly with smaller particle sizes. PS microplastic nose-only...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Characteristics of Individuals with COPD, Pre-COPD, Smokers with Normal Lung Function in Korea: Updated Analysis of the KOCOSS Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This analysis of the KOCOSS cohort highlights the distinct clinical characteristics of individuals with COPD, pre-COPD, and smokers with normal lung function. Notably, individuals without spirometric COPD still showed substantial symptom burden and inhaler use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep-Learning System for Automatic Measurement of the Femorotibial Rotational Angle on Lower-Extremity Computed Tomography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To develop and validate a deep-learning-based algorithm for automatic identification of anatomical landmarks and calculating femoral and tibial version angles (FTT angles) on lower-extremity CT scans. In this IRB-approved, retrospective study, lower-extremity CT scans from 270 adult patients (median age, 69 years; female to male ratio, 235:35) were analyzed. CT data were preprocessed using contrast-limited adaptive histogram equalization and RGB superposition to enhance tissue boundary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Late fluid flow in a primitive asteroid revealed by Lu-Hf isotopes in Ryugu]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbonaceous asteroids are the source of the most primitive meteorites¹ and represent leftover planetesimals that formed from ice and dust in the outer Solar System and may have delivered volatiles to the terrestrial planets^(2-5). Understanding the aqueous activity of asteroids is key to deciphering their thermal, chemical and orbital evolution, with implications for the origin of water on the terrestrial planets. Analyses of the objects, in particular pristine samples returned from asteroid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triplet-harvesting materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of glaucoma surgery on recurrence rate in cytomegalovirus anterior uveitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: GS significantly reduced recurrence rate by 77.4% in patients with CMV-AU.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social support and subjective care burden among the family caregivers of terminally ill cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Properly addressing the multiple dimensions of social support alleviates the subjective care burden of the FCs of terminal cancer patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of the Total Testing Process Within the Big Data-to-Big Data Loop]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Exposure to Room Temperature During Storage on Cryopreserved Umbilical Cord Blood Quality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cryopreserved umbilical cord blood (CB) for transplantation is occasionally exposed to room temperature during storage in cord blood banks. We evaluated the effect of room temperature exposure on the quality of cryopreserved CB. Forty frozen CB units stored in liquid nitrogen tanks were exposed to room temperature until they reached a target temperature of -130°C (group I), -60°C (group II), -40°C (group III), or -25°C (group IV) (N=10 in each group) and then re-stored. After re-thawing, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncovering the evolving arms race between host immunity and HIV-1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite an effective combination of antiretroviral therapy, HIV persists as a lifelong infection and global health threat. The human host equips restriction factors and interferon (IFN)-stimulated genes that target every step of the viral life cycle. However, HIV-1 has evolved a coordinated immune evasion strategy using a limited set of accessory proteins with distinct antagonistic functions. This functional division of labor allows HIV-1 to disable key immune pathways and ensure persistence....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gingival margin repositioning using biologically oriented preparation technique and digital workflow in a maxillary esthetic rehabilitation: A clinical report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This clinical report describes the management of gingival recession and gingival line asymmetry around fixed partial dentures using the biologically oriented preparation technique (BOPT). By modifying the emergence profile of the restorations through the BOPT and incorporating a digital workflow, a stable and esthetic gingival margin was achieved. The report highlights the procedural steps, advantages, and limitations of this approach in the anterior maxillary region.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Statins in Type 1 Diabetes: Bridging the Evidence Gap With Target Trial Emulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Off-label underdosing of edoxaban antithrombotic therapy for patients with atrial fibrillation and stable coronary artery disease: findings from the EPIC-CAD trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with AF and stable CAD, there was no significant difference in the rate of primary outcome between off-label underdose and standard-dose edoxaban. The benefit of edoxaban monotherapy over dual antithrombotic therapy was consistent regardless of edoxaban underdosing. However, given the analyses were underpowered and the CI was wide, the results cannot be considered clinically directive.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Core Physiologically Based Toxicokinetic (PBTK) Model for Exposure Assessment of Multiple Environmental Phenols]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Environmental phenols are widely used in consumer products and are of increasing concern due to their potential endocrine-disrupting effects. Physiologically based toxicokinetic (PBTK) models offer a powerful tool for estimating human exposure by translating biomonitoring data into external intake values. However, conventional PBTK models are typically chemical-specific and resource-intensive. In this study, we developed a core human PBTK model capable of describing the absorption, distribution,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of body mass index, waist circumference, and weight-adjusted waist index with body composition and biomarkers: A multinational pooled analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our data suggest that WWI is associated with unhealthy body composition (high fat, low fat-free mass) in populations of diverse age, sex, and race/ethnicities and may serve as an alternative index to BMI and WC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trajectories of Synchronous Subsolid Nodules in Patients with Resected Subsolid Lung Adenocarcinoma: A Multicenter Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Synchronous SSNs in patients with subsolid LUAD exhibited growth in 16.9% of cases, with varying trajectories and clinical impact. Identified risk factors were primarily related to the characteristics of each SSN. Our findings highlight the need for nodule-based, individualized management strategies, along with a more clinically relevant growth threshold to guide balanced intervention decisions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intestinal mucosa-mimetic double-layer gelatin hydrogel for recapitulation of 3D immune microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The intestinal immune microenvironment plays a crucial role in regulating systemic immune responses and is implicated in various diseases. Nevertheless, no existing model simultaneously replicates the three-dimensional (3D) immune microenvironment and the mucosal barrier. This study presents a novel mucosa-mimic model that consists of a cell-laden hydrogel matrix and a pseudo-mucus layer that emulate the intestinal lamina propria and mucosal barrier, respectively. The model was used to evaluate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world use of terlipressin in cirrhosis and acute kidney injury: frequent use beyond hepatorenal syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Terlipressin is often used for treatment of AKI outside its primary indication of HRS-AKI. Compared to patients with HRS-AKI, response to terlipressin is significantly lower in patients with ATN, in whom the risks may outweigh the benefits. Respiratory failure is common, but does not seem to be driven by the amount of albumin received nor ACLF grade.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic ammonia recovery from high-ammonia anaerobic digestate via coupled bipolar electrodialysis and membrane contactor system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates ammonia gas recovery from high-strength anaerobic digestate using a bipolar membrane electrodialysis (BPED) and membrane contactor (MC). Ammonia is a promising carbon-neutral energy carrier, while digestates present both environmental challenges and opportunities for ammonia recovery. The BPED was tested at 2,000---10,000 mg-N/L under varying voltages and flow rates, achieving up to 87.6 % ammonium separation at 10,000 mg-N/L. Subsequently, the MC enabled direct gas-phase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunometabolic biomarkers of brain aging: Nonlinear association between neutrophil-to-HDL cholesterol ratio and cognitive decline in older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: NHR serves as a potential immunometabolic biomarker for cognitive impairment in older adults, capturing chronic inflammation and metabolic dysfunction linked to brain aging. The observed non-linear pattern suggests a threshold effect, highlighting the importance of early immunometabolic monitoring. These findings support incorporating immunometabolic markers into psychoneuroimmunology-informed risk assessments for cognitive decline.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of neohepatic albumin-bilirubin scores on renal outcomes following living donor liver transplantation: a propensity score analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Neohepatic ALBI scores are significantly associated with post-LT severe AKI, RRT, CKD, and graft failure, underscoring their prognostic value in LDLT recipients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term treatment with lithium, valproate, and atypical antipsychotics on suicide risk in patients with bipolar disorder: A nationwide retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Suicide risk decreased during treatment with lithium or valproate alone. In patients with bipolar disorder who are at a high risk of suicide, atypical antipsychotics may be associated with a reduced risk of suicide when combined with lithium and valproate.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A potent NLRP3 inhibitor effective against both MCC950-sensitive and -resistant inflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The nucleotide-binding oligomerization domain (NOD)-like receptor protein 3 (NLRP3) inflammasome detects a broad spectrum of pathogen- and damage-associated molecular patterns (PAMPs and DAMPs), initiating inflammatory responses through caspase-1 activation and interleukin (IL)-1β/IL-18 release. Dysregulated NLRP3 activation is implicated in a range of diseases, including infectious diseases, autoinflammatory disorders, metabolic disorders, and cancer, making it an attractive therapeutic target....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[eHealth Self-Management Interventions for Patients With Liver Cirrhosis: Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This review identified diverse eHealth self-management interventions with core components for patients with LC, evaluated across multiple outcome domains. Nonetheless, the evidence remains limited by small sample sizes and heterogeneous study designs and outcome measures. Future research should prioritize rigorous randomized trials, standardized intervention frameworks, and core outcome sets to support clinical implementation and effectiveness evaluation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biological Age Estimation From the Age Gap Using Deep Learning Integrating Morbidity and Mortality: Model Development and Validation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: By integrating morbidity and mortality information within a transformer-based framework, the BA - CA gap model offers a more granular and clinically meaningful assessment of aging and health status than CA alone. This approach supports the potential for personalized health management and risk stratification, although external validation in diverse populations is warranted to further confirm its generalizability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceived usefulness, benefits, and needs of patient‑generated health data among older adults after lung cancer surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explored the usefulness, benefits, disadvantages, and implementation needs of patient‑generated health data (PGHD) among older adults after lung cancer surgery. Using a cross‑sectional descriptive design, a self‑administered survey was completed by 220 patients aged ≥ 65 years, and semi‑structured interviews were held with 20 of them. Survey analysis identified lung function, blood pressure, and heart rate as the most useful PGHD parameters. Higher perceived usefulness was associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photodynamic inactivation of pathogenic bacteria using chlorogenic acid and UV-A (365 nm) irradiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explored the antimicrobial efficacy and mechanism of a combined treatment using chlorogenic acid (CGA) and UV-A (365 nm) irradiation against four major foodborne pathogens-Escherichia coli O157:H7, Salmonella Typhimurium, Listeria monocytogenes, and Staphylococcus aureus-in both buffer and acidic beverage matrices. The CGA + UVA treatment showed strong bactericidal effects, particularly in green plum juice, where complete inactivation of L. monocytogenes was achieved (> 8-log...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A pilot study of evaluation of a deep-learning-based homologous recombination deficiency assay in korean patients with ovarian high-grade serous carcinoma: Diagnostic performance and clinical implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The HRD assay offers high diagnostic performance of HRD in Korean OC patients. Furthermore, the prognostic value of high GII and HRD, as well as an association with SET pattern and HRD was evident in HGSC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution and Risk Factors of Scrub Typhus in South Korea, From 2013 to 2019: Bayesian Spatiotemporal Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first study to investigate ST in South Korea using a spatiotemporal framework grounded in a holistic One Health perspective. We elucidated the critical role of spatiotemporal dynamics in ST distribution, highlighting rodent suitability and economic independence as key drivers of disease distribution. Our findings lay the groundwork for evidence-based, region-specific intervention strategies and may inform targeted public health strategies in South Korea and other...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Key factors underpinning neuroimmune-metabolic-oxidative (NIMETOX) major depression in outpatients: paraoxonase 1 activity, reverse cholesterol transport, increased atherogenicity, protein oxidation, and differently expressed cytokine networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Many OMDD patients (78.8%) show aberrations in NIMETOX pathways. The features of OMDD, including severity of illness, neuroticism, and suicidal behaviors, are caused by intertwined NIMETOX pathways that may exert additional effects depending on whether MetS is present or not.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical Risk Factors for Portal Vein Complications Following Right Hepatectomy in Living Donors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Acute angulation between the main and left PV or variant PV anatomy is associated with an increased incidence of PV-related complications following RLDH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clonal Hematopoiesis in Nonmalignant Disease: Functional Consequences of Mutated Immune Cells by Clonal Hematopoiesis in the Diseased Tissue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clonal hematopoiesis, originally identified as a precursor to hematologic malignancies, has emerged as a significant factor in various nonmalignant diseases. Recent research highlights how somatic mutations in hematopoietic stem cells lead to the expansion of circulating mutated immune cells that exert profound effects on organ function and disease progression. These mutated clones display altered inflammatory profiles and tissue-specific functional consequences, contributing to various diseases...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacterial infections and antimicrobial resistance patterns: a comprehensive analysis of health dynamics across regions in Pakistan (2013-2023)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial resistance (AMR) is a significant public health concern globally, and Pakistan is no exception. The misuse and overuse of antibiotics, inadequate regulation of their sale, and a lack of awareness contribute to the rising levels of AMR in the country. study presents a detailed analysis of blood and urine samples collected in Pakistan over various periods, focusing on pathogen prevalence, gender distribution, and age-wise patterns. From January 2013 to 2017, the North region...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural Quantum Embedding via Deterministic Quantum Computation with One Qubit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum computing is expected to provide an exponential speedup in machine learning. However, optimizing the data loading process, commonly referred to as "quantum data embedding," to maximize classification performance remains a critical challenge. In this Letter, we propose a neural quantum embedding (NQE) technique based on deterministic quantum computation with one qubit (DQC1). Unlike the traditional embedding approach, NQE trains a neural network to maximize the trace distance between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, Yonsei University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling Three Types of Fermions in a Nodal Ring Topological Semimetal through Magneto-Optical Transitions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the quasiparticles of a single nodal ring semimetal SrAs_{3} through axis-resolved magneto-optical measurements. We observe three types of Landau levels scaling as ϵ∼sqrt[B], ϵ∼B^{2/3}, and ϵ∼B that correspond to Dirac, semi-Dirac, and classical fermions, respectively. Through theoretical analysis, we identify the distinct origins of these three types of fermions present within the nodal ring. In particular, semi-Dirac fermions-a novel type of fermion that can give rise to a range...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Positive Neutrino Masses with DESI DR2 via Matter Conversion to Dark Energy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Dark Energy Spectroscopic Instrument (DESI) is a massively parallel spectroscopic survey on the Mayall telescope at Kitt Peak, which has released measurements of baryon acoustic oscillations determined from over 14 million extragalactic targets. We combine DESI Data Release 2 with CMB datasets to search for evidence of matter conversion to dark energy (DE), focusing on a scenario mediated by stellar collapse to cosmologically coupled black holes (CCBHs). In this physical model, which has the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potential role of miR-29b from mesenchymal stromal cell-derived extracellular vesicles in leukemic cell progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crosstalk between leukemic cells and their surrounding mesenchymal stromal cells (MSCs) in the bone marrow microenvironment is crucial for the pathogenesis of myelodysplastic syndromes (MDS) and is mediated by extracellular vesicles (EVs). The EV-specific miRNAs derived from MDS-MSCs remain poorly explored. EVs isolated from HS-5, an immortalized stromal cell line, promoted the proliferation and 5-azacytidine (AZA) resistance of SKM-1 cells. EVs from MDS-MSCs and HS-5 cells showed significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evidence for Similar Collectivity of High Transverse-Momentum Particles in p-Pb and Pb-Pb Collisions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Charged hadron elliptic anisotropies (v_{2}) are presented over a wide transverse momentum (p_{T}) range for proton-lead (pPb) and lead-lead (PbPb) collisions at nucleon-nucleon center-of-mass energies of 8.16 and 5.02 TeV, respectively. The data were recorded by the CMS experiment and correspond to integrated luminosities of 186 and 0.607 nb^{-1} for the pPb and PbPb systems, respectively. A four-particle cumulant analysis is performed using subevents separated in pseudorapidity to effectively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of Three Resonant Structures in the Cross Section of e^{+}e^{-}→π^{+}π^{-}h_{c}]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Using e^{+}e^{-} collision data collected with the BESIII detector operating at the Beijing electron positron collider, the cross section of e^{+}e^{-}→π^{+}π^{-}h_{c} is measured at 59 points with center-of-mass energy sqrt[s] ranging from 4.009 to 4.950 GeV with a total integrated luminosity of 22.2 fb^{-1}. The cross section between 4.3 and 4.45 GeV exhibits a plateaulike shape and drops sharply around 4.5 GeV, which cannot be described by two resonances only. Three coherent Breit-Wigner...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Onset of Constituent Quark Number Scaling in Heavy-Ion Collisions at RHIC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Partonic collectivity is one of the necessary signatures for the formation of quark-gluon plasma in high-energy nuclear collisions. Number of constituent quarks (NCQ) scaling has been observed for hadron elliptic flow v_{2} in top energy nuclear collisions at the Relativistic Heavy Ion Collider and the LHC, and this has been theoretically suggested as strong evidence for partonic collectivity. In this Letter, a systematic analysis of v_{2} of π^{±}, K^{±}, K_{S}^{0}, p, and Λ in Au+Au collisions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of depression, anxiety, and COVID-19 diagnosis on social isolation trajectories during the pandemic: A 3-year prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The three-way interaction results indicated that the severity of depressive symptoms and COVID-19 diagnosis status significantly influenced social isolation trajectory over time. Individuals diagnosed with COVID-19, particularly those experiencing severe depression, have an increased risk of worsening social isolation over time. This underscores the need for intensive and sustained psychological support and intervention for vulnerable individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Volunteering With Mild Cognitive Impairment: Implications for Subsequent Cognitive Changes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Volunteering has cognitive benefits in later life and has been theorized to protect against Alzheimer's disease and related dementias (ADRD). A small but growing body of volunteer programs target people with mild cognitive impairment (MCI)-who are presumably at elevated risk for ADRD, but we know surprisingly little about who volunteers with MCI and how volunteering affects their subsequent cognitive changes. The current study sought to address these gaps.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atelocollagen exhibits superior performance compared to growth factors in upregulating proteins associated with tendon healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AC significantly upregulated key molecular markers involved in cell proliferation, extracellular matrix remodeling, and tendon structural integrity more effectively than individual growth factors. The increased expression of these genes in myoblasts suggests AC's potential role in promoting tendon healing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Delayed Statin Initiation After High LDL-Cholesterol Detection and Cardiovascular Risk in General Health Screening Examinees]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Delayed initiation of statins following incidental detection of high LDL-C in general health screenings was associated with a progressively higher risk of MI. This association was more pronounced among younger individuals, males, or those without baseline diabetes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Report of <em>Bandavirus dabieense</em> in Bats and Ticks Collected from Bat Habitats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The zoonotic infectious disease, severe fever with thrombocytopenia syndrome (SFTS), caused by the SFTS virus (SFTSV), Bandavirus dabieense, was first identified in China in 2009 and reported in the Republic of Korea in 2013. The primary vector is the tick Haemaphysalis (H.) longicornis, which is endemic to the Asia-Pacific region and has a wide range of hosts. While SFTSV has been studied in various wildlife species, no investigation has focused explicitly on bats, which are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac Biomarkers and Risk Stratification in Liver Transplantation for Acute-on-Chronic Liver Failure: Refining Current Risk Models for Improved Prediction of Post-transplant Mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cardiac impairment is prevalent in patients with ACLF and crucial for risk stratification. Integrating cardiac biomarkers into ACLF risk models improves post-LT survival predictions and emphasizes the importance of addressing cardiac impairments before LT for better outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automatic brain segmentation in cognitive impairment: Validation of AI-based AQUA software in the Southeast Asian BIOCIS cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings demonstrate high concordance between human-based visual ratings and AQUA-based ratings of WMH. Additionally, the AQUA GM segmentation pipeline showed good differentiation in key regions between cognitively normal, MCI and dementia participants. Based on these findings, the automated AQUA software could aid clinicians in examining MRI scans of patients with cognitive impairment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hypertension Medications and Health-Related Quality of Life-Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Safety of JAK Inhibitors vs TNF Antagonists in Immune-Mediated Inflammatory Diseases: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The head-to-head studies in this systematic review and meta-analysis did not identify any meaningful difference in the risk of serious infections, malignant neoplasms, or MACEs with JAK inhibitor vs TNF antagonist use across all IMIDs, with low overall incidence. JAK inhibitor use was associated with a slightly higher risk of VTE. Further research, especially long-term studies, is needed to fully elucidate the safety of JAK inhibitors and TNF antagonists across diverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of change in sleep disturbance in Canadian long-term care facilities: a longitudinal analysis based on interRAI assessments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study underscores the high prevalence and variation of sleep disturbance in LTCFs, highlighting potential modifiable risk factors for improvement. Further research is needed to explore the interplay of institutional, environmental, and individual factors to develop targeted interventions that enhance the quality of care in LTCFs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pseudoduganella rhizocola sp. nov., Isolated from Rhizospheric Soil]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel bacterial strain, SM-13^( T) was isolated from the rhizospheric soil of Epipremnum aureum (Jade Pothos) sampled in Suwon, Republic of Korea. The isolate was Gram-stain-negative, aerobic, motile, rod-shaped, cream-coloured, oxidase- and catalase-positive. Strain SM-13^( T) grew at the range of 15-37 °C (optimum, 25 °C), at pH 6.0-9.0 (optimum, pH 7.0), and in the presence of 0-0.5% (w/v) NaCl (optimum, 0%). Phylogenetic analysis based on genome and 16S rRNA gene sequences indicated that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pressure-Driven Structural and Optoelectronic Tuning of Cl-Substituted 2D Lead Halide Perovskite (ClPMA)<sub>2</sub>PbI<sub>4</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a systematic high-pressure investigation of the chlorine-functionalized two-dimensional hybrid perovskite (ClPMA)(2)PbI(4), integrating in situ high-pressure synchrotron powder X-ray diffraction (HP-PXRD), photoluminescence spectroscopy (HP-PL), and first-principles density functional theory (DFT) calculations. Under hydrostatic compression up to 6.18 (±0.42) GPa, HP-PXRD reveals anisotropic lattice contraction (Δa/a(0) = 4.06%, Δb/b(0) = 3.00%, Δc/c(0) = 8.66%) with a bulk modulus of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations Between IgE-Allergen Sensitization and Glaucoma: An Analysis of Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest a complex relationship between allergen sensitization and glaucoma, with different allergens showing varying associations with disease risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pregnancy Outcomes After HIV Diagnosis in Women Living With HIV in Japan, South Korea and Hong Kong Special Administrative Region: A Brief Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The study analyzed pregnancy outcomes among 498 women living with HIV in East Asia. We found 15% had pregnancies postdiagnosis, with 57% resulting in live births. Older age at antiretroviral therapy initiation and higher pre-antiretroviral therapy viral loads were negatively associated with pregnancy. High rates of unplanned pregnancies (61%) and terminations (26%) highlight the need for improved reproductive counseling.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Assembled Cu<sub>3</sub>P@NiCo<sub>2</sub>O<sub>4</sub> Core-Shell Heterostructure Electrodes for High-Energy All-Solid-State Supercapacitor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Core-shell electrodes provide a potential and innovative approach for significantly enhancing the performance and capacity of supercapacitors (SCs) by combining two distinct materials. The capabilities of these advanced electrodes surpass those of conventional single electrodes. Specifically, these exhibit better energy storage, higher power density, and improved overall performance. In this study, 1D core-shell Cu(3)P@NiCo(2)O(4) heterostructure is synthesized on copper foam (CF) and utilized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Big Five Inventory-2 in Korea: Validation and Cross-Cultural Comparisons with the U.S. and Chinese Versions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Big Five Inventory-2 (BFI-2) has enjoyed global popularity due to its good balance of content coverage and brevity and has been officially translated into 12 languages in addition to the original English version. The current study aimed to further enhance the cultural accessibility of the BFI-2 by translating it into the Korean language and comprehensively validating the Korean version in two South Korean samples: working adults and college students. Across the two samples, the Korean BFI-2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermal Cross-linked Electron Transport Polymers for Suppressing Efficiency Roll-off in Green Solution-Processed Inverted OLEDs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solution-processed phosphorescent inverted organic light-emitting diodes (s-IOLEDs) have garnered significant attention due to their excellent stability and high performance. However, frequently used inorganic electron transport layers usually cause exciton dissociation at the emitting layer interface, leading to low device efficiency and severe efficiency roll-off. In this work, we designed a cross-linkable triazine-grafted electron transport copolymer (PPDPT-co-PBCB) with a high triplet energy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lithium Metal Ingrowth Toward a Porous Structure via Coble Creep along Lithium-Carbon Interface Without Ionic Conductors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All-solid-state batteries (ASSBs), equipped with highly ion-conductive sulfide solid electrolytes and utilizing lithium plating/stripping as anode electrochemistry, suffer from 1) chemical vulnerability of the electrolytes with lithium and 2) physical growth of lithium to penetrate the electrolytes. By employing an ordered mesoporous graphitic carbon (OMGC) framework between a sulfide electrolyte layer and a copper current collector in ASSB, the concerns by are addressed 1) minimizing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Geographic variation in chemical composition and bioactivity of Valeriana wallichii root oils: implications for botanical fumigant development against stored-product insects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: An acid-dominant Indian chemotype maximizes volatile bioactivity, with short-chain acids and 5-methylfurfural as primary drivers. Species-specific sensitivity supports targeted deployment (e.g., sachet-style emitters for mites/moths) and chemotype standardization. These findings advance botanical fumigant development by pinpointing active classes and geo-source effects, guiding low-residue controlled-release formulations and synergist-augmented strategies for tolerant coleopterans. ©...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasonographic Analysis of Site-Specific Plantar Skin Thickness for Melanoma Staging and Excision]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plantar melanomas present unique diagnostic and surgical challenges owing to substantial regional variations in skin thickness. Although the Breslow thickness remains the primary criterion for staging and surgical excision, its application on plantar melanoma is complicated by the inherent thickness of the glabrous plantar epidermis, which may lead to tumor depth overestimation. Accurate assessment of plantar skin thickness is essential for optimizing staging accuracy and refining surgical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-related amyloid beta dynamics modeled with the generalized additive model for location, scale, and shape (GAMLSS) across diverse populations: Cross-sectional trajectories and longitudinal validation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: We developed and validated age-related amyloid beta (Aβ) positron emission tomography (PET) trajectories using a statistical model in cognitively unimpaired (CU) individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter From the Korean Academy of Tuberculosis and Respiratory Diseases (KATRD)-Navigating Reform: South Korea's Healthcare System at a Crossroads]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Burden of Motor Neuron Diseases in the United States, 1990-2021: A Systematic Analysis of the Global Burden of Disease Study 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION/AIMS: There is a lack of up-to-date information on the burden of motor neuron diseases (MNDs) in the United States (US). This study aimed to estimate trends in the prevalence, incidence, mortality, and disability-adjusted life years (DALYs) for MNDs in the US from 1990 to 2021.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evanescent-Field-Guiding 2D Ultrathin Waveguides for Seamlessly Integrated Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seamless integration of active devices into photonic integrated circuits remains a challenge due to the limited accessibility of the optical field in conventional waveguides, which tightly confine light within their cores. In this study, we propose a two-dimensional (2D) ultrathin waveguide as a photonic platform that enables efficient interaction between guided light and surface-mounted devices by supporting optical modes dominated by evanescent fields. We show that the guided light in a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adult onset cryopyrin-associated periodic syndrome due to germline missense mutation in <em>NLRP3</em> in a previously healthy middle-aged woman]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We report a case of adult-onset CAPS in a previously healthy woman, caused by a missense mutation (c.386A>G) in the NLRP3 gene, who exhibited a remarkable response to anakinra treatment. Autoinflammatory diseases should be considered in patients presenting with fever, skin rashes, and systemic symptoms, regardless of age.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal analysis of oral microbiome changes during the neonatal period in full-term and preterm newborns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preterm newborns exhibit delayed oral microbiome development, influenced by multiple modifiable factors. Supportive strategies, such as breastfeeding and prudent antibiotic use, may help foster microbial stability and potentially reduce infection risk in this vulnerable population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pregnancy after breast cancer treatment in young patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Breast cancer (BC) treatments can impair fertility in young women, causing considerable distress and potentially influencing treatment decisions, yet comprehensive real-world data on pregnancy outcomes after BC remain limited. This study aims to provide comprehensive real-world data on pregnancy following BC treatment to guide clinical practice and patient counseling.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient electronics for sustainability: Emerging technologies and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transient electronics are emerging as a promising class of devices designed to disappear after a defined operational period, addressing growing concerns over sustainability and long-term biocompatibility. Built from biodegradable materials that undergo hydrolysis or enzymatic degradation, these systems are particularly well suited for temporary implantable applications, such as neural monitors, wireless stimulators, and drug delivery vehicles, as well as environmentally benign electronics for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retraction: Optimized Cu-doping in ZnO electro-spun nanofibers for enhanced photovoltaic performance in perovskite solar cells and photocatalytic dye degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This retracts the article DOI: 10.1039/D4RA01544D.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to: Impact of the COVID-19 outbreak on the field of hematopoietic cell transplantation in the Asia-Pacific region: APBMT Activity Survey 2020/2021 [Blood Cell Therapy. 2024; 7(4): 129-137. doi:10.31547/bct-2024-020]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.31547/bct-2024-020.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomechanical comparison of locking plate and pin-tension band wiring fixation for 3D-printed canine patellar fracture repair]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The conventional pin and tension band wiring (TBW) technique remains the standard for fixation, but is frequently associated with complications such as wire breakage, loosening, and delayed healing in patellar fracture. Locking plate fixation has demonstrated superior biomechanical stability in human studies. This study aimed to compare the biomechanical performance of locking plate fixation versus TBW in canine transverse patellar fractures and to evaluate the influence of plate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to: "Rethinking risk indices in pediatric MASLD"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Literature Review and Management Approach for Severe Skin Toxicity Induced by Enfortumab Vedotin Through Sequential Adaptation and Combination With Immune Checkpoint Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In patients with advanced urothelial carcinoma who have progressed after platinum-based chemotherapy, enfortumab vedotin (EV) improves overall survival compared to standard chemotherapy. Additionally, for treatment-naïve patients with locally advanced or metastatic urothelial carcinoma, the combination of pembrolizumab and EV demonstrates superior efficacy over platinum-based chemotherapy. Hence, EV becomes a standard treatment option. Although EV monotherapy is generally well tolerated, with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitigation of mycotoxin residues and activation of endogenous stem cells in broiler chickens using a toxin binder: Implications for meat safety and performance enhancement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Administering a toxin binder at 1.6 g/kg effectively reduced AFB1 and OTA residues and significantly activated endogenous stem cells, suggesting a protective and regenerative effect. Meanwhile, a dose of 1.1 g/kg yielded optimal growth performance and feed efficiency. These findings support the dual functional role of toxin binders in enhancing broiler meat safety and physiological resilience.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morphology and molecular phylogeny of <em>Cercospora dispori</em> from <em>Disporum smilacinum</em> and <em>Disporum viridescens</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The main objective of the present study is to compile and comprehensively reevaluate all known records of Cercospora dispori in order to establish a standardized framework for the accurate characterization and identification of this species. Nine isolates of C. dispori obtained from Disporum smilacinum and D. viridescens from various regions of Korea were analyzed. The morphological features of the fungus and isolated colonies were described and illustrated. Nucleotide sequences of the internal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling host plant associations and cryptic genetic diversity of <em>Miyalachnus sorini</em> (Aphididae: Lachninae) on cherry trees in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents the first record of Miyalachnus sorini Kanturski & Lee, 2024 (Aphididae: Lachninae) in South Korea, thereby extending its known distribution beyond Japan and identifying a new host plant, Prunus sargentii (Rosaceae). We describe diagnostic morphological traits across multiple life stages and compare them with those of Japanese populations. Comparative analyses with Japanese populations demonstrated consistent morphological differentiation, notably elevated ratios of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of deep learning for detecting implants in computed tomography scout images with multi-institution and multi-vendor for personal identification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1p9j2Ia0knT7gmGP5yr8TGKmrRRyRQ0oWVA_KWuJa7rtxBZMim&amp;fc=20250822201347&amp;ff=20250911033957&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The identification of deceased individuals is essential in forensic investigations, particularly when primary identification methods such as odontology, fingerprint, or DNA analysis are unavailable. In such cases, implanted medical devices may serve as supplementary identifiers for positive identification. This study proposes deep learning-based methods for the automatic detection of metallic implants in scout images acquired from computed tomography (CT). Using a multi-institutional and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1p9j2Ia0knT7gmGP5yr8TGKmrRRyRQ0oWVA_KWuJa7rtxBZMim&amp;fc=20250822201347&amp;ff=20250911033957&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, Yonsei University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reconciling a Kinetic Model for Dimerization of the EGFR Using Single-Molecule Tracking in Living Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR) dimerization plays a pivotal role in cellular signaling, influencing proliferation and disease progression, particularly in cancer. Despite extensive studies, the quantitative relationship between EGFR expression levels and dimerization efficiency remains incompletely understood. In this study, we investigated EGFR dimerization kinetics using ensemble-level biochemical assays and single-molecule tracking (SMT) in living cells. Our findings revealed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing Magnetic Octupole Hall Effect to Induce Torque in Altermagnets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[d-wave altermagnets have magnetic octupoles as their order parameters [S. Bhowal and N. A. Spaldin, Ferroically ordered magnetic octupoles in d-wave altermagnets, Phys. Rev. X 14, 011019 (2024)PRXHAE2160-330810.1103/PhysRevX.14.011019]. We theoretically show that magnetic octupoles injected from outside generate torque on the d-wave altermagnets. The injection can be achieved by the magnetic octupole Hall effect in an adjacent layer. We calculate the magnetic octupole Hall conductivity of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable and healthy diet index (SHDI) unveils regional differences in Europe and Northern Africa: findings from the SysOrg study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Some regions, such as Copenhagen, Kenitra, and Cilento, show beneficial eating patterns, particularly high legume intake. However, meat remains overconsumed in most CSTs. Our study highlights the need for further research to promote cultural acceptance of healthier and more sustainable dietary habits, such as increasing vegetable consumption and reducing meat intake.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shigella type-III secretion system effectors counteract the induction of host inflammation and cell death]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many enteric bacterial pathogens deliver virulence effectors to counteract host innate immune responses, such as inflammation and cell death, and colonize the intestinal epithelium. However, host cells recognize the disruption of their innate immune signaling by bacterial effectors and induce alternative immune responses, collectively termed "effector-triggered immunity", to clear bacterial pathogens. Here, we describe a mechanism of cell death induction via effector-triggered immunity and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DNA methylation cooperates with genomic alterations during non-small cell lung cancer evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aberrant DNA methylation has been described in nearly all human cancers, yet its interplay with genomic alterations during tumor evolution is poorly understood. To explore this, we performed reduced representation bisulfite sequencing on 217 tumor and matched normal regions from 59 patients with non-small cell lung cancer from the TRACERx study to deconvolve tumor methylation. We developed two metrics for integrative evolutionary analysis with DNA and RNA sequencing data. Intratumoral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In-line multi-wavelength non-destructive pharma quality monitoring with ultrabroadband carbon nanotubes photo-thermoelectric imaging scanners]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While non-destructive in-line monitoring at manufacturing sites is essential for safe distribution cycles of pharmaceuticals, efforts are still insufficient to develop analytical systems for detailed dynamic visualisation of foreign substances and material composition in target pills. Although spectroscopies, expected towards pharma testing, have faced technical challenges in in-line setups for bulky equipment housing, this work demonstrates compact dynamic photo-monitoring systems by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proximity labeling of axonemal protein CFAP91 identifies EFCAB5 that regulates sperm motility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radial spokes (RSs) are conserved multimolecular structures attached to the axonemal microtubule doublets and are essential for the motility control of both cilia and sperm flagella. CFAP91, an RS3 protein, is implicated in human male infertility, yet its molecular function remains poorly understood. Here, we demonstrate that Cfap91 knockout (KO) mice exhibit impaired sperm flagellum formation and male infertility. Using a transgenic rescue model expressing FLAG- and BioID2-tagged CFAP91, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable Photothermal Superhydrophobic Deicing Coating with Mechanochemical-Thermal Robustness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing scalable and robust deicing coatings is essential for real-world applications, yet current coatings either suffer from intrinsic fragility or low thermal conductivity, limiting sustainability and deicing effectiveness. Here, we report a scalable and durable photothermal superhydrophobic coating coupling with enhanced thermal conductivity, engineered by embedding carbon nanotubes within a perfluoroalkoxy polymer matrix. Our design achieved 97.7% solar absorptance and 280% increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiple human enhancer RNAs contain long translated open reading frames]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enhancer RNAs (eRNAs) are transcribed by RNA polymerase IIduring enhancer activation but are typically rapidly degraded in the nucleus. During states of reduced RNA surveillance, however, eRNAs and other similar "noncoding" RNAs (including, e.g., upstream antisense RNAs) are stabilized, and some are exported to the cytoplasm and can even be found on polysomes. Here, we report unexpectedly that ∼12% of human intergenic eRNAs contain long open reading frames (>300 nt), many of which can be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complex diseases meet deep phenotyping and generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Complex diseases are heterogeneous and evolve along a continuum, limiting individual-level prediction with current approaches. The Human Phenotype Project (HPP) integrates deep phenotyping with generative artificial intelligence (AI) to identify early deviations in health parameters. While the project has already provided significant insights, the challenge is converting these findings into actionable, equitable, and scalable interventions, advancing precision healthcare across diverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women in separation science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Efficacy and Drug Metabolism of Griseorhodin A Induced by a Co-culture of Actinomycete Strain TMPU-20A002 and Mycobacterium smegmatis in Silkworm Infection Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In screening for antibacterial agents from co-cultures of Mycobacterium smegmatis and microbial resources, such as actinomycetes and fungi, the known hydroxyquinone antibiotic griseorhodin A (1) was isolated from a co-culture of actinomycete strain TMPU-20A002 and M. smegmatis. Compound 1 exhibited antibacterial activity against methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA) and vancomycin-resistant Enterococcus faecalis (VRE), with minimum inhibitory concentrations of 0.25 and 2.0 μg/mL,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Drug Monitoring Using a Poly(N-isopropylacrylamide) Hydrogel-Modified Bead-Packed Column with an All-Aqueous Mobile Phase without Sample Deproteinization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Therapeutic drug monitoring (TDM) is vital for effective optimization of pharmacological treatments. In this study, we engineered a chromatography column that is sensitive to temperature fluctuations, thereby enabling safe and straightforward TDM without relying on organic solvents. Silica beads were modified by applying poly(N-isopropylacrylamide) (PNIPAAm) hydrogels, using a condensation reaction to modify the initiator, followed by radical polymerization to integrate the PNIPAAm hydrogel. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combination of Microcrystal Electron Diffraction and Solid-State NMR for the Structural Determination of Indomethacin-Nicotinamide Co-crystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of analytical techniques applicable to powdered pharmaceutical co-crystals, including those containing excipients, represents a comprehensive strategy for quality control in both drug development and regulatory settings. This study investigates the structural characterization of indomethacin-nicotinamide co-crystals using a combination of microcrystal electron diffraction (microED), solid-state NMR (SSNMR), Raman spectroscopy, and powder X-ray diffraction (PXRD). MicroED analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of daily post-training, high-concentration CO<sub>2</sub>-water immersion on thermoregulatory function in young male baseball players]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Among the different forms of hydrotherapy, carbon dioxide (CO(2)) water immersion improves peripheral vasodilation and blood flow compared with tap water immersion; however, the heat stress placed on the body through CO(2) water immersion and the appropriate immersion protocols are uncertain. Therefore, this study aimed to compare the thermoregulatory responses during CO(2) and tap water immersions. The participants were 10 male college baseball players. After daily training was completed,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cephalothin, a First-Generation Cephem Antibiotic, Works as a Potent Inducer of Parthanatos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parthanatos is a noncanonical form of regulated cell death mediated by the overactivation of poly(ADP-ribose) polymerase-1, yet its regulatory mechanisms are not fully understood. To fully elucidate its regulatory mechanisms, it is necessary to establish useful research tools to investigate parthanatos. We have previously identified the human fibrosarcoma HT1080 cells as highly sensitive cells to parthanatos, and cefotaxime, a 3rd-generation cephem antibiotic, as the parthanatos inducer. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of birth preparedness interventions on maternal and neonatal outcomes in low- and middle-income countries: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our systematic review showed that birth preparedness interventions significantly reduced perinatal mortality and increased breastfeeding initiation, as well as produced a positive impact on infant birth weight (grams) and age of gestation at birth (weeks). Future randomized controlled trials on birth preparedness interventions should be conducted and effectively promoted to enhance the health of mothers and neonates in low- and middle-income countries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of a question theme on differential responding in the Concealed Information Test: Comparison of knowledgeable versus unknowledgeable contexts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The autonomic-based Concealed Information Test (CIT) focuses on differential responses to a crime-relevant item that is significant only for knowledgeable persons. This study examined whether pre-test instructions on question themes defining knowledgeable and unknowledgeable contexts modulate the magnitude of differential responses to the relevant item. The participants (36 men 46 women) were instructed to steal one item from one of two possible locations in a mock theft task. In the subsequent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multidisciplinary Team Approach to Pelvic Floor Disorders: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: An MDT approach offers benefits for PFD management, improving patient-reported outcomes, treatment adherence, and quality of life. This review supports the broader adoption of MDT approaches for comprehensive PFD management. Further research is warranted to confirm long-term effectiveness and standardize MDT protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid kinase activity detection and kinetic analysis using a convenient EGFR FRET-based detection probe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In modern drug discovery, there is a pressing need for rapid, cost-effective, and accessible methods to evaluate the biological activities of newly synthesized compounds. Traditional kinase assay platforms are often labor-intensive, time-consuming, and require specialized equipment or expertise. To address these limitations, we developed and validated a convenient in vitro kinase assay based on a recombinant biosensor, Picchu-B, constructed using a bacterial expression system. Picchu-B, derived...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nitric oxide regulates phagocytosis through S-nitrosylation of Rab5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phagocytosis is mediated mainly by immune cells, such as macrophages, monocytes and neutrophils, that clear large pathogens including bacteria. The small GTP-binding protein Rab5 is crucial for both clathrin-dependent endocytosis and phagocytosis, but the role and mechanism of Rab5 activation during phagocytosis are poorly understood. Here we report that nitric oxide (NO), a novel regulator of Rab5, regulates phagocytosis through S-nitrosylation of Rab5. NO can promote phagocytosis by activating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The bidirectional relationship between hikikomori behavioral tendencies and depressive symptoms: A three-wave longitudinal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that depressive symptoms were prospectively associated with the development and maintenance of hikikomori, particularly when driven by avoidance of aversive social experiences. Interventions targeting depressive symptoms and maladaptive reinforcement processes, such as behavioral activation, may help interrupt this cycle. Future studies should investigate other psychiatric comorbidities and test these findings in different cultural contexts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KIF13B controls ciliary protein content by promoting endocytic retrieval and suppressing release of large extracellular vesicles from cilia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dynamic control of ciliary membrane protein content is crucial for the organelle's homeostasis and signaling function and involves removal of ciliary components by intraflagellar transport (IFT) and BBSome-mediated export, endocytic retrieval, and/or extracellular vesicle (EV) shedding. We report that the kinesin-3 motor KIF13B regulates ciliary protein composition and EV shedding in cultured kidney epithelial cells, with effects that vary over time. In early stages of ciliation, Kif13b^(-/-)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring interactions in microbial communities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Most microbial ecosystems cannot be understood without quantifying ecological interactions between their member species. Given the challenges of comprehensively resolving interactions experimentally, a range of prediction methods was developed. Here, we review genome-based prediction methods in particular and discuss their strengths and weaknesses. We then cover different experimental designs to explore microbial interactions and introduce methods to infer interaction signs and strengths from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetics of carprofen in Siamese crocodiles (Crocodylus siamensis)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carprofen (CAR) is an NSAID commonly used in veterinary medicine that preferentially inhibits cyclooxygenase-2 (COX-2), thereby mitigating inflammation and pain while minimizing adverse effects linked to cyclooxygenase-1 (COX-1) inhibition. This study characterizes the pharmacokinetics of CAR in Siamese crocodiles (Crocodylus siamensis) and was conducted at an ambient temperature range of 27-30 °C following single intravenous (IV) or intramuscular (IM) administration at 2 mg/kg, and IM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative analysis of coproporphyrin and its precursors as endogenous biomarkers for drug-drug interactions involving OATP1B1 and OATP1B3 in monkeys]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coproporphyrin (CP)-I has emerged as a promising endogenous biomarker for investigating organic anion transporting polypeptide (OATP) 1B1/1B3-mediated drug-drug interactions. The precursor eliminated analytical (PEA) method selectively quantifies the endogenous CP-I that should be monitored, whereas the precursor oxidized analytical method quantifies the total CP-I concentration by converting all precursors into CP-I during the sample preparation process. Plasma concentrations of CP-I exhibited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catalytic Asymmetric (<em>ene</em>-<em>endo</em>)-Carbonyl-Ene Type Cyclizations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The carbonyl-ene reaction between aldehydes and olefins constitutes a perfectly atom economic approach to homoallylic alcohols with concomitant C-C bond formation. However, the scope of catalytic asymmetric intermolecular versions is currently limited to activated substrates, while of the two intramolecular types only catalytic asymmetric (ene-exo)-carbonyl-ene type cyclizations can be considered mature. The corresponding (ene-endo)-cyclizations would arguably find equal utility in chemical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Factors Affecting Depth of Invasion Measurement in Tongue Squmous Cell Carcinoma Using Intraoral Ultrasonography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although intraoral US provides high accuracy in the preoperative evaluation of tongue SCC, clinicians should be aware of specific tumor characteristics that may influence measurement precision, leading to potential overestimation or underestimation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data-Driven Exploration of Critical Factors for Single-Phase High-Entropy Oxide Anode Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-entropy oxides (HEOs) are attracting significant attention owing to their compositional tunability and structural robustness. However, the identification of specific compositional combinations that yield a single-phase structure in HEOs remains unclear owing to the immense combinatorial complexity inherent in multielement systems. This study adopts a materials informatics approach that integrates experimental synthesis data with machine learning to identify key compositional factors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CME article in Die Anaesthesiologie: making a difference…!]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global challenges in diabetes research and care: which way forward? An appraisal from the EASD Global Council]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review article, developed by the EASD Global Council, addresses the growing global challenges in diabetes research and care, highlighting the rising prevalence of diabetes, the increasing complexity of its management and the need for a coordinated international response. With regard to research, disparities in funding and infrastructure between high-income countries and low- and middle-income countries (LMICs) are discussed. The under-representation of LMIC populations in clinical trials,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondrial transfer from adipose-derived regenerative cells contributes therapeutic angiogenesis in a murine hindlimb ischemia model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ADRCs can protect against ischemic limbs, at least in part by mitochondrial transfer via gap junctions and tunneling of nanotubes into injured endothelial cells and macrophages. Additionally, mitochondrial transfer is a potential mechanism for therapeutic angiogenesis with ADRCs in hindlimb ischemia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maximum likelihood estimation of log-affine models using detailed-balanced reaction networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A fundamental question in the field of molecular computation is what computational tasks a biochemical system can carry out. In this work, we focus on the problem of finding the maximum likelihood estimate (MLE) for log-affine models. We revisit a construction due to Gopalkrishnan of a mass-action system with the MLE as its unique positive steady state, which is based on choosing a basis for the kernel of the design matrix of the model. We extend this construction to allow for any finite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selective Upper-Trunk and Axillary Nerve Block for Awake Shoulder Arthroscopy in a Pulmonary Compromised Patient: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 48-year-old man with a superior labral tear and medical history including hemidiaphragmatic paresis, obstructive sleep apnea, vocal cord paresis, and glottic narrowing, underwent arthroscopic biceps tenodesis. Reduction in respiratory function presented anesthetic management challenges with general anesthesia or an interscalene brachial plexus block. Instead, ultrasound guidance was used to deliver a selective upper-trunk block with 1 % lidocaine and an axillary nerve block with 0.5 %...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A New Family of Ternary Intermetallic Compounds with Dualistic Atomic Ordering - The ZIP Phases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new family of nanostructured ternary intermetallic compounds - named the ZIP phases - is introduced in this work. The ZIP phases exhibit dualistic atomic ordering, i.e., they form two structural variants: one with the fcc diamond cubic structure (space group Fd 3 ¯ $\bar 3$ m) and one with the hexagonal structure (space group P6(3)/mmc). They are also characterized by metallic behavior, ionic bonding, and atomic zigzagging. Powder metallurgical routes involving pressure-assisted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world treatment for systemic sclerosis and systemic sclerosis-associated interstitial lung disease: information from a Japanese hospital claims database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectivesThe 2023 EULAR guidelines for systemic sclerosis (SSc) newly recommend biologics (rituximab, tocilizumab), mycophenolate mofetil (MMF), and nintedanib in addition to cyclophosphamide for interstitial lung disease (ILD). This study investigated recent actual use of these drugs in Japan. MethodsWe analysed data from a Japanese hospital claims database (2020-2023), identifying patients with SSc disease codes (ICD-10 M34.x) and/or ILD codes. Patients with coexisting autoimmune disease...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can We Combine Mouthrinses With Probiotics? An Evaluation of Their Compatibility and Combined Therapy on Oral Biofilms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The combination of mouthrinses and probiotics has the potential to improve the treatment of oral pathologies and promote a healthier oral microbiome, although compatibility varies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling psychosis risk in sexual minorities: temporal dynamics of social defeat and suspiciousness in adolescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The experience of "not fitting in" when in company may be the most poignant social factor increasing risk for psychotic experiences in sexual minority youth. The findings highlight the need for inclusive environments where sexual minority individuals feel supported and integrated.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vulvar and vaginal cancer during pregnancy: A pooled analysis of 15 cases from the International Network on Cancer, Infertility and Pregnancy and review of the literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study underscores the feasibility of adapting standard oncological care for pregnant patients, emphasizing multidisciplinary teams to optimize maternal and fetal outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indication for biologics in a real-world cohort of dupilumab treated chronic rhinosinusitis with nasal polyps patients according to international recommendations: evidence from the European CRS Outcome Registry (CHRINOSOR)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Real-world management of CRSwNP with biologics does not strictly follow the indication criteria established by international recommendations but depends on management criteria established by local authorities. These vary significantly and are either more or less stringent from one country to another. Dupilumab effectiveness in CRSwNP, whether these criteria are met or not, suggests that a broader CRSwNP population may benefit from dupilumab.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Species-specific gene expression manipulation in humanized livers of chimeric mice via siRNA-encapsulated lipid nanoparticle treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liver-humanized chimeric mice (PXB-mice) are widely utilized for predicting human pharmacokinetics (PK) and as human disease models. However, residual metabolic activity of mouse hepatocytes in chimeric mice can interfere with accurate human PK estimation. Lipid nanoparticle (LNP)-formulated small interfering RNA (siRNA) treatment makes it possible to eliminate the shortcomings of chimeras and create new models. Therefore, we aimed to create a new model in which siRNA for mouse cytochrome P450...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial: Living Well After Organ Transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solid-phase synthesis of polyunsaturated fatty acids facilitates precise structural investigation on FFAR1/4 agonist activities and the inhibition of neutrophil pseudopod formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyunsaturated fatty acids (PUFAs), fatty acids with multiple unsaturated carbon-carbon bonds, constitute a crucial class of lipids. While the vast diversity of PUFA species arises from their structural variations, most of them are poorly investigated due to their limited availability. Here, we utilize solid-phase synthesis of PUFAs, which we have recently developed, to construct a PUFA library. With the library, we investigate agonist activities for free fatty acid receptors 1 (FFAR1) and 4...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic impact of the acute reactiveness to intravenous administration of tolvaptan sodium phosphate in patients with acute decompensated heart failure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Intravenous tolvaptan sodium phosphate enhances decongestion and short-term outcomes in ADHF without worsening renal function. Early diuretic responsiveness is a robust prognostic marker.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unique halogen-π association detected in single crystals of C-N atropisomeric <em>N</em>-(2-halophenyl)quinolin-2-one derivatives and the thione analogue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In single crystals of C-N atropisomeric N-(2-halophenyl)quinolin-2-one and the thione analogue, a unique association based on a halogen-π interaction was detected. In racemic and optically pure N-(2-bromo- or 2-chlorophenyl)quinolin-2-ones, homochiral layered polymers, which consist of (P)- or (M)-atropisomers, were formed through intermolecular halogen-π association. The halogen-π association in the racemates is due to a halogen bond (C-X···π) between a σ-hole on the halogen atom and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A modification of swimmer plot for overviewing the postoperative longitudinal course]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A modified swimmer plot that includes all patients is a useful tool for visualizing longitudinal outcomes and identifying issues that may be overlooked with conventional analytical methods.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful embolization of a large intrahepatic portosystemic shunt using the coil-in-plug technique: A case report assessed with four-dimensional flow magnetic resonance imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Congenital intrahepatic portosystemic shunts are uncommon vascular anomalies that can lead to hyperammonemia and liver dysfunction. We report a 48-year-old woman with a large intrahepatic shunt presenting with elevated blood ammonia and progressive hepatic atrophy. She underwent percutaneous coil-in-plug embolization using an Amplatzer Vascular Plug II filled with coils. Four-dimensional Flow MRI performed before the procedure and at 2 days and 6 months afterward demonstrated complete shunt...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural basis of the residence time of adenosine A<sub>2A</sub> receptor ligands revealed by NMR]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Residence time, which refers to the average duration a drug remains bound to its receptor, is a crucial parameter in determining its pharmacological effects. However, the mechanisms governing the residence time of G protein-coupled receptor (GPCR) ligands remain unclear. In this study, we observed NMR signals from the methyl groups of alanine and methionine located at the intersection of the binding cavity and extracellular loops of A(2A)AR under conditions where E165Q and T256A mutations led to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associated factors for exertional heat exhaustion-related symptoms among amateur golfers in Japan: A retrospective case-control study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The associated factors for exertional heat stroke among amateur golfers remain poorly understood. We conducted a case-control study to examine exertional heat exhaustion (EHE) - related symptoms among amateur golfers in Japan using a self-administered questionnaire. Retrospective case-control study design. A web-based questionnaire was administered from September to November 2024. Data were collected on basic attributes, lifestyle habits, perceived health factors, perceived playing conditions,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive value of postoperative CRP levels for endoscopic recurrence in patients with Crohn's disease undergoing ileocolic resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Elevated CRP levels on POD 4 in CD patients undergoing ICR were associated with an increased risk of ER within 12 months. In combination with other known risk factors, CRP could serve as a marker to identify patients benefitting from closer postoperative monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel method of ultrasound-guided zygomaticotemporal nerve block for awake craniotomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-orbital hybridization in a one-dimensional monolayer of DPh-BTBT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[1]Benzothieno[3,2-b][1]benzothiophene (BTBT)-based molecules exhibit remarkably high hole mobility, sparking interest in their charge transport mechanisms. However, for thin films, the theoretically proposed mixed-orbital charge transport (MOCT) mechanism, which involves the hybridization of different frontier orbitals between neighboring molecules in the bulk, remains unexplored both experimentally and theoretically. In this study, we prepared a monolayer of 2,7-diphenyl-BTBT (DPh-BTBT) with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Network Analysis of Fear-Avoidance Beliefs, Mood and Disability in Chronic Pain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: Although the multifactorial nature of chronic pain is well established, research has predominantly examined isolated variables or singular pathways that may contribute to this condition. We use a complex systems perspective to examine the interplay of psychological factors in the context of chronic pain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Branched-Chain Amino Acids Exacerbate Colitis Progression by Lowering Colonic Fumarate Levels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: BCAA supplementation exacerbates DSS-induced colitis in mice. This effect is mediated by detrimental changes in gut microbiota composition and metabolome. DMF treatment shows promise to mitigate these adverse effects, suggesting potential therapeutic avenues to manage BCAA-induced colitis exacerbation and reinforcing the role of microbiome in UC. These findings underscore the caution needed with the use of BCAAs during inflammatory conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determination of alcohol concentration in a single drop blood obtained via fingertip using gas chromatography/mass spectrometry coupled with solid-phase microextraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated headspace solid-phase microextraction (HS-SPME)-gas chromatography (GS)/mass spectrometry as a low-complexity method for accurate measurement of blood alcohol concentration (BAC) changes in humans over time following alcohol consumption. The aim was to develop an analytical method that would require as small blood samples as possible-smaller than that required for the conventional method-thereby reducing the burden on the subject. Polyethylene glycol (PEG) was used as the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combining and integrating multiple linguistic cues during spoken language comprehension: A focus on semantics and coarticulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This research examines how adults process and integrate a combination of higher-level semantic cues (i.e., semantic context) which are followed by lower-level acoustic cues (i.e., coarticulatory cues) during online spoken comprehension. Previous studies investigating cue integration within Martin (2016)'s framework found that listeners can flexibly use and integrate a variety of available cues across linguistic representations. The current pre-registered study used an eye-tracking paradigm and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Added Value of the YLS/CMI Subscales Beyond the Total Score Among Japanese Youth Offenders in Detention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined whether subscales of the Youth Level of Service Case Management Inventory (YLS/CMI) have added value beyond the total score. Including 238 detained Japanese juvenile offenders (ages 16-19), the proportional reduction in mean squared error (PRMSE) method was applied. Most subscales showed added value, except for Attitudes/Orientation. For the younger group, all subscales except Attitudes/Orientation showed added value. For older juveniles, Family Circumstances/Parenting,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral Administration of Epigallocatechin Gallate Prevents Air Pollution-Induced Acute Lung Injury in Mice Via the Induction of Antioxidants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Health hazards caused by air pollutants are increasing worldwide (SDGs 3.9), but no established prevention methods exist. Recently, we showed that intraperitoneal administration of epigallocatechin gallate (EGCG) prevents air pollutant-induced acute lung injury. To establish EGCG ingestion as a preventive method, the efficacy of oral EGCG administration needs to be analyzed, as it is easier than that of intraperitoneal administration. Therefore, we analyzed the effects of oral EGCG...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between medium-chain triglyceride intake and Functional Independence Measure-cognition score in adults following stroke: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The provision of MCT-enhanced rice was associated with improved cognitive level, activities of daily living, and swallowing function in poststroke patients with cognitive impairment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimands for Early-Phase Dose Optimization Trials in Oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phase I dose escalation trials in oncology generally aim to find the maximum tolerated dose. However, with the advent of molecular-targeted therapies and antibody drug conjugates, dose-limiting toxicities are less frequently observed, giving rise to the concept of optimal biological dose (OBD), which considers both efficacy and toxicity. The estimand framework presented in the addendum of the ICH E9(R1) guidelines strengthens the dialogue between different stakeholders by bringing in greater...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use of a novel zipper device for wound closure of cutaneous abscesses in pediatric outpatients: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case series identifies the fifth day post-I and D as a potential threshold, and suggests that the optimal period of zipper device use is 3 days to 5 days following I and D of skin abscess to enhance early wound healing, beyond which extended intervention intervals prolong wound healing time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychological and neurophysiological measures of emotion dysregulation in borderline personality disorder and posttraumatic stress disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with BPD and PTSD exhibited a reduced emotional reactivity in response to positive and neutral information. Specifically, patients with PTSD demonstrated hypo-reactivity to neutral and trauma-unrelated negative stimuli, which might be due to altered attentional resource allocation following trauma. Although patients reported using adaptive ER strategies less frequently in daily life, they effectively implemented them when instructed to, highlighting important clinical and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911033956&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>