<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:44:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Atom Catalysts Unlock Advanced Oxidation Pathways for Sustainable Precious Metal Recovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precious metals are indispensable for applications ranging from catalysis to electronics; however, their limited availability and the environmental burden of conventional recovery methods raise urgent sustainability concerns. Herein, we propose a single-atom catalysis strategy that enables the efficient and selective recovery of Pd, Pt, Rh, and Au from industrial spent catalysts, ternary automotive catalysts, and electronic waste. Atomically dispersed Co sites activate peroxymonosulfate to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opioid Use as a Predictor of Pancreas Transplant Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Posttransplant opioid dependence is a significant predictor of graft failure after pancreas transplantation. Incorporating this variable into ML models may enhance risk stratification and candidate selection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lineage-matched Oropouche virus mRNA-LNP vaccines confer complete, cross-protective immunity in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oropouche virus (OROV) is an emerging orthobunyavirus responsible for recurrent and increasingly widespread outbreaks across South and Central America, including a recent epidemic that elevated global concern. In addition to its known neurotropic potential-manifesting as meningitis and encephalitis-OROV is now associated with vertical transmission and adverse pregnancy outcomes, underscoring its growing clinical and public health relevance. The rapid geographic expansion and extensive genetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual Targeting of Tau Kinases and Autophagy by Abemaciclib Independent of CDK4/6 Inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is marked by progressive cognitive decline driven largely by tau pathology, yet disease-modifying therapies targeting tau remain limited. In this study, we re-evaluated abemaciclib, a clinically approved CDK4/6 inhibitor for breast cancer and uncovered its previously unrecognized therapeutic potential in AD via CDK4/6-independent mechanisms. Using the APP^(NL-F)/MAPT double knock-in mouse model (dKI) and AD patient-derived brain organoids, we found that abemaciclib...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large Language Model-Generated Expansion of the RadLex Ontology: Application to Multinational Datasets of Chest CT Reports]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: RadLex is a widely used radiology-specific ontology that standardizes terminology for clinical and research uses. However, the ontology's coverage of clinical radiology reports remains limited due to radiologists' linguistic variation. Objective: To use a large language model (LLM) to generate an expanded set of lexical variants and synonyms for the RadLex ontology and to evaluate the impact of this expansion on lexical coverage and semantic term recognition using clinical radiology...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Validation of a Deep Learning Index for Aortic Stenosis Progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DLi-ASc increased in parallel with AS progression and was independently associated with severe AS progression. These findings support its role as a noninvasive imaging-based digital marker for longitudinal AS monitoring and risk stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Modular Vaccine Platform Against SARS-CoV-2 Based on Self-Assembled Protein Nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic has underscored the urgent need for deployable vaccine platforms capable of rapidly responding to emerging and re-emerging variants of human coronaviruses. BP26, an outer membrane protein of the zoonotic bacterium Brucella, self-assembles into a highly ordered, barrel-like nanoparticle that can serve as a vaccine platform, demonstrating immunogenicity against the influenza virus and cancer when combined with specific antigens. Here, we expanded its versatility by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gastric cancer organoids and their convergence in engineering approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric cancer research has rapidly progressed due to interdisciplinary advances in stem cell biology and bioengineering. Gastric organoid models, particularly those derived from adult stem cells, have emerged as powerful tools that recapitulate the cellular complexity of the human stomach. This review highlights the development of various gastric organoid platforms, with a specific focus on the convergence of engineering strategies to overcome the limitations of conventional organoid systems....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Challenges of an EMR-Based Hospital Alert Program for Micro-Elimination of Hepatitis C in Tertiary Referral Hospitals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite advances in hepatitis C virus (HCV) treatments, diagnostic gaps and linkage-to-care hinder elimination efforts. We evaluated an electronic medical record (EMR)-based automated alert system to improve HCV care at tertiary referral centers. We have screened 1,303,578 patients who were tested for anti-HCV, and analyzed 8291 patients positive for anti-HCV antibody (Ab) across four tertiary hospitals between July 2009 and December 2023. The EMR alert system, implemented in June 2021,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Neuropeptide Fam19a5a/tafa5a Regulates Inflammation and Influences Anxiety-Like Behaviours in Zebrafish]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anxiety is a future-oriented mood state that consists of a complex cognitive, affective, physiological and behavioural response system that prepares individuals for perceived or anticipated threats. Although the neural circuits underlying anxiety behaviours have been extensively studied, how inflammatory factors influence anxiety and the molecular links between them remains poorly understood. To gain novel insights into these mechanisms, we investigated the role of fam19a5a, a zebrafish ortholog...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Readily Programmable, Body Temperature-Responsive Liquid Crystal Elastomers With Dynamic Covalent Thiourea Bonds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liquid crystal elastomers (LCEs) are promising stimuli-responsive materials for applications in wearable devices, biomedical devices, and soft robotics owing to their thermotropic shape-changing behaviors. However, conventional LCEs exhibit high phase-transition temperatures, often exceeding 60°C, which limits their use in human-interfacing applications. Herein, we present body heat-responsive LCEs incorporating dynamic thiourea bonds. Body temperature actuation is achieved by introducing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Safe-by-Design Principle Aligned Mixture INteraction TOXicity (MINTOX) Framework for Predicting the Joint Toxicity Effects in Metal Oxide Nanoparticle-Metal Ion Binary Mixtures: Toward Assessment of Innovative Advanced Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Toxicity assessment in Innovative Advanced Materials is challenging owing to complex interactions between components. Here we present MINTOX as a proof-of-concept framework developed and demonstrated on binary mixtures of metal oxide nanoparticles and dissolved metal ions. The MINTOX integrated dose-response modeling based on four complementary toxicity indices to predict the nonlinear joint toxicity effects of nanomaterial-ion mixtures, and its application to 18 binary mixtures (TiO(2), ZnO,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal Analysis of the Early Stage of Amyloid Formation via Graphene Liquid Cell Electron Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Elucidating the early-stage dynamics of amyloid aggregation is crucial for comprehending the pathological mechanisms underlying neurodegenerative diseases. Conventional techniques, such as cryo-electron microscopy and ensemble-based spectroscopy, offer valuable structural insights but face challenges in capturing real-time molecular interactions due to low temporal resolution and the need for ensemble averaging, which obscures transient intermediate states. To investigate the early-stage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cellulose Nanofibers Derived From Sea Squirt Tunics for Enhancing PEM Fuel Cells Performance via Pt/C-Ionomer Agglomerate Engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, high-aspect-ratio cellulose nanofibers (CNFs) are extracted from sea squirt tunic via acid hydrolysis and use as nanofillers in the cathode catalyst layers (CLs) of polymer electrolyte membrane fuel cells (PEMFCs). Because of the aqueous-based extraction process, CNFs possess numerous hydrophilic functional groups on their surfaces, enabling their excellent dispersibility in organic solvents. By leveraging both the high aspect ratio and hydrophilic surface characteristics of CNFs,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fully automated and high-fidelity robotic platform enabling accelerated discovery of nanocatalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The discovery of heterogeneous catalysts increasingly relies on high-throughput experimentation and high-fidelity data. Here, we report a fully automated robotic platform that integrates two synchronized collaborative robotic arms, automated liquid handling, and time-resolved UV-Vis kinetic analysis for the rapid, reproducible, and data-rich evaluation of nanocatalysts. Unlike existing high-throughput systems, which often compromise data quality, our platform combines parallel reaction execution...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of a digital sexual violence prevention education program on digital sexual violence prevention knowledge, self-protection behavior, and digital citizenship among fifth-grade children: a quasi-experimental study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The four-session digital sexual violence prevention education program effectively enhanced digital sexual violence prevention knowledge and bystander self-efficacy related to digital citizenship among fifth-grade students. Further research using a randomized controlled design with a larger sample size is recommended to confirm and extend these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychometric testing of the Korean version of the Wijma Delivery Expectancy Questionnaire: a methodological study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Korean W-DEQ demonstrated satisfactory reliability and validity, confirming its usefulness for assessing maternal fear of childbirth in both nulliparous and multiparous women.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Remnant Cholesterol on the Risk for End-Stage Renal Disease in Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus: A Nationwide Population-Based Cohort Study (Diabetes Metab J 2025;49:1106-15)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health Effects of Sugar-Sweetened and Artificially Sweetened Beverages: Umbrella Review and Evidence-Based Consensus Statement of the Korean Diabetes Association and the Korean Nutrition Society]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ASBs may serve as a short-term substitution for individuals with high SSB intake, particularly those at elevated metabolic risk. However, regular or long-term use is not recommended due to uncertain safety and potential reinforcement of sweet preference. Public health strategies should emphasize reducing both SSBs and ASBs, prioritizing water and unsweetened beverages as the ultimate goal.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tegoprazan-Based Triple Therapy for Helicobacter pylori Eradication: A Phase III Multicenter Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Tegoprazan-based triple therapies, at 50- and 100-mg doses, were non-inferior to lansoprazole-based therapy and were well tolerated. Our findings indicated that tegoprazan-based triple therapy is a viable first-line option for H. pylori eradication.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced prediction of left ventricular ejection fraction using electrocardiography with the addition of clinical metadata]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The combination of ECG and metadata results using AI enhances the predictive accuracy of HFrEF detection. This approach offers a scalable and noninvasive method for HF screening and risk stratification, particularly in resource-limited settings. Further validation in diverse populations is needed to confirm its clinical utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative efficacy and safety of warfarin and direct oral anticoagulants in patients with end-stage kidney disease and atrial fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among Korean patients with ESKD and AF, both warfarin and DOACs reduced IS/SE but increased MB. Given their lower MB risk than warfarin, DOACs may be preferable for anticoagulation in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced strategies for the management of patients with diabetic foot ulcers: a comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic foot ulcers (DFUs) are among the most serious and common complications of diabetes mellitus. They significantly affect patients' quality of life and impose a substantial economic burden on healthcare systems worldwide. In Korea, the prevalence of diabetes and related complications, such as DFUs, has been increasing, reflecting a broader global trend. DFUs are associated with severe complications, including infections, neuropathy, and peripheral arterial disease, often leading to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiomics-Based Prediction of Lymphedema after Radiotherapy in Breast Cancer: Integrating Clinical and Dosimetric Features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Integrating radiomic features with clinical and dosimetric factors showed potential to enhance lymphedema prediction in patients with breast cancer receiving PORT. This model can potentially guide personalized treatment strategies and improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of third cleavage timing on blastulation and miRNA-429 expression in cryopreserved mouse embryos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Based on these findings, we suggest that the timing of the third cleavage event may be more critical than the vitrification process itself, and evaluating miRNA-429 expression could serve as an alternative non-invasive selection tool for vitrified surplus embryos.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imaging Based Modalities for Identifying "At Risk" MASH. A Diagnostic Test Meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FAST with its accessibility and robust diagnostic performance may be well-suited for large-scale application. MRI-based techniques are effective non-invasive options for diagnosing "at risk" MASH in MASLD and may provide strong alternatives. Rather than challenging existing perspectives, this study provides a reflective overview of current evidence on imaging-based modalities for "at risk" MASH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light-induced C-H activation on single-atom doped plasmonic silver nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The selective conversion of methane, a highly stable molecule, remains a central challenge in catalysis. Plasmonic antenna-reactor systems offer a promising strategy for light-driven methane activation, yet the role of single-atom dopants in modulating their activity is not fully understood. Here we show, through dynamic simulations of plasmon-induced bond-length variations, that single-atom dopants on Ag(20) plasmonic nanoparticles can dramatically enhance C-H bond activation. In particular, Ga...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Efficacy of Mesenchymal Stem Cells (MSCs) on Alzheimer's Disease: Review of Clinical Results]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The analysis of 17 clinical trials and 5 relevant clinical outcomes showed that MSCs therapy if feasible and generally safe in AD patients. There are indications of potential therapeutic benefits such as improved cognitive function or quality of life measures in some AD patients. However, its therapeutic efficacy has not been proven definitely due to small size of subjects, variations in dosage, MSCs source, and administration scheme (route, timing, and frequency). Larger subject...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal urodynamic changes and UTI risk factors in neurogenic bladder patients using clean intermittent catheterization: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-powered hierarchical classification of ampullary neoplasms: a deep learning approach using white-light and narrow-band imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A hierarchical deep learning approach integrating dual-modality imaging and synthetic data augmentation significantly improves diagnostic performance for ampullary lesions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutational Signatures and Clonal Hematopoiesis in Intestinal Metaplasia across Countries with Varying Stomach Cancer Incidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intestinal metaplasia (IM) is a premalignant condition associated with increased risk of gastric cancer-a deadly malignancy with varying geographic incidence. High-depth targeted sequencing of more than 1,500 IM samples from six countries identified 47 significantly mutated genes, including driver genes associated with high-risk populations and worse prognosis (ARID1A), KRAS/MAPK signaling (KRAS, BRAF, MAP2K1, MAP3K1, and MAP2K4), and altered mucosal immunity (PIGR). IM whole-genome sequencing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interpreting the Gastric Atrophy-ESCC Association: Avoiding Causal Overreach and Advancing Mechanistic Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Split Face Study Comparing the Effect of a PDLLA Based Product and PLLA on the Nasolabial Fold (NLF)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The PDLLA based product demonstrated non-inferiority to PLLA for NLF correction. Further studies are needed to assess long-term safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spectroscopic Signatures of Structural Disorder and Electron-Phonon Interactions in Trigonal Selenium Thin Films for Solar Energy Harvesting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Selenium is experiencing renewed interest as a elemental semiconductor for a range of optoelectronic and energy applications due to its irresistibly simple composition and favorable wide bandgap. However, its high volatility and low radiative efficiency make it challenging to assess structural and optoelectronic quality, calling for advanced, non-destructive characterization methods. In this work, we employ a closed-space encapsulation strategy to prevent degradation during measurement and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Host-Directed Antiviral Activity of SB2960 Through Selective Induction and Remodeling of Stress Granules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing prevalence of emerging infectious diseases highlights the urgent need for broad-spectrum antiviral therapeutics. Here, the discovery of SB2960, a small molecule, is reported that promotes stress granule (SG) formation and exhibits potent antiviral activity across diverse viral species. SB2960 suppresses viral replication with minimal cytotoxicity by modulating host antiviral immune responses. Target identification studies reveal that SB2960 engages receptor for activated protein C...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Does Injecting Filler Into Facial Ligaments Result in Facial Lifting?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The lifting effect of filler injection arises from a synergistic mechanism that combines volumetric restoration with biomechanical reinforcement of fibrous anchoring structures. Understanding the regional variability and mechanical behavior of facial ligaments enables anatomy-based, low-volume rejuvenation strategies that preserve natural dynamics. Further clinical and quantitative biomechanical studies are warranted to validate these observations under physiological conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prenatal exposure to ambient air pollution and risk of neurodevelopmental disorders in offspring: A nationwide population-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prenatal exposure to ambient air pollutants - particularly NO(2) and SO(2) - is associated with increased long-term risk of NDD in offspring. These findings highlight the neurodevelopmental vulnerability of the prenatal period and underscore the need for strengthened environmental policies to reduce maternal exposure to harmful pollutants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research Code Sharing in Support of Gold Standard Science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sharing research code in an open access version-controlled repository offers significant benefits for both science as a whole and for individual researchers. In this article, we focus on this practice, which is fully aligned with the NIH's Gold Standard Science (GSS) program as well as FAIR (findable, accessible, interoperable, reusable) and TRUST (transparency, responsibility, user focus, sustainability, technology) principles. Gold Standard Science supports open science by emphasizing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbamoylation of Aryl and Benzyl Chlorides by Direct C-H Functionalization of Formamide Derivatives via Ni/Photoredox-Catalyzed Cross-Coupling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a Ni/photoredox dual catalytic protocol that activates the formyl C-H bond of simple formamides to enable C(sp²)-C(sp²)/C(sp²)-C(sp³) carbamoylation with aryl and benzyl chlorides. This transformation proceeds without the need for prefunctionalized carbamoyl radical precursors, external oxidants, or halogen atom transfer (XAT)/hydrogen atom transfer (HAT) reagents by harnessing in situ-generated Cl radicals for selective HAT followed by the cross-coupling event. This strategy provides...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preprocedural Left Atrial Strain as a Predictor of Long-Term Outcomes Following Mitral Valve Interventions in Rheumatic Severe Mitral Stenosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preprocedural decreased LA reservoir strain was associated with adverse clinical outcomes after MV intervention in individuals with severe mitral stenosis. These findings suggest that LA strain could serve as a marker for optimizing the timing of MV intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social Determinants of Health and Falls Among Community-Dwelling Older Adults: A Zero-Inflated Negative Binomial Regression Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings provide empirical evidence on the critical roles of SDOH in falls among community-dwelling older adults. Specifically, a ZINB regression analysis identified distinct sets of SDOH associated with fall occurrence versus fall frequency, highlighting the complex and multifaceted nature of fall patterns among older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure Polygenic Score Predicts Long-Term Blood Pressure Control and Treatment-Resistant Hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Harnessing BP PGSs may inform anticipated trends in BP control to warrant vigilant monitoring and augment prioritization of intensive therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvent mediated hierarchically porous NiCo-LDH decorated with Au nanoparticles for catalytic platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ni-Co layered double hydroxides (LDHs) were synthesized via an ethyleneglycol-assisted sol-gel method, forming near-spherical structures with highly accessible surface layers. Uniformly deposited Au nanoparticles further enhanced electron transfer, resulting in a hierarchical hybrid catalyst with strong activity for 4-nitrophenol reduction and excellent potential as an efficient catalytic platform.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacial design strategies using metal-organic frameworks: a comprehensive review for rechargeable batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Modifying battery interfaces to improve stability and performance, and suppress side reactions has been a long-standing goal. Although there were many candidates, metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) have garnered particular attention owing to their unique porous structure, tunability, and multifunctionality. Due to these characteristics, MOFs could contribute to regulating the diffusion path of carrier ions, mitigating undesired reactions, as well as stabilizing the interfaces. Therefore, MOFs were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urinary extracellular vesicle proteins for biomarker discovery in chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic kidney disease (CKD) is a progressive condition characterized by declining kidney function principally driven by diabetes mellitus, glomerulonephritis, and hypertension. Although renal biopsy is the gold standard for diagnosing CKD, its invasive nature restricts its use for early detection and routine clinical applications. Current noninvasive biomarkers, including the estimated glomerular filtration rate and albumin-to-creatinine ratio, are useful indicators of kidney dysfunction but...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-wavelength oblique back-illumination microscopy for deep <em>in vivo</em> imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oblique back-illumination microscopy (OBM) is a label-free imaging technique that captures differential forward scattering in reflection mode to generate high-contrast pseudo-transmission images of cells and microvessels. While OBM benefits from multiple light scattering to detect forward-scattered signals, its imaging depth is constrained by tissue scattering between the objective lens and the imaging plane. In this study, we introduce a long-wavelength OBM system operating at 1650...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anisotropic mechanotransductive tissue constructs <em>via</em> brush-assisted bioprinting of microfiber-reinforced composite bioinks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Engineering aligned musculoskeletal and cardiac tissues remains a key challenge due to the lack of mechanical cues in conventional bioinks. Here, we present a synergistic strategy combining fiber-reinforced collagen bioinks with a brush-assisted bioprinting (BAB) process to fabricate highly organized, functional tissue constructs. The bioink incorporates straight and coiled poly(ε-caprolactone) (PCL) microfibers to deliver spatially defined biophysical guidance, while the BAB process applies...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An international scoping review of epidemiologic studies on severe cutaneous adverse reactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Substantial regional disparities were identified in SCAR epidemiology research. These findings highlight the need for standardized data collection, expanded surveillance infrastructure, and region-specific strategies to improve international drug safety as well as SCAR prevention and management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retrieval augmented large language model system for comprehensive drug contraindications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The versatility of large language models (LLMs) has been explored across various sectors, but their application in healthcare poses challenges, particularly in the domain of pharmaceutical contraindications where accurate and reliable information is required. This study enhances the capability of LLMs to address contraindications effectively by implementing a Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) pipeline. Utilizing OpenAI's GPT-4o-mini as the base model, and the text-embedding-3-small model for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are we looking at the average or at the distribution? Interpreting divergent signals from the Republic of Korea's national health surveys]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiological trends in emergency department visits by age group: a report from the National Emergency Department Information System (NEDIS) of Korea, 2020-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Entrustable professional activity-aligned workplace-based assessments in the emergency department: perceptions of emergency medicine residents and assessors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Two WBAs for three Korean Society of Emergency Medicine EPAs were found to be feasible and acceptable in the context of Korean EM residency training. However, perceptions varied between assessors and residents, necessitating clear communication about WBA objectives and processes. Our findings are useful for shaping future EPA-based training programs, balancing traditional and WBA methods, and enhancing feedback quality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethical considerations of artificial intelligence in emergency medicine for triage and resource allocation: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ethical and legal discussions regarding AI in emergency medicine are evolving toward seeking concrete solutions at technical, institutional, and relational dimensions. However, in-depth research on ethical challenges, such as reflecting the specificity of rapidly developing AI and the values of emergency medicine, is urgently required.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Updated Sequential Organ Failure Assessment (SOFA)-2 score: major changes and emergency department perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of a brief web-based intervention on improving intention and awareness related to reducing alcohol consumption during pregnancy among high-risk female college student drinkers: a quasi-experimental study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The brief web-based intervention significantly improved attitudes toward drinking during pregnancy, intentions to abstain from drinking during pregnancy, and drinking refusal self-efficacy, highlighting both the effectiveness and importance of this intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does health-related quality of life change across pregnancy trimesters? A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HRQOL during pregnancy follows distinct temporal patterns, emphasizing the need for trimester-specific maternal care strategies. Early pregnancy may require greater emphasis on mental health support, while late pregnancy may benefit from interventions targeting physical discomfort and functional limitations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of cognitive behavioral therapy on sleep quality and insomnia severity index in women with menopausal insomnia: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CBT-I is an effective non-pharmacological intervention for improving sleep quality and reducing insomnia severity in menopausal women. These findings support the integration of CBT-I into clinical practice, particularly as a nurse-led intervention that can be delivered in both face-to-face and remote formats. To enable broader implementation, standardized CBT-I training programs and clinical protocols should be developed. Future studies should investigate long-term effectiveness and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fertility preservation in women with cancer: shared decision-making and the essential role of nurses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New developments in women's health research and implications for nursing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drug-induced phospholipidosis of the kidney suspected to be caused by atomoxetine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drug-induced phospholipidosis (DIP) is characterized by intracellular accumulation of phospholipids with lamellar body formation secondary to drug-altered lipid metabolism, which can trigger inflammation and histopathological changes. Fabry disease and DIP both exhibit zebra bodies on electron microscopy, complicating differential diagnosis. A 17-year-old male with microscopic hematuria and proteinuria had received atomoxetine (40 mg) for 11 months to treat attention-deficit hyperactivity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revisiting human sparganosis: a pathologic review from a single institution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study underscores the importance of recognizing the characteristic histopathological features of sparganosis, which can allow for accurate diagnosis even in the absence of clinical suspicion. Although rare, sparganosis remains a relevant diagnostic consideration in endemic regions, particularly in East Asia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Significance of KM55 immunohistochemical staining in the diagnosis and prognosis of IgA nephropathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Mesangial Gd-IgA1 deposition graded by KM55 immunohistochemistry may be a useful adjunct for IgAN diagnosis and a potential prognostic biomarker.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing pathology through sixty volumes: reflections and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-Processed Food Intake and Risk of Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus: A Dose-Response Meta-Analysis of Prospective Studies (Diabetes Metab J 2025;49:1064-74)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Remnant Cholesterol on the Risk for End-Stage Renal Disease in Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus: A Nationwide Population-Based Cohort Study (Diabetes Metab J 2025;49:1106-15)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Preclinical Obesity in Korean Adults from 2014 to 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first large-scale study to apply the clinical obesity framework in an Asian population. The framework identifies high-risk individuals missed by BMI al.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exercise, Exerkines, and Sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenia is a progressive age-related musculoskeletal disorder characterized by loss of skeletal muscle mass, strength, and physical function. Closely associated with aging and physical inactivity, it significantly compromises mobility, independence, and quality of life in older adults. Exercise is widely recognized as an effective non-pharmacological intervention for managing sarcopenia. However, the underlying molecular mechanisms remain incompletely elucidated. Among the emerging mediators,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sodium-Glucose Cotransporter 2 Inhibitors as Emerging Anticancer Agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sodium-glucose cotransporter 2 (SGLT2) inhibitors are established treatments for type 2 diabetes mellitus, heart failure, and chronic kidney disease, with well-documented metabolic and cardiorenal benefits. Emerging evidence indicates that these agents may also exert anticancer effects through mechanisms independent of glucose lowering. Preclinical studies have demonstrated functional SGLT2 expression in tumors such as prostate, pancreatic, breast, colorectal, and bone cancers. Inhibition of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beneficial effects of SGLT1/2 and SGLT2 inhibitors on vaso-occlusive events and organ damage in sickle cell disease mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that DAPA and SOTA mitigate vaso-occlusive events in SCD, with SOTA providing superior benefits.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of low-dose mepolizumab in refractory eosinophilic granulomatosis with polyangiitis: systemic steroid use and remission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Low-dose mepolizumab treatment demonstrated clinical efficacy in reducing the maintenance dose of systemic steroids required for severe refractory EGPA. While not all patients achieved EGPA remission with low-dose mepolizumab, some did, and their remission persisted even after treatment discontinuation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Arteriovenous fistulas are associated with superior outcomes in very elderly hemodialysis patients: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this large-scale study, AVF use was associated with superior patency and lower mortality compared with AVG in patients aged ≥ 80 years. These findings suggest that AVF remains a beneficial option for appropriately selected elderly patients and that age alone should not be a primary barrier to its creation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between diabetes duration and hyperuricemia: Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey 2016 to 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The U-shaped association between diabetes duration and hyperuricemia was observed in a representative sample of Korean adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of experiences on telemedicine pilot projects from the perspectives of doctors, pharmacists, and patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Appropriate telemedicine systems require collaboration among doctors, pharmacists, and patients. While most groups expressed positive attitudes and future intentions, significant gaps in experience and understanding must be addressed to ensure successful implementation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of viral hepatitis A and C in patients with inflammatory bowel disease: a nationwide population-based study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HCV showed an increasing trend in Korean patients with IBD, especially those with Crohn's disease. Corticosteroids use is a risk factor for hepatitis in patients with IBD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of Helicobacter pylori eradication and development of immune-mediated disorder in children: a nationwide population-based study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study found H. pylori infection to be associated with the development of IBD in children. However, eradication does not increase IBD and asthma in children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for bleeding from gastric antral vascular ectasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A careful follow-up for bleeding is needed in GAVE patients with liver cirrhosis, CKD, use of antithrombotic agents, and duodenal bulb involvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Telemedicine in Korea: bridging the gap between convenience and clinical safety]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antidepressants and the risk of hyponatremia: A multi-institutional cohort study using observational medical outcomes partnership-Common Data Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Close monitoring of serum sodium levels is essential for SSRI users, especially those aged ≥60 years.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obstetric Outcomes of Jehovah's Witness Women Under Patient Blood Management: A Single-center, Propensity Score-Matched Cohort Study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identified no significant differences in hemorrhage-related obstetric outcomes between JW and non-JW women at a PBM-based center. The systematic application of PBM enables safe delivery in transfusion-restricted settings and may reduce reliance on blood transfusion while maintaining maternal safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Cubic Ni<sub>3</sub>Sn Bimetallic Nanoparticles as a New Polymorph by Sequential Exsolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The non-equilibrium phase among the polymorphs of the materials provides a new solution to harness the unique properties for various applications. However, advanced synthetic routes need to be developed to experimentally realize the novel phases to overcome the thermodynamic stability of their equilibrium counterparts. Here, we synthesized cubic Ni(3)Sn bimetallic nanoparticles (NPs), known as a non-equilibrium polymorph, by the sequential exsolution of Ni and Sn metallic cation species from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atypical manifestation of human herpes virus-6 encephalitis with extra-limbic lesions: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human herpesvirus-6 (HHV-6) encephalitis represents a serious opportunistic infection in immunocompromised patients that is associated with substantial mortality and long-term neurological sequelae. The disease most often involves the limbic system, with typical neuroimaging findings restricted to the hippocampal and amygdaloid structures. Here, we describe a rare case of HHV-6 encephalitis presenting with atypical imaging features, which demonstrated near-complete resolution following...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A narrative review of antiseizure medication adherence in epilepsy: determinants to clinical implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving optimal seizure control without recurrence is a critical goal in epilepsy. When evaluating whether treatment is effective, medication adherence must be carefully considered but has traditionally been overlooked. In this study, we introduce commonly used definitions of medication adherence and examine adherence findings in epilepsy and other chronic diseases. Factors influencing adherence are analyzed according to three domains: the characteristics of the medication itself,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[metaFun: An analysis pipeline for metagenomic big data with fast and unified functional searches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metagenomic approaches offer unprecedented opportunities to characterize microbial community structure and function, yet several challenges remain unresolved. Inconsistent genome quality impairs reliability of metagenome-assembled genomes, lack of unified taxonomic criteria limits cross-study comparability, and multi-step workflows involving numerous programs and parameters hinder reproducibility and accessibility. We benchmarked existing programs and parameters using simulated metagenomic data...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Routine Application of Three-Dimensional Transesophageal Echocardiography-based Device Selection for Transcatheter Closure of Atrial Septal Defect without Balloon Sizing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preprocedural determination of device size based on 3D TEE provides a safe and useful framework in routine clinical practice. Because of the diversity in maximal diameter orientation, balloon sizing using a fixed fluoroscopic angle may underestimate the true maximal diameter of an ASD.(ClinicalTrials.gov number NCT02097758).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Array Nano Configuration for High-Performance Metastable β Titanium Alloys]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Catastrophic failures in engineering metallics frequently occur at high temperatures. A fundamental understanding of plastic deformation and the mechanisms governing the strength-ductility trade-off is essential for developing titanium alloys exhibiting superior properties at elevated temperatures. Herein, a metastable β titanium alloy (Ti-15.1Mo-3.1Nb-2.77Al-0.21Si, wt.%) exhibits unexpected mechanical properties, including an ultimate tensile strength of 863 MPa and a total elongation of 78.3%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Paradoxical regression: hidden aggression in carcinoma ex pleomorphic adenoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scoping review of regulatory transparency in AI-based radiology software: analysis of PMDA-approved SaMD products]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practice disparities in palliative radiation therapy for bone metastases: insights from the Shizuoka Kokuho database study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This population-based study using medical claims data demonstrated practice disparities in pRT for bone metastases, particularly at the facility level. To improve this disparity, facility-level strategies seem to be more effective than SMA-level approaches.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-occlusive mesenteric ischemia induced by methamphetamine: an autopsy case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-occlusive mesenteric ischemia (NOMI) is an acute form of intestinal ischemia that occurs in the absence of organic stenosis of the mesenteric arteries. Vasoconstrictive agents have been recognized as potential etiological factors. This report describes the first documented Japanese autopsy case of NOMI induced by methamphetamine (MA), a potent sympathomimetic agent. A forensic autopsy was performed on a man in his 60s who died suddenly. Gross and histopathological findings of the small...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the effectiveness between propensity score-matched trabecular micro-bypass stent versus ab interno trabeculotomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In eyes with relatively well-controlled preoperative IOP-where either IS or LOT could be reasonably selected-either procedure offers similar surgical outcomes, with comparable postoperative performance and complication rates, except for postoperative hyphema.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ten-year changes in risk factors for requiring treatment of retinopathy of prematurity in extremely low birth weight infants: a multicenter study in Tokyo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Birth weight and gestational age of extremely low birth weight infants born in Tokyo have decreased significantly compared with 10 years previously, and the severity of ROP has not increased. Advances in respiratory management may have contributed to reducing the risk of developing severe ROP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and clinical features of malignant glaucoma after Preserflo MicroShunt implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although rare, MG can occur in the early postoperative period after PMS implantation, particularly in older patients with a high preoperative IOP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and risks of drug holiday in the management of medication-related osteonecrosis of the jaw in cancer patients: a single-center retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A therapeutic strategy involving planned BMA discontinuation followed by delayed surgical intervention after radiographic confirmation of sequestrum formation, may be associated with improved healing outcomes. This approach does not appear to increase the incidence of SREs, particularly when BMA therapy is appropriately resumed after successful surgical healing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomic profiling of mouse lungs after radon inhalation and lipopolysaccharide administration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radon therapy alleviates the symptoms of autoimmune diseases by enhancing antioxidant and anti-inflammatory effects. Although radon inhalation normalizes serum cytokine concentrations modulated by lipopolysaccharide (LPS) administration, it also increases pulmonary oxidative stress. Hence, its effects on lungs must be comprehensively evaluated; however, no study has reported the effects of short-term radon inhalation or the associated proteomic changes. In this study, we aimed to evaluate the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[American Association for the Surgery of Trauma-World Society of Emergency Surgery Guidelines on the diagnosis and management of cervical vascular injuries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights into the crystal packing interactions of a 960-nm-emissive DNA-stabilized silver nanocluster]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA-stabilized silver nanoclusters (DNA-AgNCs) can be finely tuned through DNA sequence design. Here, we present mutations in a DNA strand that stabilize an [Ag(28)Cl(2)]^(14+) cluster, which remains largely unaltered, as confirmed by spectroscopy and mass spectrometry. The crystal structure of one mutant further reveals previously unseen packing interactions among DNA-AgNCs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning-Based Prognostic Scoring for Spinal Metastases: A JASA Multicenter Prospective Study Integrating Modern Oncologic Advances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We developed a clinically applicable prognostic scoring system for patients with spinal metastases using machine learning techniques to enhance predictive accuracy. This model provides a practical risk assessment tool to aid surgical decision-making and optimize postoperative management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Background-Free Nanopore Decoding of microRNA Expression Patterns Using Circular Diagnostic DNA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a background-free nanopore decoding method to identify microRNA (miRNA) expression patterns that are both upregulated and downregulated. This method uses a circular DNA construct on MinION, a commercially available nanopore device. This system uses a pair of complementary diagnostic DNAs (dgDNAs) that form a closed structure too large to pass through the nanopore. This effectively prevents translocation and eliminates background signals. When the target miRNAs bind to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graphene oxide in the fight against viruses: from biosensing and antiviral action to protective materials and vaccine delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graphene oxide (GO) has evolved from a laboratory curiosity into a practical and multifunctional material against viral threats. Owing to its large surface area, adjustable surface chemistry, sharp-edged 2D morphology, and intrinsic conductivity, GO finds utility throughout the pandemic response pipeline including fast diagnostics, direct virion inactivation, antiviral coatings, and vaccine delivery. This review compiles and critically evaluates evidence of how GO captures and ruptures viruses,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unexpected dynamics of peptoid-conjugated dyad systems: ultrafast photoinduced electron transfer in off-facial arrangement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peptoids (oligo-N-substituted glycines) offer a promising scaffold for photophysical platforms enabling precise control over the geometry between electron acceptor (A) and donor (D) moieties. In this study, we synthesized two peptoid dyads with an anthracene acceptor and an N,N-dimethylaniline donor, designed to adopt co-facial (i,i + 3)-Ac and a distant off-facial (i,i + 2)-Ac. Initial photophysical characterization presented a puzzle: while steady-state measurements confirmed different spectra...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beta-3 Adrenoreceptor Agonist Mirabegron Improves Right Ventricular Function in a Rat Monocrotaline-Induced Pulmonary Hypertension Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Considering the beta-3 adrenoceptor agonist, mirabegron, may display vasodilator and cardioprotective properties, we investigated the therapeutic potential of mirabegron in monocrotaline-induced pulmonary hypertension in rats. High-dose mirabegron improved right ventricular function, and endothelium-dependent relaxation in isolated rat pulmonary arteries, suggesting that mirabegron may be beneficial in pulmonary arterial hypertension.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a digital analysis system for a novel 3D culture-based colony formation to detect malignantly transformed cells in human cell-based therapeutic products]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Finally, by systematizing the digital analysis system for the LACF assay (D-LACF assay), which streamlines the overall workflow from the performance evaluation of the test method to product testing and result interpretation, the limitations of the conventional soft agar-based D-SACF assay were addressed, and its practicality and utility were enhanced. This in vitro evaluation system is expected to provide a promising approach for improving the quality and safety of hCTPs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41532030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D printed system using <em>ex vivo</em> porcine eye globes to investigate intracorneal absorption of dexpanthenol from contact lens care solution and eye drops]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reduction of the use of animal models in research is encouraged for the sake of animal wellbeing. However, available in vitro models in the specific case of topical ocular delivery/penetration studies are often oversimplified by the use of excised corneal or scleral tissue and the frequent lack of dynamic barriers such as the lacrimal outwash. This is why we have developed our novel ex vivo porcine eye globe 3D printed laboratory setup with simulated tear flow, using enucleated porcine eyes....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum HER2 extracellular domain as a predictive biomarker for trastuzumab deruxtecan treatment response in HER2-positive gastric cancer: a real-world study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Baseline serum HER2 ECD may be a potential non-invasive predictor of T-DXd response in HER2-positive AGC, particularly in IHC 2+/ISH+ cases. Dynamic HER2 ECD level changes during therapy may also reflect treatment response.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a radioiodinated boronic acid probe for the detection of hydrogen peroxide and peroxynitrite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen peroxide and peroxynitrite play important roles as signaling molecules to maintain the biological functions; however, excess levels of these oxidants are associated with various diseases. Despite their important roles in vivo, effective methods to measure these oxidants in the body with high sensitivity have not yet been established. Therefore, in this study, we aimed to design a radioiodinated boronic acid probe for the in vivo detection of hydrogen peroxide and peroxynitrite. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient and accurate prime editing system in plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41531318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes after switching from sulfamethoxazole-trimethoprim to atovaquone due to intolerance in patients with non-HIV Pneumocystis pneumonia: a single-center retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our data suggest that switching from SMX/TMP to Atov may not be associated with worse survival. Long-term administration of SMX/TMP is often challenging due to its side effects, and in this study, more than 30% of patients were unable to tolerate its therapeutic dose. Our findings support the role of Atov as a viable second-line treatment for PCP in immunocompromised patients, such as those with non-HIV PCP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influenza A virus infection dynamics in two sow herds and effects of interventions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41530816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The RNA-binding protein HuR modulates the expression of the disease-linked <em>CCL2</em> rs1024611G-rs13900T haplotype]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CC-chemokine ligand 2 (CCL2) is involved in the pathogenesis of several diseases associated with monocyte/macrophage recruitment, such as HIV-associated neurocognitive disorder (HAND), tuberculosis, and atherosclerosis. The rs1024611 (alleles: A>G; G is the risk allele) polymorphism in the CCL2 cis-regulatory region is associated with increased CCL2 expression in vitro and ex vivo, leukocyte mobilization in vivo, and deleterious disease outcomes. However, the molecular basis for the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Negative feedback regulation of alcohol ingestion through the FGF21-PVH oxytocin-VTA dopamine system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alcohol has a notable negative impact on global health. Understanding its physiological regulation is crucial to addressing alcohol use. Here, we show that FGF21-oxytocin neurons in the paraventricular nucleus of the hypothalamus (PVH^(OXT))-dopamine neurons in the ventral tegmental area (VTA^(DA)) negatively regulate the drive to drink alcohol. Alcohol induces FGF21 signaling, which activates PVH^(OXT) and induces oxytocin release in the VTA. The VTA^(DA) neurons are activated hours after...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Shigella</em> OspF blocks rapid p38-dependent priming of the NAIP-NLRC4 inflammasome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The NAIP-NLRC4 inflammasome senses pathogenic bacteria by recognizing the cytosolic presence of bacterial proteins such as flagellin and type III secretion system (T3SS) subunits. In mice, the NAIP-NLRC4 inflammasome provides robust protection against bacterial pathogens that infect intestinal epithelial cells, including the gastrointestinal pathogen Shigella flexneri. By contrast, humans are highly susceptible to Shigella, despite the ability of human NAIP-NLRC4 to robustly detect Shigella T3SS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum and urinary metabolomics reflect the early stages of de novo metabolic syndrome after liver transplant: a two-center longitudinal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: LT is followed by distinct metabolic shifts reflecting changes in both hepatic lipid metabolism and gut-liver microbial co-metabolism. Elevated urinary TMAO, together with reduced serum phosphocholine and lipid-CH3 responses, characterize patients who develop post-LT MetS and may serve as early biomarkers of cardiometabolic risk in LT recipients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Development of the Pain Threshold During a Long-Distance Run]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study found no significant changes in PPT, cPPT, or CPM following aerobic exercise. A significant change was observed in TSP. CPM and EIH predicted changes in PPT during the 15 km run (increasing vs. decreasing) in an explorative analysis. Further research should test if baseline tests can predict pro- or anti-nociceptive responses to long-distance running.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diacetyl-induced occupational lung disease: insights from two cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Inhalation of diacetyl-containing flavoring powder may play a more critical role in occupational lung disease than exposure to diacetyl vapor alone, but the underlying injury mechanisms remain poorly understood.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in County-Level Childhood Vaccination Exemptions in the US]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De Novo Germline L858R EGFR Variants and Generalized Acanthosis Nigricans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The findings of this case series study define a syndromic disorder with increased risk of pulmonary disease and lung nodules in patients with acquired, generalized AN that is associated with activating EGFR variants. Pulmonary nodules are precursor lesions for lung cancer, and treatment with EGFR inhibitions is associated with near-complete resolution of skin and pulmonary disease. Early recognition of syndromic EGFR AN will permit identification of individuals at risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electronic Intervention for Patient-Managed Benzodiazepine Tapering: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This randomized clinical trial found a large effect of a low-cost, self-administered electronic intervention for reducing benzodiazepine use among long-term users. Findings from this replicated clinical trial are encouraging given the prevalence of benzodiazepine dependence and the constraints on clinician time available to address it. Dissemination of this intervention-which is in the public domain-by health care and public health systems seems warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adverse Events After Metastases-Directed Stereotactic Radiotherapy and Biological Cancer Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study of 433 patients, severe adverse events after SRT and concurrent BCT were uncommon (<10%), continuing BCT during SRT was not associated with increased risk of severe adverse events, and interrupting BCT was not associated with worse OS when correcting for patients' performance status. These findings suggest a favorable safety profile of metastases-directed SBRT in combined modality treatment settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blastomycosis, Histoplasmosis, and Coccidioidomycosis in Outpatient Community-Acquired Pneumonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study of patients with unspecified CAP, testing rates for blastomycosis, coccidioidomycosis, and histoplasmosis were low in many locations. Increased awareness of these fungal infections may help increase timely testing for fungal diseases among patients with CAP, decrease health care utilization and inappropriate antibiotic use, and improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Work Hours, Stress, and Burnout Among Resident Physicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION AND RELEVANCE: In this cross-sectional nationwide study of resident physicians in high-burnout specialties, longer work hours were associated with higher stress and self-perceived competency, but not with burnout. This suggests that work hours alone may not explain high burnout levels in residency; a more comprehensive approach beyond work hour restrictions is needed to support resident well-being in training.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Group Vs Individual Grief-Focused Cognitive Behavioral Therapy for Older Adults: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, GF-CBT group was noninferior to GF-CBT individual at 6-month follow-up in reducing PGD symptoms, but also symptoms of PTSD, depression, and anxiety. Both formats had large effects on symptoms over time and appear to be relevant treatment formats for older adults with symptoms of PGD and other disorders post loss.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biologics Prescribing in Dermatology by Advanced Practice Clinicians-Trends in the Practice of Advanced Practice Clinicians in Dermatology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and the Potential Transformation of Mental Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The likely benefits of AI for psychiatric care delivery must be balanced against substantial risks. Strategies to mitigate this risk may require regulation to enhance transparency and systematically evaluate the impact of AI in practice, as well as clinician training to make optimal use of these emerging methods.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediabetes, Subclinical Myocardial Injury or Stress, and Heart Failure Risk for Adults With Hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These findings suggest that among adults with hypertension, prediabetes in combination with subclinical myocardial injury or stress is associated with a significantly elevated risk for HF. These findings support the integration of glycemic status and cardiac biomarkers profiling to improve HF risk stratification and guide prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facile Access to IDT-Based Acceptor via Direct C-H Arylation and Its Exploration in Binary and Ternary Organic Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pursuit of efficient and environmentally benign synthetic routes for electron acceptors via is vital to advancing the commercialization of organic solar cells (OSCs). In this study, we leverage a direct C-H arylation strategy to synthesis a novel A-D-π-D-A-type acceptor (D1), which offers significant advantages in step and atom economy, along with a reduced environmental impact compared to conventional cross-coupling methods. When combined with the polymer donor PM6, the optimized PM6:D1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic signature for the effectiveness of anti-PD-1 therapy combined with vascular normalization therapy in recurrent glioblastoma: A randomized phase 2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study shows that combining tislelizumab and low-dose bevacizumab improves survival in rGBM patients with good safety and tolerability. Dynamic changes in TISF-based molecular markers reflect genomic evolution and predict prognosis. Increased CD163^(+) cell infiltration in recurrent tumors may activate M2 macrophages, promoting tumor growth and immune evasion. Elevated GDF-15 levels may further suppress antitumor immunity, facilitating immune escape.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hypoxemia secondary to a modified y-connector of a double-lumen bronchial tube]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Comparative Effects of Boric Acid and Calcium Fructoborate on Breast Cancer Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tellurium Nanoparticles in Biomedicine: Harnessing a "Jekyll and Hyde" Element for Therapy and Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tellurium, long considered a toxic element, now represents a unique platform for biomedical nanomaterials. Its fundamental paradox lies in its dual nature: depending on the form and dose, it exhibits both potent pro-oxidant activity against tumor cells and pathogens, and pronounced antioxidant properties. Tellurium nanoparticles (TeNPs) serve as a tool for managing this duality. This review systematizes modern methods of TeNPs synthesis, including laser ablation as a source of high-purity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Italian translation of the Nine-Item ARFID Screen (NIAS-IT) for ARFID surveillance in a dietetic service]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Italian version of the NIAS is perfectly comprehensible and can be applied to the Italian population for both clinical and research purposes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Effects of Long-Term Treatment with TV-46000 on Symptom Improvement Over Time in Stabilized Patients with Schizophrenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical efficacy of dual growing rods technique with preoperative halo-femoral traction in the treatment of early onset scoliosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The DGR technique combined with preoperative HFT is a safe and effective treatment for EOS, achieving substantial deformity correction and supporting spinal growth. Preoperative HFT is a necessary adjunct for severe rigid deformities, directly enabling DGR implantation and enhancing correction efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of enoxaparin and aspirin on metastatic spread in a murine melanoma model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both aspirin and enoxaparin treatment affect the progression of metastases in mice, with enoxaparin being the most effective.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic impact of TROP2 in adenocarcinoma of the esophageal junction and stomach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In Caucasian AEG/S patients, TROP2 is expressed in the majority of cases. TROP2 expression intensity itself has an impact on survival, which could be explained by a more aggressive phenotype, which leads to lymphatic invasion and lymph node metastasis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Childhood obesity, dietary patterns and gut microbiota: a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DMOG Enhances hUC-MSCs Paracrine Activity to Promote Endometrial Epithelial Cells Reconstitution Via VSELs Formation in Ovariectomized Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Estrogen deficiency-induced uterine atrophy is a major cause of menstrual disorders and infertility in postmenopausal women and patients with premature ovarian failure. However, current hormone replacement therapies carry long-term risks and fail to achieve physiological endometrial regeneration. It has been demonstrated that dimethyloxalylglycine (DMOG) can augment the therapeutic effects of mesenchymal stem cells (MSCs), but the effects of DMOG-pretreated MSCs on Estrogen deficiency-induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning in the development and application of patient-reported outcome measures (PROMs) for surgical patients: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AI and ML have the potential to improve PROM utilization in surgical care by enhancing efficiency and personalization while maintaining data quality. Clinicians can use AI-driven PROMs to reduce patient burden and integrate ML models for accurate post-surgical outcome prediction, thereby optimizing patient-centered care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parental Resolution of Children's Neurodevelopmental Disorders Among Asylum Seekers: Associations with Trauma, Stress, and Protective Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Caregiver-reported quality of life in individuals with developmental and epileptic encephalopathy and other severe neurodevelopmental encephalopathies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Regression tree analysis suggests that cognition and use of touchscreens were important factors for QOL. Findings suggest small neurodevelopmental and functional gains may meaningfully improve quality of life for individuals with severe neurodevelopmental encephalopathy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neurocaf™, A green coffee bean extract containing eicosanoyl-5-hydroxytryptamide and chlorogenic acids enhances cognitive function and neuronal plasticity in a scopolamine-induced amnesia mouse model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to evaluate the memory health benefits of Neurocaf™, a standardized green coffee bean extract. Neurocaf was characterized for the presence of 5-hydroxytryptamide esters, eicosanoyl-5-hydroxytryptamide (EHT), and chlorogenic acids using HPLC-PDA detector. The inhibitory kinetics of Neurocaf against acetylcholinesterase (AChE) were assessed in vitro. Cognitive efficacy was further investigated in a scopolamine-induced amnesia mouse model. In a 25-day study, male Swiss albino mice...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Switching from Dupilumab to Upadacitinib in Adults and Adolescents with Moderate-to-Severe Atopic Dermatitis After Inadequate Response to Dupilumab: Efficacy and Safety Results from Period 2 of Phase 3b/4 Study (LEVEL UP)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The current findings suggest that switching from dupilumab to upadacitinib may be an effective treatment strategy for patients who do not meet moderate-to-optimal treatment targets with dupilumab.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adverse childhood experiences negatively impact sustained attention in adulthood]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest lasting, negative ACE effects on sustained attention in adulthood. Additionally, the fully online design proved to be a reliable method for detecting subtle variations in sustained attention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impaired Mitophagy-Induced Apoptosis of Gingival Fibroblasts Exacerbates Diabetic Periodontitis Via THBS-1/CD36-Dependent Macrophage Activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic periodontitis (DPD) is a severe inflammatory complication characterized by accelerated destruction of periodontal tissues and dysregulated immune responses. Gingival fibroblast (GF)-macrophage interactions drive DPD progression, but the mechanisms linking hyperglycemia, mitochondrial dysfunction, and immune activation remain unclear. Single-cell sequencing analysis of diabetic gingival tissues revealed significant apoptotic activation of GFs, closely linked to mitochondrial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing Health Disparities through Community Engagement in Artificial Intelligence-Driven Prevention Science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence and machine learning (AI/ML) in prevention science may improve or perpetuate health inequities. Community engagement is one proposed strategy thought to empirically mitigate bias in AI/ML tools. We outline how to incorporate community engagement at every stage of the model development and implementation. Borrowing from a framework for phases of prevention research, we describe the value and application of engaging communities to help shape more rigorous and relevant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasensitive biosensor based on AgNPs-functionalized perylene derivative nanosheets with enhanced electrochemiluminescence at narrow potential sweep range]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemiluminescent (ECL) luminophore with high quantum efficiency is one of the most essential components in ECL biosensor system. However, high excitation potential caused oxygen emission in electrolyte damages the modified electrode and biological activity, which limits the efficiency of luminophores. Herein, perylene-3,4,9,10-tetracarboxylic acid (PTC) was employed as an organic ligand to synthesize a perylene derivative nanosheet (PDIP) which was characterized by a significantly lower...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hemodynamics-guided therapy for hypertensive disorders of pregnancy: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study shows that hemodynamically triggered antihypertensive therapy can improve outcomes for both mother and child in cases of hypertensive pregnancy disorders. However, further placebo-controlled studies are necessary before a final assessment of this therapy can be made.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When Death Meets Dobbs: Fear as Policy in Organ Donation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[pH-Dependent Effects of Short-chain Carboxylic Acids and Buffer Systems On Clostridioides difficile in Vitro and in Vivo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The spore-forming anaerobe Clostridioides difficile colonizes the highly dynamic gut environment early after birth, frequently without causing disease. In this study, we aimed to determine how environmental conditions indicative of the infant gut impacted prevalence and physiology of C. difficile. We examined the effect of pH, fermentation derived short-chain carboxylic acids (SCCA) and buffering systems combining in vitro and in vivo analysis, and experimental and modelling approaches. In vivo,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intersegmental gait coordination differs by walking ability in subacute stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comment on: The association of bone density and hip fracture risk among Asian women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41533086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260115024412&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>