<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:41:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recommendation for use of 15- and 20-valent pneumococcal conjugate vaccines in Korean infants and children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pneumococcal disease remains the leading cause of morbidity in young children worldwide. Recent advances have expanded pneumococcal conjugate vaccines (PCVs) beyond 13-valent (PCV13) to 15-valent (PCV15) and 20- valent (PCV20) vaccines, which add 2 and 7 serotypes, respectively, thereby broadening their potential protective effects against invasive pneumococcal disease (IPD). Although policies vary among countries, Korea incorporated PCV15 and PCV20 into its National Immunization Program for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reactive air plasma treatment enhances extraction yield and bioactive anti-aging properties of wheat lipids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Few studies have investigated reactive air plasma (ReAP) treatment to enhance wheat lipid extraction and evaluate its potential anti-aging properties. Here, the effects of ReAP treatment on wheat lipids were assessed with a focus on improving lipid yield and bioactivity. Wheat samples were treated with a surface dielectric barrier discharge (sDBD) for 0, 5, 10, and 30 min, with the 10-min treatment yielding the highest lipid extraction using the Folch method, increasing from 1.78% in the control...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Arterial flow volume measurement using signal intensity gradient versus phase contrast]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Determining blood flow in major cerebral arteries is crucial for understanding cerebrovascular diseases. This study focused on comparing flow volumes derived from the signal intensity gradient (SIG) of Time-of-flight magnetic resonance angiography (TOF-MRA), referred to as SIG volume, and two-dimensional phase-contrast MR (PC-MR) and assessing their correlation in both experimental and human studies. The SIG volume of TOF-MRA could be calculated based on the concept of SIG as velocity gradient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cooperative ETS transcription factors are required for lymphatic endothelial cell integrity and resilience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lymphatics maintains fluid homeostasis, immune surveillance, and tissue integrity. Here, we identified the E26 transformation-specific (ETS) transcription factors Erg and Fli1 as essential, cooperative regulators of lymphatic integrity and function. Using inducible, lymphatic endothelial cell-specific deletion in mice, we demonstrated that combined loss of Erg and Fli1 in adults results in fatal lymphatic failure, including chylothorax, chylous ascites, and impaired lymphatic drainage....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rice gs3 allele and low-nitrogen conditions enrich rhizosphere microbiota that mitigate methane emissions and promote beneficial crop traits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Methane emissions from rice paddies represent a critical environmental concern in agriculture. Although genetic strategies for mitigating emissions have gained attention, the specific microbial and molecular mechanisms remain underexplored. Here, we investigated how the gs3 loss-of-function allele in the near-isogenic rice line Milyang360 modulates rhizosphere and endosphere microbial communities under distinct nitrogen regimes. Field experiments revealed that Milyang360 consistently reduced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiplex CRISPR/Cas9-mediated editing of seven glycosyltransferase homologs in <em>Nicotiana benthamiana</em> to produce stable, Cas9-free, glycoengineered plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Plant-based systems hold great potential for producing therapeutic proteins, but differences in N-glycosylation pathways between plants and mammals present major technical and regulatory barriers. In particular, plant-specific α-1,3-fucosylation and β-1,2-xylosylation can generate immunogenic glycan structures, necessitating genome engineering to humanize plant glycosylation profiles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid Liquid Metal Cathode Enables High-Performance Intrinsically Stretchable OLEDs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intrinsically stretchable light-emitting diodes (LEDs) are essential for next-generation wearable and implantable optoelectronics. However, achieving high-performance in intrinsically stretchable LEDs remains elusive due to the absence of a stretchable cathode that concurrently ensures efficient electron injection, mechanical compliance, and high optical reflectance. Here, we introduce a hybrid liquid metal-liquid metal particle (Hyb-LM) cathode, engineered by selective rupture of surface liquid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Architected Redox-Active Colloids for Tunable Charge Transport in Aqueous Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colloids, a foundational class of soft matter, are increasingly explored as programmable frameworks for electrochemical function. Traditionally regarded as passive carriers, colloids can be architected to form internal pathways for ion and electron transport. Their dispersibility, processability, and compatibility with aqueous media make them promising candidates for safe and sustainable redox systems, yet aqueous electrolytes remain limited by narrow potential windows, poor stability of redox...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative mitochondrial genome analysis of Panax ginseng reveals structural variation and genetic diversity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gut microbiome and metabolite signatures for predicting acute kidney transplant rejection: a prospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute rejection (AR) remains a significant challenge in kidney transplantation (KT) despite advances in immunosuppressive treatment. Recognizing the critical influence of the gut microbiome on modulating host immunity, we investigated the association between gut dysbiosis and AR in KT recipients. A total of 97 patients with KT were prospectively enrolled from two centers, and their samples were collected at multiple time points, such as pre-transplant (n = 97), three months (n = 66), and twelve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Arthroscopy assisted single bone tunnel two stranded en Masse repair for peripheral triangular fibrocartilage complex tears]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed (1) to provide a stepwise, reproducible description of a single-bone-tunnel, two-stranded, anchorless ligament-specific ('en Masse') repair for traumatic peripheral TFCC tears, and (2) to evaluate one-year clinical outcomes and exploratory prognostic factors in a retrospective consecutive case series. Forty-eight patients were retrospectively included. Postoperatively, ballottement testing revealed no detectable distal radioulnar joint (DRUJ) laxity (p < 0.001). The mean visual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three different patterns of food allergen sensitization according to age and sex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although various studies have been conducted on food allergy worldwide, large-scale population-based data on food allergen sensitization patterns in South Korea remain limited. In this study, we analyzed age- and sex-specific sensitization patterns to various food allergens by analyzing large-scale multiple allergen simultaneous test (MAST) data. In this study, we analyzed the results of MASTs performed for 344,678 patients with suspected allergies (0.66% of South Korea's total population)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Auditory genotype-phenotype correlation of patients with variants in STRC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pathogenic variants in the STRC gene are among the most common causes of autosomal recessive non-syndromic hearing loss, particularly in cases with mild-to-moderate sensorineural hearing loss (SNHL). Despite its prevalence, the clinical phenotype and natural history of STRC-related SNHL remain undercharacterized due to diagnostic challenges posed by a highly homologous pseudogene, pSTRC. This study included 23 families enrolled in the Yonsei University Hearing Loss cohort. Genetic testing was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expansion of cagA Copy Number in Helicobacter pylori During Co-Infection in a Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that co-infection with S. promotes an increase in the cagA copy number, thereby enhancing the virulence potential of H. pylori. The study highlights the complex interplay between H. pylori and co-infecting pathogens and their combined impact on H. pylori-mediated disease, and the utility of high-cagA copy isolates as valuable models for in vivo studies addressing pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OPERA-01: a phase III study of palazestrant for ER+, HER2- advanced breast cancer after CDK4/6 inhibitor therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endocrine therapy (ET) resistance is a major concern when treating estrogen receptor-positive (ER+) human epidermal growth factor receptor 2-negative (HER2-) breast cancer. A combination of cyclin-dependent kinase 4/6 inhibitors (CDK4/6i) and ET is the current first-line standard of care (SOC) for patients with ER+, HER2- advanced breast cancer. Despite the benefits of ET plus a CDK4/6i, disease progression due to endocrine resistance remains a significant challenge. More effective ETs that can...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nb<sub>2</sub>CT<sub><em>x</em></sub>@UiO-66-Bi<sub>2</sub>Fe<sub>4</sub>O<sub>9</sub> Ternary Hybrid for Efficient Piezo-photocatalytic Removal of Sulfamethoxazole from Water]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The widespread and uncontrolled use of antibiotics poses significant dangers and challenges in water treatment and public health. A three-component nanocomposite, Nb(2)CT(x)@UiO-66-Bi(2)Fe(4)O(9), was rationally assembled via a straightforward hydrothermal mixing approach to combine photocatalytic and piezoelectric effects for the efficient decomposition of the antibacterial sulfamethoxazole (SMX). The morphological, chemical, and surface properties of the materials were tested by electron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utility of Peroral Cholangioscopy in the Diagnosis and Management of Intraductal Papillary Neoplasms of the Bile Duct (With Videos)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: POC is a useful diagnostic modality for the detection of IPN-Bs and facilitates accurate decision-making for subsequent management planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacterial and fungal metagenomes associated with atmospheric particulates in Republic of Korea: Comparison of PM<sub>2.5</sub> and TSP larger than PM<sub>2.5</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Particulate matter (PM) significantly contributes to air pollution, potentially causing health issues, with PM-associated microorganisms implicated in some cases. While studies have explored microbial concentration and structure in PM based on particle size, comprehensive analysis of microbial functional traits and environmental influences is limited. This study evaluated microbial concentrations and diversity in PM with a diameter of 2.5 µm or lower (PM(2.5)) and total suspended particles (TSP)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrophobic neutral dissolved organic matter: First insights into compositional changes and formation of disinfection by-products induced by rainfall and degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the structural characteristics of dissolved organic matter (DOM) in bulk river samples and their fractionations (isolated using Supelite™ DAX-8 resin) under rainfall conditions, as well as two primary degradation processes: biodegradation and photodegradation. Compared to bulk samples, DAX-8 resin fractionations provided more detailed insights into structural changes in DOM influenced by rainfall and subsequent degradation. Rainfall was found to increase the proportions of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toxicodynamic and toxicokinetic mechanisms underlying deltamethrin resistance and dinotefuran cross-resistance in two resistant strains of common bed bug, Cimex lectularius]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The common bed bug, Cimex lectularius (Heteroptera: Cimicidae), is a resurging pest with significant public health impacts. We investigated toxicodynamic and toxicokinetic mechanisms underlying deltamethrin resistance and dinotefuran cross-resistance in two resistant strains (NYSS-BB and PT-BB). Both strains carried two voltage-sensitive sodium channel mutations (V419L and L925I) at 100 % frequency, conferring knockdown resistance (kdr). In NYSS-BB, the kdr alleles persisted for more than 20...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amino Acid Signaling in Skeletal Muscle Is Blunted by Prematurity in a Piglet Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preterm birth impairs the abundance and activation of multiple amino acid-sensing components upstream of mTORC1 in skeletal muscle. This disruption attenuates amino acid-induced mTORC1-dependent translation initiation and protein synthesis, and likely contributes to the anabolic resistance, reduced lean mass, and extrauterine growth faltering frequently observed in premature infants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhaled polystyrene nanoparticles may cause fibrotic lesions via immune dysregulation and energy metabolism disturbance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microplastics have emerged as a major risk to human health. In this study, we dosed polystyrene nanoparticles (PS-NPs) via the pharynx for 90 days and assessed local and systemic toxicity. PS-NPs increased white blood cell counts and decreased blood potassium levels, and they were widely distributed in the lungs and hearts. The total count of pulmonary cells increased with dose, whereas the proportion of macrophages decreased. Levels of immune regulation-related cytokines increased markedly in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune-related adverse events in hepatocellular carcinoma: organ-specific patterns and management approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is a major cause of cancer-related mortality worldwide. The recent introduction of immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) has transformed the therapeutic landscape of advanced HCC. Combination regimens such as atezolizumab plus bevacizumab, durvalumab plus tremelimumab, and nivolumab plus ipilimumab have demonstrated significant survival improvements over conventional tyrosine kinase inhibitors (TKIs) and have become the new standard of care. However, ICIs can trigger...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Foreign body retained in the sole of the foot for over 30 years: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 41-year-old man presented with discomfort in the medial arch of his foot, which worsened with weight-bearing. The condition had initially been misdiagnosed as plantar fasciitis, and he had received conservative treatment without imaging, with no relief of symptoms. Plain radiography and computed tomography later revealed a 2.5-cm radiopaque, needle-like foreign body in the superficial midfoot. Further history-taking revealed that the patient had stepped on a sewing needle during childhood,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of the medical professional shortage caused by a resident walkout on scene-to-door time: a retrospective cohort study at a trauma center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The resident walkout was associated with marked delays in scene-to-door time and shifts in in-hospital patient flow. These findings suggest that even temporary workforce shortages can disrupt both prehospital and in-hospital trauma care, underscoring the importance of response planning and adaptable system operations during workforce disruptions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitigating semantic label divergence in federated learning: Obfuscated encoding and alert filtering for security monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is emerging as a key approach for collaborative machine learning (ML) in distributed information systems where direct data sharing is infeasible due to policy constraints. In security operations center (SOC) settings, we study FL for the classification of network intrusion detection system (IDS) alerts-structured event records emitted by sensors (e.g., Snort/Suricata)-where consistent interpretation of event data is critical for reliable ML-based decision support....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Highly Cross-Linked and Conventional Polyethylene During Simultaneous Bilateral Cruciate-Retaining Total Knee Arthroplasties: Results at a Minimum Follow-up of 15 Years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings of this long-term study (minimum follow-up of 15 years) indicate that CR-Flex TKAs with HXLPE and CP bearings both yielded excellent clinical outcomes and implant survivorship. However, no significant clinical advantage was observed for HXLPE over CP bearings in this patient population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal Single Extracellular Vesicle Profiling Technologies to Unveil Clinical Heterogeneity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles (EVs) play significant roles in disease progression through their molecular cargos, including proteins, transcriptomes, and metabolites. However, the inherent heterogeneity of EVs in body fluids, originating from various cells with different functions, has impeded the translation of their biological significance to clinical applications, such as disease diagnosis, prognosis, and therapeutics. To address this heterogeneity issue, single EV profiling technologies have...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment outcomes and prognostic factors in external auditory canal squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[External auditory canal carcinoma (EACC) is a rare and aggressive malignancy with substantial variability in prognosis depending on tumor stage and adjacent structure involvement. We retrospectively reviewed 56 patients with histologically confirmed squamous cell carcinoma of the external auditory canal treated at a tertiary referral center between 2000 and 2022. Clinical data including demographics, tumor stage, treatment modalities, surgical approach, and survival outcomes were analyzed....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of blood culture practices in multicenter university-affiliated hospitals in Korea: A retrospective study focused on procedural optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Blood culture practices, particularly regarding test ordering and the use of two or more sets per episode, appear generally appropriate. However, specific aspects-including the indications for repeat cultures, adequacy of collected blood volume, and timeliness of Gram stain reporting-require further evaluation and targeted quality improvement efforts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[C-terminal Truncation and Fusion Partner Determine Oncogenicity of FGFR3]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genomic alterations affecting components of the fibroblast growth factor (FGF) signaling axis can trigger aberrant pathway activation and tumor development. Genomic truncation of the FGF receptor 2 (FGFR2) exon 18 (E18) disrupts the FGFR2 carboxy-terminal tail (C-tail), acting as a potent driver alteration across multiple tumor types. Here, we analyzed human oncogenomic datasets to reveal that E18 truncations are similarly prevalent in FGFR3, an FGFR2 paralog. FGFR3 E18 truncations primarily...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Creativity in AI Advertising: The Mediating Role of Perceived Uncanniness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extending previous research on creative AI to the context of AI advertising, the present study examined whether creativity in AI advertising could evoke perceptions of uncanniness and consequently have a negative impact on ad outcomes. Based on a two (ad creativity: low vs. high) by two (creator label: human vs. AI) between-subjects experimental design, the present study showed that ad creativity in general had a positive direct impact on attitude toward the ad (A(ad)), attitude toward the brand...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced exposure and visualization in splenic flexure mobilization with comparable perioperative outcomes: experience with Artisential<sup>®</sup> during laparoscopic low anterior resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Angulated traction was utilized for splenic flexure mobilization in laparoscopic low anterior resections using a grasper from Artisential^(®), a line of articulated laparoscopic instruments. The surgeon was able to create a significantly larger working field and better exposure of target structures. This implementation did not affect operation time, recovery, or specimen integrity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex differences in bile acid homeostasis and excretion underlie the disparity in liver cancer incidence between males and females]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC), the common liver cancer, exhibits higher incidence in males. Here, we report that mice lacking bile acid (BA) regulators, Farnesoid X Receptor (FXR also termed NR1H4) and Small Heterodimer Partner (SHP also termed NR0B2), recapitulate the sex difference in liver cancer risk. Since few therapeutic options are available, we focused on understanding the intrinsic protection afforded to female livers. Transcriptomic analysis in control and NR1H4 and NR0B2 double...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Documented advance care planning elements and end-of-life care patterns in malignant glioma vs. major solid tumors: a single-center retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this single-center cohort, malignant glioma patients were less likely to have documented ACP elements and more likely to die in nursing hospitals than those with solid tumors. Early ACP and tailored palliative strategies are essential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JI017 induces cell line specific anticancer effects in hepatocellular carcinoma by suppressing the STAT3 signaling pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: JI017 exerts cell line-specific anticancer effects in HCC through STAT3 pathway suppression, resulting in apoptosis in SNU-387 and cell cycle arrest in HepG2. These results support the potential of JI017 as a STAT3-targeted therapeutic candidate for HCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic impact of endocrine therapy and BDNF-TrkB axis in breast cancer brain metastases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct plasma inflammatory signatures reflect disease severity and progression in progressive supranuclear palsy: a prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroinflammation is increasingly recognized as a key driver of progressive supranuclear palsy (PSP), but the role of blood inflammatory markers remains unrevealed. This prospective cohort study aimed to characterize blood inflammatory protein profiles in PSP and to assess their associations with clinical severity, longitudinal progression, blood-based neurodegeneration markers, and brain morphometric changes. We enrolled 71 probable PSP patients and 30 age-matched healthy controls. Plasma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D Printed Patient-Specific Resorbable Bone Scaffolds for Alveolar Bone Regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: 3D printed patient-specific biodegradable scaffolds represent a promising alternative to conventional grafting, offering precise defect reconstruction, improved biological integration, and translational potential in maxillofacial surgery. Continued optimization of material printing combinations and vascularization strategies will be critical to achieving long-term clinical success.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How tax structures for retail cannabis shape cannabis use among youth and young adults: evidence from a volumetric choice experiment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: For AYAs who are using or susceptible to using cannabis, tax increases can effectively reduce the quantity and THC consumption, albeit a tax rate beyond 60% of pretax prices or equivalent generating no additional reductions. Compared to weight-based taxes, potency-based and price-based taxes reduce the consumption of high THC products, but potency-based taxes may also increase the consumption of low THC products. Given that higher prices on cartridges and edibles do not drive AYAs'...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health expenditure in Africa: examining the synergistic impact of economic policy uncertainty and governance quality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the relevance of governance quality in shaping the effect of economic policy uncertainty on several health expenditure indicators, including external health expenditure, national health expenditure, public health expenditure, and private health expenditure. The analysis is based on a sample of fifty-three African countries spanning 2005 to 2022. The adopted empirical strategy comprises the interactive dynamic two-step System Generalized Method of Moments (SGMM). The analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MAPK Pathway Mutations Emerge in Mutant-IDH1 Inhibitor-Resistant Cholangiocarcinoma and Attenuate the Interferon Response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MAPK-pathway alterations represent a recurrent mechanism of resistance to mIDH1 inhibition in ICC, while emergent IDH1/IDH2 mutations appear infrequent. Functional data suggest that MAPK-mediated resistance may involve impaired IFN signaling. These results support MAPK-directed combination strategies and highlight the utility of ctDNA profiling to identify predictive and resistance biomarkers in mIDH1-driven ICC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erdafitinib in Patients with FGFR-altered Advanced or Metastatic Cholangiocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pooled analyses confirm the robust efficacy of erdafitinib in a diverse population of pretreated patients with advanced/metastatic CCA harboring prespecified FGFR alterations. These findings are consistent with previously observed efficacy of FGFR-targeted agents in patients with CCA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure Dependent Accessibility of Active Sites Governs Catalytic Activity and Stability of Iridium Oxides in the Acidic Oxygen Evolution Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep understanding of the structural influence on the activity-stability relationship of iridium oxides in acidic oxygen evolution reaction (OER) is desired for better catalyst designs and, consequently, improved atom efficiency of the rare-earth element. However, identifying the variables governing the reaction mechanism remains a challenge in environments where multistep reactions and catalyst degradation occur simultaneously. Surface interrogation scanning electrochemical microscopy (SI-SECM)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acupuncture for Anxiety: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis of Randomized Controlled Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MA effectively reduces anxiety symptoms in the short term, with effects sustained at follow-up when compared to SA but not UC/WLC. Further research is needed to confirm long-term efficacy and standardize methodologies. Acupuncture remains a promising, safe, and minimally invasive therapy for chronic anxiety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adverse Childhood Experiences and Depressive Symptoms Among Older Korean Americans in Affordable Senior Housing: The Moderating Role of Social Networks and Family Solidarity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite growing evidence of the long-term mental health effects of adverse childhood experiences (ACEs), little is known about protective factors that buffer this relationship among older adults. This study examined personal (e.g., sense of mastery), interpersonal (e.g., social networks and family solidarity), and community (e.g., social cohesion) resources as potential moderators of the association between ACEs and depressive symptoms among older Korean Americans residing in affordable senior...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone hypertrophy and reduced quality after nucleus pulposus aspiration induces low back pain-like behavior and neuronal hyperexcitability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Intradiscal injury caused by puncture and NP aspiration induces spinal structural remodeling and peripheral neuronal sensitization, contributing to chronic LBP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Invasively measured aortic pulse pressure and long-term prognosis in patients undergoing invasive coronary angiography: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Invasively measured aPP is a strong and independent predictor of long-term cardiovascular outcomes in patients undergoing ICA. aPP could be a valuable addition to current risk assessment tools in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D enhancer architecture coordinated by CTCF determines immune-related gene expression patterns via RNA polymerase II pause-release in CD4+ T cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CTCF (CCCTC-binding factor) is crucial for organizing mammalian genomes into domains and structural loops, yet its role in enhancer-promoter interactions remains unclear. Here, we demonstrate that 3D enhancer architecture undergoes marked reorganization upon CTCF depletion in activated CD4+ T cells. Despite this, active transcription, particularly driven by STAT5-bound super-enhancers, maintains enhancer loops independently of CTCF. Interestingly, robust enhancer-promoter interactions are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Foundation Models for Neural Signal Decoding: EEG-Centered Perspectives Toward Unified Representations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neural signals such as EEG, ECoG, and intracortical recordings offer a valuable window into brain dynamics but remain difficult to decode due to high dimensionality, nonstationarity, and substantial interindividual variability. Traditional machine learning and deep learning models often show limited generalizability and insufficient interpretability in these settings. Foundation models (FMs)-large-scale architectures pretrained on diverse datasets-have recently emerged as a promising paradigm...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case report: orthopedic treatment of the maxillopalatal complex using RAMPA combined with a novel hybrid intraoral appliance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper reports on a clinical case of craniofacial displacement from treatment with a Right Angle Maxillary Protraction Appliance (RAMPA). A seven-year-old girl was treated over 17 months using VomPress (4 months) and Hybrid (13 months) intraoral devices with RAMPA. Finite Element Analysis (FEA) simulations of a skull model with all sutures and validated material properties supported clinical findings. RAMPA produced an anterosuperior maxillary shift, counterclockwise mandibular rotation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Skin-inspired phototherapeutic cryogel ameliorates infected wound healing by orchestrating mechanotransduction and immunomodulation" [Bioact. Mater. 57 (2026) 768-790]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1016/j.bioactmat.2025.11.028.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between motor symptom severity and urinary dysfunction in Parkinson's disease: a retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study provides evidence that urinary dysfunction intensifies with motor symptom progression in PD. These findings highlight the importance of early detection and proactive management of urinary symptoms in patients with PD to enhance their overall quality of life.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An investigation of the factors influencing college students' rural cultural preservation behaviors in the context of rural cultural revitalization: a hybrid SEM-ANN approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The protection and inheritance of rural culture have emerged as critical components of rural cultural revitalization amid the ongoing implementation of the rural revitalization strategy. College students, characterized by both academic knowledge and social responsibility, have not yet been systematically examined in terms of the mechanisms underlying their participation in rural cultural preservation. Although rural cultural protection has received significant scholarly attention,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Climate change perception and pro-environmental behavior among urban park visitors: the mediating role of place attachment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Place attachment serves as a key mechanism linking climate concern to sustainable actions in leisure settings. Strengthening emotional and social bonds to urban parks may enhance both localized and general pro-environmental behaviors, offering practical implications for urban sustainability strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction and alcohol-associated liver disease (MetALD)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction and alcohol-associated liver disease (MetALD) is a recently implemented nomenclature and disease terminology for patients with metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease, who consume greater amounts of alcohol. MetALD is diagnosed in individuals who have at least one metabolic risk factor (such as obesity, type 2 diabetes mellitus, hypertension, etc) and consume 140-350 g/week of alcohol for women or 210-420 g/week for men. Conversely, alcohol-associated liver...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opportunities and challenges in application of VASARI features in neuro-oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The application of objective radiological data in glioma research remains an underexplored opportunity in neuro-oncology. Despite multiple efforts to incorporate radiomic features in glioma analysis, the lack of a unified imaging reporting system in gliomas prevents large-scale, multi-center scientific collaborations from integrating comparable imaging variables to their work. VASARI lexicon, a set of 30 semantic radiomic features using controlled vocabulary and visual guides, was created to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Antibacterial Activity of Fe<sub>3</sub>O<sub>4</sub>@mPEG-Ag Nanoparticles with Molecular Docking Analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: This study aims to develop methoxy poly(ethylene glycol) (mPEG) and silver-modified magnetite nanoparticles termed Fe(3)O(4)@mPEG-Ag NPs as efficient non-antibiotic antibacterial agents to address the growing challenge of drug-resistant bacterial infections. Impact Statement: This work demonstrates a synergistic nanomaterial design that achieves high antibacterial efficacy, stability, and biocompatibility, positioning it as a promising alternative to conventional antibiotics in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intersectional identity, risk behaviors, and adolescent mental health in South Korea: who suffers the most in the loneliness epidemic?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Interventions targeting alcohol and tobacco use may be important to prevent loneliness for adolescents with intersectional identities. Loneliness may be shaped by both structural and behavioral factors, supporting the intersectionality as a useful analytical framework to better understand mental health disparities among adolescents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of early detubularization on urethro-intestinal anastomosis during robot-assisted radical cystectomy and intracorporeal neobladder among bladder cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Early detubularization appears to reduce UIA leaks following RARC with ICN. Our findings support its adoption as a technical refinement to improve anastomotic outcomes, though further prospective validation is needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural characterization of anti-CRISPR protein AcrIE9]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The arms race between bacteria and bacteriophages has driven the evolution of both CRISPR-Cas systems and anti-CRISPR (Acr) proteins. AcrIE9, a type I-E Acr protein identified in Pseudomonas aeruginosa, inhibits Cascade-mediated DNA binding by interacting with the Cas7e subunit. However, its structural basis and precise inhibitory mechanism have remained unclear. Here, we report the crystal structure of AcrIE9 at 1.73 Å resolution, along with additional structural and biochemical analyses....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comparative Analysis of Survival Based on Body Mass Index at Diagnosis in Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Heterocypris exodonta</em> sp. nov. (Ostracoda, Cyprididae), morphological and molecular description of a high altitude asexual microcrustacean from the Nam Co region, Southern Tibetan Plateau]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new ostracod species, Heterocypris exodonta Bonilla-Flores & Karanovic, sp. nov. is described from a high-altitude temporary pond near Nam Co, Southern Tibetan Plateau. Detailed morphological analyses of valves, soft body, and the partial mitochondrial COI (cytochrome c oxidase subunit I) sequence distinguish this species from its close congeners, Heterocypris incongruens and Heterocypris salina. Key taxonomic features include the morphology of the female genital lobe and the structure of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Humanistic burden and medical care patterns of real-world patients with myasthenia gravis in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Most patients in this Japanese cohort with gMG received maintenance therapy and the time from symptom onset to diagnosis was relatively short. However, impaired HRQoL remained.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apathy, depression, and dementia risk in older adults: A global collaborative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The role of apathy in predicting dementia risk, especially with coexisting depression, remains unclear in community-dwelling older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomistic Insights into the Electrochemical Oxygen Evolution Activity of Hollandite IrO<sub>2</sub> Surfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lowering the overpotential for the oxygen-evolution reaction (OER) is central to designing efficient water-splitting catalysts. However, the atomistic origin behind the enhanced OER activity of hollandite IrO(2) compared to rutile has remained unclear. Here, using grand-canonical DFT with an implicit solvation model, the electrochemical stability and reactivity of the most stable hollandite facets, (100) and (112) are elucidated. The thermodynamic analysis identifies that hollandite is more...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Needles Versus Cannulas: Advantages, Disadvantages, and Selection Criteria for Injecting Dermal Fillers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review explores the efficacy and safety of using needles compared with cannulas for administering dermal fillers. We assessed and compared needles and cannulas based on the accuracy of injection, amount of associated tissue damage, procedural duration, vascular complications, and injection techniques and also highlighted their respective advantages and limitations. Needles facilitate rapid, precise injections and are suitable for shallow, targeted applications; however, because of their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Exosome-Containing Skin Booster and Microneedling Treatment on Facial Aging: A Retrospective Analysis of 40 Cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skin aging is caused by extrinsic and intrinsic factors and can lead to various aesthetic concerns and psychosocial stress. Exosome-based treatments have recently gained attention in the field of skin rejuvenation. This study aimed to retrospectively analyze the clinical efficacy of an exosome (CUREDOC EXOSOME REPAIR Advanced Solution Skin Booster, CUREDOC, Sejong, Korea) combined with microneedling treatment. We analyzed the medical records of 40 patients who received exosome skin booster (50...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Educational-Setting Feeding Interventions and Health Outcomes: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This work enhances the crucial role of educational-setting feeding interventions, highlighting their association with multiple health outcomes, and draws attention to the importance of integrated approaches to achieve better and more sustainable results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commissioning and robustness evaluation of external laser sensor for respiratory gating in carbon-ion radiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ANZAI laser sensor system is accurate and reliable, and it meets clinical latency requirements in respiratory-gated CIRT. It provides stable tracking under varied respiratory conditions. For optimal performance, maintaining a perpendicular sensor angle is recommended to ensure amplitude accuracy and mitigate crosstalk from adjacent lasers. These findings confirm the clinical readiness of the system and inform practical implementation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic blood dose estimates in radiotherapy and correlations with adverse clinical outcomes in brain, head-and-neck, and lung cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The dynamic blood dose model exhibited a statistically significant correlation with adverse clinical outcomes in five out of seven cases, compared to just two cases for the static blood dose models. Consideration of temporal aspects such as blood flow dynamics and treatment delivery time was therefore essential to some of the observed correlations. For each treatment site, particularly relevant blood compartments were identified, allowing for their inclusion during radiotherapy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Manipulating the Second Coordination Shell of Single-Atom Fe for Enhanced Fenton Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While current methods use oxidizable metals as electron donors to effectively reduce Fe^(3+), they suffer from the irreversible oxidation of these metals, ultimately compromising the catalyst's longevity. To address this challenge, we engineered the second coordination shell of a single-atom Fe center by doping boron (B) onto a graphene-based support (Fe(1)/B-graphene) and utilized H(2)O(2) as the electron source for efficient Fe^(2+) regeneration. Experimental results, supported by theoretical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Micro-Corrugated Hydrogel Electrodes for High-Performance Biofuel Cells via Capillary Force and Ligand Exchange-Induced Metal Nanoparticle Assembly]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biocompatible enzyme-based biofuel cells (EBFCs) with enzymatic electrodes show great potential as power sources for wearable and implantable biomedical devices. However, their practical application has been limited by poor electron transfer efficiency and insufficient operational stability. In this study, we present a mediator-free, hydrogel-based EBFC that addresses these challenges through the integration of capillary force-assisted assembly and hydrophobic metal nanoparticle (NP) deposition....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elucidating the Sigmoidal Adsorption Behavior of Xenon in Flexible Hofmann-Type MOFs Through Experiments and Molecular Dynamics with Machine Learning Potentials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sigmoidal adsorption in flexible metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) can be achieved through a dramatic phase transition from narrow to large pores; however, such a unique phenomenon, which is not induced by abrupt phase changes, has rarely been reported. We report a series of flexible Hofmann-type MOFs, CoNi-Pipe, NiNi-Pipe, and CoPd-Pipe, pillared with a dimensional (3D) piperazine linker. Owing to the rotational flexibility and 3D dimensionality of the piperazine linker, CoNi-Pipe and CoPd-Pipe...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized treatment approaches in neurocritical care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute brain injuries-including traumatic brain injury, subarachnoid hemorrhage, and intracerebral hemorrhage-exhibit profound pathophysiological heterogeneity, yet are often managed using standardized treatment protocols. While evidence-based guidelines have improved outcomes at a population level, they frequently overlook patient-specific variations in cerebral compliance, autoregulation, and metabolic reserve. This review explores the evolving paradigm of personalized neurocritical care, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nurse-led glycemic control protocols in intensive care units: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nurse-led glycemic management in critical care settings has been demonstrated to reduce the incidence of dysglycemia, including hyperglycemia and hypoglycemia, while stabilizing glycemic variability, contributing to enhanced patient outcomes. This scoping review aimed to identify nurse-led glycemic management protocols in intensive care units, analyze their components (e.g., target glucose range, monitoring frequency, and implementation methods), and evaluate their effectiveness. Seven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soda consumption and the risk of metabolic syndrome in Korean adults during the period surrounding the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is limited research on the association between soda consumption and the risk of metabolic syndrome (MetS), particularly during the COVID-19 pandemic. This study investigated the relationship between soda consumption and MetS in Korean adults, stratified by sex, and compared differences before and after the pandemic using data from the Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (2017-2021). A total of 13,051 adults aged 19-64 years were included. Soda consumption was assessed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-Stratified Genetic Spectrum of Retinitis Pigmentosa in Korean Patients: Predominance of <em>RPGR</em> Variants in Early-Onset Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results underscore distinct, age-related genetic contributions to RP in Korean patients, with RPGR variants demonstrating relevance in early-onset disease, and provide diagnostic insights to improve current practices. These findings can aid in prioritizing gene therapy targets and refining screening strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic obesity phenotypes and breast cancer risk before and after menopause: A nationwide cohort study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: After menopause, obesity was associated with elevated breast cancer risk, which was further increased by metabolic syndrome. In contrast, no elevated risk was observed before menopause. The current findings highlight differences in breast cancer risk by menopausal status across metabolic obesity phenotypes, emphasizing the need for targeted prevention strategies and further research into underlying mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incremental Value of Workload-Indexed Blood Pressure Response Over Exaggerated Blood Pressure Response to Exercise in Detecting Adverse Left Ventricular Remodeling and Function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SBP/MET slope was independently associated with concentric LV structure and diastolic dysfunction, providing incremental clinical value over ExBPR in detecting subclinical cardiac abnormalities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mimickers of Pathologic Calcifications and Uncommon Hyperechoic Lesions on Neck Ultrasound: A Pictorial Essay]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound is essential for distinguishing malignant from benign thyroid nodules by identifying suspicious features like microcalcifications and macrocalcifications. Microcalcifications strongly indicate malignancy, while entirely calcified nodules ≥ 1 cm show an 18.4%-23.3% malignancy risk. However, not all hyperechoic lesions are calcifications. Misinterpretation of these lesions can lead to unnecessary invasive procedures like fine needle aspiration or core needle biopsy. This review...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revisiting the relationship between stomatal size and speed across species - a meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rate of stomatal opening and closure in response to changes in light affects leaf photosynthesis and water use. However, it is unclear how strongly stomatal size (SS) and density (SD) influence stomatal conductance (g(s)) kinetics, and whether variation arises from methodological differences, guard cell type or degree of amphistomaty. We divided published records combining stomatal kinetics and anatomical traits from 89 species into kidney and dumbbell-shaped guard cells, and evaluated four...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations Between Mental Disorders and Risk of Mild Cognitive Impairment: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings advocate for a comprehensive approach addressing both disorder types and further cognitive deterioration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In silico analysis of sodium ion permeation mechanisms in transient receptor potential vanilloid 1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transient receptor potential vanilloid 1 (TRPV1) is a non-selective cation channel activated by heat, acidity and chemical ligands. While molecular dynamics simulations have shed some light on the cation permeation processes of TRPV1, the mechanisms in the native-state structure under near-physiological conditions remain unestablished. Therefore, the present study conducted molecular dynamics simulations of near-full-length human TRPV1 under a membrane potential of - 100 mV. During permeation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative outcomes of transcatheter arterial embolization versus open surgery for blunt abdominal solid organ injury with concurrent traumatic brain injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective observational study compared the outcomes of transcatheter arterial embolization (TAE) versus open surgery in patients with blunt abdominal solid organ injury (liver, spleen, or kidney; abdominal Abbreviated Injury Scale [AIS] ≥ 3) with traumatic brain injury (TBI) (head AIS ≥ 3), using data from the Japan Trauma Data Bank (2004-2019). Patient characteristics were adjusted using propensity score matching. The primary endpoint was in-hospital mortality; secondary endpoints...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a machine learning-based model for predicting the functional outcome of patients with proximal femur fractures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early-stage rehabilitation is crucial for the functional recovery of patients with proximal femur fractures. Predicting functional prognosis at such an early stage can simplify the process of planning for transfers and discharge destinations, as well as setting rehabilitation goals. The current study aimed to develop a model using machine learning to predict the functional prognosis of patients with proximal femur fractures based on parameters at the time of hospital admission. Our research...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonlinear effects of ambient temperature and treatment days on nocturnal enuresis using generalized additive models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To examine the effects of the average daily ambient temperature and treatment days on the outcomes of patients with nocturnal enuresis (NE), a common urinary symptom in children. The panel data of 19 children with NE (12 boys and 7 girls; median age: 9 years; age range: 6-15) were prospectively collected (up to 1,469 days; total number of records: 3194). NE status (presence of incontinence), treatment type, and weather-related variables (ambient temperature, precipitation, sunshine hours, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monomer Isolation from Oligomeric Proteins within Coordination Cages to Study Interface Ligand Binding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Isolating native monomers of oligomeric proteins offers a promising yet underexplored approach to elucidating their functions and identifying drugs that target oligomerization interfaces. Here, we present a strategy for isolating monomers from oligomeric proteins by confinement within spherical Pd^(2+)-coordination cages. Upon encapsulation of a stable dimeric protein, superoxide dismutase 1 (SOD1), a well-defined cavity of the metallo-cage selectively captured its monomer, retaining the same...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wetting-Mediated Remodeling of the Cytoskeletal Cortex by Phase-Separated Condensates in Cell-Free Reactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Living cells dynamically coordinate gene expression with the spatial organization of their membranes and cytoskeletons. Unraveling how membrane-less organelles arise and interact with cytoskeletal networks remains a fundamental challenge in cell biology, biophysics, and bioengineering. Here, we present a synthetic biology platform that integrates cell-free transcription-translation (TXTL) reactions with phase-separated protein condensates, enabling precise investigation of their interplay with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The spatio-temporal dynamics of phoneme encoding in aging and aphasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During successful language comprehension, speech sounds (phonemes) are encoded within a series of neural patterns that evolve over time. Here we tested whether these neural dynamics of speech encoding are altered for individuals with a language disorder. We recorded EEG responses from human brains of 39 individuals with post-stroke aphasia (13♀/26♂) and 24 healthy age-matched controls (i.e., older adults; 8♀/16♂) during 25 minutes of natural story listening. We estimated the duration of phonetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expansion of the rhizosphere soil and phyllosphere bacterial resistomes following repeated farmland application of high-temperature granulation-treated antibiotic fermentation residues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibiotic fermentation residue (AFR), a nutrient-dense biosolid waste from the pharmaceutical industry, holds the potential for recycling as fertilizer. However, its high concentration of antibiotic residues poses a significant risk for the dissemination of antibiotic resistance within the ecosystem. In this study, industrial-scale high-temperature granulation (HTG) technology was tested for its ability to remove antibiotics from three bulk AFRs (penicillin, cephalosporin, and abamectin)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A mixed-methods study examining the ripple effect of inclusive employment on reducing stigma toward autistic people in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This mixed-methods study examines how contact with Autistar, a Korean company providing strength-based, institutional-level support to autistic designers, is associated with stigma toward autistic people. One-hundred thirty-eight non-autistic community members completed an online survey; mixed-effects and stepwise regression analyses assessed relationships between contact with Autistar and stigma. Focus group interviews with 11 participants drawn from this full survey sample who had extensive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyaluronic acid regulates cellular UDP-GlcNAc levels through CD44 to affect glycosylation and cell biological functions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyaluronic acid (HA) is a key component of the extracellular matrix. Higher HA levels are strongly associated with poor prognosis in advanced cancer. Notably, the biosynthesis of N-glycans, O-GlcNAc, and HA all depend on UDP-GlcNAc as the essential donor substrate. Therefore, there may be functional relationships among different glycan types, although the specific mechanisms behind these interactions remain unclear. We established knockout (KO) cell lines for hyaluronan synthase 2 (HAS2) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of cranial nerve disorders in pharyngo-laryngeal herpes zoster: A retrospective study of 34 cases at a single institution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pharyngo-laryngeal HZ is a distinct clinical entity typically manifesting as cranial polyneuropathy. The IX and X nerves are most often involved, with laryngeal paralysis associated with poorer outcomes. A substantial proportion of patients experience severe or prolonged dysphagia, necessitating nutritional support and rehabilitation. The frequent occurrence of zoster sine herpete highlights the critical role of serological testing in diagnosis. These findings emphasize that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pro- and Antifluoride Use Messages on YouTube in Japan: Content Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Anti-fluoride content on YouTube appears to reach broader audiences than expert-generated profluoride videos. Opponent messages tend to use emotionally charged communication, whereas proponents focus on scientific information. These differences in style may influence public perceptions of fluoride use. Public health professionals should develop engaging and accessible communication strategies to counter misinformation and promote evidence-based practices.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive Molecular and Functional Analysis of NUTM1-Rearranged Leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[NUTM1-rearrangement (NUTM1-r) defines a significant subset of B-cell acute lymphoblastic leukemia (B-ALL), particularly in infants lacking KMT2A-rearrangements (KMT2A-r), yet its underlying molecular characteristics remain poorly understood. Here, we establish that NUTM1-r leukemia is a discrete entity characterized by a unique transcriptional and epigenetic landscape, notably featuring global DNA hypomethylation, irrespective of the 5' fusion partner. Functional interrogation of NUTM1 fusions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inverse modeling unveils governing law of mechano-chemical dynamics of epithelial migration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Collective cell migration is fundamental to tissue homeostasis and underlies biological processes such as wound healing and cancer invasion. Previous work has proposed governing equations to describe how chemical and mechanical inputs regulate these movements, but the quantitative validity of such models remains to be thoroughly assessed. Here, we developed a machine-learning framework that infers the governing equation from live-cell imaging data. Applied to epithelial sheet migration driven by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of an automated ultrasonographic detection method for fecal retention using a transgluteal cleft approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to develop an artificial intelligence-based classification system using ultrasound images obtained via a transgluteal cleft scanning approach for detecting fecal retention in the lower rectum. The goal was to support accurate, objective constipation assessment by nurses in home care settings, where traditional diagnostic tools are often unavailable. Ultrasound videos of the lower rectum were collected from 24 patients undergoing dialysis at a mixed-care hospital. From 90 videos,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pinpointing the Preterm Behavioural Phenotype in School-Aged Children Without Major Impairments: A Multi-Informant Approach Combining the Perspectives of Child, Parent and Clinician]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Even in a PT population without major neurological impairments or a clinical diagnosis of autism, important clinical-behavioural differences were evident in line with a preterm behavioural phenotype. Thus, delineating this subclinical PT pattern can be of relevance to recognize and validate meaningful difficulties experienced by these children that fail to reach the clinical threshold but could still benefit from certain interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-care in heart failure: time to update measures and assess cognitive capacity?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460518/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460518/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical outcomes and prognoses of patients with clinical stage I lung cancer and interstitial lung disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A relatively high 90-day mortality rate was observed. Deaths from causes other than lung cancer recurrence were observed more frequently than those from lung cancer recurrence. Hence, when selecting treatment strategies for early lung cancer combined with interstitial lung disease, the risks of acute exacerbation and progression of interstitial lung disease should be considered.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human factors and team safety in robotic-assisted surgery: a narrative review of ergonomic risks and educational implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RAS enhances precision but introduces human-factor risks. Sustainable safety requires integrating ergonomics, NTS, and communication into robotic training through simulation, feedback, and reflection-ensuring innovation supports both performance and humanity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient bradycardia during <sup>177</sup>Lu-DOTATATE therapy: A clinically manageable phenomenon with increased risk in patients with cardiac enlargement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative management of emergency cesarean delivery in a pregnant woman with uncorrected diabetic ketoacidosis: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heat generation and histological analysis of peri-implant bone cutting using piezoelectric surgery for implant removal: an in vitro study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: No bone damage was observed in the histological analysis. In contrast, piezoelectric peri-implant bone cutting caused a significant increase in temperature, especially for continuous bone cutting during implant adjustments. However, intermittent cutting for 3 and 5 s significantly suppressed the temperature increase. The results suggest that shortening the continuous cutting time may be effective in preventing heat generation when using piezoelectric surgery for peri-implant bone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-Effectiveness of Current Therapeutic Strategies for Melanoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The treatment landscape for melanoma has been dramatically transformed by the advent of novel therapeutic approaches, particularly immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) and targeted therapies (TTs). Clinical outcomes, such as overall survival, progression-free survival, objective response rate, and the incidence of immune-related adverse events, are useful metrics for evaluating these agents; however, cost considerations have become increasingly important. Globally, the medical costs associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two-stage recurrent events random effects models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We consider semiparametric random-effects models for recurrent events in the presence of a terminal event. The recurrent events have either a proportional marginal rate model (Cox in J Roy Stat Soc Ser B 34:406-424, 1972) or a proportional marginal mean model (Ghosh and Lin in Stat Sin 34: 663-688, 2002), while the marginal rate of the terminal event is given by a proportional model. The dependency between the recurrent events and the terminal event is described by two variants of random effects...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to letter to the editor on "Preoperative treatment and postoperative outcomes in osteoporotic patients with vertebral fractures: a longitudinal database study"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fatal black esophagus and duodenum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Black esophagus (BE) is a rare finding characterized by a black appearance on the distal esophageal mucosa. In the forensic field, BE is often reported in cases of diabetic ketoacidosis and hypothermia. Coexistence of acute duodenitis (black duodenum) has also been reported. Serious complications, such as esophageal perforation and hemorrhagic shock from bleeding from the esophageal mucosa, can be life-threatening. We report a forensic autopsy case of a relatively young man who died of BE and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic and therapeutic utility of gastric tissue culture in a case of phlegmonous gastritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phlegmonous gastritis is a rare, potentially life-threatening bacterial infection affecting the gastric mucosa and submucosa. Clinical presentation is often non-specific, typically including symptoms such as fever, epigastric vomiting, or hematemesis. Due to its rarity and vague clinical features, diagnosis is frequently delayed, increasing the risk of severe complications such as septic shock and death. We describe the case of a 74-year-old previously healthy female who presented with vomiting,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ViMOP: A user-friendly and field-applicable pipeline for untargeted viral genome nanopore sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MOTIVATION: Untargeted, also known as metagenomic, nanopore sequencing is a powerful tool for virus genomic surveillance, particularly in resource-limited settings and when paired with the portability of the MinION device (Oxford Nanopore Technologies, ONT). However, a major bottleneck for global access is the absence of a user-friendly software capable of efficiently analyzing untargeted nanopore sequencing data to generate high-quality consensus genomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lotus root-like appearance in angiographically mild coronary artery disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac vagal tone is associated with physical activity but not with depressive symptoms, work stress, and social support: A large-scale 10-year follow-up study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardiac vagal tone has been associated with mental and physical health and presents opportunities for preventive and therapeutic applications in mental health and cardiovascular medicine. Vagally-mediated heart rate variability (vmHRV), a marker of cardiac vagal tone, has been associated with multiple factors related to well-being. Recent research further suggests that stress regulation, social connection, and lifestyle jointly contribute to improved well-being. In a large-scale study (n =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Nonviral Neo-Nucleocapsid for Cell-Specific RNA Delivery Developed by Pseudo-Cyclic Peptide Grafting and Directed Evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonviral protein vehicles for RNA delivery hold significant promises for various biotechnological applications due to their scalability, ease of engineering, and high biocompatibility. Directed evolution is a powerful approach to enhance protein activity, yet few nonviral protein vehicles have been evolved due to the challenges in linking genotype and phenotype. Here, we report engineering and directed evolution of a neo-nucleocapsid enabling receptor-specific RNA delivery. We applied the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41460065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JPOS/JASCC clinical guidelines for psychological distress in adult cancer patients: a summary of recommendations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: This article aims to describe the newly developed Japanese practice guidelines for psychological distress of adult individuals with cancer who have elevated levels of psychological distress.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Humoral and T-cell immune responses to coronavirus disease 2019 vaccines in patients with hematological malignancies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides confirmatory real-world evidence that CD19 recovery is a key determinant of humoral response, while vaccine-induced T-cell immunity may be preserved even in antibody-nonresponders, supporting continued vaccination efforts in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medical device regulation and dialysis practice - impact on patients, doctors and manufacturers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The medical device regulation (MDR) was adopted in 2017 to replace the medical device directive (MDD). Key changes included more rigorous clinical evidence requirements, increased scrutiny of notified bodies, and improved traceability of medical devices, with the overarching aim to improve their safety and quality. For chronic haemodialysis, the impact of the MDR on devices has been substantial, resulting in niche devices being no longer available, and critical shortages, especially in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Costs Associated with In Home Post-Operative Eyedrop Nursing Care in Belgium - Implications for a Switch to Dropless Cataract Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cataract surgery is among the most frequently performed procedures globally, with over 176,000 surgeries conducted in Belgium in 2024. Postoperative care traditionally involves daily administration of antibiotic, steroid, and non-steroidal anti-inflammatory eye drops for four weeks, often requiring home nursing support due to poor patient compliance and technique. This conventional approach incurs significant costs for the Belgian healthcare system. A nationwide transition to dropless surgery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a humanized mouse model of graft-versus-host disease to assess human regulatory T cell function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Regulatory T cells (Treg)-based therapies are increasingly used for treating autoimmune or graft-versus-host (GVHD) disease. Given their low frequency, several approaches aimed at amplifying them or at increasing their immunosuppressive activities are currently investigated. Unfortunately, the impact of these strategies on human Treg function has remained difficult to assess in vivo. Here, we report the development of a novel humanized mouse model of allogeneic and xenogeneic GVHD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of novel anti-CDH1/E-cadherin monoclonal antibodies for versatile applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cadherin (CDH)-mediated extracellular homophilic binding is crucial for maintaining tissue homeostasis. The epithelial cell-cell adhesion molecule cadherin 1 (CDH1/E-cadherin) forms the adherens junctions in epithelial cells, and the loss of CDH1 facilitates the migration and invasion of carcinoma cells. Although several anti-CDH1 monoclonal antibodies (mAbs) are available for western blotting and immunohistochemistry (IHC), a highly sensitive anti-CDH1 mAb suitable for flow cytometry has not...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dog temperament is correlated with body weight and climate in country of origin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antifungal Resistance Surveillance: Insights From National Mycology Reference Centers and Expert Mycology Laboratories]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fungal pathogens and the infections they cause are notoriously understudied and underrepresented in public health surveillance programs. Recent initiatives, such as that of the Joint Programming Initiative on Anti-Microbial Resistance (JPIAMR), recognize these gaps and have supported the development of a fungal surveillance resistance network. The International Fungal Network for One-Health Resistance Surveillance: Antifungal Resistance (INFORM-AFR) network sought to enhance understanding of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In-depth look at the use of pixel variance and the noise power spectrum in digital mammography quality control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The evaluated noise metrics were reproducible, identified changes in X-ray detector performance, and have a useful role to play in QC testing. The average values have application as reference performance data.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41459001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lipid nanoparticle-encapsulated microRNA-192: An anti-inflammatory adjuvant that enhances vaccine efficacy in aged mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proinflammatory cytokines are essential for initiating immune responses; however, excessive or aging-related chronic inflammation impairs immunity and reduces vaccine efficacy. In this study, we developed lipid nanoparticles (LNPs) encapsulating anti-inflammatory microRNA-192 (miR-192) to attenuate inflammation and improve vaccine performance in the elderly. Results revealed that specific proinflammatory cytokines, including interleukin (IL)-6 and tumor necrosis factor (TNF)-α at the vaccination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of Provitamin A Maize and Iron-Rich Bean-Based Composite Flour for Improved Child Nutrition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bio-fortification is a strategy that has been proven to not only reduce the prevalence of micronutrient deficiencies, but also to tackle other forms of malnutrition. Therefore, the inclusion of flour from bio-fortified crops as major components of composite flours can significantly alleviate malnutrition. In this study, the effect of replacing white maize with provitamin A bio-fortified maize in a bean-based composite flour was studied. Response surface methodology was used to optimize the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Basic swimming or water safety skills training for drowning prevention in children: an updated systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Swim training may reduce drowning-related mortality and increase water safety skills in children. The used pedagogical approach (focus on familiarization and motor awareness), mode of delivery (using video-taped feedback) and setting (shallow water) may be determining factors for swimming skills acquisition. Water safety training is effective to enhance knowledge of and safe behaviour in/around water, and may reduce drowning mortality. These results, highlighting the importance of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The association of nationwide trainee doctor mass resignations in South Korea with hospital utilization, expenditure, and patient outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In February 2024, over 90% of trainee doctors in South Korea's teaching hospitals resigned en masse, severely disrupting healthcare delivery. We evaluated the associations of this mass resignation with hospital admission and length of stay, expenditure, and patients' health outcomes in a tertiary teaching hospital. We analyzed inpatient claims data from Jeju National University Hospital (August 2022-July 2024), encompassing 40,577 hospital episodes. Using a difference-in-differences method, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute Promyelocytic Leukemia with double minute chromosomes: a rare case with high relapse risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute promyelocytic leukemia (APL) is a subtype of acute myeloid leukemia (AML); it has a high response rate and long-term survival with differentiation therapy and chemotherapy. However, only one previous case of APL with double minute chromosomes (DMs, a poor prognostic factor for AML) has been reported. We report the case of a patient with APL and DMs. A 44-year-old woman was treated with all-trans retinoic acid (ATRA) and chemotherapy and achieved molecular complete remission (mCR). However,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Donepezil-Induced Severe Anorexia and T-Wave Inversion in Early-Onset Alzheimer's Disease: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Donepezil hydrochloride, used to treat Alzheimer's disease, is typically initiated at a low dose and titrated to minimize gastrointestinal side effects. Despite its favorable safety profile, the patient developed severe anorexia, dehydration, and electrocardiographic abnormalities. This case highlights the need for individualized dosing and careful monitoring of caregivers during pharmacotherapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41458192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation Between Caregiver Mental Health and Stimulating Parenting Practice: Evidence From Rural China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although rural Chinese caregivers now supply more play materials, limited diversity and widespread caregiver mental health risks persist. Strengthening caregiver mental health and social support could enrich home stimulation and improve early childhood development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Engineering of Au─Ag Heterometallic Nanoparticles Using Multidentate Polyoxometalate Ligands]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heterometallic nanoparticles possess immense potential in catalysis and materials science; however, achieving precise structural control remains a major challenge. In this work, we report a facile co-reduction strategy for the preparation of gold-silver (Au-Ag) heterometallic nanoparticles stabilized by multidentate polyoxometalates, which act as functional inorganic ligands. Notably, core-shell-structured Au-Ag nanoparticles are preferentially obtained even under co-reduction conditions, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Integration of Quantum Materials with Smart Electrolytes for Next-Generation Multifunctional Supercapacitors: Advances, Challenges, and Future Prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rapid advancements in artificial intelligence and growing global demand for sustainable energy solutions have accelerated the integration of intelligent functionalities into electrochemical energy storage devices, notably supercapacitors (SCs). Quantum materials (QMs), including quantum dots (QDs), MXenes, metal-organic frameworks (MOFs), covalent organic frameworks (COFs), and transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDs), combined with smart electrolytes, have emerged as critical components for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Kind of Social Preparations Are Needed for Xenotransplantation? A Survey Study of the Japanese General Public]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results imply the Japanese public is not ready enough to accept xenotransplantation. This study proposes four points that policymakers and researchers should prepare for social issues before the clinical trial begins in Japan.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phosphorylation of Atg12 for optimal autophagy in yeast Komagataella phaffii]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macroautophagy is an evolutionarily conserved degradation pathway in eukaryotes that mediates the turnover of cytoplasmic components. The formation of autophagosomes, a hallmark of autophagy, involves autophagy-related (Atg) proteins, including two ubiquitin-like conjugation systems, Atg12 system and Atg8 system. In most species, Atg12 covalently binds Atg5, forming the Atg12-Atg5-Atg16 complex that functions as an E3-like enzyme to promote Atg8 conjugation with phosphatidylethanolamine (PE), a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insight into factors contributing to sensory burden after acquired brain injury: An experience sampling approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings underscore the dynamic and individualized nature of sensory burden after ABI, emphasizing the need for personalized interventions targeting sensory hypersensitivity. Future research should explore additional triggers, resources, and causal pathways to further elucidate the proposed mechanisms and inform treatment development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41457364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of screen habits on attentional skills and prosocial behaviors in 6-to 36-month-old toddlers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rise of digital tools in the 21st century has significantly increased screen exposure among toddlers, raising concerns about its impact on their overall psychological development. Since attentional skills and prosocial behaviors play a key role in the development of toddlers' cognitive, emotional, and social functioning, the current research explores the links between screen habits of 6- to 36-month-old toddlers and their development of attentional skills and prosocial behaviors. For this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fast Discharging Stabilizes Electrochemical Interfaces: Achieving Close-to-Unity Reversibility in "Dendrite-Forming" Battery Electrodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing resilient aqueous energy storage systems, such as Zn batteries, is essential for advancing energy sustainability. A key challenge in these systems is the dendritic growth of metals, which causes poor rechargeability in battery electrodes. Classical diffusion-limited dendritic growth is predicted to occur when the charging rate exceeds the limiting current density J(lim) determined by electrolyte transport properties. Understanding the electrochemical behavior of dendrites is critical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting natural enemy efficacy in biological control using ex-ante analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Massive losses in agricultural and natural systems accrue globally due to invasive species, and yet the success rate of natural enemy introductions to control them is low. The high failure rate is due to the unknown efficacy of the introduced natural enemies. Furthermore, reviews of prior biological control efforts have not led to the development of assessment methods to predict their pre-release efficacy. To demonstrate a potential solution, we deconstructed the biological control of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mixed-mode control of multiphase interleaved parallel circuit for pulsed laser diode driving]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With advancements in industrial technology, the switching power supply has gradually emerged as a preferred choice for laser power supplies due to its advantages of lower power consumption and compact size. However, the simultaneous achievement of short rise time, current flatness, and high accuracy pose significant difficulties for the switching power supply. In this paper, a mixed-mode control of multiple interleaving parallel circuits is proposed. The proposed mixed-mode control incorporates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health and well-being among older adults in Zhejiang Province, China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[By the end of the 20th century, China had transitioned into an aging society. With the aging population, the health problems of older adults have become a central concern for both families and society. Identifying and addressing these health issues is of paramount importance. The main objective of this study was to investigate the health and well-being of Chinese older adults aged ≥ 60 years. A cross-sectional design was employed, and 16,276 participants from 11 non-randomly selected counties in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analyzing water recharge mechanisms and predicting water inflow in deep mining based on hydrogeological structures: a case study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding water recharge mechanisms and accurately predicting water inflow are the fundamental objectives of mine hydrogeology investigation, particularly for ensuring deep mining safety. These investigation findings establish a scientific basis for planning drainage systems, optimizing mining layouts, and developing water hazard prevention and control measures. This paper takes the Maoping lead-zinc mine in Northeast Yunnan, China as a case study, which is a typical deep mine with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-omics and machine learning refine HCC molecular subtypes and prognosis based on liquid-liquid phase separation related genes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accumulating evidence has demonstrated that biological processes associated with liquid-liquid phase separation (LLPS) play a critical role in cancer development. However, the effect of LLPS on hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) remains largely unknown. In this study, we integrated consensus clustering with an ensemble machine learning framework to establish robust LLPS-related molecular subtypes and a consensus machine learning-driven LLPS-related signature (CMLLS) for HCC. The consensus clustering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Osprey optimization algorithm integrated with graph neural networks for intrusion detection in wireless sensor networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the complexity of the cyber-attacks increasing tremendously, framing an efficient intrusion detection system (IDS) has proved to be highly vital and crucial in ensuring security across the wireless sensor networks (WSNs). The major function of IDS is to prevent the WSNs from suspected attacks. Conventional IDS face numerous challenges which include limited capability, inadequate identification of attacks and detection of high false alarm rates, leading to complex data processing and pattern...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial temporal variation characteristics and driving factors of net primary productivity in the Huaihe River Economic Belt on seasonal scale]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Net Primary Productivity (NPP) is a key indicator of terrestrial ecosystem functioning and a major regulator of the global carbon cycle. Yet, its interannual fluctuations and seasonal drivers remain unclear. Using Theil-Sen trend analysis, Mann-Kendall test, R/S analysis, and the Geographically and Temporally Weighted Regression (GTWR) model, this study examined the spatiotemporal dynamics and driving mechanisms of seasonal NPP in the Huaihe River Economic Belt from 2010 to 2021. Results show a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic analysis unlocks the potential of denosumab as a targeted therapy for Crohn's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crohn's disease (CD) is a chronic, relapsing inflammatory disorder of the gastrointestinal tract with limited curative therapies. Genomic drug repurposing offers a rapid strategy to identify existing drugs that could be redirected to treat CD. We retrieved 1,333 CD-associated single-nucleotide polymorphisms from the GWAS Catalog and expanded these to 15,590 variants using linkage disequilibrium analysis in HaploReg. Fourteen layers of functional annotation prioritized 45 high-confidence risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring cue-elicited responding in the context of gaming and online shopping: Validity and reliability of a short Pavlovian-to-instrumental transfer paradigm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploiting a centrally powered coherent microcomb for lightweight optical transmission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The exponential growth of data capacity in intelligent terminals drives higher data traffic toward network edges. Compact I/O systems are essential to support space-constrained infrastructures at the computing edges or modular data centers. However, scaling high-capacity transmission via increasing physical channels is constrained by limited source coherence and low carrier-to-noise ratios (OCNR), hindering lightweight, efficient applications like distributed edge computing. Here, we exploit an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergence of the enhanced equatorial Atlantic warming as a fingerprint of global warming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The response of tropical sea surface temperature (SST) to global warming plays a crucial role in shaping both global and regional climates, so it receives immense attention and remains being debated. Here, we demonstrate that enhanced equatorial warming (EEW) is a more robust response to global warming than the commonly examined changes in the zonal SST gradient across the tropical Pacific, which is marked by discrepancies between observations and models. EEW is defined as the annual-mean SST...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Confinement-induced acceleration of CO<sub>2</sub> mineralization through interfacial water thinning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current projections demand atmospheric CO(2) removal at the gigatonne-per-year scale through mineral carbonation, yet conventional aqueous routes remain energy-intensive and kinetically limited. Here we apply a water thinning strategy to engineer the interfacial water-film (IWF) with thicknesses below 8.5 nm. We achieve complete carbonation of calcium hydroxide (Ca(OH)(2)) within 1 h under ambient conditions, realizing a 16-fold acceleration compared to bulk solution systems. The IWF exhibits...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging genomic and transcriptomic data of diverse ancestry to uncover mechanisms of psychiatric risk in the adult and developing brain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We explore strategies to harness ancestral diversity in PsychENCODE Consortium Genotype-Expression (GEx) reference panels (adult and developing brain) and Psychiatric Genomics Consortium GWAS data to improve genetically regulated expression (GReX) models and their use for Transcriptome-wide association study (TWAS) discoveries, uncovering previously unknown aspects of psychiatric functional genomics. We trained multiple GReX models on rigorously constructed GEx panel subsets, generated by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41461652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251230024134&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>