<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:20:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel synthesis of Al<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub> short fibers/Ti-12Mo-6Zr composites for cranial reconstruction applications: spark plasma sintering, microstructure and nanomechanical properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ceramic-Titanium matrix composites have recently attracted significant interest as a new type of biomaterials protecting the brain from external force and infections of cranial defects due to its biocompatibility and good mechanical and corrosion properties matched with the bone tissue. Spark plasma sintering (SPS) is one of powder technology techniques that can be utilised in the fabrication of final net complex and irregular shape parts used for cranial reconstruction and maxillofacial trauma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Denitratimonas tolerans gen. nov., sp. nov., a denitrifying bacterium isolated from a bioreactor for tannery wastewater treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regenerable Water Remediation Platform for Ultrafast Capture and Mineralization of Per- and Polyfluoroalkyl Substances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Concerns about per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS) arise from their persistence, toxicity, and widespread presence in aquatic environments. Currently, activated carbon and ion exchange resins have been used to remove perfluorooctanoic acid (PFOA), the most commonly studied PFAS, but these methods face challenges like low adsorption capacity and slow kinetics, leading to secondary waste issues. Here, it is observed that a high interlayer crystallinity of nitrate intercalated Cu(x)Al...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibody-based alternatives to animal testing for toxin detection and antitoxin evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Animal experiments have long played a central role in biomedical research and toxicology, yet their limitations in translational accuracy and ethical concerns have intensified the demand for reliable alternatives. Antibody-based technologies are versatile tools used to develop non-animal testing methods capable of detecting toxins and evaluating antitoxins. Enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay and lateral flow assays, among other techniques, have demonstrated high specificity, sensitivity, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of pathogenic <em>MEFV</em> variants in Korean patients with familial Mediterranean fever via whole-genome sequencing: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Familial Mediterranean fever (FMF) is an autoinflammatory disorder characterized by recurrent episodes of fever, serositis, and arthritis. It is caused by variants in the MEFV gene, which encodes the pyrin protein. FMF primarily affects individuals of Mediterranean and Middle Eastern descent, and six cases have been reported in the Korean population to date. However, the pathogenicity of the MEFV gene variants identified in previous Korean cases remains uncertain. Here, we report two cases of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-based artefact reduction in low-dose dental cone beam computed tomography with high-attenuation materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper examines the current challenges in computed tomography (CT), with a critical exploration of existing methodologies from a mathematical perspective. Specifically, it aims to identify research directions to enhance image quality in low-dose, cost-effective cone beam CT (CBCT) systems, which have recently gained widespread use in general dental clinics. Dental CBCT offers a substantial cost advantage over standard medical CT, making it affordable for local dental practices; however, this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ferroelectric 3D Nanoweb-Incorporated <em>In Situ</em> Cross-Linked Composite Solid Electrolyte for High-Performance Lithium-Metal Polymer Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All-solid-state Li-metal batteries (ASSLBs) are promising for next-generation energy storage systems owing to their high energy density and intrinsic safety. However, their practical applications are impeded by challenges such as low ionic conductivity, uncontrolled Li-dendrite growth, and interfacial instability. This study presents a scalable strategy to address these limitations by incorporating ferroelectric BaTiO(3) into poly(vinylidene fluoride-co-hexafluoropropylene) (PVDF-HFP) nanowebs....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Nocardioides lacus</em> sp. nov., a novel member of the <em>Actinomycetota</em> isolated from a freshwater pond]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A Gram-positive, aerobic, short rod-shaped, white-coloured bacterium, designated strain BP30^(T), was isolated from a freshwater pond. Growth occurred at 15-35 °C (optimum, 30 °C) and pH 5.5-8.5 (optimum, pH 7) in the presence of 0-0.5 % NaCl (optimum, 0 %). 16S rRNA gene phylogenetic analysis showed that this strain was most closely related to Nocardioides marinus CL-DD14ᵀ (97.07%), Nocardioides terrae VA15ᵀ (97.03%), Nocardioides opuntiae OS1-21ᵀ (96.96%), Nocardioides panacihumi Gsoil 616ᵀ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ribociclib Plus Endocrine Therapy in Hormone Receptor-Positive/ERBB2-Negative Early Breast Cancer: 4-Year Outcomes From the NATALEE Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This exploratory analysis of the NATALEE randomized clinical trial, with a median follow-up beyond the 3-year treatment duration, demonstrated consistent iDFS benefit with ribociclib plus NSAI over NSAI alone.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of Clinical Obesity in US Adults Based on a Newly Proposed Definition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging EGFR-Targeted Therapy in Head and Neck Cancer: A Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The emerging data of combinatorial approaches and novel EGFR-targeting therapeutic agents offer renewed optimism for patients with advanced HNSCC who have limited treatment options. Future progress will depend on novel agents leveraging a deeper understanding of tumor biology, innovative approaches to reduce on-target off-tumor toxic effects of targeting EGFR, and improving efficacy in the growing population of patients with HPV-positive HNSCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automatic genetic phenotype normalization from dysmorphology physical examinations: an overview of the BioCreative VIII-Task 3 competition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present here an overview of the BioCreative VIII Task 3 competition, which called for the development of state-of-the-art approaches to automatic normalization of observations noted by physicians in dysmorphology physical examinations to the Human Phenotype Ontology (HPO). We made available for the task 3136 deidentified and manually annotated observations extracted from electronic health records of 1652 paediatric patients at the Children's Hospital of Philadelphia. This task is challenging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient methods of isolation and purification of extracellular vesicles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Living cells produce nanometer scales of extracellular vesicles (EVs) that have attracted considerable interest due to their transformative effects on diagnostics and therapies for cancer and other diseases. While significant advancements have been made in grasping the physical and chemical foundations of separation techniques for EVs, challenges must be overcome to ensure effective EV purification for diverse life sciences and clinical applications. This review highlights the most significant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual inhibitors of P-glycoprotein and breast cancer resistance protein for overcoming the blood-brain barrier: in silico discovery and preclinical evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[P-glycoprotein (P-gp) and breast cancer resistance protein (BCRP) are typical ABC efflux transporters that play important physiological and pharmacological roles. At the blood-brain barrier (BBB), P-gp and BCRP function cooperatively as the main efflux transporters, hindering the entry of drugs into the brain. Therefore, dual inhibition of P-gp and BCRP is needed to deliver drugs effectively to the brain. This study sought potential dual P-gp/BCRP inhibitors to determine their ability to enhance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colloidal systems as experimental platforms for physics-informed machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colloidal systems offer a unique experimental window for investigating condensed matter phenomena, uniquely enabling simultaneous access to microscopic particle dynamics and emergent macroscopic responses. Their particle-scale size, thermal motion, and tuneable interactions allow for real-time, real-space, and single-particle-resolved imaging. These features make it possible to directly connect local structural changes, dynamic rearrangements, and mechanical deformation with system-level...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning reconstruction for temporomandibular joint MRI: diagnostic interchangeability, image quality, and scan time reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DL-reconstructed TMJ MRI is diagnostically interchangeable with conventional MRI, offering improved image quality with a shorter scan time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Work-related risk factors of sleep apnea: evidence from the Korean work, sleep, and health study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Work-related psychosocial and environmental factors contribute meaningfully to sleep apnea risk. Addressing workplace conditions may represent an important strategy for sleep apnea prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Handgrip Strength With Urinary Incontinence in Postmenopausal Korean Women: A Machine Learning Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Handgrip strength is independently associated with UI in postmenopausal women. As a practical and noninvasive measure, it may be useful in identifying individuals at increased risk of incontinence and guiding early interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delphi consensus on melasma management by international experts and pigmentary disorders society]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These recommendations aim to improve the outcomes of melasma patients globally by integrating expert opinion and evidence-based strategies. Future research should focus on evaluating emerging therapies and optimizing long-term maintenance strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-Channel Neural Interface for Neural Recording and Neuromodulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neural interfaces have emerged as pivotal platforms for advancing digital neurotherapies by enabling the real-time acquisition and monitoring of neural signals. Traditional single-channel systems are inherently limited in their capacity to capture the complex and large-scale interactions among diverse neuronal populations. In contrast, multi-channel systems provide the high spatiotemporal resolution necessary to decode the dynamic activity of neural circuits across multiple brain and spinal cord...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuromorphic Visual Receptive Field Hardware with Vertically Integrated Indium-Gallium-Zinc-Oxide Optoelectronic Memristors over Silicon Neuron Transistors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Event-driven processing in neuromorphic vision systems, utilizing spiking neural networks, can offer improved energy efficiency compared to conventional von Neumann systems. This study proposes an artificial retinal neuron with a vertically integrated optoelectronic memristor (optomemristor) and a neuron transistor (neuristor), inspired by the visual receptive field (VRF) of the biological retina. This design performs pre-processing in the sensor to extract essential image features, such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioengineered Skin Grafts from Patient-Derived Decellularized Extracellular Matrix and Autologous Cells for Personalized Regenerative]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The skin, as the body's largest organ, plays vital protective and regulatory roles, making it a key target in regenerative medicine. However, current skin models often lack patient specificity and fail to recapitulate native extracellular matrix (ECM) composition, limiting their clinical relevance. This study presents a 3D-bioprinted skin model using a patient-derived decellularized ECM (pddECM) bioink combined with keratin-alginate (KA) bioink, mimicking native skin architecture and function....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultralong and Thermally Enhanced Persistent Luminescence in Printable Recycled Polymers for Advanced Thermal Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving long persistent luminescence (LPL) in fully organic materials with both hour-level duration and high thermal stability remains a fundamental challenge attributable to rapid exciton quenching and poor resistance to thermal disturbances. Herein, a trap engineering strategy is reported based on rigidified triphenylamine derivatives and boronic ester functionalization embedded in recycled poly(ethylene terephthalate) (PET), enabling the first fully organic polymer-based LPL system that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hepatocellular Carcinoma Risk in Chronic Hepatitis B Patients Treated With Tenofovir Alafenamide or Tenofovir Disoproxil Fumarate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study showed that TAF had a hepatoprotective effect against HCC in patients with CHB, providing valuable guidance for clinicians in selecting the appropriate initial treatment for these patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Specific detectivity-oriented low-noise management in organic photodetectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The need to detect faint light signals with unparalleled precision is redefining organic photodetectors (OPDs) and unlocking their transformative applications in biosignal monitoring, optical communication, and quantum-level photodetection. The specific detectivity (D*) is an essential metric in such scenarios that captures the ability of an OPD to extract weak signals from noise and is a function of the active area, bandwidth, and noise-equivalent power of the device. This review reframes the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive study of organic-inorganic hybrid [N(C<sub>2</sub>H<sub>5</sub>)<sub>4</sub>]<sub>2</sub>CdBr<sub>4</sub>: crystal structure, phase transitions, and structural geometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The compound [N(C(2)H(5))(4)](2)CdBr(4), an organic-inorganic hybrid compound, has garnered attention for its potential applications across various fields. In this study, single crystals of [N(C(2)H(5))(4)](2)CdBr(4) were grown, and two distinct phase transition temperatures were identified: approximately 232 K (T (C1)) and 476 K (T (C2)). Single-crystal X-ray diffraction analysis at 300 K revealed a tetragonal structure belonging to the space group P4̄2(1) m. The thermal properties of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the gastric microbiota based on body mass index using 16S rRNA gene sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Obesity is a multifactorial condition influenced by various factors, including the gut microbiota. However, the relationship between the gastric microbiota and obesity remains poorly understood. This study aimed to investigate the composition of gastric microbiota, excluding Helicobacter pylori, in relation to body mass index (BMI) and metabolic indicators.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of combined transcranial direct current stimulation and cognitive training on brain microstructure and network homogeneity in late-life depression: a pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cognitive training leads to improved white matter integrity in older adults experiencing cognitive deficit and depression. Changes in the structural integrity of the cingulum can predict clinical outcomes. No additional benefits of tDCS on white matter integrity or network homogeneity were observed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacopuncture for patients with psychological stress caused by traffic accidents: A pragmatic randomized controlled pilot trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Stress-focused pharmacopuncture may alleviate anxiety and depression symptoms and potentially accelerate recovery after traffic accidents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validity of a claim-based algorithm for classifying disease activity levels using Systemic Lupus Erythematosus Disease Activity Index 2000 in Korean patients with systemic lupus erythematosus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A claims-based algorithm using diagnostic and medication codes demonstrated a PPV of 77.2% for classifying mild disease activity in SLE. This approach may offer a practical method for disease activity assessment in Korean claims-based research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical treatment of rheumatoid arthritis of the elbow]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is a chronic inflammatory condition that significantly impacts multiple joints, including the elbow, crucial for daily activities. Despite advancements in medical treatments like disease-modifying antirheumatic drugs that delay disease progression, surgical interventions are often necessary to improve the quality of life in RA patients. This review provides a comprehensive evaluation of the elbow, focusing on history taking, physical examination, and radiographic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between serum urate, gout and chronic kidney disease: a scoping review of systematic reviews and meta-analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyperuricemia is highly prevalent in patients with chronic kidney disease (CKD) due to reduced renal urate clearance, which leads to an increased incidence of gout in this population. Additionally, hyperuricemia may be associated with the progression of CKD. Hyperuricemia, gout, and CKD are closely interconnected; however, high-quality evidence to guide the management of hyperuricemia and gout in CKD patients remains insufficient. This literature review aimed to describe the association between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rituximab in Sjögren's disease: reconciling evidence from randomized and observational studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Breast Cancer Screening Between Medicare Beneficiaries With and Without Food Insecurity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest the importance for identifying female Medicare beneficiaries who are at increased risk of food insecurity and missed breast cancer screening in clinical settings during and after the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Isolation of a SARS-CoV-2 strain from pediatric patients in South Korea: biologic and genetic characterization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fmicb.2025.1654224.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Report: A case of traumatic subgaleal hematoma with delayed massive exophthalmos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Progressive exophthalmos occurring after minor trauma is very rare, it is important to consider subgaleal hematoma in the differential diagnosis. If diagnosis is delayed, permanent vision loss may occur due to optic nerve damage or corneal damage due to pressure, so performing decompression surgery at an appropriate time is effective in preventing blindness. A 16-year-old male patient with Lennox-Gastaut syndrome and developmental disability was admitted to the hospital 2 weeks after a head...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor-informed circulating tumor DNA detection for personalized monitoring of treatment response in epithelial ovarian cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates the clinical utility of ddPCR for monitoring treatment responses in EOC by targeting patient-specific mutations. Integrating ddPCR with NGS-based mutation identification offers an effective approach for assessing therapeutic outcomes in EOC patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gait Improvement Following CSF Tap Test in NPH Patients With and Without Striatal Dopaminergic Deficit: A Preliminary Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Recent studies have highlighted the occurrence of reduced striatal signal intensity on dopamine transporter (DAT) scans in patients with idiopathic normal pressure hydrocephalus (iNPH). The aim of our study was to investigate whether the extent of symptom improvement after a CSF tap test (TT) differs between iNPH patients with reduced striatal DAT uptake and those with normal uptake.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-based prediction of cerebral white matter hyperintensity burden using carotid magnetic resonance angiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Carotid TOF MRA alone can serve as a predictive marker for WMH burden when analyzed using deep learning. This approach highlights the potential utility of extracranial carotid imaging as a non-invasive surrogate for early and accessible assessment of cerebrovascular risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of Bacteriocin Production Ability of <em>Pediococcus acidilactici</em> JM01 and Probiotic Properties Isolated From Tarak, a Conventional Korean Fermented Milk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to isolate and characterize a bacteriocin-producing lactic acid bacterium from Tarak, a traditional Korean fermented milk, for potential applications in food safety and health. Pediococcus acidilactici JM01 was identified and shown to produce a bacteriocin with strong antimicrobial activity against Listeria monocytogenes. The maximum activity (2560 AU/mL) was observed after 12 h of incubation and remained stable across a broad pH range (2-11) and under various heat treatments....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multinational Study of Patient and Caregiver-Reported Insights Into ADSS1 Myopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION/AIMS: Adenylosuccinate synthase-like 1 (ADSS1) myopathy is an ultra-rare disorder caused by biallelic pathogenic variants in the ADSS1 gene. This results in progressive muscle weakness, fatigue, dysphagia, and, in severe cases, cardiomyopathy and respiratory failure. The aim of the study was to evaluate how ADSS1 myopathy impacts patients' lives and to comprehensively assess their quality of life.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of health insurance status on hospitalization and mortality from emergency department admission in patients with end-stage kidney disease: a Korean nationwide registry analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Young, economically active MA patients were less likely to be admitted but had poor clinical outcomes after admission, suggesting their reluctance toward hospitalization for economic reasons.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disaster preparedness and awareness among medical staff in Korean dialysis units]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: There were high levels of disaster preparedness among medical staff in HD units. Cooperation between each HD unit, the Korean Society of Nephrology, and the national government should be warranted to deal with future disasters in HD units.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Step Chemical Treatment of Wafer-Scale Metal-Organic Chemical Vapor Deposition Grown Monolayer Molybdenum Disulfides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two-dimensional (2D) transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDs) possess distinct optical and electronic properties, making them promising candidates for optoelectronic applications. Recently, major advances in the wafer-scale growth of TMDs using the metal-organic chemical vapor deposition (MOCVD) have enabled their integration with standard electronics. However, such materials continue to suffer from defects and unwanted doping, which lower semiconductor performance, as exemplified by poor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter: Risk Prediction Model for HCC in Subjects Without Apparent Chronic Liver Disease: A Dilemma in Asia. Author's Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detachable Microneedle Patch for Local Delivery of TGF-β Inhibitor to Suppress Scar Formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe wounds often lead to delayed healing and fibrotic scar formation, primarily driven by dysregulated transforming growth factor beta (TGF-β) signaling, which causes excessive collagen accumulation. Current treatments face limitations, including poor drug delivery, systemic side effects, and patient compliance issues. To address these challenges, we developed a detachable microneedle (d-MN) patch made of biodegradable poly(lactic-co-glycolic acid) for the localized, sustained delivery of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CT Findings for Differentiating Pulmonary Mucormycosis From Invasive Pulmonary Aspergillosis, Prior to Invasive Procedure Such as a Biopsy or Surgery: A 22-Year Single-Center Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CT findings of large consolidative lesions, the presence of a reverse halo sign, and the absence of airway invasion may aid in the early differentiation of PM from IPA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Normalization of network activity in an epilepsy model with a constitutively active GABBR2 variant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The neurotransmitter GABA activates G protein-coupled GABAB receptors (GBRs) that mediate neuronal inhibition in the brain. These receptors function as obligate heterodimers, consisting of the GB1 and GB2 subunits, with GB1 binding GABA and GB2 interacting with the G protein. The monoallelic variants p.A567T, p.S695I, and p.I705N in the GABBR2 gene, which encodes the GB2 subunit, have been associated with epileptic encephalopathy and Rett-like disorders. The clinical phenotypes overlap with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating Birth and Thyroid Outcomes of Maternal-Fetal Environmental Exposures (IBM-E): A Cohort Protocol for Dietary Iodine and Endocrine Disruptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The IBM-E cohort is designed to enable the longitudinal assessment of gestational environmental exposures and their potential impacts on maternal and fetal thyroid function, as well as pregnancy and neonatal outcomes. The findings of this study may inform preventive strategies and guide policy development in perinatal environmental health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Systolic and Diastolic Blood Pressure with the Risk of End-Stage Renal Disease in Older Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus Patients without Cardiovascular Disease: A Nationwide Population-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Maintaining blood pressure at less than 120/80 mm Hg might prevent progression to ESRD in older T2DM patients without cardiovascular disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Giant Traumatic Pneumatocele Manifesting as Hemoptysis in an Adolescent: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traumatic pneumatocele (TP) is a rare, benign pulmonary lesion that primarily affects children and young adults following blunt chest trauma. We present the case of a 16-year-old male judo athlete who developed persistent hemoptysis. Imaging identified a large hydropneumothorax. During video-assisted thoracoscopic surgery, a cystic lesion was discovered in the left lower lobe, and intraoperative bronchofibroscopy revealed a minor bronchopleural fistula. A wedge resection was performed, resulting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Self-Myofascial Release and Dynamic Neuromuscular Stabilization Exercises on Pain, Balance, Muscle Function, and the Autonomic Nervous System in Women with Chronic Low Back Pain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND This study investigated the combined effects of self-myofascial release (SMR) and dynamic neuromuscular stabilization (DNS) exercises on pain, balance, muscle function, and autonomic nervous system regulation in women with chronic low back pain. MATERIAL AND METHODS Forty women with chronic low back pain, recruited from an exercise center in Seongnam City, were randomly assigned to an experimental group (n=20) or a control group (n=20). The experimental group performed 20 minutes of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Timing of postmastectomy radiation therapy in two-stage expander/implant-based breast reconstruction: a systematic review and meta-analysis for the 2022 Japanese breast cancer society clinical practice guideline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PMRT to expander was associated with higher reconstruction failure and lower severe capsular contracture rates, with no significant differences in major complications by timing. There is insufficient evidence to favor one approach over the other.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cellular responses in rainbow trout Oncorhynchus mykiss to experimental Anisakis simplex infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fish in wild and cultured populations may be infected with numerous types of pathogens but the host responses vary dependent on both host and parasite species. The present study demonstrates how an experimental infection with endoparasitic nematode larvae (Anisakis simplex) induces cellular and humoral immune responses in rainbow trout Oncorhynchus mykiss. The nematode larvae invaded the peritoneal cavity of the fish following oral administration and became encapsulated by a range of host cells...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Paradoxical embolism due to a pulmonary arteriovenous fistula with a string-like thrombus traversing the left atrium and ventricle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Poly(3-Hydroxybutyrate-Co-3-Hydroxyhexanoate): Real-Time Monitoring of Microbial Degradation via Quartz Crystal Microbalance and Electrochemical Measurement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Poly(3-hydroxybutyrate-co-3-hydroxyhexanoate) (PHBH), produced by some bacteria, including Aeromonas strains, exhibits excellent environmental biodegradability, even in marine environments where biodegradation is typically poor. However, the exact mechanisms underlying this biodegradability remain to be elucidated. To evaluate the mechanisms of microbial degradation of PHBH, focusing on the initial stages, PHBH degradation by Comamonas testosteroni is analyzed, using a quartz crystal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pan-cancer analyses reveal disparities in tumor genomic profiles by race/ethnicity, age, and sex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Distinct spectrums of somatic mutations exist across various racial/ethnic, age-onset, and sex groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boundary conditions for exploiting the cooperation of <em>Aminobacter niigataensis</em> MSH1 with <em>Piscinibacter</em> sp. K169 to support 2,6-dichlorobenzamide biodegradation in sand filters for drinking water treatment: role of cell density and organic carbon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aminobacter niigataensis MSH1 mineralizes the groundwater micropollutant 2,6-dichlorobenzamide (BAM) and is a candidate for bioaugmentation of sand filters in drinking water treatment plants (DWTP) to avert BAM-contamination. Piscinibacter sp. K169 is a sand filter isolate that improves MSH1-mediated BAM mineralization through a cooperative interaction, and co-inoculation of MSH1 with K169 is proposed as a strategy to support bioaugmentation with MSH1. In this study, boundaries regarding the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isotopic and genetic evidence of partial mycoheterotrophy in leafy variants of Cremastra aphylla, a predominantly leafless orchid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings provide the first integrated isotopic and genetic evidence for partial mycoheterotrophy in leafy C. aphylla individuals, although they remain highly dependent on fungal carbon. Our results refine the current understanding of the nutritional continuum in partially mycoheterotrophic orchids and highlight C. aphylla as a valuable model for investigating the evolutionary transition toward full mycoheterotrophy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of vasopressin delivery via the proximal humerus and proximal tibia in healthy dogs under general anesthesia: implications for emergency intraosseous administration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During cardiopulmonary resuscitation, securing intravenous access for medication delivery can be problematic due to the size of the patient and vasoconstriction due to hypotension. The osseous route is a promising alternative to the intravenous route. The proximal humerus and proximal tibia are two commonly utilized sites in dogs. While some studies have reported the superiority of the proximal humerus route over the proximal tibia route for drug delivery in humans, there is a lack of knowledge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Candida albicans</em> Hxk1 influences expression of metabolic- and virulence-related genes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Hxk1 protein of Candida albicans phosphorylates N-acetylglucosamine (GlcNAc) which is necessary for various cellular functions, including energy production and chitin synthesis. Further, this protein also regulates morphogenesis independently of its role in GlcNAc catabolism. When HXK1 is deleted, cells are hyperfilamentous on serum-containing medium. Furthermore, Hxk1 translocates to the nucleus in the presence of glucose. To gain a broad understanding of the effect of Hxk1 on gene...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virtual Reality for Balance in Individuals With Diabetes: A Systematic Review of Assessment and Intervention Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This systematic review summarizes VR as an innovative and interactive approach, demonstrating its applicability and usefulness in both balance assessment and intervention among individuals with DM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of vancomycin population pharmacokinetic models for pediatric patients using a real-world web application database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: For Japanese pediatric patients aged three months or older, the developed popPK model is suitable for both empirical and Bayesian-guided vancomycin dosing. Two-point sampling improves the accuracy of clearance estimation and is recommended when feasible.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Materials Innovation and the Changing Face of Photocatalytic and Electrocatalytic Carbon Dioxide Reduction Research: From Metal Nanoclusters to Extended Frameworks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The accelerating rise in atmospheric CO(2) levels, driven by anthropogenic emissions, underscores the urgent need for transformative carbon management strategies. Photocatalytic and electrocatalytic CO(2) reduction reactions (CO(2)RRs) offer a promising route to valorize CO(2) into energy-rich fuels and chemical feedstocks, yet the intrinsic thermodynamic and kinetic barriers necessitate catalysts that combine high activity, selectivity, and durability. Recent breakthroughs in materials...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationships between sporadic and repetitive non-suicidal self-injury and mental disorders among first-year college students: results from the World Mental Health International College Student Initiative]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings offer unique insights into the temporal order between NSSI and mental disorders. Further work exploring the mechanism underlying these associations will pave the way for early identification and intervention of both NSSI and mental disorders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pilot Study: Minimally Invasive Hyoid Suspension Lift: A Case Series and Technical Description]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The MIHS lift appears to offer a low-morbidity, natural-appearing option for neck contouring by minimizing invasiveness. Although early outcomes are promising, further validation is needed. This technique may be useful for individuals prone to hypertrophic scarring (eg, Asian patients).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Space-time graded-index interfaces and related chirping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Space-time modulated systems have recently emerged as a powerful platform for dynamic electromagnetic processing in both space and time. Most of the related research so far has assumed abrupt parameter profiles. This paper extends the field to generalized graded-index (GRIN) interfaces, which are both more practical than ideal profiles and offer new avenues for wave manipulations. It presents an exact solution for wave propagation across arbitrary space-time modulated GRIN interfaces and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiation-Associated Breast Angiosarcoma Versus Recurrent Invasive Ductal Carcinoma After Partial Mastectomy: A Diagnostic Dilemma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Postradiation angiosarcoma (PRAS) of the breast occurs after irradiation. It is categorized separately from primary angiosarcoma (PAS) in the 2019 World Health Organization classification of tumors. PRAS diagnosis is challenging owing to its occurrence in circumstances similar to breast cancer recurrence, thus complicating cytomorphological analysis. In Japan, breast-conserving therapy is prevalent, with postoperative radiation therapy often employed to mitigate recurrence risk. Given that the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrathyroidal Thymic Carcinoma With Arterial Invasion and Presumed Poor Tolerance to Cerebral Ischemia Safely Treated With Intraoperative Carotid Artery Protection With a Covered Stent: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This report demonstrates the effectiveness of covered stents in surgery for a patient with thyroid cancer suspected of carotid artery invasion and poor tolerance to cerebral ischemia. Covered stents allowed safe management of blood vessels while maintaining blood flow, potentially expanding their applicability in head and neck tumor surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum Speedups for Multiproposal MCMC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiproposal Markov chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) algorithms choose from multiple proposals to generate their next chain step in order to sample from challenging target distributions more efficiently. However, on classical machines, these algorithms require 𝒪 ( P ) target evaluations for each Markov chain step when choosing from P proposals. Recent work demonstrates the possibility of quadratic quantum speedups for one such multiproposal MCMC algorithm. After generating P proposals, this quantum...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of biogenic silver nanoparticles using <em>Piper chaba</em> leaf extract for dual-functional applications: Hg(ii) sensing and catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study reports the green synthesis of biogenic silver nanoparticles (AgNPs) for dual applications in mercury (Hg^(2+)) sensing and catalysis. AgNP formation was visually confirmed by a color change and corroborated by a surface plasmon resonance band at 441 nm in UV-vis spectra. FTIR spectroscopy, EDX, TGA, and DLS analyses confirmed phytochemical capping. XRD revealed a face-centered cubic structure with a crystallite size of 17 nm, while SEM and TEM showed monodispersed spherical AgNPs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Projected population exposure to dangerous heat stress around Lake Victoria under a high-end climate change scenario]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent global temperature increases and extreme heat events have raised concerns about their impact on health, particularly in vulnerable regions like Africa. This study assesses future heat stress and population exposure in the Lake Victoria region under the high-emission SSP5-8.5 climate change scenario, using a convection-permitting climate model, heat stress indices (humidex and heat index), and high-resolution population projections under the high-emission SSP5-8.5 scenario, interpreted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perampanel-associated exacerbation of de novo psychosis and lateralized rhythmic delta activity: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The observed LRDA in this case may represent cerebral dysregulation, possibly induced by PER, concurrent with the worsening of psychiatric sequelae. Psychosis during PER treatment could signify underlying brain dysfunction, highlighting the potential utility of EEG monitoring in managing these patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights into recent findings and therapeutic potential of nonhistone lactylation in cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lactylation, a recently identified post-translational modification, has become a crucial regulatory mechanism beyond its conventional metabolic role. Unlike histone lactylation, which regulates gene expression, nonhistone lactylation directly acts on effector proteins involved in processes such as signal transduction, metabolic reprogramming, and DNA damage repair. This article systematically reviews how nonhistone lactylation regulates biological processes related to cancer via mechanisms such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative assessment of fracture healing using patient-specific CT finite element analysis: A novel approach to external fixation management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated the possibility of implementing postoperative weight-bearing management among patients with external fixation based on quantitative assessment using patient-specific CT finite element analysis rather than relying solely on clinical experience. Further accumulation of clinical data is expected to improve analytical accuracy and contribute to the establishment of fracture treatments based on more objective indicators.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Paddling through palpitations: when genes, myocardial inflammation and exercise collide-a case report of arrhythmogenic cardiomyopathy in a young competitive rower]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Arrhythmogenic cardiomyopathy (ACM) is characterized by fibrofatty replacement of myocardium, predisposing to ventricular arrhythmias and sudden cardiac death. Arrhythmogenic cardiomyopathy is often linked to desmosomal gene mutations, particularly PKP2, which encodes plakophilin-2, a key structural protein in cardiac intercalated discs. In individuals with PKP2 mutations, exercise has been shown to accelerate disease progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DACN-Based Switchable Fluorescent Click Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The copper-free switchable fluorescent click reaction using 4,8-diazacyclononyne (DACN) and 3-azido-7-alkoxycoumarin was realized and applied to the conjugation of biomolecules. This new method using DACN has characteristics superior to those of the corresponding azadibenzocyclooctyne (DBCO) derivative in terms of fluorescence quantum yield and photostability under UV light irradiation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40994235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research Metrics: An Overview]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Editor's note: This is the 29th article in a series on clinical research by nurses coordinated by the Heilbrunn Family Center for Research Nursing at Rockefeller University. The series is designed to be used as a resource for nurses to understand the concepts and principles essential to research. Each column will present the concepts that underpin evidence-based practice-from research design to data interpretation-and most can be read without knowledge of the preceding articles. To see all the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40993876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CSF-1 Receptor Blockade in Pulmonary Arterial Hypertension - Keeping Macrophages in Check?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of 17α-estradiol treatment on endocrine system revealed by single-nucleus transcriptomic sequencing of hypothalamus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated 17α-estradiol's effects on aged hypothalamic physiological activity via long-term administration. Single-nucleus transcriptomic sequencing (snRNA-seq) was performed on pooled hypothalami from each group: aged male Norway brown rats treated with 17α-estradiol (O.T), aged controls (O), and young controls (Y). Supervised clustering of neurons (based on neuropeptides/receptors) evaluated subtype responses to aging and 17α-estradiol. Aging-induced elevation of neuronal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FGF21 acting on the noradrenergic nervous system protects against influenza virus infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The hormone fibroblast growth factor 21 (FGF21) is induced in murine liver in response to both bacterial and viral infection. In this report, we show that FGF21 is induced by infection with influenza virus in both humans and mice. Mice lacking FGF21 had decreased food intake, body weight, and body temperature compared to wild-type mice following influenza virus inoculation, indicating reduced tolerance to the infection. Conversely, pharmacologic administration of FGF21 after viral infection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glycan microarray analysis of <em>Candida</em>-related antibodies in human and mice sera guides biomarker discovery and vaccine development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Invasive, high-mortality yeast infections caused by pathogenic Candida species are the most common fungal nosocomial bloodstream infections. The World Health Organization (WHO) has called for improved prevention and diagnostic strategies for fungal pathogens. Here, we demonstrate that Candida-related antibodies can be detected using glycan microarrays containing synthetic glycans to guide the discovery of oligosaccharide epitopes for diagnostics and vaccine design. Pure, synthetic mannans and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of Amputation Following Severe Pediatric Lower Extremity Injury: Application of the Mangled Lower Extremity (MangLE) Score in a Pediatric Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundSevere lower extremity injuries in pediatric patients present significant challenges for surgeons deciding between repair and amputation. A novel scoring system, the MangLE score, has been developed to identify adult patients who are unlikely to require amputation after severe lower extremity injury. This study sought to evaluate the predictive ability of the MangLE score in pediatric patients.MethodsA retrospective analysis was conducted using the 2013-2021 American College of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantifying viral load and characterizing virus diversity in wildlife samples with target enrichment sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metagenomics is a powerful tool for characterizing viruses, with broad applications across diverse disciplines, from understanding the ecology and evolutionary history of viruses to identifying causative agents of emerging outbreaks with unknown aetiology. Additionally, metagenomic data contain valuable information about the amount of virus present within samples (i.e. viral load), which can provide insights into transmission potential, time since infection and, in turn, epidemic trajectories....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Motor Competence and Response Time in Portuguese Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explores the association between motor competence (MC) and response time (RT) in schoolchildren. 251 participants (mean age 14.58 ± 3.07 years) completed assessments over two sessions using standardized procedures. MC was evaluated through the Motor Competence Assessment, which includes stability, locomotor, and manipulative skills, while RT was measured using a structured reaction task. Pearson correlations and multiple linear regression analyses examined the relationships between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporary threshold shifts in the Eastern painted turtle (Chrysemys picta picta) in response to narrowband underwater noise exposures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sound is important to many turtle species, emphasizing the need for data-driven predictive models of acoustic impacts of noise pollution. Freshwater turtles experience temporary threshold shifts (TTSs) and data of the specific frequencies and duration inducing hearing loss are critical for TTS modeling. Three adult female Eastern painted turtles (Chrysemys picta pica) were exposed to 1/6-octave-narrowband noise centered at 200 or 400 Hz at varying durations and amplitudes (received sound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural encoding of speech-in-noise in neonates: A frequency-following response study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background noise disrupts the neural encoding of speech, making it particularly challenging to extract a speaker's voice from competing voices-an ability crucial for successful speech processing and communication. This disruption occurs across all ages, with infants and older adults being particularly vulnerable. In infancy, when robust speech encoding is fundamental for native language acquisition, the presence of background noise could have significant consequences for the development of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antioxidant Treatment and the Chance to Conceive in Men Seeking Fertility Care: The SUMMER Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This randomized clinical trial found that ongoing pregnancy rates did not improve with the antioxidant supplement compared with a placebo. Therefore, the investigators do not support its use in men seeking fertility care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[School Provision of Universal Free Meals and Blood Pressure Outcomes Among Youths]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This cohort study of schools matched to child and adolescent patient medical records from a large network of community health organizations found that school participation in the Community Eligibility Provision was associated with a net reduction in blood pressure outcomes. These findings add to mounting evidence that universal free school meals may be associated with improved child health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Olfactory Dysfunction After SARS-CoV-2 Infection in the RECOVER Adult Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study of RECOVER-Adult participants, self-reported change or loss in smell or taste was an accurate signal of verified hyposmia, but a high rate of hyposmia among those with no reported change or loss was also observed. Formal smell testing may be considered in those with prior SARS-CoV-2 infection to diagnose occult hyposmia and counsel patients about risks.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reflections on Medical Trainee Unions and Health Care Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atropine or Cyclopentolate to Diagnose Premyopia in Preschool Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This study found that use of atropine for cycloplegia in preschool children was associated with less myopic refraction compared with cyclopentolate and may potentially avoid overestimation of premyopia prevalence; however, this investigation did not evaluate each cycloplegic agent in the same children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Limitations in Artificial Intelligence-Driven Patient-Centered Cancer Nursing Research-Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-Dose Aspirin for Individualized Cancer Prevention in Older Adults: A Secondary Analysis of the ASPREE Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The findings of this study suggest significant heterogeneity in the effectiveness of LDA for cancer prevention among older adults, with CHIP identified as a key predictive factor. Further study is needed to fully understand the implications of these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Respectful Communication for Pediatric Patients With Overweight-Insights and Next Steps-Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An instrument to facilitate value-driven conversations on surveillance technology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundThe application of care technology is complex, and has an impact on all stakeholders. A specific issue with surveillance technologies is the resulting ethical dilemmas. These dilemmas often touch on people's values, which arise from their perspectives and determine their attitudes and behaviour. One of the prerequisites for successful stakeholder involvement is knowing and acknowledging their values. Schwartz's theory of human values has been empirically tested and facilitates the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age and sex influence bleeding score in mild VWF deficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DrugCombo: an informatics bridge for anticancer drug combination Phase I trial design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The promise of combinational drug therapies for cancer is hindered by the high failure rate of Phase I trials, perhaps attributable to the inavailability of an integrated source of toxicity data for cancer drugs to aid clinicians and biostatisticians designing trials. To this end, we developed DrugCombo, a knowledge base that integrates drug toxicity along with other data for single drugs and drug combinations from various sources. We extracted drug toxicity data from drug labels using the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A new database of chestnut DNA fingerprints for genetic diversity assessment, precise varietal identification, and traceability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The European chestnut (Castanea sativa Mill., Fagaceae) is ecologically and economically important, particularly in countries like Italy, Greece, Spain, and Turkey, where it supports rural economies and ecosystems. Accurate varietal recognition is crucial for managing chestnut groves but is hindered by the limitations of traditional methods, which require costly expertise and struggle to identify young, dormant, or scion trees. Recent advances in molecular tools, particularly single nucleotide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BrAPI v2: real-world applications for data integration and collaboration in the breeding and genetics community]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Population growth and the impacts of climate change are placing increasing pressure on global agriculture and breeding programmes. Recent advancements in phenotyping techniques, genotyping technologies, and predictive modelling are accelerating genetic gains in breeding programmes, helping researchers and breeders develop improved crops more efficiently. However, these advancements have also led to an overwhelming torrent of fragmented data, creating significant challenges in data integration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A review on Gene Ontology evaluations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The analysis of the large and heterogeneous datasets that characterize modern biology demands systems capable of representing biological knowledge in a formal, standardized manner. The most widely used structured vocabulary in molecular biology and biomedicine is the Gene Ontology (GO). Although employed in many different data analysis tasks, its main application is in the functional annotation of gene products and the subsequent functional enrichment analysis of large gene/protein datasets...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NK92 cells stably transfected with CD16 are efficient against multiple myeloma cells <em>ex vivo</em> and <em>in vivo</em>, especially if combined with daratumumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adoptive cell therapy and the use of monoclonal antibodies are two therapeutic modalities implemented in the treatment of multiple myeloma (MM). In this study, we combined the anti-CD38 therapeutic mAb daratumumab with different types of NK cells, leveraging the antibody-dependent cell-mediated cytotoxicity (ADCC) performed by these immune cells. Daratumumab was initially combined with activated and expanded NK cells (eNK), resulting in significant cytotoxic activity against human MM cell lines....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors and long COVID risk in patients with depression: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In adult patients with depression, SSRIs compared with non-SSRI antidepressants were associated with a lower risk of long COVID. These results offer preliminary evidence that SSRIs may help prevent long COVID in high‑risk populations and warrant further preclinical and clinical investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of Staging Systems for Non-head and Neck Cutaneous Squamous Cell Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both systems performed similarly in predicting poor outcomes in non-HNCSCCs. Specificity and NPV were high, sensitivity and PPV were low, and c-indices were moderately high. As the c-indices were comparable to those seen in the HNCSCC literature, it is reasonable to use the BWH and AJCC8 staging systems for tumors located off the head and neck. However, further refinement of CSCC staging systems is needed to improve prognostication.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Group-based trajectory modeling identifies distinct glycemic patterns predictive of mortality in aneurysmal subarachnoid hemorrhage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Distinct glycemic trajectories following aSAH were independently associated with 90-day mortality. Dynamic glucose trends, particularly rising-to-plateau and highly fluctuating pattern, have prognostic significance and may inform individualized glycemic management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retraction Note: The Telehealth chain: a framework for secure and transparent telemedicine transactions on the blockchain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigate the potential inhibitors of sphingosine kinase 1 (SphK1) with molecular dynamics and artificial intelligence drug design methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONTEXT: Sphingosine kinase 1 (SphK1) is a sphingosine kinase that can catalyze the phosphorylation of sphingosine to generate sphingosine-1-phosphate. The J-type channel of SPHK1 plays an important role in processes such as cell signaling. Therefore, this study aims to investigate the interaction mechanism between Epidanshenspiroketallactone, PF-543, and SPHK1 in the J-type channel, and to design new small molecules using AI Drug Design (AIDD). Molecular dynamics (MD) simulations reveal that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forming capability of advanced customized jetting additive manufacturing for restorations with different margin morphologies and surface textures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ACJ restorations exhibited lower RMS values than CAD/CAM in both non-marginal region and marginal region with heavy-chamfer, chamfer, and BOPT margins. Circle textures have the highest accuracy and larger aperture improves printing accuracy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NCBI Orthologs: Public Resource and Scalable Method for Computing High-Precision Orthologs Across Eukaryotic Genomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orthologs are fundamental for enabling comparative genomics analyses that further our understanding of eukaryotic biology. The unprecedented increase in the availability of high-quality eukaryotic genomes necessitates scalable and accurate methods for orthology inference. The National Center for Biotechnology Information (NCBI) developed "NCBI Orthologs", a resource and a computational pipeline designed to meet this challenge within the NCBI RefSeq framework. This system integrates protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of singlet excited state dynamics of bacteriochlorophyll a in Fenna-Matthews-Olson (FMO) complex by PscB, a subunit with an intrinsically disordered region in Chlorobaculum tepidum reaction center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Modulation of the chlorophyll singlet state by protein environment is a key aspect of photosynthesis and light-harvesting in biological systems. This modulation affects excited-state dynamics, energy transfer efficiency, and photochemical reactivity. The PscB subunit of the reaction center (RC) of green sulfur bacterium Cba. tepidum contains an iron-sulfur cluster domain that is involved in light-driven electron transfer and a domain of intrinsically disordered region. The latter seemingly coil...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive analysis of the clinical feature, myeloid neoplasm-related gene mutation profiles and T cell diversity acquired pure red cell aplasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study described the clinical features, mutation landscape and TCR rearrangement profile in a relatively larger PRCA cohort, which may contribute to the clear perception of PRCA and the development of more potent treatment approaches.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of a potent ROR1 inhibitor using μs-scale MD simulations, wt-metadynamics, and absolute binding free energy calculations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONTEXT: Receptor tyrosine kinase-like orphan receptor 1 (ROR1) is a cancer-associated pseudokinase with low expression in normal adult tissues but elevated levels in various malignancies, making it a promising therapeutic target. Among ~ 4 million compounds, CHEMBL3926946 emerged as the most promising candidate, demonstrating a persistent binding pose and a well-defined free energy basin. Well-tempered metadynamics (wt-MetaD) revealed a deep minimum of 26.00 ± 2.44 kcal/mol, indicating a highly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing Self-Management Coping in Urinary Incontinence: Psychometric Evaluation of the UI-SMCSI in Middle-Aged Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION AND HYPOTHESIS: Urinary incontinence (UI) significantly impairs women's quality of life and often leads to the adoption of self-management coping strategies. This study aimed to develop and validate the UI Self-Management Coping Strategies Instrument (UI-SMCSI) to assess coping strategies in women with UI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RIPK1 autophosphorylation at S161 mediates cell death and inflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RIPK1 regulates cell death and inflammation and has been implicated in the pathogenesis of inflammatory diseases. RIPK1 autophosphorylation promotes cell death induction; however, the underlying mechanisms and the role of specific autophosphorylation sites remain elusive. Using knock-in mouse models, here we show that S161 autophosphorylation has a critical physiological function in RIPK1-mediated cell death and inflammation. S161N substitution partially suppressed RIPK1-mediated catalytic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Combined Neuroanatomy, Ex Vivo Imaging, and Immunohistochemistry Defined MRI Mask for the Human Paraventricular Nucleus of the Thalamus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The paraventricular nucleus of the thalamus (PVT) is an evolutionarily conserved midline thalamic structure known to contribute to arousal, interoceptive states, and motivated behaviors. Yet, a consensus anatomical definition of the human PVT across tissue-based and MRI-based approaches remains elusive, thereby limiting reliable translation between its cellular characteristics and in vivo functional connectivity. To address this challenge, we describe a histologically informed PVT segmentation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming Care: The Impact of COVID-19 on Telehealth Adoption in U.S. Home Health Care Agencies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The COVID-19 pandemic accelerated the adoption of telehealth in home health care (HHC). However, the extent and sustainability of telehealth use among Medicare-certified HHC agencies remain unclear. Objective: To examine the adoption and utilization of telehealth modalities among U.S. HHC agencies following the COVID-19 pandemic. Methods: A nationally representative survey of 474 Medicare-certified HHC agencies assessed telehealth use, modalities, and purposes, comparing adoption...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanism of Typical Atrial Flutter in a Patient After Cardiac Transplant: Functional Slowing From Geometric Distortion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Atrial flutter and atrial fibrillation occur after orthotopic heart transplant (OHT) in 25% of patients. Hemodynamic and medication restrictions in this unique population limit treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated With Rehabilitative Home Exercise Adherence Among Older Adults With Chronic Back Pain: Secondary Analysis of a Randomized Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among this sample of older adults with CLBP, baseline patient characteristics did not predict adherence to home exercise recommendations. Further, adherence was not associated with clinically meaningful change in disability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neurobehavioral Therapy Is Associated With Improvements in Social Functioning in Patients With Functional Seizures and Traumatic Brain Injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION AND IMPLICATIONS FOR PRACTICE: Seizure worry appears to be an important component of social functioning in patients with FS and TBI and could be a worthwhile target of intervention. Our results suggest that multimodal NBT may be associated with improvements in aspects of social functioning for these patients. Those with TBI who were treated with SMC (no NBT) displayed no symptomatic or social benefit. This study highlights the importance of assessing and considering treatments for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of Systematic JAK2V617F Screening in 996 Patients With Venous Thromboembolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capturing frailty in cirrhosis: Bridging disciplinary gaps, clinical decision-making, and research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perspectives on Dissemination of Sleep Knowledge and Standards Across Wider Europe and Beyond, the ESRS Assembly of National Sleep Societies Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sleep medicine and research have profound roots and traditions in Europe. Medical and health structure standards, including those related to sleep medicine, are currently regulated by respective national organisations within the European Union. However, despite this fact, the organisation and practice of sleep medicine are far from harmonious across countries, being highly dependent on national medical systems. Moreover, there is a need to involve countries outside the European Union, especially...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metal-Organic Cages for Ultrafast Photocatalytic Synthesis of Hydrogen Peroxide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the realm of photocatalytic production, discrete metallo-organic cages have emerged as promising photocatalysts. However, their performance is often constrained by limited substrate accessibility and sluggish oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) kinetics. Herein, we designed and synthesized two novel nonnoble metallo-cages, S1 and S2, and evaluated their photocatalytic activities. Benefit from the high structural stability, low exciton binding energy (52.9 meV), ultrafast intramolecular electron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lymph Node Ratio Predicts Adjuvant Chemotherapy Benefit in Esophageal Squamous Cell Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that LNR is a valuable marker for identifying ESCC patients who would benefit from postoperative adjuvant chemotherapy. A threshold LNR of 11% can help personalize treatment strategies, and patients with higher LNRs may require more intensive approaches like chemoradiotherapy to improve survival. Further prospective studies are needed to validate these results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variational autoencoder-based deep learning and radiomics for predicting pathologic complete response to neoadjuvant chemoimmunotherapy in locally advanced esophageal squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We constructed a DLR model to predict pCR in nCIT treated LA-ESCC patients, which demonstrated superior performance compared to the DL model.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENO2 regulates CD4<sup>+</sup> T cell pyroptosis via mitochondrial ROS to drive immunological non-response in HIV infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Approximately 10-40% of patients with acquired immune deficiency syndrome (AIDS) fail to restore the number of CD4^(+) T cells after antiretroviral therapy (ART). They are referred to as immunological non-responders (INRs) and have increased morbidity and mortality of AIDS and non-AIDS events. Pyroptosis is one of the key factors driving CD4^(+) T cell death in human immunodeficiency virus (HIV) infection, but its relationship with immune reconstitution and the underlying mechanisms is poorly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic airborne mycobiome in the metropolitan city transit system is driven by seasonality and station type]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Subway transit systems serve as the primary transportation mode in metropolitan areas. The quality of the airway in transit plays a crucial role in human health as commuters and workers are exposed to microbes transmitted from passengers and circulated within built environments. The diversity and dynamics of bacterial microbiome in these environments have been relatively well studied. However, the fungal communities remain poorly investigated. In this study, we conducted a year-long...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Respiratory syncytial virus phosphoprotein has NTPase and helicase-like activities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Respiratory syncytial virus (RSV), a non-segmented, negative-sense RNA virus (NNSV) in the family Pneumoviridae, represents a significant global health burden causing severe lower respiratory tract infections in infants and immunocompromised adults. While RNA helicases are essential for viral replication through their RNA remodeling functions, the presence of such enzymatic activities in RSV remains unclear. Here, we reveal that the RSV phosphoprotein (P), despite lacking canonical helicase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Contact-Electro-Catalysis and Photocatalysis via TiO<sub>2</sub>@PTFE Composites for Efficient N<sub>2</sub> to NH<sub>3</sub> Conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Catalytic nitrogen fixation from N(2) and water under mild conditions offers a sustainable NH(3) synthesis route. Herein, we report a synergistic nitrogen fixation strategy combining contact-electro-catalysis (CEC) with photocatalysis via one-step in situ hydrothermally synthesized TiO(2) @PTFE catalyst, and achieved an activity of 133.6 µmol g^(-1) h^(-1). It represents 10.9-fold and 7.5-fold enhancements over pristine TiO(2) and PTFE, respectively, outperforming current CEC systems and many...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On-Site Visualized Periodontitis Screening via Dual-Signal H<sub>2</sub>S Probe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Periodontitis is a destructive disease that causes irreversible damage to periodontal supporting tissues, posing a serious threat to patients' oral health. Given the insidious nature of periodontal tissue destruction, early diagnosis of periodontitis is crucial. Salivary hydrogen sulfide (H(2)S) has been identified as a potential biomarker for periodontitis monitoring. However, existing detection methods struggle to precisely locate the source of H(2)S release within the oral cavity, making it...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence and Nuclear Weapons Proliferation: The Technological Arms Race for (In)visibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A robust nonproliferation regime has contained the spread of nuclear weapons to just nine states. Yet, emerging and disruptive technologies are reshaping the landscape of nuclear risks, presenting a critical juncture for decision makers. This article lays out the contours of an overlooked but intensifying technological arms race for nuclear (in)visibility, driven by the interplay between proliferation-enabling technologies (PETs) and detection-enhancing technologies (DETs). We argue that the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using network pharmacology and molecular docking to investigate the mechanism of action of the active components of agarwood moxibustion therapy for the treatment of chronic atrophic gastritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic atrophic gastritis (CAG) is a long-term inflammatory condition of the gastric mucosa characterized by glandular atrophy, intestinal metaplasia and reduced acid secretion, often considered a precancerous lesion of the stomach. This study utilized a combined network pharmacology and molecular docking approach to elucidate the mechanisms of moxibustion therapy against CAG. Disease-related targets were retrieved from GeneCards, OMIM, PharmaGkb, TTD and DrugBank, while moxibustion's active...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nursing Professional Development Role Expansion: Progression in a Large Hospital System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neighborhood enrichment for the identification of antigen-specific T-cell receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding T-cell receptor (TCR) specificity is not only essential for fundamental research, but could open up novel avenues for diagnostics, cancer immunotherapy, and the targeted treatment of autoimmune diseases. The immune system responds to challenges through groups of T-cells with similar TCR sequences. In recent years, searching for TCRs with an enrichment of similar sequences - neighbors - in a TCR repertoire has become a standard procedure for antigen-specific TCR identification. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of latent tuberculosis infection in older adults: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The prevalence of LTBI is relatively high amongst older adults, emphasising the high burden of undetected infection in this population. Future research integrating cost-effectiveness analyses and intervention studies is needed to further explore the feasibility of population-based screening and prevention strategies to promote TB prevention and control.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Home Treatment of Childhood Illnesses Prior to Seeking Formal Care: A Cross-Sectional Study at Different Health Care Levels in Ghana]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The discrepancy between self-reported antibiotic use and antibiotic inhibition suggests a lack of awareness about medication identification and appropriate use. This presents a challenge for clinicians in obtaining an accurate treatment history, which is highly relevant to the timely diagnosis and treatment of the illness in the facility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methadone Blockade of Inward Rectifier Potassium Current Promotes Both Early and Delayed Repolarization Arrhythmias: Mechanistic Insights From Computational Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Methadone promotes both early and delayed repolarization arrhythmias. Early repolarization may be responsible for methadone-related deaths occurring mainly during sleep and occurring more often in men. Blocking I(K1) can work synergistically with other channel blockers to disproportionately increase arrhythmia propensity, greatly increasing methadone's risk when it is combined with other proarrhythmic drugs or under disease conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic Insights Into Depression Induced by Tuberculosis via Mediating Roles of Interleukins: Evidence From Mendelian Randomization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Interleukin-1R2 may mediate depressive symptoms in tuberculosis patients, potentially through specific inhibition of interleukin-1-related inflammatory signalling. These findings elucidate genetic mechanisms underlying tuberculosis-depression comorbidity and suggest novel targets for preventive and therapeutic interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Static disorder-induced renormalization of polariton group velocity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Molecular exciton-polaritons exhibit long-range, ultrafast propagation, yet recent experiments have reported far slower propagation than expected. In this work, we implement a nonperturbative approach to quantify how static energetic disorder renormalizes polariton group velocity in strongly coupled microcavities. The method requires no exact diagonalization or master equation propagation and depends only on measurable parameters: the mean exciton energy and its probability distribution, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Importance of basic science and research training for the future generation of cardiologists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advances in the battle against cardiovascular diseases depend upon continuously translating emerging scientific knowledge from preclinical studies and clinical trials into innovative and effective therapeutic strategies. Over the past three decades, molecular and cellular biology have undergone a profound transformation, and large-scale, single-cell, and multi-omics studies have enabled investigations on cardiac disease mechanisms with unprecedented precision. However, these rapid advancements...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drug-coated vs non-drug-coated devices for femoropopliteal artery interventions: long-term outcomes of the SAFE-PAD study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this final report from the SAFE-PAD study, there was no evidence of long-term mortality risk associated with DCDs used for femoropopliteal revascularization. The SAFE-PAD study helped inform the reversal of regulatory warnings against routine DCD use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reprogramming Stars #24: Pluripotency and Oncogenic Transformation: A Series of Intermingling Events-An Interview with Dr. Fabrice Lavial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural and mechanistic insights into symmetry conversion in plant GORK K+ channel regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[GORK is a shaker-like potassium channel in plants that contains ankyrin (ANK) repeats. In guard cells, activation of GORK causes K+ efflux, reducing turgor pressure and closing stomata. However, how GORK is regulated remains largely elusive. Here, we solved the cryo-EM structure of Arabidopsis GORK, revealing an unusual symmetry reduction (from C4 to C2) feature within its tetrameric assembly. This symmetry reduction in GORK channel is driven by ANK dimerization, which disrupts the coupling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Static and Dynamic Effects of Stroke Onset on Depressive Symptoms in Middle-Aged and Older Adults: Evidence Across 21 Countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This research underscores the complex relationship between stroke and depressive symptoms, highlighting the need to further identify underlying mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Illustrating an Adaptive Prespecification Framework for Observational Research: Target Trial Emulations Comparing Immunomodulator Treatments for COVID-19]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rigid prespecification can be impractical for noninterventional studies using secondary datasets, where data-driven flexibility is often required. Using target trial emulations comparing immunomodulator treatments for COVID-19, we piloted an adaptive strategy that accommodates warranted mid-course refinements within a prespecified framework. Our preregistered protocol outlined an initial study plan along with predetermined diagnostic thresholds and contingencies. Implementation proceeded through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Barriers and Facilitators to Women's Careers in Academic Cardiology: A Multicenter Qualitative Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Professional barriers remain for women in academic cardiology, fundamentally linked to the conflict between personal values and the culture of their division. Academic cardiology divisions committed to gender equity should align policies with practice to increase both women's representation as well as success in cardiology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intracranial Occlusion in Cryptogenic Stroke Is Not Predictive of Recurrent Ischemic Stroke: A Propensity-Score Matched Analysis of the Cardiac Abnormalities in Stroke Prevention and Risk of Recurrence Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Intracranial occlusion in patients with embolic stroke of undetermined source is not associated with a greater risk of recurrence when compared with patients without an intracranial occlusion. There was no difference in rate of recurrent stroke with anticoagulation when stratified by presence or absence of occlusion.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are We Striking the Right Balance? Finding a Sustainable Equilibrium in Academic Publishing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Are we truly synthesizing new evidence, or simply restating it?]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deciphering the Pharmacodynamic Basis of Biyan Qingdu Granules: Integrated key Pharmacodynamic Components Identification, Multi-Tissue Distribution, and Metabolic Profiling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biyan Qingdu Granules (BYQD) is a traditional Chinese medicine (TCM) formulation used to treat symptoms associated with increased secretion during nasopharyngeal carcinoma (NPC) radiotherapy. However, a comprehensive investigation into its pharmacodynamic material basis has not been conducted. This study presents a method that integrates UHPLC-HRMS and UHPLC-MS/HRMS with network pharmacology to investigate the pharmacodynamic components, multi-tissue distribution and biotransformation processes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40996023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights into the Lowest Excited State of Anthracene: Kerr-Gated UV Resonance Raman Spectroscopy (S<sub>1</sub> ← S<sub>0</sub>) with Tunable Excitation and DFT Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present the first, well-resolved Raman spectrum of anthracene, a model system of polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons, in resonance with the first electronic state. Until now, the autofluorescence associated with the S(1) ← S(0) transition had impeded the characterization of anthracene's S(1) state through resonance Raman. To overcome this limitation, we employ state-of-the-art Kerr-gated UVRR spectroscopy with tunable excitation for effectively suppressing the UV-excited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40995993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250925152035&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>