<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:36:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptual metacognition and self-esteem: the role of feedback valence in local and global monitoring bias]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previous studies suggest that individuals with low self-esteem tend to undervalue themselves, a tendency that may reflect a metacognitive monitoring bias, which in turn can be shaped by feedback valence. However, research specifically exploring how self-esteem and feedback valence affect metacognitive monitoring remains scarce. Through three experiments, the study revealed that individuals tend to exhibit an underestimation bias in perceptual metacognitive monitoring. However, compared to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence-assisted ultrasound screening for breast cancer in China: a prospective, clustered, controlled, population-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AI-assisted ultrasound screening significantly increases the detection rate of early breast cancers. Trial registration This study is registered at ClinicalTrials.gov under the number NCT06521788 (Initial Release Date: 07/22/2024).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of the BFR-7211 on lower limb muscle strength in older adults: A randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A four-week massage chair-based PNF stretching program significantly improved lower limb strength, physical function, and perceived health in older adults. This intervention offers a safe, accessible, and effective strategy for enhancing musculoskeletal health and reducing fall risk in older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Production of chemicals by metabolically engineered Escherichia coli]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Escherichia coli is increasingly employed for chemical production, with its industrial competitiveness now depending on both the expansion of its molecular repertoire through first-in-class pathways and achieving best-in-class titer, rate, and yield (TRY). Recent milestones include the first demonstration of producing aromatic homopolyester and poly(ester amide)s from glucose using engineered E. coli. To optimally maximize TRY, systems metabolic engineering leverages diverse tools such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acupuncture-Related Therapies for Primary Dysmenorrhea: A Systematic Review and Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Primary dysmenorrhea (PD) is characterized by a cramping pain in the lower abdomen during menstruation. Acupuncture-related therapy is frequently used to treat patients with PD. We conducted a network meta-analysis to compare the efficacy and safety of acupuncture-related therapies based on Korean and Chinese clinical practice guidelines. Methods: We searched 10 databases from their inception to November 1, 2024, including the Cochrane Central Register of Controlled Trials, Embase,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Logical Exploration of Cinnamoyl-Containing Nonribosomal Peptides via Metabologenomic Targeting and Regulator Overexpression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A targeted method for discovering cinnamoyl-containing nonribosomal peptides (CCNPs), a unique class of bioactive compounds, was devised by using cinnamoyl isomerase, a key enzyme in the biosynthesis of the cinnamoyl moiety, as a genome mining probe. A total of 39 hit strains were obtained, including 35 from polymerase chain reaction-based screening of the in-house bacterial library (2.5% of 1400 strains) targeting the cinnamoyl isomerase-encoding gene and 4 from the genome mining of online...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The noncoding circular RNA <em>circHomer1</em> regulates synaptic development and experience-dependent plasticity in the mouse visual cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circular RNAs (circRNAs) are closed-loop, single-stranded RNAs particularly enriched in the brain. Despite this enrichment, and evidence showing that synaptic development and plasticity alter their expression in vitro, circRNA regulation by and function in experience-dependent plasticity in vivo remain unexplored. Through transcriptome-wide analysis in juvenile mouse primary visual cortex (V1) following monocular deprivation (MD), we identified that the circular and the activity-dependent mRNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fostering sustainable infection prevention behaviors through organizational culture and psychological resources in healthcare settings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infection prevention is a critical aspect of healthcare, directly impacting patient safety and outcomes. Previous studies have investigated various individual factors influencing infection control behaviors; however, limited research has examined the combined impact of organizational culture, environmental factors, and self-efficacy. This study aims to explore the multidimensional determinants of infection prevention behaviors using the information-motivation-behavioral skills framework. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transformative Mechanical and Piezoelectric Properties in Organic-Inorganic Hybrid Materials for Biomedical Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic-inorganic hybrid materials are multifunctional composites that combine distinct organic and inorganic components to yield synergistic enhancements in properties such as mechanical strength and piezoelectric performance, resulting in performance that exceeds that of the individual materials. This review begins by examining organic-inorganic hybrid structures found in nature, particularly within biological systems, and highlights the historical development of synthetic hybrids inspired by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decision-making factors related to palliative care and hospice use in the community: a systematic review based on Andersen's behavioural model of health services use]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patient and caregiver characteristics, personal experience, communication context, knowledge, preferences, and physical condition were the key factors related to the decision to use palliative care and hospice. This study highlights the importance of addressing these factors to support informed and patient-centred decision-making in end-of-life care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Everyday norms have become more permissive over time and vary across cultures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Every social situation that people encounter in their daily lives comes with a set of unwritten rules about what behavior is considered appropriate or inappropriate. These everyday norms can vary across societies: some societies may have more permissive norms in general or for certain behaviors, or for certain behaviors in specific situations. In a preregistered survey of 25,422 participants across 90 societies, we map societal differences in 150 everyday norms and show that they can be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-term and long-term effects of vitamin D supplementation for preterm infants: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Meta-analysis conducted to evaluate the effectiveness of high-dose (≥800 IU/day) and low-dose (<800 IU/day) vitamin D supplementation on preterm infants. Study quality was evaluated using the Revised Cochrane risk-of-bias tool 2 for randomized trials. 21 studies included 1130 infants. Regarding short-term (before 40 weeks' postmenstrual age [PMA] or at discharge) outcomes, high-dose vitamin D supplementation was associated with increased serum 25-hydroxyvitamin D (25[OH]D) levels (mean...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of subretinal drusenoid deposit on retinal sensitivity in age-related macular degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective study aimed to assess the impact of subretinal drusenoid deposit (SDD), also known as reticular pseudodrusen, on retinal sensitivity (RS) in patients with intermediate age-related macular degeneration (iAMD) using microperimetry. Eyes meeting the modified criteria of iAMD, including SDD, and total drusen area greater than 0.50 mm² were included. The presence of SDD, as well as soft drusen (SD), and specific type of SDD (dot or ribbon) were determined through multimodal imaging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning approaches overcome imbalanced clinical data for intraoral free flap monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Free flap reconstruction is essential for treating intraoral defects; however, failure can lead to complex and prolonged complications. While various monitoring methods have been employed to prevent such situations, they are qualitative and sometimes unfamiliar to novices. The purpose of this study was to develop a user-friendly model using artificial intelligence that quantitatively represents flap status. We analyzed 1877 images from 131 patients who underwent free flap reconstruction for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asian Pacific Association of Gastroenterology task force recommendations on surveillance for <em>Helicobacter pylori</em> associated gastric premalignant conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These statements aim to provide a structured, evidence based surveillance framework for clinical practice in the Asia Pacific region, while also identifying priority areas for future research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amplification of electrochemical signal by moving interdigitated electrode array for highly sensitive detection of Alzheimer's disease markers in blood]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical biosensors are widely utilized in disease diagnosis due to their high sensitivity, low detection limits, and cost-effectiveness. However, conventional electrochemical ELISA (e-ELISA) measurements face several challenges and limitations, including limited analyte volume, reduced sensitivity, signal instability, and surface fouling. To overcome the limitations, we developed a novel vertically moving sensor system integrated with a laser-induced graphene metal interdigitated array...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced regenerative potential of human dental pulp stem cells for the pulp-dentin complex through coculture with iPSC-derived endothelial cells: An in vitro study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrated in vitro that coculturing hDPSCs with iPSC-ECs enhances both odontogenic and angiogenic differentiation compared to hDPSCs cultured alone. These findings highlight the potential of iPSC technology in regenerative endodontics and indicate a promising cell-based approach for future therapeutic applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biodegradation of low-density polyethylene microplastics by Fusarium and Penicillium strains isolated from agricultural soil mulched with polyethylene film]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The presence of low-density polyethylene (LDPE) in agricultural soils poses significant ecological risks due to its resistance to biodegradation. Despite the widespread use of polyethylene mulch, the potential of soil microorganisms to degrade LDPE microplastic particles (MPPs) remains underexplored. This study represents one of the first attempts to isolate and evaluate the LDPE MPP degradation potential of fungal strains isolated from agricultural soils exposed to polyethylene mulch. Four LDPE...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive mixed-methods usability evaluation of COVID-19 home test kits: focusing on effectiveness, efficiency, and satisfaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated COVID-19 home test kit usability focusing on effectiveness, efficiency, and satisfaction across diverse users and environments. Using a mixed-methods approach-including use analysis, user experience survey (n = 1045), and usability testing (n = 80) in South Korea-we identified a significant gap between high user satisfaction and actual performance. Despite positive satisfaction metrics (SUS score: 74.37 %), we observed concerns regarding effectiveness (29.9 % error rate) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adverse outcome pathway networks of microplastic ecotoxicity to aquatic organisms: A critical review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Numerous studies have documented the ecotoxicity of microplastics in aquatic organisms, yet the mechanistic pathways linking early molecular disturbances to higher-level biological outcomes remain poorly understood. In this paper, we conducted a comprehensive multi-level ecotoxicological review integrated with automated text-mining using AOP-helpFinder 3.0. This approach retrieved confidence scores for stressor-event and event-event relationships, enabling systematic identification of candidate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported outcomes of a randomized phase III clinical trial of adjuvant radiation versus chemoradiation in intermediate risk, stage I/IIA cervical cancer patients treated with initial radical hysterectomy and pelvic lymphadenectomy (NRG/GOG-0263)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: QOL declined in both groups after treatment initiation, with greater short-term deterioration in the RT + CIS group. By 36 weeks, QOL and other PROs returned to baseline in both groups. Neuropathy, GI/GU symptoms, and pain showed no significant differences between treatment arms over time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virtual Reality-Based Assessment of Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder and Comorbid Symptoms in Children: Framework Development and Standardization Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides empirical evidence on VR-derived movement variables that can inform the development of standardized methodologies for ADHD and comorbid behavior assessment. The identified metrics and their predictive patterns offer a basis for integrating VR-based measures into future research and clinical applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Paired snRNA-seq and scRNA-seq analysis of MASLD patients to identify early-stage markers for disease progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Significant molecular and immune alterations occur in disease progression of MASLD to MASH, reflecting both localized hepatic changes and systemic immune dysregulation. The identified transcriptomic signatures provide a promising tool for fibrosis prediction and monitoring, underscoring the need to target early disease mechanisms for improved diagnosis and therapeutic strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Secondary <em>N</em>-Methylamines via Reductive Amination of Aldehydes with <em>N</em>-Boc-<em>N</em>-Methylamine Using Me<sub>2</sub>SiHCl]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel protocol for the synthesis of secondary N-methylamines via reductive amination of aldehydes with N-Boc-N-methylamine has been developed, using Me(2)SiHCl as the reductant. The reaction proceeds through the formation of Boc-protected secondary N-methylamines, which undergo in situ Boc-deprotection facilitated by HCl generated during the initial reductive amination. This method features a broad substrate scope, efficiently accommodating a wide range of aldehydes and affording the desired...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effective strategies for typhoid conjugate vaccine delivery: Health and economic insights from the 2015 Kampala outbreak]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Typhoid fever remains a major public health threat in low- and middle-income countries (LMICs), where inadequate access to clean water and sanitation drives recurrent outbreaks. With antimicrobial resistance on the rise, the urgency of deploying preventive strategies such as typhoid conjugate vaccines (TCVs) have grown. In this study, we developed a dynamic compartmental model calibrated to the 2015 typhoid outbreak in Kampala, Uganda, to assess the health and economic outcomes of various...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and internal validation of the patient safety experience scale for inpatients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is an increasing need for a practical instrument that captures patient safety experiences from the inpatient perspective and is suitable for clinical application. This study aimed to develop a Patient Safety Experience Scale (PSES) reflecting inpatient safety indicators and to evaluate its reliability and validity. An initial pool of 90 items was generated through a literature review and qualitative interviews, from which 60 items were selected based on expert evaluation and content...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systematic review protocol: The effects of theory-based interventions for self-help practices in the management of mild to moderate depression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: This protocol outlines a planned systematic review to assess the effects of theory-based interventions for self-help practices in managing mild to moderate depression. Depression is a leading global cause of disability and contributes significantly to the worldwide burden. Self-help practices present promising avenues for care. When grounded in psychological theory, these interventions may offer a structured and effective approach to symptom management. However, their effectiveness...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the necessity of prophylactic lateral neck dissection in medullary thyroid carcinoma based on preoperative calcitonin levels: a multicenter retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Prophylactic LND did not significantly impact long-term oncologic outcomes in MTC patients without clinically evident lateral LN metastasis, even among those with elevated preoperative calcitonin levels above 200 pg/mL. Although prophylactic LND was associated with higher biochemical cure rates, this did not translate into reduced recurrence rates or improved survival. Routine prophylactic LND may not be necessary, and the decision to perform it should be carefully individualized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Slow magnetic relaxation in a trinuclear spin-crossover Co(II) compound with metal-metal bonding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the molecular spin-qubit properties of a rigid trinuclear cobalt complex, presenting the first example of spin-crossover in a compound with metal-metal bonds. Pulsed electron paramagnetic resonance spectroscopy provides deeper insight into the spin-qubit behaviour, including the spin-lattice and spin-spin relaxation times.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large Language Models Versus Human Readers in CAD-RADS 2.0 Categorization of Coronary CT Angiography Reports]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the accuracy of large language models (LLMs) in assigning Coronary Artery Disease Reporting and Data System (CAD-RADS) 2.0 categories and modifiers based on real-world coronary CT angiography (CCTA) reports and compared their accuracy with human readers. From 2752 eligible CCTA reports generated at an academic hospital between January and September 2024, 180 were randomly selected to fit a balanced distribution of categories and modifiers. The reference standard was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward personalized hepatocellular carcinoma treatment using liver MRI: predicting intratumoral tertiary lymphoid structure maturity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cephalometric differences between patients with REM- and NREM-Predominant OSA: implications for selecting surgical candidates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Anatomical factors, including nasal and maxillary width, hyoid bone position, and tongue length, are linked to OSA type. These findings may suggest that targeted treatments strategies, including MAD, MMA, genioglossus advancement, or transverse maxillary expansion, may be effective based on individual anatomical characteristics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation and Optimal Cutoff Value of the Japanese Society for Surgery of the Hand Score for Postoperative Satisfaction in Radial Polydactyly: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We noted a significant correlation between JSSH score and parental satisfaction in patients with radial polydactyly and established an optimal cutoff value of 18.5 points.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polycaprolactone Impregnated 3D Printed Nanohydroxyapatite for Sinus Augmentation: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dimensional stability of the augmented bone was comparable between the groups. However, group 3DPHA-PCL demonstrated inferior new bone formation and implant survival compared to group BB. Long-term follow-up is warranted to monitor the behavior of 3DPHA-PCL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imaging Features and Diagnostic Performance of US in Nonmass Lesions with Varying Clinical Indications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background The diagnostic performance of breast US for nonmass lesions (NML) is not well validated. Purpose To evaluate and compare the imaging features and diagnostic performance of US for NMLs across clinical indications. Materials and Methods This retrospective study included NMLs that underwent US-guided biopsy from January 2014 to February 2021. Lesions were also classified by their clinical indications as screening, diagnostic: work-up (DWU), or diagnostic: current breast cancer (DCBC)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying an Active Intermediate and Monitoring O─O Bond Formation in Water Oxidation by a Cobalt(III)-TAML Complex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A cobalt(III) -TAML complex, [(TAML)Co^(III)]^(-) (TAML = tetraamido macrocyclic ligand), catalyzes water oxidation using one-electron oxidants like cerium(IV) ammonium nitrate (CAN) or tris(4-bromophenyl)ammonium hexachloroantimonate radical cation (TBPA^(•+)). Two redox tautomers were characterized: a ligand-centered Co(III)-OH species, [(TAML^(•)⁺)Co^(III)(OH)]^(-) (1), and a metal-centered Co(IV)= O species, [(H-TAML)Co^(IV)(O)(HOTf)]^(-) (2), formed by oxidation with iodosylbenzene (PhIO)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Biocatalytic Synthesis of Capsaicinoids Using Ferulic Acid: A Versatile Two-Step Strategy for Natural Product Diversification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The wide-ranging application of capsaicinoids, the active compounds in chili peppers, has driven increasing interest in the development of sustainable production strategies. However, capsaicinoid synthesis remains a challenge. The objective of this pioneering study is to report the total biocatalytic synthesis of structurally diverse capsaicinoids from bio-based ferulic acids. An X-ray crystallographic study elucidated the structural basis for the exceptional potential of a novel transaminase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Sodium Rare Earth Silicate Solid Electrolyte with Grain Boundary Electronic Insulation for Ultra-Durable Solid-State Sodium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sodium rare earth silicate is regarded as a novel and promising solid electrolyte (SE) for solid-state sodium metal batteries (SSSMBs) because the merits of high ionic conductivity, low sintering temperature, and excellent chemical stability. However, impurity phases and voids induced by sintering always cause weak ion conduction and large electron conduction at grain boundaries, resulting in the growth of Na dendrites. Herein, a facile grain boundary modification strategy is conducted by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interplay of tail length and confinement in the formation of interior loops in flexible chains]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Loop formation between distant interior segments of a polymer is a fundamental process for biological functions such as gene regulation and protein folding. While prior studies predominantly focus on end-to-end looping, interior loop formation is more relevant in vivo. Using Langevin dynamics simulations, we investigate the kinetics of interior loop formation in confined flexible polymers with specific internal segments having attractive interactions, focusing on the effect of tail length (lt)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brain-Inspired Topological Surface Modulation for Advanced Nonvolatility in Organic Artificial Synapses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human intelligence has evolved dramatically as topological adaptations have taken precedence over volumetric expansion in brain development. Inspired by the remarkable functional enhancements achieved through cortical gyrification, organic synaptic transistors (OSTs) are demonstrated with active layers engineered via controlled surface topologies. Macroscopic compressive forces induce wrinkling in the active polymer layer, generating localized stress that compresses microscopic crystallites....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel GLP-1-Based Medications for Type 2 Diabetes and Obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The approvals of semaglutide and tirzepatide have set new benchmarks in the treatment of type 2 diabetes and obesity. Building on their success, novel GLP-1-based therapeutics are rapidly advancing. These next-generation agents engage not only GLP-1 receptors but also those for other gastro-entero-pancreatic hormones such as glucose-dependent insulinotropic polypeptide (GIP), glucagon, amylin, and peptide YY (PYY) to enhance energy uptake, storage, and expenditure through synergistic mechanisms....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A privacy-preserving HLA imputation method with homomorphic encryption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent years, several HLA imputation methods on local servers have been developed, using single nucleotide polymorphisms (SNPs) as inputs to predict Human Leukocyte Antigen (HLA) genotypes. However, these methods require HLA reference panels, which are often unavailable and memory-intensive. Cloud-based outsourced HLA imputation overcomes these limitations by utilizing built-in reference panels on the cloud server, removing local storage needs. However, uploading genotype data online raises...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiregional single-cell transcriptomics reveals an association between partial EMT and immunosuppressive states in oral squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oral squamous cell carcinoma (OSCC) is highly heterogeneous and metastatic, and the mechanisms driving OSCC development, progression, and metastasis remain elusive. Here, we performed single-cell RNA sequencing on 231,442 cells obtained from the tumor core (TC), tumor periphery (TP), adjacent surrounding tissue (ST), and metastatic lymph node (mLN) samples of 10 patients with human papillomavirus (HPV)-negative OSCC. TP and TC showed no major immune cell phenotype differences. Interestingly,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reviewer Comment on Almekhlafi et al. "Adjunctive Intraarterial Thrombolysis after Thrombectomy in Large Vessel Occlusion Stroke: A Meta-Analysis of RCTs"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global safety profile of PD-1/PD-L1 inhibitors in hepatic autoimmune disorders: A global disproportionality analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing use of programmed cell death protein-1 (PD-1) and programmed death-ligand 1 (PD-L1) inhibitors in cancer therapy has raised concerns regarding immune-related adverse events. However, global pharmacovigilance studies on autoimmune diseases remain scarce. This study aimed to evaluate the signal detection between PD-1/PD-L1 inhibitors and hepatic autoimmune disorders. A global pharmacovigilance study was conducted using data from individual case safety reports. The analysis centered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enterocutaneous fistula as a long-term complication of jejunostomy tube placement in a dog with hyperadrenocorticism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This case highlights enterocutaneous fistula as a delayed and previously unreported complication of JT placement in a dog with HAC. Given the adverse effects of HAC on wound healing, clinicians should recognize the potential for such complications and implement vigilant postprocedural monitoring and appropriate endocrine management in patients undergoing enteral tube placement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Performance and Scalable Ferroelectric Diodes Enabled via 2D-MoS<sub>2</sub> Buffer Layer Under Low Thermal Budget]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hafnium-based (Hf(0.5)Zr(0.5)O(2), HZO) ferroelectrics exhibit robust polarization switching even in ultrathin films and are compatible with atomic layer deposition (ALD), making them promising for two-terminal (2-T) non-volatile memory devices. However, their practical use remains limited by low ON/OFF ratios, high leakage currents, and poor endurance. Herein, A high-performance ferroelectric diode (FE-diode) based on a W/MoS(2)/HZO/TiN stack is demostrated, fabricated entirely below 400 °C for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resilience-Enhancing Additive Design Enabled by Macrocyclic Additive-Mediated Failure Suppression in Lithium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The high-voltage operation of mid-nickel NCM Li-ion batteries (LIBs) increases the energy density but accelerates cell degradation owing to transition-metal dissolution and oxygen-radical formation. In this study, the macrocyclic additive 1,4,7,10,13-pentaazacyclopentadecane is introduced, which enhances cell resilience through a dual-protection mechanism. The additive spontaneously chelates the dissolved Mn ions, suppressing their migration and subsequent contamination at the negative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable valorization of fish head wastes into nitrogen-based nutrients: a comparative life cycle assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[White matter hyperintensities precede other biomarkers in GRN frontotemporal dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Increased white matter hyperintensities (WMHs) have been reported in genetic frontotemporal dementia (FTD) in small studies, but the sequence of WMH abnormalities relative to other biomarkers is unclear.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative inhalable dry powder: nanoparticles loaded with Crizotinib for targeted lung cancer therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crizotinib is a targeted therapy for metastatic non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) that is ALK- or ROS1-positive, as well as for conditions such as ALK-positive anaplastic large cell lymphoma and inflammatory myofibroblastic tumor. However, the associated toxicity poses a significant challenge to its use. To mitigate this issue, a novel dry powder inhalation formulation was developed using Crizotinib-loaded polyethylene glycol-based polymeric nanoparticles (NPs). These nanoparticles were created...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Myeloperoxidase-positive mononuclear cells predominate over CD3-positive T-lymphocytes in the epidermis of Stevens-Johnson syndrome and toxic epidermal necrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stevens-Johnson syndrome and toxic epidermal necrolysis (SJS/TEN) are life-threatening mucocutaneous conditions traditionally regarded as severe T cell-mediated hypersensitivity reactions. However, recent evidence has highlighted the potential role of myeloperoxidase (MPO), primarily produced by neutrophils, in the pathogenesis of SJS/TEN. Here, we examined the expression of MPO in skin biopsy specimens from patients with SJS/TEN (n = 15) to evaluate its diagnostic utility, comparing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of sweeteners and sweetness enhancers on weight management and gut microbiota composition in individuals with overweight or obesity: the SWEET study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Consumption of sweeteners and sweetness enhancers (S&SEs) is a popular strategy to reduce sugar intake, but the role of S&SEs in body weight regulation and gut microbiota composition remains debated. Here, we show that S&SEs in a healthy diet support weight loss maintenance and beneficial gut microbiota shifts in adults with overweight or obesity. In this multi-centre, randomized, controlled trial, we included 341 adults and 38 children with overweight or obesity. Adults followed a 2-month...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time Prediction Accuracy and Influencing Factors in Colorectal ESD by Trainees: A Mixed-Model Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Prediction accuracy in colorectal ESD varies among trainees and is significantly affected by lesion complexity. Tumor size, morphology, and flexure involvement should be considered in structured training programs to enhance procedural planning and operator preparedness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of perirenal fat accumulation on cardiometabolic and renal functions and mineralocorticoid receptor activation in primary aldosteronism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perirenal fat (PRF), an ectopic fat depot lying adjacent to kidneys, is a risk factor for cardiometabolic and renal dysfunctions in patients with obesity and type 2 diabetes. We aimed to investigate the involvement of PRF in the pathophysiology and treatment of primary aldosteronism (PA). To this end, we measured PRF volume by abdominal CT and evaluated the relationships among PRF volume, cardiometabolic and renin-angiotensin-aldosterone system (RAAS) parameters, and therapeutic response to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methylation reprogramming associated with aggressive prostate cancer and ancestral disparities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[African men are disproportionately impacted by aggressive prostate cancer (PCa). The key to this disparity is both genetic and environmental factors, alluding to epigenetic modifications. However, African-inclusive prostate tumour DNA methylation studies are lacking. Assembling a multi-geo-ancestral prostate tissue cohort, including men with (57 African, 48 European, 23 Asian) or without (65 African) PCa, we interrogate for genome-wide differential methylation. Overall, methylation appears to be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Demonstration of the rotational viscosity transfer across scales in Navier-Stokes turbulence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mechanical effects that span multiple physical scales-such as the influence of vanishing molecular viscosity on large-scale flow structures under specific conditions-play a critical role in real fluid systems. The spin angular momentum-conserving Navier-Stokes equations offer a theoretical framework for describing such multiscale fluid dynamics by decomposing total angular momentum into bulk and intrinsic spin components. However, this framework still assumes locally non-solid rotational flows,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Realtime monitoring of internal morphology of gel samples during drying process by X-ray computing tomography image using synchrotron radiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study was conducted to evaluate the change in the internal morphology of a wheat-based gel sample subjected to a drying process using X-ray computed tomography (CT) imaging with synchrotron radiation. To monitor the process in real time, the instrument was equipped with a developed drying system. The water contents of the sample decreased from around 0.42 to 0.1 g-water/g-dry solid and the falling rate drying was observed in the 0-180 min of drying period. The mechanical properties of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Partial Occlusion on Response Dynamics and Interregional Processing within Primate Superior Temporal Sulcus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recognizing partially occluded objects is a critical visual function that primates perform with ease, yet the underlying neural mechanisms remain incompletely understood. Previous studies in macaque inferotemporal cortex have reported mixed results on whether occlusion delays and reduces responses to partially occluded objects. To address this, we recorded single-unit activity from body-responsive regions of the middle and anterior Superior Temporal Sulcus (STS) in male macaques while presenting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of toilet seat height and inclination on sit-to-stand motion for subjects with limited trunk mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to clarify the toilet seat height and inclination conditions that promote sit-to-stand motion for users with simulated kyphosis and reduced trunk mobility. The study was performed on healthy subjects with spinal orthosis to simulate a kyphotic posture and reduced trunk mobility (simulated kyphosis) in which the toilet seat was either not adjusted ("standard setting"), supplemented by 3 cm or 5 cm ("3 cm higher" or "5 cm higher"), or tilted forward by 5° or 15° ("5° tilt" or "15°...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shared decision-making using a decision aid for patients with breast cancer considering breast reconstruction: study protocol for a cluster-randomised controlled trial in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Shared decision-making (SDM) requires that individuals are correctly and smoothly supported to make decisions. However, in Japan, development of decision aids (DAs) to support implementation of SDM is lagging behind Western countries, and there are few reports focused on breast reconstruction. Thus, it is unclear if SDM using a DA in the context of the unique national character and medical culture in Japan is useful in decision-making for breast reconstruction, including whether or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ibogaine alters the firing rate and afterhyperpolarization in mouse ventral tegmental area I<sub>h</sub>-negative neurons in a sex-dependent manner]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Depression and substance use disorder affect millions world-wide, and risk factors include sex. Conventional pharmacotherapies show at best a 50 % success rate. Psychedelics exhibit both anti-addictive and anti-depressive properties. One of these, ibogaine, a root bark sourced alkaloid, interacts with receptors implicated in anti-depressive and anti-addictive effects with affinities in the micromolar range. However, cellular actions underlying therapeutic properties are not well understood. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incomplete lineage sorting, hybridization and polyploidization blurred phylogenetic relationships of gentians from the Qinghai-Tibetan Plateau]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Resolving evolutionary relationships among species undergoing radiation is challenging. Gentiana is a species-rich genus with a sub-cosmopolitan distribution, in which several sections have undergone recent radiation. In this study, we reassessed the phylogeny of Gentiana with particular focus on the controversial section Kudoa, and elucidated the complex phylogenetic relationship as well as their underlying causes in this section. Combining with a large number of single-copy orthologous genes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Control of pharmacokinetics of radioimmunoconjugates using chelating agents containing poly(ethylene glycol)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radioimmunoconjugates (RICs) composed of a monoclonal antibody (mAb) and radioisotope (RI) offer an attractive modality in oncology; however, their low tumor/blood ratio has limited their utility. To establish a novel strategy to improve the tumor/blood ratio without compromising the tumor accumulation of RICs, we developed novel DOTA-based chelating agents containing maleimide and discrete poly(ethylene glycol) (dPEG) scaffolds to synthesize RICs degrading into residualizing radiometabolites...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vitro system completely restores oogenesis in congenitally infertile mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[STUDY QUESTION: Can in vitro systems, combined with transient gene expression or factor supplementation, completely restore fertility in congenitally infertile mice?]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Physical Activity in Rural Life and Low Grip Strength: Findings From the Uonuma Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study found an inverse association between physical activity in rural life and low grip strength in middle-aged and older adults. The findings highlight the significance of physical activity related to environmental features in preventing reduced muscle strength in rural communities. Significance/Implications: Physical activity in rural life, such as farming and snow removal, may effectively support muscle strength maintenance and reduce sarcopenia risk in community-dwelling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Common Mistakes in Bone and Soft Tissue Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate diagnosis of bone and soft tissue tumors is critical for effective management, yet radiologic errors remain a significant challenge and may lead to inappropriate interventions or delays in adequate treatment. This article describes common radiologic mistakes encountered in evaluating these tumors, including key errors such as mischaracterizing benign versus malignant lesions, overreliance on single imaging modalities, and failure to integrate clinical and histopathologic data. We focus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-time estimation of boron concentration using an improved gamma-ray telescope system for boron neutron capture therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An online, real-time estimation method to determine the spatial distribution of boron-10 (B-10) concentrations is required for improved dose estimation in boron neutron capture therapy. By using a gamma-ray telescope technique to analyze the 478-keV prompt gamma rays generated from the nuclear reaction of B-10 with thermal neutrons, information regarding the B-10 concentration distribution can be obtained. The improved gamma-ray telescope system was settled at the Heavy Water Neutron Irradiation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Specificity of Drosophila innubila Nudivirus infection in Drosophila cell culture]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Viral host range is an important aspect of both viral biology but also the pragmatic issue of producing viral stocks for experimentation. Host range is important both in terms of the species a virus can infect (taxonomy), and the types of host cells the virus can infect (tropism). Nudiviruses are large DNA viruses that infect several arthropods and are generally poorly studied. Several nudiviruses infect Drosophila species including the Drosophila innubila Nudivirus (DiNV). We aimed to identify...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic comparison of acute exacerbations across idiopathic interstitial pneumonia subtypes: A nationwide observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with AE-IIPs, those with IPF, NSIP, and AIP exhibited significantly higher in-hospital mortality compared with COP. These findings underscore the inferior prognosis associated with AE-IPF and AIP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of astatine-211-labeled benzoate derivatives for improved in vivo stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings indicated that if ^(211)At-labeled compounds can place the steric hindrance of the tripeptide size in the vicinity of ^(211)At-astatobenzene, in vivo stable ^(211)At-labeled compounds can be produced, even when using the ^(211)At-astatobenzen structure as a ^(211)At-labeling moiety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graphitic Carbon Nitride-Reinforced Chitosan/Ca<sup>2+</sup>-Alginate Nanocomposite Films with Multifunctional Properties for Sustainable Packaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents the synthesis and characterization of Ca²^(+)-cross-linked alginate (ALG), chitosan (CHT), and g-C(3)N(4)-based ternary composites for multifunctional applications. The electrostatic interactions between ALG and CHT, combined with the ionic interaction of Ca^(2+) with ALG, significantly enhanced the composite properties. Furthermore, incorporation of g-C(3)N(4) into the ALG/CHT matrix resulted in a uniform dispersion in the ALG/g-C(3)N(4)/CHT composite, as confirmed by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase I Study of Rogocekib in Patients with Relapsed or Refractory Hematologic Malignancies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rogocekib (development name CTX-712) is a first-in-class, orally available, highly potent, and selective small molecule inhibitor of CDC2-like kinase (CLK), a key regulator of the RNA splicing process. Preclinical studies demonstrated anti-proliferative activity on various in-vitro and in-vivo models of hematologic malignancies. Based on these findings, a phase I study of rogocekib was conducted to evaluate the safety and preliminary efficacy in patients with relapsed or refractory acute myeloid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating sampling bias in discrete phylogeographic analysis: assessing the performance of an adjusted Bayes factor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bayesian phylogeographic inference is widely used in molecular epidemiological studies to reconstruct the dispersal history of pathogens. Discrete phylogeographic analysis treats geographic locations as discrete traits and infers lineage transition events among them, and is typically followed by a Bayes factor (BF) test to assess the statistical support. In the standard BF (BFstd) test, the relative abundance of the involved trait states is not considered, which can be problematic in the case of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of kVCT- and MVCT-guided helical tomotherapy for total body irradiation: evaluation of process times and residual setup errors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Helical tomotherapy-based total body irradiation (TBI) traditionally employs megavoltage computed tomography (MVCT) for image-guided setup; however, its 390 mm field of view (FOV) and long acquisition times constrain workflow efficiency and whole-body alignment. This study evaluated whether a newly implemented whole-body fan-beam kilovoltage CT (kVCT; 500 mm FOV) can streamline this process. In a retrospective study involving 14 patients treated with a Radixact X9 system (September...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathogenesis-based treatment strategies for brain metastases from non-small cell cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[More than half of brain metastases (BMs) in patients with non-small cell lung cancer are diagnosed at the time of lung cancer diagnosis and are therefore potentially amenable to systemic treatment. Before the introduction of molecular targeting therapy, medical treatment was thought to be ineffective owing to the presence of the blood-brain barrier (BBB). However, the molecular activities of cancer cells in the central nervous system affect the brain microenvironment, changing the function of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of Pyridine-Fused Azacorroles through Multicomponent-Coupling Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A facile and efficient protocol for the synthesis of π-extended azacorroles with a variety of fused-pyridine rings is described. A three-component one-pot reaction of 3-amino-5,15-dimesityl-10-azacorrolatonickel(II), 4-chlorobenzaldehyde, and 1,3-diketones in the presence of acetic acid at 110 °C and the subsequent p-chloranil oxidation furnished pyridine-fused azacorrole derivatives in moderate yields. This simple method provides an efficient approach for π-extension of azacorroles for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of non-invasive preimplantation genetic testing for aneuploidies (niPGT-A) in a Japanese population: experience from seven clinics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We have shown results that are consistent with the existing literature, indicating the feasibility of applying the niPGT-A protocol described here, and thus using the SBM result to establish a priority for embryo transfer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship Between the Incidence of Metabolic Syndrome and Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MetS is associated with the less frequent breast cancer incidence in females, especially aged < 50 years.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between baseline cerebral oxygen saturation, preoperative B-type natriuretic peptide and hemoglobin levels, and mortality after cardiac surgery in non-dialysis patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Baseline cerebral regional oxygen saturation (rSO₂) measured with the INVOS 5100C near-infrared spectroscopy (NIRS) device has been reported to correlate primarily with preoperative B-type natriuretic peptide (BNP) and hemoglobin levels. It has also been reported to be associated with postoperative mortality. This study evaluated whether similar associations exist for other NIRS-derived indicators, including tissue oxygenation index (TOI) and tissue oxygen saturation (StO₂), measured with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shared Decision-Making. A Primer for Clinicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This primer portrays a reflective clinician who is aware of power asymmetry, patient vulnerability, risk communication, health literacy, agenda setting, and goal clarification. It envisages a clinician who is curious about personal perspectives and who can offer collaborative, iterative, and deliberative steps.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world use of HIF-PH inhibitors and ESAs in non-dialysis-dependent CKD with anemia: insights from a Japanese database study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Real-world database analysis shows that initiation of HIF-PH inhibitors for renal anemia in NDD-CKD increased to match that of ESAs by 2024, although switching from ESAs remained low. HIF-PH inhibitors showed a trend toward improvement in anemia compared to ESAs, suggesting clinical benefit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associated Factors to Nonadherence to Routine Appointments after Kidney Transplantation: The ADHERE Brazil Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study is the first to examine the association of health system factors with missed appointments after KT. The identified patient factors allow us to recognize patients at risk for NApp. Modifiable variables at the health professional and KT center levels suggest targets for effective interventions aiming to reduce this behavior and improve outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-standardized mortality-to-incidence ratio for ovarian cancer in the world]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multistage control of near-infrared and magnetic properties <em>via</em> π-dimer modulation in TCNQ radical anion salts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a liquescent 7,7,8,8-tetracyanoquinodimethane radical anion (TCNQ˙^(-)) salt with an N,N'-di-n-octylimidazolium ion that exhibits unprecedented three-stage switching of magnetic and NIR-II absorption properties upon thermal stimulation. This behavior originates from stepwise transformations between co-facial and slipped-stacking π-dimers and monomeric TCNQ˙^(-) species.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of protein capsules from novel amphiphilic two-helix bundle proteins (GP-ZiPs), designed by fusing the transmembrane region of glycophorin A with coiled-coil peptides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To further validate our protein capsule construction strategy based on amphiphilic two-helix-bundled proteins, we designed GP-ZIPs (GP-ZIP41, GP-ZIP29, GP-ZIP20), combining a truncated glycophorin A transmembrane region and a dimeric coiled-coil. Using an emulsion method, we successfully constructed stable hollow capsules (70-200 nm) capable of encapsulating hundreds of protein molecules.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modelling adsorbate coverage on complex alloy surfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In order to extend catalysis theory to complex alloys and multiple adsorbates, we have to face the fact that the number of possible surface site-adsorbate combinations gets too large to calculate. We, instead, define rules for adsorbate-adsorbate interactions; specifically, blocking rules in terms of disallowed local adsorbate-adsorbate configurations. We then conduct simple simulations to investigate how different rules entail certain outcomes. For the PdAg intermetallic and PdAg solid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Challenges in Implementing a Mobile AI Chatbot Intervention for Depression Among Youth on Psychiatric Waiting Lists: Randomized Controlled Study Termination Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Significant barriers to engagement suggest that digital interventions may need simpler protocols and trusted environments to improve feasibility. Future studies could test these interventions in supportive settings, like schools or community centers, to enhance accessibility and participation among youth.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thrombospondin-4 from Cancer-associated Fibroblasts Downregulates ERBB2 Expression in Gastric Cancer Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The intra-tumoral heterogeneity of HER2 expression is associated with resistance to anti-HER2 therapy in HER2-positive gastric cancers (GCs). We previously reported that thrombospondin-4 (THBS4) is overexpressed in cancer-associated fibroblasts (CAFs) in the GC microenvironment and is associated with GC remodeling. To clarify the relationship between CAFs and the intra-tumoral heterogeneity of HER2 in GC, the effect of CAFs on HER2 expression was investigated in GC cells. Two HER2-positive GC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential Growth and Transpiration Responses Among Banana (Musa Spp.) Hybrids-Hope for Breeding Drought Tolerant Bananas?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stiff and Fracture-Resistant Ion Gels Enabled by Synergetic Physical Entanglement and Hydrogen Bonding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, ion gels are developed that simultaneously exhibit exceptional stiffness and fracture resistance through the synergistic effects of physical entanglements and hydrogen bonding between polymer chains within an ionic liquid matrix. Through radical copolymerization conducted in an ionic liquid under extremely low initiator concentrations, ultrahigh molecular weight polymers in situ with nearly complete monomer conversion are successfully synthesized. This strategy enabled the one-pot...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Voltage-dependent ionic polarization in TlBr: alternate square-wave bias application for ionic polarization control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Scientific insights into the polarization of TlBr pellets under applied voltage were investigated to develop stable TlBr-based electronic devices. The polarization originates from the electrophoretic migration of Tl^(+) and Br^(-) ions and shows a clear dependence on the applied voltage. Importantly, the polarization can be effectively suppressed by applying an alternate square-wave bias.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urinary metabolite signatures to detect and differentiate graft injury in kidney transplant patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current biomarkers are either lagging indicators of injury or have been developed to maximize negative predictive value only for active rejection. In this study, we aimed to demonstrate the utility of urinary metabolites to detect and differentiate types of graft injury. Retrospective urine samples from a training cohort of 102 patients were used to develop a metabolite signature to detect and differentiate a stable graft from graft injury including borderline rejection, active rejection due to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual molecular therapy targeting tumor cell heterogeneity improves therapeutic efficacy in glioblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The intratumoral heterogeneity of glioblastoma, comprising glioblastoma stem cells (GSCs) and differentiated glioblastoma cells (DGCs), contributes to treatment resistance. We explored combination therapy targeting both GSCs and DGCs. Candidate drugs predicted to be highly effective against GSCs and DGCs were identified through in silico screening, which utilized antitumor efficacy data of therapeutic agents and gene expression profiles of cancer cell lines. IC50 values of the candidate drugs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helicobacter pylori Infection Is a Risk Factor for Severe Hyperemesis Gravidarum Requiring Prolonged Hospitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings suggest that testing for anti-H. pylori IgG antibodies may help identify patients at a higher risk for a longer hospital stay due to severe HG. Pregnant women who test positive for anti-H. pylori IgG antibodies may benefit from closer monitoring. Additionally, these results raise the possibility that preconception care could be a preventive measure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two molecular subtypes of skull base meningiomas with extracranial extension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251008033643&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the marketing of BMS in China through pregnant women and new mothers' diary]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Chinese pregnant women and mothers of infants aged 0-18 months encounter frequent, multifaceted BMS marketing (activities, or strategies, or tactics) predominantly through digital channels. China's current regulatory framework governs food labelling but affords limited monitoring of BMS advertising across all channels-particularly digital platforms-underscoring the need for comprehensive regulation that explicitly includes online marketing tactics. A multisectoral strategy-combining...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond diabetes: harnessing the power of metformin in burn care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Burn injuries are complex and devastating traumas that trigger a profound systemic metabolic response, characterized by hyperglycemia, insulin resistance, and a hypermetabolic state. Notably, hyperglycemia is a critical determinant of worse prognoses in burn patients. While insulin has long been the gold standard for managing post-burn hyperglycemia, its therapy is associated with a risk of hypoglycemic events, which can exacerbate morbidity and compromise patient outcomes. As such,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A ternary-code DNA methylome atlas of mouse tissues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our work reveals how tissue, sex, and age jointly govern the dynamics of the two cytosine modifications, augments the scope of DNA modification biomarker discovery, and provides a reference atlas to explore epigenetic dynamics in development and disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insulin-like peptides activate egg formation in the Asian malaria mosquito Anopheles stephensi]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Regulation of gonotrophic cycles in An. stephensi shares some features with Ae. aegypti but also exhibits differences.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potential therapeutic benefit of exogenous ketone ester administration in delirium: a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Delirium is a prevalent neuropsychiatric syndrome during critical illness and is associated with prolonged hospitalization, increased mortality, and post-ICU cognitive decline. It is hypothesized to result from systemic inflammation, disrupted neurotransmission, and failure of cerebral energy metabolism. This narrative review highlights the key role of altered neurometabolism and neuroinflammation, which occurs due to peripheral inflammation, compromised blood-brain barrier integrity, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and external validation of a machine learning-based predictive model for acute kidney injury in hospitalized children with idiopathic nephrotic syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Predictive models for live birth outcomes following fresh embryo transfer in assisted reproductive technologies using machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stem cells as biological drugs for incurable diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel clinical and genetic insights into Gitelman syndrome from 95 Chinese patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study characterized the phenotypic and genotypic features of Chinese GS patients, highlighting age and mutation genotype as key factors influencing phenotype, underscoring the importance of standardized potassium and magnesium supplementation, and expanding the known mutation spectrum with novel variants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Publisher Correction: The performance evaluation of the AI-assisted diagnostic system in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overexpression of CCK Neuropeptide in brain is linked to ZBTB20 mutations: potential diagnostic relevance in glioblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-precision cell-type mapping and annotation of single-cell spatial transcriptomics with STAMapper]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a heterogeneous graph neural network, STAMapper, to transfer the cell-type labels from single-cell RNA-sequencing (scRNA-seq) data to single-cell spatial transcriptomics (scST) data. We collect 81 scST datasets consisting of 344 slices and 16 paired scRNA-seq datasets from eight technologies and five tissues to validate the efficiency of STAMapper. STAMapper achieves the best performance on 75 out of 81 datasets compared to competing methods in accuracy. STAMapper...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corneal eccentricity and related factors in Chinese children and adolescents with astigmatism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In Chinese children and adolescents with moderate to high corneal astigmatism, the anterior cornea demonstrates aspheric characteristics with distinct meridional asymmetry. The flat e value may was associated with corneal curvature (flat K and ΔK values), whereas the steep e value was not associated with these parameters.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Planning and proposing evaluations to support project success]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Faculty who are interested in leading grants, education and outreach projects, and other initiatives need evidence to make data-based decisions and demonstrate successes. Evaluations are essential for supporting these efforts and are often required to obtain funding. In fact, a strong evaluation plan within a proposal can ensure alignment between clearly constructed goals and activities in order to promote the likelihood of a project's success as well as provide reviewers with insight into how...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How can we reduce psychological burden for patients of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis and their family caregivers? - Insights from the participatory multi-method study "potentiALS"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study highlights the distinct yet interconnected psychosocial needs of ALS patients and their caregivers. Tailored interventions should blend emotional support, open dialogue, and a structured therapeutic framework, while also emphasizing the need for adaptable delivery models in clinical practice. These findings support the development of scalable, patient-centered psychosocial support approaches as part of the multidimensional care in ALS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterogeneity of treatment preferences in the absence of guideline recommendations - a case vignette study in colorectal cancer tumor boards in Germany, Austria and Switzerland]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In prototypical case vignettes without evidence-based guideline recommendations, pronounced heterogeneity of treatment preferences between centers was found. Reconstructing these treatment preferences can contribute to enhancing the quality of evidence derived from observational studies. This seems especially important in the context of clinical questions that cannot be assessed in randomized trials; clinical routine data represent an adequate resource for evidence generation in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lineage-specific expansions of the Dicer gene family in tardigrades]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study identified multiple distinct tardigrade-specific dicer duplications following an ancient duplication that is shared in both Eutardigrades and Heterotardigrades. Phylogenetic analyses are consistent with a Dicer duplication before the split of Tardigrada and Arthropoda that led to Dicer-2, which also groups with duplications found in Kinorhyncha and Platyhelminthes. Our study provides insights into Dicer evolution in Tardigrada by characterizing dicer duplications and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of "colored teeth and digital evaluation" on preclinical tooth preparation training]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychometric properties of the German version of the clinician-administered PTSD scale for DSM-5 (CAPS-5) in routine clinical settings: a multi-trait/multi-method study in civilians and military personnel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The Clinician-Administered PTSD Scale (CAPS-5) is a structured diagnostic interview developed for diagnosing post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD). To ensure compliance with PTSD inclusion criteria, an initial study investigated the psychometric properties and factorial structure of the German version of CAPS-5 using data collected previously. The present study's objective was to validate the robustness of the psychometric properties of the German CAPS-5 by assessing its validity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychological wellbeing and occupational stress among public secondary school teachers in Beni Municipality, Nepal: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study reveals that a significant proportion of secondary school teachers in public schools of Nepal experience psychological distress and occupational stress, with key factors including job satisfaction, salary dissatisfaction, and perceived job demands associated with them. The findings underscore the need for targeted interventions to improve teachers' well-being, such as improving salary structures, clarifying job roles, offering professional development, providing access to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Milk temperature reducing necrotizing enterocolitis in very preterm infants: study protocol for a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study aims to clarify the relationship between feeding temperature and NEC risk, potentially influencing future neonatal care guidelines. By identifying optimal feeding practices, this trial aims to reduce the morbidity and mortality associated with NEC in very preterm infants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Whole genome sequencing for tuberculosis disease species identification, lineage determination, and drug resistance detection in Kashgar prefecture, China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: WGS can be an important approach in assessing TB control strategy and for determining therapeutic schemes in high TB-burden regions. The drug resistance TB of Kashgar prefecture is at low level and the application of WGS may prevent the increase of resistance rate.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating rates and factors associated with cesarean section and inpatient cost among low-risk deliveries in selected U.S. states]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Cesarean sections are commonly performed in the United States, including among patients for whom vaginal delivery may be clinically feasible. This study aimed to evaluate rates and factors associated with cesarean section use and inpatient cost among low-risk deliveries in selected U.S. states.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A prediction model of preterm birth in singleton pregnancy after assisted reproduction therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The prediction model developed in this study is effective for predicting preterm birth risk in ART pregnancies. This model can help clinicians identify high-risk pregnancies early and implement targeted interventions. Cervical length monitoring may be a useful tool in predicting preterm birth, especially after the second trimester.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring patient experiences with a mindfulness course in a general practice setting: a qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study indicates that patients in general practice have a positive attitude towards mindfulness as a part of the stress treatment in general practice. The patient's interest was supported by trustful doctor-patient relationships. The participants experienced improved emotion regulation and enhanced coping strategies. These findings underscore the benefits of integrating mindfulness into general practice. However, mindfulness is not available within Denmark's free healthcare...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The two sub-genomes of the allotetraploid frog Xenopus laevis are evolving under similar selective pressure in extant populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The model species Xenopus laevis is an allotetraploid species, whose genome consists of two sub-genomes (the L and S sub-genomes) that were inherited from its parental species. Previous studies comparing the genome of X. laevis with other species of the genus revealed that the L sub-genome was more conserved than the S sub-genome suggesting it has been evolving under stronger purifying selection. However, it remains unclear if this difference reflects evolutionary processes that are still at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating seasonal metabolic variations in bipolar disorder: a targeted metabolomics study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings indicate a seasonal modulation of serum metabolite profiles in individuals with BD, which may underlie or reflect mood-related changes. However, causal relationships and mechanistic pathways require further validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of clinical and bronchoscopic features of multidrug-resistant tracheobronchial tuberculosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The clinical manifestations of multidrug-resistant tracheobronchial tuberculosis are non-specific. The main clinical features are cough and fever. It often invades the right upper bronchus. The main bronchoscopic manifestation is inflammatory infiltration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic insights into the population structure and adaptive variation of Mullus barbatus in the Mediterranean Sea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study presents the first genomic resource for M. barbatus, providing valuable insights into its genetic structure and adaptive mechanisms. While the identification of loci under selection offers promising leads, these findings are preliminary due to the limited genomic coverage of the dataset. Nonetheless, they pave the way for future genomic studies to explore how M. barbatus adapts to environmental and anthropogenic pressures. These results hold significant implications for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Visual Abstract: Social Vulnerability is Associated with Significant Delays to Definitive Surgery for Stage IA-IIIA Non-small Cell Lung Cancer and Consequential Increased Rates of Pathologic Upstaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Trauma Informed Family Meeting: A New Model of Information Sharing and Family Support During Cardiac Admission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While best practice guidelines for family meetings in pediatric CICU settings emphasize empathic listening, deliberation, and a focus on family experiences and values, recent research reveals that cardiac care teams face barriers when putting these guidelines into practice. Exposure to traumatic medical experiences impacts the degree to which both family members and cardiac clinicians are able to engage in collaborative conversations during family meetings. Instead, these meetings often become...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-dependent Zap70 expression in thymocytes regulates selection of the neonatal regulatory T cell repertoire]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Foxp3⁺ regulatory T (T(reg)) cell repertoire carries age-dependent biases, with neonatal subsets enriched for highly self-reactive clones. However, the thymocyte features distinguishing neonatal from adult T(reg) selection remain unclear. Here, we show that neonatal double-positive mouse thymocytes, unlike their adult counterparts, fail to upregulate Zap70 during thymic selection, creating a calcium signaling bottleneck. This attenuated Zap70-dependent signaling limits negative selection,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Use of Long-Acting Injectables for People with Schizophrenia: Consensus Panel Recommendations for Overcoming Barriers and Implementing Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This expert consensus panel provided recommendations to guide HCPs on how to overcome barriers to LAI use and to implement, monitor, and maintain LAIs as routine schizophrenia treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors associated with beta-peripapillary atrophy in individuals of African ancestry with primary open-angle glaucoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Beta-PPA is strongly associated with older age and high CDR among individuals with POAG. These regions are vulnerable to RNFL loss.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-iridium stabilized ruthenium oxide anode catalyst for durable proton-exchange membrane water electrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While mixing iridium (Ir) with ruthenium oxide (RuO(2)) has proven to be an effective strategy for reducing Ir loading in anode catalysts for proton-exchange membrane (PEM) water electrolysers, achieving industrially relevant long-term stability typically requires an Ir-rich, Ru-lean combination. Here, by combining density functional theory with Metropolis Monte Carlo methods, we discovered that sufficient stabilization in the RuO(2) lattice could be achieved with less than 50 at.% of Ir, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adaptive ecosystem restoration to mitigate zoonotic risks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infectious diseases pose a substantial threat to global health security. Key wildlife species, potentially harbouring numerous zoonotic pathogens, are increasingly being forced to adapt to disturbances from land-use change, human encroachment and climate change. Although the evidence is rather convincing pertaining to the increased risks of zoonotic diseases with degradation and disturbances, the scientific literature on the mitigating effects of ecosystem restoration on zoonotic spillover is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cellular and spatial atlas of TP53-associated tissue remodeling defines a multicellular tumor ecosystem in lung adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor protein p53 (TP53) is the most frequently mutated gene across many cancers and is associated with shorter overall survival in lung adenocarcinoma (LUAD). Here, to define how TP53 mutations affect the LUAD tumor microenvironment (TME), we constructed a multiomic cellular and spatial atlas of 23 treatment-naive human lung tumors. We found that TP53-mutant malignant cells lose alveolar identity and upregulate highly proliferative and entropic gene expression programs consistently across LUAD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DNA methylation of genes involved in lipid metabolism drives adiponectin levels and metabolic disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS/INTERPRETATION: Taken together, these large-scale and integrative analyses uncovered links between adipokines and widespread, yet functionally specific, differences in regulation of genes with a central role in type 2 diabetes and its risk factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Divergent molecular pathways drive monomorphic epitheliotropic and enteropathy-associated intestinal T-cell lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enteropathy-associated intestinal T-cell lymphoma (EATL) and monomorphic epitheliotropic intestinal T-cell lymphoma (MEITL) have distinctive clinical context, morphology, and immunophenotype. To characterize their genetic and molecular specificities, we compared 30 EATLs and 52 MEITLs by whole-exome, RNA and miRNA sequencing and DNA methylation profiling. Highly recurrent SETD2 loss-of-function alterations and frequent mutations of H3-3A/B consistently altering H3R2, implying deregulation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Socioeconomic position and access to supportive cancer care in Europe: a scoping review of literature from 2000 to 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Research on the association of SEP with access and uptake of supportive care is increasing but still limited. Methodology varies and is mostly exploratory. The majority of the included studies indicate that socioeconomic differences in engagement with supportive cancer care in Europe persist. More research is needed to explain the causal pathways through which SEP affects engagement with supportive care, and how its accessibility can be improved in different European countries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generation of modified cows and sheep from spermatid-like haploid embryonic stem cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In rodents, injection of haploid androgenetic embryonic stem cells (haES cells) into intact oocytes enables full-term development of offspring. The value of this method in research and genome engineering has not been replicated in ruminants because ruminant haES cells are yet to be obtained. Here we report the derivation of cow and sheep haES cells and their application to generate offspring by a method we call intracytoplasmic haES cell injection (iCHI), in analogy with intracytoplasmic sperm...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large-scale generation of iNK and CAR-iNK cells from CD34<sup>+</sup> haematopoietic stem and progenitor cells for adoptive immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimaeric antigen receptor (CAR) natural killer (CAR-NK) cells are a promising alternative to CAR-T cells for immunotherapies. High and multiple doses of CAR-NK cell infusions are essential to maintain therapeutic efficacy in clinical trials, requiring efficient methods for generating CAR-NK cells at scale. Here we develop a three-step strategy to generate high yields of induced NK (iNK) and CAR-iNK cells from human umbilical cord blood CD34^(+) haematopoietic stem and progenitor cells (CD34^(+)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A prospective longitudinal study of the changes in multidimensional fatigue and its associated factors in patients undergoing brachytherapy for cervical cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The changes of multidimensional fatigue and associated factors in patients undergoing brachytherapy for cervical cancer are unknown. This study aimed to evaluate changes in multidimensional fatigue with associated factors during and one month after the brachytherapy. This prospective longitudinal study recruited 188 patients undergoing brachytherapy for cervical cancer. They were assessed before the brachytherapy began (T0), after three sessions of brachytherapy (T1), after five sessions of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hippocampal CaMKII-α β-hydroxybutyrylation induces memory deficits in mice with type 1 diabetes mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memory loss is a manifestation of type 1 diabetes mellitus (T1DM)-induced brain damage resulting from hyperglycemia. However, the mechanism underlying T1DM-induced memory deficit remains largely unknown. In diabetes, ketogenesis occurs upon insulin deficiency, and β-hydroxybutyrate (β-OHB) is synthesized and plays a dominant role in diabetic ketoacidosis. In the present study, we investigate the effect of β-OHB-mediated lysine β-hydroxybutyrylation (kbhb) of hippocampal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning framework for mapping nitrate pollution in coastal aquifers under land use pressure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diffuse nitrate (NO₃^(-)) contamination is a critical environmental concern threatening the quality of coastal groundwater resources, particularly in regions undergoing agricultural intensification and rapid land use changes. This study presents an explainable deep learning framework for predicting nitrate concentrations and identifying areas at risk of elevated contamination. The framework integrates key hydrochemical parameters electrical conductivity (EC), chloride (Cl^(-)), organic matter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Secondhand fashion consumers exhibit fast fashion behaviors despite sustainability narratives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fashion industry contributes 2-8% of global greenhouse gas emissions, driven by rising clothing consumption and the proliferation of fast fashion. Fast fashion accelerates environmental harm through rapid production cycles, low costs, and short garment lifespans. Secondhand clothing markets are often promoted as a sustainable alternative, promising extended use and reduced waste. These markets have grown rapidly, with global sales reaching $177 billion in 2022 and projected to double by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progenitor exhausted PD-1<sup>+</sup> T cells are cellular targets of immune checkpoint inhibition in atherosclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs), targeting checkpoint receptors such as programmed cell death protein 1 (PD-1), are associated with increased risk of cardiovascular events, but the underlying mechanisms remain poorly understood. Here we show that PD-1^(+) T cells from murine atherosclerotic aortas mainly display a progenitor exhausted phenotype (PD-1^(int)Slamf6^(+)Tim3^(-)), produce IFNγ in vivo, exhibit signs of recent proliferation and maintain polyfunctionality. PD-1 blockade induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of Soluble Inflammatory and Endothelial Activation Biomarkers with Cognitive Function Over Three Years After Ischemic Stroke-PROSCIS-B]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vascular inflammation is involved in the pathophysiology of post-stroke cognitive impairment. We aimed to assess whether blood-based biomarkers of inflammation and endothelial dysfunction, such as interleukin 6 (IL-6), vascular cell adhesion molecule (VCAM-1), and tumor necrosis factor-alpha (TNF-α), are associated with cognitive function over time in a prospective cohort of first-ever ischemic stroke patients. Data were obtained from the Prospective Cohort with Incident Stroke Berlin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of prompt, voice, and personality factors in the acceptance and evaluation of AI-generated mindfulness exercises]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AI-generated mindfulness exercises have the potential to provide tailored mindfulness interventions. However, the role of quality of AI-generated mindfulness exercises on their acceptance and evaluation is as of yet underexplored. The present work investigates effects of prompting (tailored versus non-tailored versus human), voice (trained versus non-trained versus human), and matching voice personality factors on the uncanniness, human likeness, and acceptance of AI-generated mindfulness...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding replication stress responses through post-translational modifications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA replication is a fundamental cellular process that ensures the faithful duplication of the genome during cell division. However, this process is frequently challenged by various intrinsic and extrinsic factors that can impede replication fork progression and jeopardize genomic integrity. To safeguard against these challenges, cells have evolved intricate stress response mechanisms, including replication checkpoint activation, translesion DNA synthesis, repriming and fork reversal, all of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell transcriptomic profiling reveals cell type heterogeneity between HFpEF and HFrEF]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heart failure with preserved ejection fraction (HFpEF) as a high heterogeneity clinical syndrome, is commonly associated with diastolic dysfunction, and has no effective therapy, which is obviously distinct from Heart failure with reduced ejection fraction (HFrEF). Currently the differences of cell type heterogeneity between HFpEF and HFrEF remain largely unknown. Here we illustrate an atlas consisting of 21,747 cardiac cells, including both HFpEF and HFrEF. Cell-cell communication analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The origins of aquaculture feed ingredients matter more than composition for aquafeed environmental footprint assessments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The net environmental implications of shifting aquaculture feed provisioning from wild-caught fishmeal to crop-based ingredients remain understudied, with little attention paid to multiple environmental pressures or the importance of where ingredients are sourced from. Here we model the change in environmental footprint (a cumulative and spatial measure of greenhouse gas emissions, habitat disturbance, excess nutrient and water consumption pressures) of shifting dependence from largely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A hybrid calorimetry-simulation model of mixing enthalpy for molten salt]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Calorimetric determination of enthalpies of mixing (ΔH(mix)) in multicomponent molten salts is often interpreted using empirical models that lack physically meaningful parameters. However, for improving pyrochemical separation of spent nuclear fuel, where lanthanides are major fission products and critical elements, a deeper thermodynamic understanding of the link between excess thermodynamic properties and solvation structure is critically needed. In this work, we implement a hybrid and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Covalent organic frameworks as infinite building units for metal-organic frameworks with compartmentalized pores]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-organic frameworks typically rely on discrete molecules as building units, and creating frameworks featuring continuous organic or inorganic subnet moieties, such as chains and layers, is challenging. While all-inorganic subnets have been used as units with infinite connectivity, the intrinsic disorder in organic chains and layers hinders their role as well-defined building blocks for reticular materials. Here we report the one-pot synthesis of a series of Zr(6)O(8)-based or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251008033644&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>