<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 19:19:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of oseltamivir with neuropsychiatric and behavioral adverse events: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first comprehensive meta-analysis examining the associations of oseltamivir with various NPEs and behavioral adverse events, and we found no evidence supporting increased risks of these adverse events with oseltamivir use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Surveillance of Avian Coronaviruses from Wild Bird in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We examined 2,868 fecal samples from migratory wild birds collected from multiple geographical locations in South Korea during the winter seasons between 2014 and 2022. All samples were obtained from four avian species belonging to the genus Anas within the order Anseriformes: Eurasian teal (Anas crecca), Eastern spot-billed duck (Anas zonorhyncha), Mallard (Anas platyrhynchos), and Northern pintail (Anas acuta). The presence of coronaviruses (CoVs) was confirmed through nested PCR targeting a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CYP2D6 genotyping in a Korean cohort: comparative analysis with Asian, Caucasian, and African populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the largest study of CYP2D6 polymorphisms in a Korean population to date. It provides a comprehensive reference for Korean pharmacogenomics and highlights important interethnic differences. The findings support the development of personalized medicine strategies based on population-specific pharmacogenetic data.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Properties of Putative APSES Transcription Factor AfpA in <em>Aspergillus fumigatus</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aspergillus fumigatus is a major opportunistic pathogenic fungus that causes invasive aspergillosis with high mortality rates in immunocompromised patients. APSES family transcription factors regulate fungal development and virulence, but the function of the putative APSES-type transcription factor AfpA (AFUA_5g11390) remains uncharacterized. To investigate the roles of AfpA in A. fumigatus, we constructed the ΔafpA mutant and performed phenotypic analyses, RT-qPCR analyses, and virulence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Chromium Adhesion Layer Thickness on Contact Resistance and Schottky Barrier Characteristics in WSe<sub>2</sub> Field-Effect Transistor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While metal adhesion layers are commonly used in the fabrication of field-effect transistors (FETs) based on two-dimensional (2D) materials, the impact of adhesion layer thickness on device performance remains insufficiently explored. In this study, we systematically investigate how the thickness of a Cr adhesion layer influences the contact resistance and Schottky barrier characteristics of multilayer WSe(2) FETs. Contact resistance results, extracted via the transfer length method for Cr...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilization Pattern of Acupuncture and Its Associated Predictors for Cancer Pain in South Korea: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first study to explore real-world use of acupuncture for cancer pain in South Korea. Greater pain severity, perceived safety, ease of access, and social support were associated with higher acupuncture use. These findings suggest that improved patient education and integration of acupuncture into cancer care may enhance pain management for Korean patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell-Free DNA Versus Circulating Tumor Cells: A Pilot Study of Alpha-Fetoprotein Analysis for Diagnosis and Treatment Monitoring in Hepatocellular Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Serum alpha-fetoprotein (AFP) is widely used for hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) management, yet its limited sensitivity and specificity restrict diagnostic and prognostic utility. In this study, we explore the clinical potential of AFP quantification from cell-free DNA (cfDNA) and circulating tumor cells (CTCs) using a novel bead-based liquid biopsy platform. Following isolation, AFP abundance in cfDNA was quantified by qPCR, while AFP protein expression in CTCs was assessed via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical redox agent-mediated dealloying enables structural tuning of nanoporous Mg for hydrogen storage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We synthesized nanoporous Mg via chemical dealloying, utilizing various redox-active aromatic hydrocarbons. The nanoporous structure offers a high specific surface area and shortened hydrogen diffusion pathways, leading to enhanced hydrogen sorption kinetics. The resulting performance closely correlates with redox-driven structural features, highlighting the importance of agent selection for optimising hydrogen storage behaviour.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monomeric Sr Complexes Combined with Tetradentate Enaminolate Ligands for Containing Sr Thin-Film Deposition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[New strontium complexes, Sr(ONO1)(2) (strontium-1-(bis(2-methoxyethyl)amino)-3,3-dimethylbut-1-en-2-olate) (1), Sr(ONO2)(2) (strontium-1-(bis(2-ethoxyethyl)amino)-3,3-dimethylbut-1-en-2-olate) (2), and Sr(ONO3)(2) (strontium-2-(bis(2-methoxyethyl)amino)-1-(dimethylamino)ethen-1-olate) (3), were successfully synthesized and characterized using tetradentate ligands. The molecular structures of 1-3 were elucidated by nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) spectroscopy, thermogravimetric analysis (TGA),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and Anti-Inflammatory Effects of Engineered Extracellular Vesicles (ILB-202) for NF-κB Inhibition: A Double-Blind, Randomized, Placebo-Controlled Phase 1 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Excessive activation of NF-κB is implicated in the pathogenesis of numerous inflammatory and autoimmune diseases; however, conventional NF-κB inhibitors often cause widespread immunosuppression. In contrast, extracellular vesicles (EVs) are promising vehicles for therapeutic cargo delivery with advantages including reduced risk of replication. In this single-centre, randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled phase 1 trial, we evaluated ILB-202, an engineered, allogeneic EV derived from HEK293...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Biportal Endoscopic Laminectomy Equivalent to Microscopic Laminectomy in Patients With Lumbar Spinal Stenosis? A Multicenter, Assessor-blind, Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study found biportal endoscopic laminectomy to be equivalent to microscopic laminectomy in functional outcomes at 12 months. However, the observed differences do not represent clinically meaningful benefits that patients would perceive. Until high-quality evidence demonstrates patient-important advantages, we recommend against the wide adoption of this technique in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strain-Engineered Monolithic Multi-Band LEDs for Simultaneous Short-Wavelength and Mid-Wavelength Infrared Emission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiple quantum well (MQW) light-emitting diodes (LEDs) provide precise wavelength control, making them ideal light sources. However, achieving simultaneous short-wavelength infrared (SWIR, 1-3 µm) and mid-wavelength infrared (MWIR, 3-5 µm) emission from a single LED presents significant technical challenges due to lattice mismatch and reduced quantum efficiency when MQW structures with distinct bandgap energies are integrated onto a single substrate. As a result, most LEDs typically operate in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defect Localized Mechanoluminescence Model in Copper Doped Zinc Sulfide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Doped zinc sulfide microparticles exhibit the ability to mechanically tune their luminescence properties, making them promising candidates for mechanoluminescence materials that can be used in a diverse array of next-generation optoelectronics. However, their mechanism remains unclear and is often attributed to intricate analytical misinterpretations, which impede the development of a fundamental theory for improving this innovative technology. Here, we visualize the mechanoluminescence dynamics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MITE: the Minimum Information about a Tailoring Enzyme database for capturing specialized metabolite biosynthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Secondary or specialized metabolites show extraordinary structural diversity and potent biological activities relevant for clinical and industrial applications. The biosynthesis of these metabolites usually starts with the assembly of a core 'scaffold', which is subsequently modified by tailoring enzymes to define the molecule's final structure and, in turn, its biological activity profile. Knowledge about reaction and substrate specificity of tailoring enzymes is essential for understanding and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of metabolite profiles and policosanol contents in the sprout of Oriental wheat cultivars (<em>Triticum turgidum</em> ssp. <em>turanicum</em>)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings provide valuable insights into the phytochemical metabolism of Oriental wheat sprouts and illustrate the influence of geographical conditions on metabolite profiles. The study highlights the potential of Oriental wheat sprouts as a valuable dietary source of policosanols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of surgical outcomes of laparoscopic appendectomy performed by six surgeons with different subspecialties: a retrospective cohort study using risk-adjusted cumulative summation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Outcomes of laparoscopic appendectomy varied by subspecialty and length of experience. However, each surgeon showed trends of decreasing surgical failure over time. These results suggest that the surgeon's subspecialty minimally affects the outcomes of laparoscopic appendectomy, reflecting its fundamental nature within general surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Spinal Cord and Canal Segmentation in Degenerative Cervical Myelopathy : The Role of Interactive Learning Models with manual Click]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We found that the interactive segmentation model significantly outperformed the auto-segmentation model. By incorporating simple manual inputs, the interactive model effectively identified regions of interest, particularly in the complex and irregular shapes of the spinal cord, demonstrating both enhanced accuracy and adaptability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electron and proton FLASH beam dosimetry using unified alanine, EBT-XD, and HD-V2 Gafchromic film dosimeters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The unified alanine and film dosimeters enabled simultaneous irradiation of the alanine and the films, with combined relative standard uncertainties of 2.4% (k = 1) for the alanine dosimeter and 3.5% (k = 1) for the EBT-XD films at the electron FLASH beam. For the proton FLASH beam, these uncertainties were 3.2% (k = 1) for both the alanine dosimeter and the EBT-XD films. Until dosimetry guidelines for the FLASH RT community are established by a working group such as AAPM TG-359,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proposal for setting a passing score for the Korean Nursing Licensing Examination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The modified Angoff and Hofstee methods were successfully applied to the KNLE. Using the actual correct answer rate as an indicator to derive expected minimum competency was shown to be effective. This approach could streamline future standard-setting processes, particularly when converting to CBT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intranasal NS1-truncated live attenuated canine influenza vaccine confers superior protection compared to inactivated vaccine in beagles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canine influenza virus (CIV) H3N2 continues to circulate among companion animals, posing a zoonotic risk due to its potential for cross-species transmission. However, currently available inactivated vaccines offer limited mucosal immunity and suboptimal protection. Here, we developed a novel intranasal live attenuated CIV H3N2 vaccine carrying a truncated nonstructural protein 1 (NS1) gene and evaluated its safety, immunogenicity, and protective efficacy in beagle dogs. The NS1-truncated LAIV...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aberrant neuronal firing: a paracrine route to glioblastoma expansion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings illuminate a pathway through which environmental factors contribute to GBM regrowth following chemotherapy and propose a potential therapeutic target, neuron-cancer communication, to prevent GBM recurrence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of home-visit counselling on maternal and child health and nutrition by Barangay health workers: a quasi-experimental study from Eastern Visayas, Philippines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ttCF strategy improved the frequency and quality of BHW home visits and demonstrated promising impacts on maternal mental health. However, additional enabling interventions are needed to improve maternal and child diet and nutrition outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Periodontitis and high phosphate intake alone or in combination adversely affect the kidney]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Regardless of periodontitis, 0.9% HP intake did not affect periodontal tissue. Renal fibrosis and macrophage infiltration induced by HP intake and periodontitis, respectively, worsened when combined, indicating a synergistic adverse effect. These changes were reversed by IFX, suggesting that TNF-α inhibition may alleviate renal injury caused by periodontitis and HP intake.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exercise as a Therapeutic Intervention for Alzheimer's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a common form of dementia characterized by cognitive decline and abnormal accumulation of proximate neurotoxins in older adults. It accounts for up to 80% of all dementia cases. AD is not exclusively attributed to aging; rather, it involves complex and multifactorial brain changes that can lead to severe functional dependence and ultimately death. Although there has been progress in the development of novel treatments for AD, they are yet to yield disease-modifying...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potential Role of Extracellular Vesicles in Mediating Effects of Exercise on Brain Function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exercise has a remarkable capacity to improve brain function by fostering neuronal plasticity, which enables us to better cope with various psychological and cognitive challenges. Numerous studies have demonstrated the neuroprotective effects of exercise. However, the underlying molecular mechanisms of the neuroprotective effects of exercise are not yet fully understood. In particular, the role of exercise-induced secretion of peripheral factors into circulation that influence the brain is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimum Exercise Model in Humans Based on Oxygen Uptake and Physiological Parameters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding exercise intensity is essential for optimizing training outcomes and minimizing health risks. This chapter introduces key physiological and subjective parameters used to assess exercise intensity, including heart rate reserve (HRR), oxygen uptake reserve (VO2R), maximal oxygen consumption (VO2max), and ratings of perceived exertion (RPE). Standardized classifications from organizations such as the American College of Sports Medicine (ACSM) are presented, alongside practical methods...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In-silico and In-vitro Gene Expression Analysis on Docetaxel and Methotrexate-induced Cytotoxicity in Oral Cancer Cell Line]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FairDITA: Disentangled Image-Text Alignment for Fair Skin Cancer Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep learning have significantly improved skin cancer classification, yet concerns regarding algorithmic fairness persist because of performance disparities across skin tone groups. Existing methods often attempt to mitigate bias by suppressing sensitive attributes within images. However, they are fundamentally limited by the entanglement of lesion characteristics and skin tone in visual inputs. To address this challenge, we propose a novel contrastive learning framework that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meaningful changes in physical function and pain in patients with knee osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impacts of grain source and sodium bicarbonate supplementation level on calf performance, nutrient digestion, and rumen fermentation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tracking glymphatic dysfunction in isolated rapid eye movement sleep behavior disorder: a longitudinal neuroimaging study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The baseline DTI-ALPS index may be a promising biomarker for predicting iRBD patients at risk for conversion to alpha-synucleinopathy. The decrease in the ALPS index observed over time may reflect progressive neurodegenerative processes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between cerebrovascular imaging markers and glymphatic function in a large-scale cognitively normal population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cerebrovascular imaging findings are significantly associated with glymphatic dysfunction in cognitively normal individuals, highlighting the need for further studies on glymphatic-targeted interventions in cerebrovascular disease prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complete genome sequence of turbot circovirus strain TurCV10LN-18/2021 from diseased <em>Scophthalmus maximus</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We reported the complete genome sequence of turbot circovirus (TurCV) strain TurCV10LN-18/2021, detected in a diseased turbot (Scophthalmus maximus) in China. TurCV is responsible for the emerging acute hemorrhagic syndrome (EAHS) in farmed turbot. The availability of the complete genome sequence facilitates the investigation of circovirus epidemiology in turbot.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of intraoperative complications in men undergoing inflatable penile prosthesis placement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In men undergoing IPP placement, a history of ICI, a history of radical prostatectomy, and a history of radiation are all independently associated with increased risk of intraoperative complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Learning-Based Diagnosis of Femoropopliteal Artery Steno-Occlusion Using Maximum Intensity Projection Images of CT Angiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: To develop and validate deep learning-based models for detecting significant steno-occlusion (SSO)-defined as luminal narrowing greater than 50%-of the femoropopliteal arteries using maximum intensity projection (MIP) images from lower extremity CT angiography (CTA). Methods: This retrospective study utilized MIP images of lower extremity CTA performed between January 2021 and December 2023 for internal model development. Deep learning-based models were developed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanotechnology-based strategies for overcoming clinical limitations of PROTACs in cancer therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proteolysis-targeting chimeras (PROTACs) have emerged as a promising next-generation therapeutic modality by enabling complete degradation of target proteins rather than transient inhibition. However, increasing clinical studies have reported adverse effects of PROTACs that resemble those observed with conventional small-molecule drugs, highlighting the need for strategies to improve tumor specificity and reduce systemic toxicity. To overcome these limitations, tumor-targeted approaches have...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating Price Elasticity of Cannabis Use Among U.S. Adolescents: Evidence From States With Recreational Cannabis Commercialization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: The commercialization of recreational cannabis has led to increased concern over adolescent cannabis use in the U.S. Given that price-based regulations have the potential to reduce cannabis consumption and mitigate the adverse effects associated with cannabis use, this study aims to assess the price elasticity of cannabis use among U.S. adolescents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of Current, Daily, and Heavy Smokers Among Adolescents in 97 Countries: A Global Population-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Understanding adolescent smoking behavior is crucial for developing effective prevention strategies; however, research on adolescent smoking remains limited. Thus, we investigated the global prevalence of current, daily, and heavy smokers among adolescents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved Perceptual Loss for Sketch Image Domain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditional perceptual loss functions, primarily designed for photographic images, often perform poorly in the sketch domain due to significant differences in visual representation. To address this domain gap, we propose an improved perceptual loss specifically designed for sketch images. Our method fine-tunes a pre-trained VGG-16 model on the ImageNet-Sketch dataset while strategically replacing max-pooling layers with spatial and channel attention mechanisms. We comprehensively evaluate our...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Nature and Measure of Critical Thinking: The PACIER Framework and Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Based on the PACIER model of critical thinking, involving six facets for critical thinking (Problem solving, Analysis, Creative thinking, Interpretation, Evaluation, Reasoning), the empirical results of a new computer-based assessment (PACIER Critical Thinking Assessment) are presented. The data is based on a study of 700 middle school 11-year-old students in the United Arab Emirates, who were tested five times during a school year. In the assessment framework, test items are described, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is the Prognostic Significance of Culture-Documented Breakthrough Invasive Pulmonary Aspergillosis in Patients with Hematological Malignancies? A Propensity Score-Adjusted Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mold-active prophylaxis has reduced the incidence of invasive pulmonary aspergillosis (IPA) in patients with hematological malignancies (HMs), but breakthrough IPA (Bt-IPA) is increasingly encountered. Therefore, we studied determinants of Bt-IPA risk and its prognostic significance. We retrospectively reviewed culture-positive proven/probable IPA cases in HM patients at MD Anderson Cancer Center (2016-2021). Bt-IPA and non-Bt-IPA cases were compared to characterize risk factors, clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Insulin Resistance with Dysglycemia in Elder Koreans: Age- and Sex-Specific Cutoff Values]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Dysglycemia including pre-diabetes mellitus (Pre-DM) and type 2 diabetes mellitus (T2DM) is associated with insulin resistance. This study aimed to support personalized early diagnosis of dysglycemia by proposing optimal, sex- and age-specific cutoff values for Homeostatic Model Assessment of Insulin Resistance (HOMA-IR) and Homeostatic Model Assessment of Beta-Cell Function (HOMA-β) in Koreans aged ≥65 years. Methods: This study analyzed 3862 older Koreans from the 8th...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine-Learning-Based Survival Prediction in Castration-Resistant Prostate Cancer: A Multi-Model Analysis Using a Comprehensive Clinical Dataset]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose: Accurate survival prediction is essential for optimizing the treatment planning in patients with castration-resistant prostate cancer (CRPC). However, the traditional statistical models often underperform due to limited variable inclusion and an inability to account for complex, multidimensional data interactions. Methods: We retrospectively collected 46 clinical, laboratory, and pathological variables from 801 patients with CRPC, covering the disease course from the initial disease...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Repurposing SGLT-2 Inhibitors as a Novel Therapeutic Strategy for Treatment-Resistant Meniere's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Meniere's disease (MD) is a chronic inner ear disorder affecting approximately 0.2% of the population, with 30% of patients remaining refractory to conventional treatments. The pathophysiology involves endolymphatic hydrops, suggesting that agents affecting fluid homeostasis might provide therapeutic benefit. Sodium-glucose cotransporter 2 (SGLT-2) inhibitors, originally developed for diabetes, offer unique mechanisms including natriuresis and osmotic diuresis that may address the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nano-Heterojunction NO<sub>2</sub> Gas Sensor Based on <em>n</em>-ZnO Nanorods/<em>p</em>-NiO Nanoparticles Under UV Illumination at Room Temperature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Room-temperature (RT) gas sensors for nitrogen dioxide (NO(2)) detection face persistent challenges, including reliance on high operating temperatures and inefficient charge carrier utilization under UV activation. To address these limitations, we engineered a p-n nano-heterojunction (NHJ) gas sensor by integrating p-type nickel oxide (NiO) nanoparticles onto n-type zinc oxide (ZnO) nanorods. This architecture leverages UV-driven carrier generation and interfacial electric fields at the NHJ to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication and Evaluation of Ceramic-Based Hollow Fiber Membrane Modules for Hemodialysis Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The application of ceramic membranes in hemodialysis modules remains underexplored, as prior investigations have primarily concentrated on flat-sheet samples or small-scale assessments. This study advances the field by fabricating Al(2)O(3) hollow fiber membranes, integrating them into a lab-scale module, and systematically evaluating the influence of sintering temperature on their structural characteristics, hemocompatibility, and dialysis performance. Al(2)O(3) hollow fiber membranes were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hypoxia and Multilineage Communication in 3D Organoids for Human Disease Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organoids, self-organizing, three-dimensional (3D) multicellular structures derived from tissues or stem cells, offer physiologically relevant models for studying human development and disease. Compared to conventional two-dimensional (2D) cell cultures and animal models, organoids more accurately recapitulate the architecture and function of human organs. Among the critical microenvironmental cues influencing organoid behavior, hypoxia and multilineage communication are particularly important...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Maritime Search and Rescue Planning via Genetic Algorithms: Incorporating Civilian Vessel Collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a biomimetic optimization approach for maritime Search and Rescue (SAR) planning using a Genetic Algorithm (GA). The goal is to maximize the number of detected drifting targets by optimally deploying both official and civilian Search and Rescue Units (SRUs). The proposed method incorporates a POD-adjusted fitness function with collision-avoidance constraints and is enhanced by a greedy initialization strategy. To validate its effectiveness, we compare the GA against a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graph-Driven Micro-Expression Rendering with Emotionally Diverse Expressions for Lifelike Digital Humans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Micro-expressions, characterized by brief and subtle facial muscle movements, are essential for conveying nuanced emotions in digital humans, yet existing rendering techniques often produce rigid or emotionally monotonous animations due to the inadequate modeling of temporal dynamics and action unit interdependencies. This paper proposes a graph-driven framework for micro-expression rendering that generates emotionally diverse and lifelike expressions. We employ a 3D-ResNet-18 backbone network...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Advances in Optoelectronic Synaptic Devices for Neuromorphic Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We explore recent advancements in optoelectronic synaptic devices across four key aspects: mechanisms, materials, synaptic properties, and applications. First, we discuss fundamental working principles, including oxygen vacancy ionization, defect trapping, and heterojunction-based charge modulation, which contribute to synaptic plasticity. Next, we examine the role of 0D, 1D, and 2D materials in optimizing device performance, focusing on their unique electronic, optical, and mechanical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Micro-CT and Histomorphometric Analysis of Degradability and New Bone Formation of Anodized Mg-Ca System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The surface treatments and various magnesium alloys are applied to improve the fast degradation rate and resulting negative effects of magnesium alloys. This study aimed to assess the effect of anodic oxidation treatment of magnesium-calcium (Mg-Ca) systems by creating artificial bone defects in the tibia of rats. The cylinder magnesium implants were fabricated using a Mg-xCa (x = 0, 1, 5 wt.%) binary alloy. Degradability and new bone formation were observed at two and six weeks using micro-CT....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polymer Network-Based Nanogels and Microgels: Design, Classification, Synthesis, and Applications in Drug Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymer network-based nanogels (NGs) and microgels (MGs) have emerged as highly versatile platforms for advanced drug delivery, owing to their tunable architecture, biocompatibility, and responsiveness to diverse stimuli. This review presents a comprehensive and structured analysis of NG/MGs, encompassing their classification based on polymer origin, crosslinking mechanisms, composition, charge, stimuli-responsiveness, and structural architecture. We detail synthesis strategies-including inverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applications of Hydrogels for Next-Generation Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogels have garnered significant attention as multifunctional materials in next-generation rechargeable batteries due to their high ionic conductivity, mechanical flexibility, and structural tunability. This review presents a comprehensive overview of hydrogel types-including natural, synthetic, composite, carbon-based, conductive polymer, and MOF hydrogels-and their synthesis methods, such as chemical crosslinking, self-assembly, and irradiation-based techniques. Characterization tools like...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Flavor Stability of Yuja (<em>Citrus junos</em> Tanaka) Oil-Based Nano-Carriers and Dried Gels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nano-carriers and dried gels were prepared to prevent the inherent flavor of Yuja (Citrus junos Tanaka) from rapidly deteriorating. The properties and stability of volatile components of Yuja dried gels were compared by using colloidal systems (nanoemulsion (NE) and nanostructured lipid carrier (NLC)), coating materials (maltodextrin (MD) and a mixture of MD and β-cyclodextrin (MD/βCD)), and drying processes (spray-drying and freeze-drying). Drying was found to have a significant effect on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applications of Conductive Polymer Hydrogels for Supercapacitor, Solar Cell, and Energy Conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogels are rapidly emerging as a versatile and promising platform for advancing energy storage and conversion technologies. Their intrinsic properties-such as high water content, excellent ionic conductivity, and inherent mechanical flexibility-position them as key materials for a wide range of applications, including supercapacitors, flexible membranes, and components in fuel cells and solar cells. Despite significant progress, challenges remain in enhancing their mechanical durability,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polymer Gel-Based Triboelectric Nanogenerators: Conductivity and Morphology Engineering for Advanced Sensing Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymer gel-based triboelectric nanogenerators (TENGs) have emerged as versatile platforms for self-powered sensing due to their inherent softness, stretchability, and tunable conductivity. This review comprehensively explores the roles of polymer gels in TENG architecture, including their function as triboelectric layers, electrodes, and conductive matrices. We analyze four operational modes-vertical contact-separation, lateral-sliding, single-electrode, and freestanding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Size-Controlled Fabrication of Alginate Hydrogel Microbeads Optimized for Lipase Entrapment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enzyme entrapment in alginate hydrogel microbeads is an effective method of immobilization for industrial applications, but many fabrication methods for alginate microbeads involve oil, organic solvents, or high temperatures that reduce enzymatic activity. In this study, we employed an oil- and solvent-free gas-shearing technique to prepare alginate microbeads for the entrapment of Candida rugosa lipase (CRL), thereby minimizing thermal- and solvent-induced inactivation. To enhance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inflammation-Responsive Hydrogels in Perioperative Pain and Wound Management: Design Strategies and Emerging Potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surgical procedures trigger dynamic inflammatory responses that influence postoperative pain, wound healing, and long-term outcomes. Conventional therapies rely on the systemic delivery of anti-inflammatory and analgesic agents, which often lack spatiotemporal precision and carry significant side effects. Inflammation-responsive hydrogels offer a promising alternative by enabling localized, stimulus-adaptive drug release aligned with the evolving biochemical milieu of surgical wounds. These...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Astrocytes in Fear Memory Processing: Molecular Mechanisms Across the Amygdala-Hippocampus-Prefrontal Cortex Network]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fear memory is a critical adaptive process that enables organisms to avoid potential threats and survive in complex environments. Traditionally viewed as a neuronal phenomenon, emerging evidence has demonstrated that astrocytes play a fundamental role in fear memory acquisition, consolidation, extinction, and retrieval across the distributed neural network encompassing the amygdala, hippocampus, and prefrontal cortex. This review presents recent advances in our understanding of the molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rolling Circle Amplification as a Molecular Tool for Spatially Resolved Signal Amplification in Single Molecule Counting Assay]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There have been rising interests in ultra-sensitive biosensing technologies for early diagnosis and prognosis monitoring of infectious diseases, cancers, and neurodegenerative diseases. Digital signal readout strategy represented by digital ELISA or digital PCR, advanced biosensing field enormously, which enables detection of biomolecules under the detection limit of conventional biosensing methods. However, due to the need for compartmentalization and limited multiplex capability, it has been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Evaluation of Combined Denoising and Resolution Enhancement Algorithms for Intravital Two-Photon Imaging of Organs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intravital two-photon microscopy enables deep-tissue imaging of subcellular structures in live animals, but its original spatial resolution and image quality are limited by scattering, motion, and low signal-to-noise ratios. To address these challenges, we used a combination of tissue stabilization, denoising methods, and motion correction, together with resolution enhancement algorithms, including enhanced Super-Resolution Radial Fluctuations (eSRRF) and deconvolution, to acquire high-fidelity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexible and Stretchable Microneedle Electrode Arrays by Soft Lithography for Continuous Monitoring of Glucose]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous monitoring of glucose (CGM) level is of utmost importance to diabetic patients, especially with no or minimal pain. Microneedle arrays with desired electrode patterns have been fabricated by soft lithographic molding, and the patterned electrodes were formed via shadow evaporation through a shadow mask that was made from a modified molding technique. With immobilization of glucose oxidase (GOx), the microneedle electrode arrays (MEAs) have been successfully employed for the in vitro...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SERS-Driven Evolution of Lateral and Vertical Flow Assays in Medical Diagnostics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface-enhanced Raman scattering (SERS) has emerged as a powerful signal amplification strategy to address the inherent limitations of conventional flow-based diagnostic methods such as lateral flow analysis (LFA) and vertical flow analysis (VFA). By incorporating SERS-active nanostructures into these platforms, SERS-integrated LFA and VFA systems have significantly improved sensitivity, specificity, and multiplexing performance while maintaining the simplicity and portability of conventional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Innovation: The Impact of National Health Policies on Optometry Research in East Asia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the optometric research landscape in three East Asian countries-China, Japan, and Korea-analysing how research trends align with each country's national health strategies. By evaluating published articles and reviews from national journals between 2006 March 2025, we identify key areas of focus, including paediatric optometry, refractive errors, and advanced diagnostic techniques. China's research emphasises pathogenesis and retinal diseases, driven by its aging population...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Co-essentiality Network of Cancer Driver Genes Better Prioritizes Anticancer Drugs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diverse molecular networks have been extensively studied to discover therapeutic targets and repurpose approved drugs. However, it is necessary to select a suitable network since the performance of network medicine relies heavily on the completeness and characteristics of the selected network. Although a network using gene essentiality from cancer cells could be an effective platform for identifying anticancer targets, efforts to apply these networks in therapeutic applications have been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physical Reservoir Computing System via Hybrid Ferroelectric-Ionic Transistors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In-materia computing, harnessing material complexity for energy-efficient computation, drives breakthroughs in constructing physical reservoir computing (PRC), a promising paradigm for energy-efficient handling of dynamic temporal tasks. However, the integration of PRC components into complementary metal-oxide-semiconductor (CMOS)-compatible and very large-scale integration (VLSI)-scalable platforms remains challenging, particularly in two-terminal devices that utilize exotic material systems....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNF4 and USP7 coordinate spatial regulation of SLX4 stability within the PML nuclear bodies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To protect the genome from the formation of DNA breaks by nucleases involved in DNA repair, cells have evolved multiple levels of regulatory strategies. One key regulator of nuclease activity is the scaffold protein SLX4, which plays important roles in repairing DNA damage induced by mitomycin C (MMC) and camptothecin (CPT) as well as in the resolution of stalled replication forks. Since SLX4 regulates the activity of nucleases such as SLX1, MUS81, and XPF, whose uncontrolled activity could...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-Newtonian Behavior of Spherical Coacervate Micelle Dispersions in Aqueous Media]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-Newtonian viscoelastic behavior of disordered spherical micelle dispersions composed of complex coacervate core micelles (C3Ms) in aqueous media is investigated by combining rotational rheometry and microfluidic particle focusing measurements. C3Ms were prepared by mixing oppositely charged block copolymers, resulting in spherical micelles with electrostatically neutral coacervate cores surrounded by hydrophilic coronas. Despite the spherical morphology and dispersion in low-viscosity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biodegradable Implantable Electronics with Wireless Technology for Real-Time Clinical Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wireless biodegradable electronics offer a transformative approach to transient biomedical applications by combining fully implantable, resorbable architectures with untethered communication and power delivery. These systems address key limitations of conventional implants, including infection risk, foreign body response, and the need for surgical retrieval. As biodegradable implants are designed to disappear after fulfilling their function, wireless operation is essential to avoid permanent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic Insights into Short Stature in Children Born Small for Gestational Age: A Korean Multicenter Exome Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SGA-SS has a heterogeneous genetic basis, with CNVs significantly contributing. The variable presentation of 22q11.2 microdeletion syndrome highlights its relevance. A genetic diagnosis is more likely in familial cases or those with ID/DD, supporting the utility of genetic testing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intervention of Rutin and Ochnaflavone in the Attenuation of Neuroinflammation and Neuronal Apoptosis in Spinal Cord Injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignA multimethod experimental study.ObjectivesSpinal cord injury (SCI) has devastating neurological consequences, mainly through secondary injury mechanisms. Chinese medicine-derived flavonoids, including rutin (RUT) and ochnaflavone (OCE), have shown potential in modulating these processes, although their molecular mechanisms are not understood. This study aims to elucidate the neuroprotective mechanisms of RUB and OCE in SCI, with an emphasis on their regulatory function in microglia...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lipid-Oxidative Enzymes and Fenton-Like Reactions Are Synergistic in Promoting Membrane Lipid Peroxidation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipid peroxidation (LPO) of cellular membranes is a near-universal indicator of aging and disease, yet the mechanistic link between the LPO and disease remains elusive. In this study, we demonstrate that efficient LPO in model membranes is accomplished through synergy between selective enzymatic oxidation by lipoxygenase (LOX) and nonspecific oxidation by reactive oxygen species (ROS). Through fluorescence-based oxidation kinetic measurements, we show that soluble ROS alone fails to induce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Pd/CeO<sub>2</sub> on the Abatement of Unburnt Hydrocarbon Emissions from Gasoline Vehicles during the Cold-Start Period]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unburnt hydrocarbon emissions from gasoline vehicles contribute to air pollution and pose health risks, necessitating effective removal strategies. Conventional three-way catalysts (TWCs) effectively oxidize hydrocarbons to CO(2) at temperatures above 250 °C. However, the increasing adoption of turbocharged gasoline engines, which emit exhaust gases at significantly lower temperatures (∼300 °C versus ∼ 800 °C in conventional vehicles), has renewed concerns over hydrocarbon emissions. The primary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Duodenal Strictures Between Crohn's and Non-Crohn's Diseases in Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although acquired duodenal strictures are rare in children, they can develop in pediatric patients with CD or EGID. The measurement of serum ASCA and fecal calprotectin levels before endoscopic and histopathological investigations may identify the presence of organic causes of duodenal strictures in children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation climate and clinic personnel attitudes in primary care towards a mental health and drug use preventive intervention for hispanic families: preliminary findings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the availability of preventive interventions to address mental health and drug use among Hispanic adolescents, few are implemented in real-world settings. Favorable attitudes towards evidence-based practices and a better implementation climate can facilitate the successful execution of interventions in real-word settings to ameliorate health disparities among Hispanic youth. The purpose of this study was to investigate how implementation climate influences attitudes toward a mental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[System Development for Measuring Nursing Workload Based on the Real-Time Location Information]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: There are no objective measurement methods that provide empirical data on nursing workload. Aim: This study aimed to develop a system to measure nursing workload using beacons and a smartphone based on the real-time location information. Methods: This was a study of the technological development of a system for measuring nursing workload using beacons and smartphones. The validation of the system developed was performed by assessing the recognition rate of beacons by multiple...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of Dermal Thickness Across 10 Areas and Injection Depth After Polynucleotide Injection Using Rejumate Automatic 0.8-mm 9-pin Injector on the Face Using 33-MHz Sonography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Rejumate automatic injector reliably delivers PN at a controlled depth, showing minimal variability across injections. This precision supports improved safety and efficacy in PN delivery, providing a valuable reference for clinical application in aesthetic treatments. Given the anatomical differences in dermal thickness across facial regions, this standardized approach may optimize outcomes and increase patient satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of glycolytic enzyme expression and thyroiditis on the aggressiveness of papillary thyroid carcinoma: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Overexpression of LDHA, PKM2, GLUT1, and MCT4 is associated with PTC. CLT is significantly associated with an increased incidence of gross ETE and, paradoxically, with a reduced recurrence rate in PTC. LDHA expression was lower in the presence of CLT, whereas PKM2 remained consistently linked to a higher recurrence rate in its absence. Among the evaluated glycolytic enzymes, PKM2 may serve as a biomarker for recurrence in PTC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Statistical cure fraction in patients with borderline resectable pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma undergoing neoadjuvant therapy followed by radical resection: a secondary analysis of reconstructed individual patient data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: From this study, we concluded that a cure can be expected in around eight percent of patients with BR-PDAC after NAT followed by radical resection, which would be helpful in counseling patients, as well as deciding whether to perform the surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgeon's aspect of an expert consensus-based practical recommendation for surgical treatment of hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factor analysis and surgical outcomes in emergency gastrectomy for gastric perforation: a single-center retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Emergency gastrectomy can be a viable treatment for gastric perforation in regions with a high incidence of gastric cancer. However, patients with advanced age, delayed symptom onset, or poor physical status require careful surgical planning. Tailored strategies may improve outcomes, particularly in high-incidence regions for gastric cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical treatment of hepatocellular carcinoma: an expert consensus-based practical recommendation from the Korean Liver Cancer Association]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Compared with other treatments, surgical resection is an effective treatment method with the lowest local recurrence rate and the highest survival rate for hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC). To achieve excellent results after surgical treatment, it is essential to carefully select patients who are suitable for hepatic resection and minimize postoperative complications and liver function decline through standardized surgical methods and pre- and postoperative management. However, domestic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Limited survival benefit of preoperative transarterial chemoembolization in huge hepatocellular carcinoma due to the prognostic impact of satellite nodules: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preoperative TACE for huge HCC was associated with reduced MVI but did not improve RFS and OS. Survival outcomes were more significantly influenced by SN, suggesting that upfront hepatectomy without TACE should be prioritized.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Effects of the Spatial Distribution of Catalytic Sites on Sulfur Nucleation Behaviors and Electrochemical Performances of Lithium-Sulfur Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving 3D Li(2)S morphologies and accelerating polysulfide conversion reactions are critical for realizing high-energy lithium-sulfur (Li-S) batteries. Although electrolytes containing high Gutmann donor number components facilitate transition from film-like to 3D Li(2)S morphologies, challenges arising from polysulfide diffusion and incomplete polysulfide conversion remain unresolved. Catalyst design strategies optimized for high donor electrolyte systems are essential in overcoming these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Status quo of histocompatibility testing and prospects for virtual crossmatching within the Korean kidney allocation system: survey of laboratory directors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Korean HLA laboratory directors broadly support the concept and need for VXM, acknowledging its potential to improve both efficiency and equity for sensitized patients. However, the lack of standardization in HLA testing application and interpretation remains a significant practical challenge. National initiatives and multidisciplinary collaboration are essential before integrating VXM into the Korean KAS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deceased organ donation: laboratory testing and histocompatibility assessment in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Histocompatibility testing is essential for ensuring both safety and fairness in deceased donor organ transplantation. In Korea, such testing is strictly regulated under the Organ Transplant Act and centralized within organ procurement organization laboratories. Standardized evaluations include ABO blood typing, infectious disease screening, human leukocyte antigen (HLA) typing, and crossmatching. Current allocation policies rely on low-resolution HLA typing and mandatory complement-dependent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-human leukocyte antigen antibodies in kidney transplantation: pathogenic mechanisms, detection methods, and clinical implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The importance of non-human leukocyte antigen (HLA) antibodies in transplant immunology has become increasingly evident, as their pathogenic role in kidney allograft injury is being clarified beyond the well-established effects of donor-specific anti-HLA antibodies. This review summarizes current evidence regarding antigenic targets, pathogenic mechanisms, detection platforms, and clinical implications of non-HLA antibodies in kidney transplantation. Major antigenic targets include angiotensin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive model of public health impact of herpes zoster vaccination and related costs for adults aged ≥50 years in Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given the rapidly aging population in South Korea, the growing incidence and burden of herpes zoster (HZ) increase the need for HZ prevention. However, the public health impact of HZ vaccination has not been assessed in South Korea. This predictive modeling study estimated the public health and economic impact of available HZ vaccination strategies, using the ZOster ecoNomic Analysis (ZONA) model adapted with South Korea-specific inputs. Base case analysis involved adults ≥50 y of age (YOA),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced disc regeneration through CRISPR/Cas9-mediated SOX9 and TGFβ1 coexpression in tonsil-derived mesenchymal stromal cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mesenchymal stem cell-derived extracellular vesicles exert Th1-mediated anti-inflammatory effects via miR-146a/NF-κB pathway: comparison with dupilumab in a mouse model of atopic dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MSC-EVs offer a novel cell-free therapy for AD, demonstrating comparable or superior efficacy to dupilumab, with broader immunomodulatory effects and the advantage of a single-dose administration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of antifibrotics on the progression of pulmonary hypertension in patients with interstitial lung disease listed for lung transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2025 Position statement on active outdoor play]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The 2025 Position Statement calls for systemic changes that prioritize equitable access to active outdoor play opportunities and aims to create healthier communities. Achieved through international collaboration and consensus, the 2025 Position Statement aspires to connect, advise, inspire, and activate active outdoor play worldwide.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effectiveness of physical activity intervention on mobile phone addiction in college students: the chain mediating role of emotion regulation strategies and positive coping style]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compared with single-form exercise, combined PA is more effective in alleviating mobile phone addiction among college students, primarily through the chain mediating effects of improved emotion regulation strategies and enhanced positive coping styles. It is recommended that universities and relevant institutions promote combined physical activities to help college students reduce mobile phone addiction and improve their overall well - being.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2025 position statement on active outdoor play: process and methodology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40999371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroprotective and Neurotrophic Effects of Astaxanthin on the Brain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oxidative stress in the brain is associated with the development and progression of neurological disorders, posing antioxidant nutrients as an effective strategy for protecting neuronal cells and potentially slowing cognitive decline. Bioactive compounds from natural sources with antioxidant effects promote brain health. Among various natural compounds, astaxanthin (ASX), a potent red-pigment carotenoid found in various microorganisms and marine animals, is well recognized for its potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of hub regions in the superficial white matter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The superficial white matter (SWM) comprises short-range fibers that connect adjacent cortical regions; however, its structural connectivity remains poorly understood. In a previous dissection study, we identified anatomical "crossings" where superficial white matter fibers converge from multiple directions. Building on this, the present study investigated superficial white matter characteristics associated with these crossings using diffusion-weighted imaging data from 10 individuals in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41004160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimation of organ and effective doses for rotational cerebral angiography using the National Cancer Institute Dosimetry System for Radiography and Fluoroscopy (NCIRF)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rotational cerebral angiography requires accurate dosimetry. The National Cancer Institute Dosimetry System for Radiography and Fluoroscopy (NCIRF), a Monte Carlo-based dosimetry software, can evaluate the organ dose (OD) and effective dose (ED) with higher accuracy than the conventional Monte Carlo software (PCXMC). We estimated the OD and ED for three-dimensional digital subtraction angiography (3D-DSA) and cone beam computed tomography (CBCT) using the NCIRF, reflecting dose variations during...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-fast whole-brain T2-weighted imaging in 7 seconds using dual-type deep learning reconstruction with single-shot acquisition: clinical feasibility and comparison with conventional methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The combination of SSTSE with dual-type DL reconstruction allows for the acquisition of clinically acceptable T2WI images in just 7 s. This technique shows strong potential to reduce MRI scan times and improve clinical workflow efficiency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[<sup>11</sup>C]HSP990 PET as a translational tool to investigate the role of Hsp90 in tumours and support the development of Hsp90 therapeutics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: [^(11)C]HSP990 is a promising tracer for identifying Hsp90-overexpressing tumours and may hold potential for patient stratification, prognosis, and therapy monitoring of novel Hsp90 therapeutics. High healthy brain uptake of this tracer precluded the differentiation of the tumour in the intracranial NS/CT-2A tumour model, therefore [^(11)C]HSP990 might not be a suitable tracer for the glioblastoma imaging. Tracer with a longer half-life might be needed to compare the washout of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative anaphylaxis attributed to acetaminophen following intravenous acetaminophen administration: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Accurate identification of the causative component in intravenous acetaminophen formulations is critical. Clarifying whether the reaction is due to the active ingredient or an excipient such as mannitol helps prevent unnecessary drug restrictions and expands future treatment options.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Propeptide-mediated enhancement of hyperthermophilic subtilisin-like protease expression in Escherichia coli]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative evaluation of thyroid bed accumulation in I-131 radiotherapy: a comparison of laryngeal edema and non-edematous cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rupture of the external iliac and bilateral femoral arteries in a patient with anorexia nervosa]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This case highlights a previously unreported and fatal vascular complication of anorexia nervosa. Extreme malnutrition may cause vascular fragility, increasing the risk of arterial rupture due to structural collapse of the vessel wall. Clinicians should be aware of this rare but life-threatening complication when treating patients with severe anorexia nervosa.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PAI-1 in Skin Malignancies: a Central Regulator of Tumor Progression and Therapeutic Resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plasminogen activator inhibitor-1 (PAI-1) plays a multifaceted and central role in the tumor biology of various skin malignancies. Beyond its classical function in fibrinolysis, PAI-1 contributes to tumor progression by promoting immunosuppression, angiogenesis, cellular senescence, and tissue remodeling. Its expression is particularly elevated in aggressive disease stages across cutaneous melanoma, cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma (cSCC), cutaneous angiosarcoma (CAS), and mycosis fungoides...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Worsening Renal Function in Acute Heart Failure: Not Always Harmful]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Worsening renal function (WRF) frequently occurs in acute heart failure (AHF) and represents a clinical challenge, as it may lead to inappropriate alterations in therapy. Understanding its mechanisms and prognostic implications is essential for optimization of treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single versus two implant-supported mandibular overdentures: a systematic review and meta-analysis of implant survival and prosthetic complications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although 1-IOD may be a less invasive alternative to 2-IOD, careful consideration is necessary because of its increased incidence of prosthetic complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-dose epidural morphine for postpartum pain relief: a randomized, single-blind study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Epidural morphine following vaginal delivery reduces contraction pain but not perineal pain and prolongs the time until initial request for additional analgesia without increasing side effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and treatments of Sleep-Disordered breathing in people with down syndrome: A narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The prevalence of SDB is high in people with DS regardless of age and might be associated with characteristics of DS (craniofacial hypoplasia, obesity, and congenital heart disease). USPs might be an easy and useful screening tool for SDB in DS. Non-invasive ventilation therapy and hypoglossal nerve stimulation therapy would be effective and tolerable treatments in people with DS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of AI-driven anatomical recognition in robotic gastrectomy: A multicenter retrospective analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The AI model demonstrated strong external validity and improved surgeons' recognition of anatomical structures during RDG. Its integration into clinical practice can potentially reduce the rate of surgical complications and improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2 infection in lung transplant recipients: a single-center retrospective study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The incidence of COVID-19 in LTx recipients was similar to that in the general Japanese population, whereas the disease severity in LTx recipients remained high even after the Omicron era. Continuous development of preventive and early therapeutic interventions is required for these vulnerable groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Nonlinear Heart Rate Variability in Postoperative Complex Congenital Heart Disease: Insights From Repaired Tetralogy of Fallot and Fontan Palliation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Postoperative patients with complex congenital heart disease (CHD), such as those who have undergone Fontan procedures or Tetralogy of Fallot (TOF) repairs, often experience complications, including arrhythmias and heart failure. Heart rate variability (HRV) analysis assesses autonomic function and predicts cardiac outcomes; however, conventional linear methods have limitations, particularly in pediatric populations with variable heart rates. Nonlinear HRV analysis offers a robust alternative....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coupled-Cluster in Density Functional Theory Embedding Applied to Static Polarizabilities in Aqueous Environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a study of static polarizabilities of organic molecules in aqueous environments using projection-based coupled-cluster in density functional theory quantum embedding. We propose two methods for the computation of supermolecular polarizabilities: an iterative embedding approach and a finite-field approach. The performance of these methods is tested against regular coupled-cluster singles and doubles (CCSD) theory. The static polarizability tensor of the investigated organic molecules...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conducting composite scaffolds for antibacterial drug release and <em>in situ</em> electrochemical monitoring of bacterial growth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conducting polymer scaffolds have gained significant attention as dynamic platforms for interfacing with biological systems, particularly in bioelectronic and tissue engineering applications. However, their potential in antimicrobial therapy and infection-responsive drug delivery remains unexplored. This study presents a multifunctional scaffold system based on PEDOT:PSS/MXene composites loaded with tetracycline hydrochloride (TCH), designed to deliver an antibacterial agent and monitor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolation and Structure Elucidation of Uric Acid Lowering Lipopeptides from an <em>Okeania</em> sp. Marine Cyanobacterium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two linear lipopeptides mabuniamide B (1) and C (2) were isolated from an Okeania sp. marine cyanobacterium collected from the coast of Okinawa. Their structures were elucidated by spectroscopic analyses, and their absolute configurations of amino acid residues were determined using Marfey's analysis of the hydrolysates of 1 and 2. In addition, 1 and 2 inhibited uric acid production in cultured AML12 cells.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knowledge of Targeted Muscles and Proper Form in Strength Training: A Cross-Sectional Survey of 1000 Adults Across Age, Sex, and Instructional Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the growing availability of strength training information through online platforms and social media, there is an increasing need to ensure that individuals possess sufficient knowledge to train safely and effectively. Nonetheless, previous studies on strength training literacy have primarily focused on university students and have not adequately examined differences in knowledge across age groups or the roles of training experience and instruction. This study aimed to assess the knowledge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers: Understanding the Impact of Intellectual Impairment on Inductive Reasoning in Basketball]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Access to high-performance sports is crucial for the holistic development and well-being of athletes with intellectual impairment (II). However, ensuring fair and equitable participation requires effective eligibility systems. This study investigates how basketball-specific inductive reasoning impacts athletes with II. A total of 92 elite male players with II (average age 26.3 ± 7 years) and 128 control players without II participated. This study used a tailored test to assess the ability to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Evaluation of the Bone Regenerative Potential of a Novel Calcium Silicate-Modified Calcium Carbonate Graft Material: Histological and Micro-Computed Tomography Assessment Using a Rat Calvarial Defect Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the present study, we evaluated the usefulness of a porous sintered calcium carbonate body with CaSiO(3) by comparing its osteogenic capacity with that of calcium carbonate without CaSiO(3) and that of β-tricalcium phosphate (TP). A cranial defect model of eight-week-old male Wistar rats was divided into three groups: calcium carbonate (CC), calcium carbonate-CaSiO(3) composite (CC+CS), and TP. Micro-computed tomography (CT) and histological analysis were performed at four and eight weeks...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three-Dimensional Objective Evaluation of the Changes in the Alveolar Ridge Before and After Horizontal Bone Augmentation Along with Implant Placement Using Intraoral Digital Scanning: A Prospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Implant treatment in the aesthetic regions of the jaw often requires hard and soft tissue augmentation to ensure optimal prosthetic outcomes. Radiological evaluation with cone-beam computed tomography (CBCT) and visual inspection of intraoral photographs are effective for assessing hard tissues but are limited in evaluating soft tissues. This study aimed to objectively evaluate volumetric and dimensional changes of the alveolar ridge, including both hard and soft tissues, following simultaneous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41003383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effects of Co-Culturing ND7/23 Sensory Neuron-like Cells and IFRS1 Schwann Cells on Myelination: A Single-Arm Nonrandomized Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Co-culture models of neurons and Schwann cells have been used to explore the mechanisms of myelination during development, axonal regeneration after injury, and the pathogenesis of various demyelinating neuropathies. A spontaneously immortalized Fischer rat Schwann cell line 1 (IFRS1), established from the primary culture of adult Fischer344 rat peripheral nerves, can myelinate neurites in co-cultures with primary cultured dorsal root ganglion neurons and neuronal cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large-Scale Molecular Dynamics of Anion-Exchange Membranes: Molecular Structure of QPAF-4 and Water Transport]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the molecular structure and water transport behavior in anion-exchange membranes (AEMs) is essential for advancing efficient and cost-effective alkaline fuel cells. In this study, large-scale all-atom molecular dynamics simulations of QPAF-4, a promising AEM material, were performed at multiple water uptakes (λ = 2, 3, 6, and 13). The simulated systems comprised approximately 1.4 to 2.1 million atoms and spanned approximately 26 nm, thus enabling direct comparison with both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Poly(Ionic Liquid)-Based Composite Electrolyte Membranes: Additive Effect of Silica Nanofibers on Their Properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Poly(ionic liquids) (PILs) show great promise as a new class of solid electrolytes for energy applications, including high-temperature polymer electrolyte fuel cells, owing to their combination of the unique electrochemical properties of ionic liquids and macromolecular architecture. In this study, we prepared and characterized PIL-based composite polymer electrolyte membranes containing silica nanofibers (SiO(2)NFs). The SiO(2)NFs were prepared via electrospinning, followed by calcination, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable Fabrication of Biomimetic Antibacterial Nanospikes on PMMA Films Using Atmospheric-Pressure Low-Temperature Plasma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibacterial surfaces inspired by biological micro- and nanostructures, such as those found on the wings of cicadas and dragonflies, have attracted interest due to their ability to inhibit bacterial adhesion and damage microbial membranes without relying on chemical agents. However, conventional fabrication techniques like photolithography or nanoimprinting are limited by substrate shape, size, and high operational costs. In this study, we developed a scalable method using atmospheric-pressure...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging Metal Additive Manufacturing for Individualized Dental Therapies: A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal additive manufacturing (AM) techniques, particularly laser powder bed fusion, are being increasingly recognized not as brand-new technologies, but as emerging technologies with their recent advancements-such as the development of optimized alloys, seamless digital workflow integration, and applications in patient-specific prostheses. With the rise in patient-specific approaches in dentistry, clinicians are seeking customized devices that precisely match individual anatomical and functional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiotherapy for Genitourinary Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the second most common cancer in men, prostate cancer was diagnosed in 1 [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in Systemic Therapy for Hepatocellular Carcinoma and Future Prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The focus of treatment of hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) has shifted significantly from local therapy to systemic drug therapy. Recently, the efficacy of drug therapy for HCC has made rapid progress. We have transitioned from eras of sorafenib monotherapy and sequential therapy with multiple tyrosine kinase inhibitors that slightly improved patient prognoses, to an era where the introduction of immunotherapy combining atezolizumab and bevacizumab has achieved further improvements in patient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NCPA-templated red-emitting gold nanoclusters: a turn-off-on fluorescent probe for rapid and selective detection of Cu<sup>2+</sup> ions in live cells and evaluation of anticancer activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Red-emitting gold nanoclusters (AuNCs) have gained significant attention as promising fluorescent probes for chemical and biomedical applications due to their excellent optical properties and inherent biocompatibility. In this study, a turn-OFF-ON red-emitting AuNC fluorescent probe was synthesized using N-cholyl D-penicillamine (NCPA) as a stabilizing and templating agent above its critical micellar concentration (CMC) under UV light irradiation. The developed synthesis protocol was simple,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Mechanotransduction and Inflammation in Human Cartilaginous Endplate Cells in Blended Collagen-Agarose Hydrogels Under Cyclic Compression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Little is known about cartilaginous endplate (CEP) mechanobiology or how it changes in a catabolic microenvironment, partly due to difficulties in conducting mechanotransduction in vitro. Recent studies have found blended collagen-agarose hydrogels to offer improved mechanotransduction in chondrocytes compared to agarose alone. It was hypothesized that blended collagen-agarose hydrogels would be sufficient to improve the mechanobiological response in CEP cells relative to that in agarose alone,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Printable Conductive Hydrogels and Elastomers for Biomedical Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Printed flexible materials have garnered considerable attention as next-generation materials for bioelectronic applications, particularly hydrogels and elastomers, owing to their intrinsic softness, tissue-like mechanical compliance, and electrical conductivity. In contrast to conventional fabrication approaches, printing technologies enable precise spatial control, design versatility, and seamless integration with complex biological interfaces. This review provides a comprehensive overview of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel GelMA/GelMA-AEMA Hydrogel Blend with Enhanced Printability as a Carrier for iPSC-Derived Chondrocytes In Vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cartilage tissue engineering aims to restore damaged cartilage using biomaterials, cells, and/or biological cues to support cell growth and tissue repair. Although in the past decades scientific advances have moved the field forward, their translation to a clinical setting is still hampered. One major hurdle to take is to reduce process variability to ensure a predictable biological outcome. Using enabling technologies such as bioprinting has shown the potential to improve process robustness....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Advances in Microfluidic Biofuel Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditionally, fuel cells operate by using small fuel molecules such as hydrogen and methanol to produce energy, water, and carbon dioxide. Enzyme biofuel cells use enzymes rather than precious metals as electrode catalysts. In recent years, enzyme-immobilized electrodes have been developed by combining enzyme biofuel cells with microfluidic technology to improve the efficiency and performance of fuel cells. In this review, we will provide an overview and describe the current status of recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral β-lactam combinations are effective <em>in vitro</em> against <em>Mycobacterium avium</em>, regardless of clarithromycin susceptibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global incidence and prevalence of pulmonary disease caused by the Mycobacterium avium complex (MAC), mainly comprising M. avium and Mycobacterium intracellulare, is increasing. However, treating MAC pulmonary disease is challenging in cases of clarithromycin (CLR)-resistant MAC or where the patients experience adverse effects or drug interactions with the few available antibiotics. Therefore, developing novel and highly effective antibiotics against MAC is crucial. Although the efficacy of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41002148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research on Quantum Circuit Learning Models for Molecular Dynamics Simulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the past decade, many hybrid quantum-classical algorithms have been applied to various industrial fields, reflecting the growing interest in NISQ devices. For example, in the field of chemistry, many studies were conducted to calculate the energies of eigenstates with high precision. However, there is still little research on molecular dynamics using quantum computers, because traditional approaches based on variational quantum algorithms are not suitable for the long-time steps of molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glucose/Glucuronate Copolymers Stripped from Oxidized Cell Wall Cellulose by Mechanical Shearing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alternating copolymers often exhibit specific physical properties, such as a narrow glass transition temperature range and a highly uniform micelle size. Alternating copolymers are, however, synthesized from only limited combinations of monomers. Herein, we report the semisynthesis of copolymers with a basic skeleton composed of alternating glucose (G)/glucuronate (U) units via the regioselective surface oxidation of plant cellulose crystallites, followed by mechanical shearing of the oxidized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly selective 1,4-NADH regeneration <em>via</em> hydrogenated NAD<sup>+</sup> analogs using a Pt/SiO<sub>2</sub> catalyst with low pressure hydrogen gas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The hydrogenation of nicotinamide analogs using a Pt/SiO(2) catalyst, followed by hydride transfer to NAD^(+), results in the highly selective regeneration of 1,4-NADH. N-Methyl nicotinamide exhibits the highest reactivity, achieving 98% selectivity at 20 °C under 1 atm H(2). This strategy provides a practical and sustainable pathway for 1,4-NADH regeneration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effect of a Post-Learning Nap on Motor Memory Consolidation in People With Parkinson's Disease: A Randomised Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Motor memory consolidation is a process by which newly acquired skills become stable over time in the absence of practice. Sleep facilitates consolidation, yet it remains unknown whether sleep-dependent consolidation is intact in people with Parkinson's disease. Here, we investigated whether a post-learning nap-as compared to wakefulness-improves motor memory consolidation in Parkinson. Thirty-two people with Parkinson's disease and 32 healthy older adults learnt a finger-tapping sequence task...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>fac</em>-Re(2,2'-bipyridine)(CO)<sub>3</sub>Cl Catalyzes Visible-Light-Driven Functionalization of an Organic Substrate with CO<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The molecular photocatalyst fac-Re-(2,2'-bipyridine)-(CO)(3)Cl ([Re-Cl]) is well established and has been extensively investigated for the highly active and selective conversion of CO(2) to CO. However, its reactivity in processes other than CO(2) reduction has rarely been explored. Herein, we report the application of [Re-Cl] as a catalyst for the visible-light-driven carboxylation of an alkene using CO(2), with phenyl vinyl sulfone (1) serving as a model substrate. The catalytic system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequential, Multiplexed Immunofluorescent Imaging of Live Cells Based on DNA-Mediated Reversible Fluorophore Attachment/Detachment with Antibodies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given the spectral overlap of fluorophores, traditional immunofluorescence imaging is limited by the number of proteins that can be imaged simultaneously. Although sequential imaging techniques have been proposed, in which repeated staining and destaining are performed to obtain the merged image of several proteins, they are applied only to fixed cells presumably due to their harsh conditions. Therefore, observation and analysis of live cells have not been achieved with the sequential imaging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introducing Sulfur Ylides as Charge-Neutral Termini for Mitigating Poly(ethylene glycol) Antigenicity in Nanomedicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The widespread use of polyethylene glycol (PEG) in biomedical applications has led to the emergence of anti-PEG antibodies, which accelerate systemic clearance and undermine the performance of PEGylated systems, including those of nanomedicines. Antibody recognition often involves the hydrophobic PEG terminus, highlighting the need for alternative end-functionalization strategies that enhance hydrophilicity while maintaining stealth properties. Here, we introduce a novel PEGylation concept using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recyclable Whole-Cell Biotransformation System for the Direct Hydroxylation of Propane Catalyzed by a Robust Intracellular Wild-Type Cytochrome P450BM3 Activated by Decoy Molecules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a decoy molecule-based whole-cell biotransformation system that achieves the direct hydroxylation of propane to 2-propanol using wild-type cytochrome P450BM3 expressed in Escherichia coli. With the most effective decoy molecule N-(2-cyclopentylethyl)-prolyl-phenylalanine (2CPE-Pro-Phe), 2-propanol was produced at a final concentration of 29 mM with a high selectivity of 99%. The catalytic activity achieved using this approach was higher than that achieved using previously reported...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single Photocatalytic Hydrosilylation of Alkenes for the Synthesis of Bis(silyl) and Silaboryl Alkanes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bis-(silyl) and silaboryl alkanes are of interest as bioactive compounds and highly functionalized synthetic building blocks, but conventional hydrosilylation reactions lack generality and/or selectivity for synthesizing multielement-containing alkanes. Here, we present a versatile photoactivated hydrosilylation reaction of silicon- or boron-containing alkenes using silylborane as a silyl radical source to construct bis-(silyl) or silaboryl alkanes. This method employs a single...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health programme spillover effects on childhood vaccination in India: a difference-in-differences analysis of the Zinc and Oral Rehydration Salts Programme using retrospective demographic health surveys data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Existing studies rarely evaluate spillover effects or unintended consequences of public health campaigns. We find that a public health programme to reduce diarrhoeal diseases was associated with increased vaccination coverage in India. These findings highlight the potential horizontal health effects of disease-specific public campaigns and household behaviour responses to the programme. The evidence shows that actionable approaches to improve immunisation coverage exist that do not...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Arm-hand BOOST (AHA-BOOST) therapy to improve recovery of the upper limb after stroke: rationale and description by means of the TIDieR checklist]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In a phase II RCT, the AHA-BOOST program proved to be feasible and safe and suggests positive, clinical meaningful effects on arm and hand function. A phase III RCT including clinical, health economic and process evaluations of the AHA-BOOST program is currently ongoing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Chrysene-Based Nanographenes by a Successive APEX Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chrysene-based nanographenes (ChrNGs), despite their relatively small structures, have been reported to exhibit low highest occupied molecular orbital (HOMO)-lowest unoccupied molecular orbital (LUMO) energy gaps and strong long-wavelength fluorescence, making them attractive for various applications. However, the precise synthesis of ChrNGs remains challenging, and their availability is limited compared with other classes of nanographenes. Herein, we report the synthesis of novel ChrNGs by a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41001094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cervical disc arthroplasty in Australia: An epidemiological study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although there is growing evidence supporting the safety and efficacy of CDA, its utilization in Australia has remained stable over the past 6 years, with the highest uptake among young to middle-aged patients. Further analysis of utilization trends may help identify factors influencing adoption and guide future surgical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic dissection of soybean lodging tolerance in recombinant inbred-line populations of major Japanese and modern US varieties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In soybean production, lodging poses a significant challenge to modern mechanized agriculture, such as the use of combine harvesters. Most Japanese varieties are prone to lodging because of the local weather conditions, such as wind and rain, resulting in a decline in productivity. In the United States (US), where mechanized agricultural production systems are prevalent, lodging tolerance (LT) is essential in soybean breeding. We thus used two recombinant inbred-line (RIL) populations developed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic control of seed iron and zinc concentration in Rwandan common bean population revealed by the Genome Wide Association Study (GWAS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Common bean (Phaseolus vulgaris L.) is one of the most abundantly consumed legume crops as foods worldwide. In many African countries, this crop is an important staple food because of its rich nutrients. The Great Lakes region of Central Africa, which includes Rwanda, the nation with the highest per capita consumption of common beans worldwide, is known to be a center of common bean diversity in Africa. Increasing the amount of iron and zinc in common bean for biofortification has been a key...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pollen parent affects rutin content of seeds of buckwheat (<em>Fagopyrum esculentum</em>)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Buckwheat (Fagopyrum esculentum) is a heterostylous self-incompatible crop that requires outcrossing for seed formation. Pollen parents influence the traits of seeds in many plants, but their influence in buckwheat is unknown. Here, we crossed self-incompatible (SI) and self-compatible (SC) lines with different rutin contents. The average rutin contents of SI leading cultivars were all 0.15-0.21 mg/g, and a SI high rutin content line that we had developed was 0.6 mg/g, although it has wide range...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyphyletic domestication and inter-lineage hybridization magnified genetic diversity of cultivated melon, <em>Cucumis melo</em> L]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Melon accessions with diverse geographical origins were classified into large and small seed-types by length of seed at the boundary of 9 mm, and into five populations based on polymorphisms in the nuclear genome. They were further divided into three maternal lineages, Ia, Ib, and Ic, by polymorphisms in the chloroplast genome. By combining these three classifications, the Europe/US subsp. melo and the East Asian subsp. agrestis were characterized as [large seed, Ib, PopA1 or A2] and [small...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and interlaboratory validation of a cultivar-specific identification method for the table grape 'Shine Muscat' using loop-mediated isothermal amplification (LAMP)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA['Shine Muscat' is an elite table grape cultivar developed by the National Agriculture and Food Research Organization in Japan. Recently, the infringement of breeders' rights in various fruits has become a serious problem in Japan. In this study, a loop-mediated isothermal amplification (LAMP)-mediated cultivar identification method for 'Shine Muscat' was developed. We comprehensively analyzed retrotransposon insertion sites using 24 major grape cultivars and identified two insertions,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wave after wave: The suggestibility of noise in the experience of multisensory hallucinations under multimodal Ganzfeld stimulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A multimodal Ganzfeld (MMGF) consists of homogeneous stimulation in both the visual and auditory modalities. Exposure to this unique perceptual environment can elicit the awareness of hallucinatory percepts. The nature of these hallucinatory percepts, and specifically the frequency of visual, auditory and multisensorial hallucinations, remains unclear. In this study, an MMGF refers to the stimulation paradigm itself. The perceptual experiences elicited, however, can be unimodal (occurring in one...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41000273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250926151929&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>