<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:42:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Avarol protects HT22 neuronal cells from BV2 microglia cell-derived neuroinflammation in lipopolysaccharide-induction model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pathological neuroinflammation is a critical factor that disrupts neuronal activity and, when sustained, ultimately contributes to neuronal death. Among the primary mediators of neuroinflammation, microglia play a central role in modulating brain immunity. However, their overactivation is closely associated with neuronal damage and structural remodeling of brain tissue, leading to the onset and progression of various neurodegenerative diseases. In this study, we investigated the neuroprotective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rheological performance and strength on two component backfilling grout in shield TBM]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ground settlement and segmental displacement during mechanized tunneling require immediate and stable filling of annular gap. Two-component grouts are widely adopted to control gelation and compressive strength. Previous studies suggest that partial replacement of OPC with ground granulated blast-furnace slag (GGBFS) enhances performance, yet the combined effects of cement type and silicate hardener dosage have not been fully clarified. This study investigates the influence of cement type and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid feed component assessment to enhance livestock productivity and reduce emissions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rising global demand for livestock products necessitates innovations in feed management to enhance efficiency and sustainability. Variability in livestock feed nutrient composition highlights the need for real-time monitoring to ensure animals receive proper nutrition. In this study, we first used Analysis of Variance (ANOVA) to measure differences in moisture content (MC), crude protein (CP), and neutral detergent fiber (NDF) across eight feed types from seven factories in the Gyeongsang...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical vs Physiological Lesion Characteristics in Prediction of Acute Coronary Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Luminal narrowing, plaque quality and quantity, and local hemodynamics were independent predictors of ACS, offering specificity in physiology and sensitivity in anatomy. A comprehensive assessment of them further refined the risk prediction for future ACS. (Exploring the Mechanism of Plaque Rupture in Acute Coronary Syndrome Using Coronary CT Angiography and Computational Fluid Dynamics II [EMERALD II]; NCT03591328).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of selumetinib-loaded solid dispersion based on low molecular weight methylcellulose for the enhanced solubility, stability, dissolution, and bioavailability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The poor water solubility and bioavailability of selumetinib sulfate (SEL) limit its clinical potential as a promising anticancer drug. The aim of this study was to develop a solid dispersion (SD) of SEL as a new formulation strategy. Methylcellulose 4 cP (MC 4 cP) and Soluplus® were selected as SD carriers for their high solubility of SEL (>1400 μg/mL at pH 1.2). Furthermore, the low molecular weight MC 4 cP was effective in the solubilization of SEL due to its specific molecular affinity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable production methodology of radionuclide reference materials for nuclear decommissioning and food safety monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional production of solid reference materials (RMs) for radionuclide monitoring is often plagued by heterogeneity and scalability issues. This study presents a 'ball-growth' granulation technique that resolves these bottlenecks, enabling the production of 100 kg batches in under five days. To validate the method's versatility across hazardous material domains, two Certified Reference Materials (CRMs) were developed: a simulated concrete matrix containing ^(137)Cs and ^(60)Co for nuclear...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A mechano-gated ionic diode enables low-power synaptic tactile spiking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionic diodes, which enable unidirectional ion transport, hold great promise for adaptive and energy-efficient ionotronic systems. However, conventional designs often rely on high ion concentrations, which promote ion pairing and clustering, thereby reducing mobility and impeding the formation of stable ion depletion layers (IDLs). Here, we report a mechano-gated ionic diode with balanced ionic conductivity between cationic and anionic polymer layers, achieved through copolymer engineering. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrathin Iridium Nanosheets on Titanium Oxide for High-Efficiency and Durable Proton Exchange Membrane Water Electrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reducing iridium (Ir) usage is essential for the commercial viability of proton exchange membrane water electrolysis (PEMWE), where the oxygen evolution reaction (OER) is a major performance and cost bottleneck. Conventional Ir nanoparticles (∼5 nm) suffer from low dispersion and limited surface utilization. Here, we report a catalyst architecture comprising ultrathin Ir nanosheets (Ir NS) supported on spherical TiO(2) particles (Ir NS/TiO(2)). The ∼100 nm TiO(2) particles effectively disperses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Mobile Neurofeedback on Theta-Gamma Coupling and Clinical Outcomes in Children with ADHD: A Double-Blind, Sham-Controlled Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MNF produced measurable neurophysiological modulation-reflected in enhanced TGC-when used as an adjunct to medication. Although clinical improvements were modest, these findings support TGC as a sensitive biomarker of MNF-induced brain regulation in ADHD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utility of Machine Learning to Characterize Gut Microbiota Dysbiosis and Its Clinical Implications in Inflammatory Bowel Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) arises from complex interactions among host genetics, immune dysregulation, environmental factors, and the gut microbiome. Numerous studies have demonstrated alterations in microbial composition and function, including reduced diversity and changes in metabolic pathways. Traditional biostatistical approaches, such as differential abundance analysis, have advanced our understanding but are remain limited in handling nonlinear and high-dimensional data. Machine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alternative splicing of KRAS exon 4 promotes tumor progression via enhanced KRAS4A oncogenic activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[KRAS is a well-established oncogene that exhibits high-frequency mutations at cancer-driver hotspot loci across human cancers. While the oncogenic roles of mutant KRAS have been extensively investigated, the functional significance of KRAS splicing isoforms generated by exon 4 (E4) alternative splicing remains poorly understood. Here, we analyzed the expression patterns of KRAS E4 splicing variants in cancer tissues using The Cancer Genome Atlas (TCGA) data and found that certain cancer types...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Affecting the Decision for Surgery in Patients with Carpal Tunnel Syndrome Using a Nationwide Cohort in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Individuals covered by comprehensive public aid insurance had quicker surgical interventions. Female patients undergo surgery more frequently, but they tend to delay it. The likelihood of undergoing surgery increases with age until the 50s. Individuals with disabilities undergo surgery more frequently and promptly. These findings suggest that physicians should encourage timely surgical interventions among female patients and younger patients who tend to delay surgery. For healthcare...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A dual-branch network for lesion segmentation in medical images using state space models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The proposed model integrates SSMs and deep convolutional networks to improve lesion segmentation by effectively capturing both local and global features. It offers new insights for medical image segmentation with potential clinical applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Humanized Mouse Models as a Cellular Platform for Investigating Immune-Hormonal Crosstalk and Therapeutic Strategies in Menopause]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Menopause is a complex biological transition marked by the decline of ovarian function and estrogen levels, leading to a wide range of physiological and immunological changes in women. Traditional animal models, particularly ovariectomized rodents, have been instrumental in studying menopause; however, they often fail to fully replicate human hormonal and immune responses. Humanized mouse models, which incorporate human immune systems and tissues, represent a promising alternative for bridging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly Reliable and Ultraflexible Organic Light-Emitting Diode Patch for Psoriasis Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Psoriasis is a chronic inflammatory skin disease that significantly affects the quality of life of patients. Photodynamic therapy is effective in treating psoriasis; however, existing light sources, such as lasers and light-emitting diodes (LEDs), have limitations in terms of flexibility, uniformity of light irradiation, and patient convenience. In this study, a high-power ultraflexible organic LED (OLED) patch is fabricated on a PET adhesive film, resulting in a high output of 60 mW cm^(-2) at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Osteoporosis in Korean men over 40 years: Prevalence and risk factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoporosis is increasingly being recognized as a significant health concern in men. However, research on male osteoporosis in Korea remains limited. This study aimed to investigate the prevalence and factors influencing osteoporosis in Korean men aged ≥40 years. Secondary analysis utilized data from the Korean Genome and Epidemiology Study urban cohort (2004-2013), focusing on 58,976 men aged ≥40 years. Variables included sociodemographic characteristics, lifestyle factors, medical history,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glymphatic Dysfunction Reflects Post-Concussion Symptoms: Changes Within 1 Month and After 3 Months]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41373077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Mild traumatic brain injury (mTBI) may alter glymphatic function; however, its progression and variability remain obscure. This study examined glymphatic function following mTBI within 1 month and after 3 months post-injury to determine whether variations in glymphatic function are associated with post-traumatic symptom severity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41373077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced methanol tolerance and utilization in Pichia pastoris revealed by adaptive laboratory evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute neuroinflammation induces prolonged transcriptional reprogramming in microglia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute neuroinflammation rapidly activates brain immune responses, but its lasting effects on microglia are unclear. Using systemic LPS administration and LCMV-Armstrong infection, we found that blood-brain barrier disruption and cytokine shifts resolved within 30 days, yet microglial recovery was incomplete-marked by persistent numerical loss and an IFN-γ-low phenotype in the LPS model and reduced relative abundance in the LCMV model. Single-cell RNA sequencing revealed sustained transcriptional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between watching mukbang and cookbang and alcohol use among adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A significant association was found between watching mukbang and cookbang and alcohol use among adolescents. The association varied according to economic status, with stronger associations observed in the low and middle economic status groups. These findings suggest that mukbang and cookbang media content may have substantial effects on adolescents' health-related behaviors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative pain outcomes following thyroidectomy: a systematic review and network meta-analysis of various surgical approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MIVAT and TOA provide superior postoperative pain outcomes than those of CTA and other remote-access approaches. Robotic techniques may offer additional benefits over endoscopic methods in selected cases. These findings may support more patient-centered surgical decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing microenvironment classification models for personal exposure assessment based on global positioning system tracking data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Accurate personal exposure assessment to air pollution is crucial in environmental epidemiological studies, but it remains challenging due to substantial differences in pollutant concentrations between indoor and outdoor environments. Indirect assessment methods estimate personal exposure by incorporating microenvironment-specific pollutant concentrations and personal time-activity patterns, while requiring participants to record detailed time-location diaries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogel-elastomer-based conductive nanomembranes for soft bioelectronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conformal integration of electronics with soft, irregular organ topologies remains challenging, as tissue-like platforms with bulky dimensions ranging from a few millimetres to several hundred micrometres result in incomplete signal acquisition and chronic tissue compression. Although ultrathin nanoscale devices have recently been developed to address these challenges, they involve complex and delicate handling processes that limit their practical use and compromise their intrinsic performance....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive topological modeling of the structure-property relationships in naturally occurring anti-cancer chalcones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a comprehensive predictive topological modeling framework was employed to investigate the quantitative structure-property relationships (QSPR) of naturally occurring anticancer chalcones. A series of degree-based topological indices, including the first and second Zagreb indices, first and second redefined Zagreb indices, sum-connectivity index, symmetric division index, Randić index, and harmonic index, were computed to represent key molecular structural features. Statistical and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A numerical framework for an electrically-charged PCM brick to reduce winter peak heating demand]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The substantial peak electrical demand for space heating in cold and freezing climates poses a significant challenge to grid stability and energy affordability. This study proposes and numerically investigates a novel active thermal energy storage system integrated directly into a building brick to address this challenge. The system features an encapsulated Phase Change Material (PCM) composite, enhanced with a high-conductivity copper oxide foam, and is coupled with a low-wattage electrical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of physical mechanisms for channel-length-dependent PBTS reliability in SA TG coplanar IGZO TFTs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the physical mechanisms for channel-length-dependent positive bias temperature stress (PBTS) reliability in self-aligned top-gate (SA TG) coplanar indium-gallium-zinc oxide (IGZO) thin-film transistors (TFTs). We fabricated devices with channel lengths of 3 µm, 12 µm, and 20 µm and characterized them using high-low frequency capacitance-voltage measurements and low-frequency noise analysis. Experimental results show that the 3 µm channel length device exhibits a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-based artificial intelligence models predict survival in patients with oral cavity squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditional survival predictions for oral squamous cell carcinoma (OSCC) rely on TNM staging, which lacks individualized prognostic value. Clinical factors such as performance status, age, sex, and lifestyle affect outcomes but are underrepresented in conventional models. This study applied artificial intelligence (AI) to integrate diverse factors for OSCC survival prediction. We retrospectively analyzed 1,018 OSCC patients surgically treated between 1996 and 2020. Variables included...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ophtimus-V2-Tx: a compact domain-specific LLM for ophthalmic diagnosis and treatment planning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) show promise for clinical decision support but often struggle with case-specific reasoning. We present Ophtimus-V2-Tx, an 8-billion-parameter ophthalmology-specialized LLM fine-tuned on more than 10,000 case reports. Evaluation is conducted on a pre-collected dataset. Alongside text metrics (ROUGE-L, BLEU, METEOR) and a semantic similarity score, we use CliBench to map outputs to standardized codes (ICD-10-CM, ATC, ICD-10-PCS) and compute hierarchical F1 (L1-L4 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chromosome-level genome assembly of the white-spotted sawyer Monochamus scutellatus (Coleoptera: Cerambycidae)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The white-spotted sawyer, Monochamus scutellatus (Say) (Coleoptera: Cerambycidae), is an important vector of pinewood nematode (PWN), Bursaphelenchus xylophilus (Steiner and Buhrer) Nickle, in North America. While Monochamus species from the Palearctic region have been extensively studied for their role in transmitting PWN that causes pine wilt disease in Asia and Europe, the genetic mechanisms underlying Monochamus-PWN interactions in their native range remain largely unknown. Here, we present...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular architecture of the human TRPC1/C5 heteromeric channel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transient receptor potential (TRP) ion channels form heteromers through combinatorial associations of distinct subunits, contributing to the diversity of TRP channel functions. Among them, TRPC5, which forms a heteromer with TRPC1, represents an attractive pharmaceutical target for treating anxiety and depression. Here, we present the cryo-electron microscopy structure of the human TRPC1/C5 heteromer, composed of one TRPC1 subunit and three TRPC5 subunits. The incorporation of TRPC1 into the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Altered cortical gyrification as a marker of treatment resistance in patients with first-episode psychosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Predicting treatment resistance from the first stage of psychosis aids in personalized treatment, promotes a better prognosis, and contributes to healthcare cost savings. Currently, no biomarker accurately predicts treatment resistance in patients with first-episode psychosis (FEP). This study aims to investigate the potential of cortical gyrification as a biomarker for predicting resistance in the first episode of schizophrenia. A cohort of 101 individuals diagnosed with FEP and an equivalent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public health impact and cost-effectiveness of implementing gender-neutral immunization with the nonavalent human papillomavirus vaccine in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study assessed the impact and cost-effectiveness of gender-neutral immunization with the nonavalent human papillomavirus (HPV) vaccine in South Korea. An established dynamic transmission model of HPV epidemiology was adapted to the South Korean population. Vaccinating both girls and boys with the nonavalent HPV vaccine was compared to the currently administered program of vaccinating girls only with the quadrivalent vaccine. Compared to vaccination of girls only with the quadrivalent HPV...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domain-general neural effects of associative learning and expectations on pain and hedonic taste perception]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Predictive cues significantly influence perception through associative learning. However, it is unknown whether circuits are conserved across domains. We investigated how associative learning influences perceived intensity and valence of pain and hedonic taste, and whether expectancy-based modulation varies by aversiveness or modality. Sixty participants (37 females, 23 males) were randomly assigned to receive either painful heat, unpleasant liquid saline, or pleasant liquid sucrose during fMRI...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Another Score in the Flood, or a Needed Step Toward East Asian Precision?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights From the PHOENIKS Cohort: Shaping the Future of Pulmonary Arterial Hypertension (PAH) Management in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Emerging Lipid Risk: Lipoprotein(a)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Based on epidemiological and genetic studies in recent decades, lipoprotein(a) (Lp(a)) has been accepted as a causal risk factor for atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease and aortic stenosis. Although inter-ethnic differences exist, Lp(a) level ≥50 mg/dL is commonly reported to indicate elevated cardiovascular risk. Blood Lp(a) levels are largely determined based on genetic background, and the kringle IV type 2 repeat variant is a major factor. Lp(a) is structurally similar to low-density...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Volume of Targeted Temperature Management and Neurological Outcomes in Comatose Out-of-Hospital Cardiac Arrest Survivors: Nationwide Population-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher TTM case volume was associated with better neurological outcome in comatose OHCA survivors and may reflect greater overall post-arrest care capability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the Asian-Dual Antiplatelet Therapy Score]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ADAPT scores were validated for predicting ischemic and bleeding risks in patients receiving DAPT. This scoring system can aid in evaluating both ischemic and bleeding risks for East Asians, who exhibit unique risk profiles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Efficacy of Tafamidis in Korean ATTR-CM Patients: A Retrospective Observational Strain Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tafamidis was associated with improved survival and slower disease progression in Korean ATTR-CM. LASI and RV-pulmonary circulation coupling index may serve as sensitive markers of treatment response.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term and Temporal Relationships Between Post-Stent Fractional Flow Reserve and Clinical Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The prognostic impact of post-PCI FFR on TVF persisted over a 5-year follow-up period, but it was more prominent during the first 3 years after PCI. In contrast, its impact on TVR in the nonstented segments was sustained throughout the entire 5-year follow-up period. (International Post-PCI FFR Extended Registry; NCT05672862).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Double Outlet Right Ventricle With a Not-Directly-Committed Ventricular Septal Defect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhibition of NOD-like receptor pyrin domain-containing protein 3 inflammasome activation by MK-571, a multidrug resistance protein inhibitor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proinflammatory cytokines such as interleukin (IL)-1β and IL-18 are known to be activated through the NOD-like receptor pyrin domain-containing protein 3 (NLRP3) inflammasome, a multi-protein intracellular complex. MK-571 has been identified an efflux inhibitor of multidrug resistance protein (MRP) transporters. In this study, we have revealed that MK-571 effectively suppresses the activation of the NLRP3 inflammasome in bone marrow-derived macrophages (BMDMs) by elevating intracellular cAMP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural characterization of kraft lignin fractions obtained via pH adjustment and polyvinyl alcohol compatibility evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The heterogeneous structure and poor compatibility of lignin with polymer matrices have limited its widespread application. In this study, kraft lignin (KL) was fractionated via acid precipitation at different pH levels (9, 7, 5, and 3) to obtain sub-fractions with distinct physicochemical properties. Among them, the fraction obtained at pH 5 (KL5) showed the most favorable characteristics, including the highest yield (~34 %), low sugar content (~2.2 %), and the lowest zeta potential (-37.8 mV),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel peptide explicitly induces prostate cancer cell death by destabilizing AR and inhibiting AR-mediated transcription]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current treatment strategies for prostate cancer primarily focuses on regulating androgen receptor (AR) activity, either through androgen deprivation or the use of anti-androgen therapies. While these approaches are initially effective, many patients eventually develop resistance, resulting in the emergence of castration-resistant prostate cancer (CRPC). This transition not only complicates disease management but also leads to persistent side effects, underscoring the urgent need for alternative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What injury makes an isolated small coronoid fracture? Morphological analysis using 3D CT reconstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Small, isolated coronoid fractures often reflect underlying complex elbow instability, particularly PMRI, despite their benign radiographic appearance. Detailed evaluation using 3D CT and assessment of associated ligamentous injuries are essential for appropriate diagnosis and treatment planning. These findings highlight the limitations of current classification systems and suggest a need for a revised system incorporating injury mechanism and associated soft tissue damage.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epcoritamab, lenalidomide, and rituximab versus lenalidomide and rituximab for relapsed or refractory follicular lymphoma (EPCORE FL-1): a global, open-label, randomised, phase 3 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: An unmet need persists for chemotherapy-free regimens that induce durable responses for relapsed or refractory follicular lymphoma. Lenalidomide and rituximab (R²) is an accepted standard of care in this population. The EPCORE FL-1 trial aimed to evaluate the efficacy and safety of epcoritamab plus R² versus R² in participants with relapsed or refractory follicular lymphoma after at least one previous line of chemoimmunotherapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developmental and multi-organ toxicity of fludioxonil in zebrafish through apoptosis, oxidative stress, and mitochondrial dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fludioxonil, a widely used phenylpyrrole-class fungicide, has drawn growing concerns owing to its persistent detection in the environment and its potential for diverse toxic effects. This study investigated the developmental toxic effects of fludioxonil using zebrafish (Danio rerio) as a model organism. Exposure to fludioxonil resulted in reduced survival rates and induced multi-organ toxicity. Fludioxonil-induced organ-specific toxicity was assessed using transgenic fluorescent reporter lines,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microplastics bound to fine particulate matter in subway air: A pathway for toxic metal transport to enhanced carcinogenicity in human lungs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the role of microplastics (MPs; components of inhalable particulate matter (PM)) in promoting cancer development in the human respiratory system. Findings reveal that fine PM-bound MPs significantly influence inhalation cancer risk (ICR) by transporting carcinogenic metals (CM) deep into the lungs. Airborne PM, MPs, and trace metals were measured in underground and subsurface subway stations in Korea, as well as at control and outdoor sites. The study further assessed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation of an alert system for the care cascade of Hepatitis C infection in patients undergoing elective surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The EMR-based automatic alert system effectively increased HCV screening for patients undergoing elective surgery before admission. However, it could not link them to care cascade in surgery departments. Combining more proactive approaches would be beneficial, such as reflex testing or a call-back strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early childhood sleep patterns and cognitive development: reduced daytime sleep and increased nighttime proportion linked to better outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Shorter daytime sleep and a greater proportion of nighttime sleep in early childhood were associated with better cognition at ages 4 and 6. These findings highlight the importance of supporting healthy sleep patterns during routine pediatric care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-derived 3D organoid platform for functional assessment of GPC3-targeted CAR T cell cytotoxic activity in head and neck squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This proof-of-concept study introduces a patient-derived 3D organoid platform for functional assessment of CAR T cell cytotoxic activity in HNSCC. Our findings suggest that GPC3-CAR T therapy may be clinically applicable to subsets of patients with HNSCC, while emphasizing the need for functional validation to account for interpatient heterogeneity in clinical translation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling Diverse Stacking Sequence in CVD-Grown WSe<sub>2</sub> Multilayers via Electron Diffraction Polarity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The transition from two-dimensional (2D) to three-dimensional (3D) layered systems has significantly expanded the research landscape for functional materials. Among these, polar layered materials with noncentrosymmetry, such as 3R-MoS(2), 3R-WSe(2), and In(2)Se(3), are particularly intriguing due to their inherent structural asymmetry, which leads to exceptional properties, such as ferroelectricity, piezoelectricity, and nonlinear optical responses. However, precisely determining the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lignocellulosic Films: Preparation, Properties, and Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lignocellulosic films (LCFs) have garnered significant attention due to their unique combination of flexibility, functionality, cost-effectiveness, and eco-friendliness. Defined as thin, compact, and continuous sheets with a typical thickness in the range of 10-100 μm, LCFs have been used in various fields, including packaging, flexible electronics, energy storage and harvesting, sensing, water treatment, and agriculture. Based on preparation strategies and chemical compositions, LCFs can be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prenatal Exposure to Antiseizure Medications and the Risk of Congenital Anomalies: A Nationwide Population-Based Study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Valproate has a well-documented teratogenic risk, whereas lamotrigine and levetiracetam seem relatively safe. However, evidence for other antiseizure medications (ASMs) and specific congenital anomalies remains limited and inconsistent. We aimed to assess the risk of overall and specific congenital anomalies associated with prenatal exposure to individual ASMs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trastuzumab Deruxtecan in Residual HER2-Positive Early Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with high-risk, residual invasive HER2-positive breast cancer, postneoadjuvant T-DXd resulted in a significantly higher likelihood of invasive disease-free survival than T-DM1; toxic effects were mainly gastrointestinal and hematologic. An important identified risk of T-DXd is interstitial lung disease, which requires appropriate monitoring and management. (Funded by Daiichi Sankyo and AstraZeneca; DESTINY-Breast05 ClinicalTrials.gov number, NCT04622319.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Venetoclax-Dexamethasone Versus Pomalidomide-Dexamethasone in t(11;14)-Positive Relapsed/Refractory Multiple Myeloma: Primary Results of the Randomized, Phase III CANOVA Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The primary end point of PFS was not met. PFS and OS were numerically longer with venetoclax-dexamethasone versus pomalidomide-dexamethasone in t(11;14)-positive RRMM. Consistent with previous studies, infections were associated with venetoclax-dexamethasone; no new safety signals were observed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoupling Visual Parsing and Diagnostic Reasoning for Vision-Language Models (GPT-4o and GPT-5): Analysis Using Thoracic Imaging Quiz Cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Vision-language models (VLMs) have potential to identify findings on radiologic imaging (i.e., visual parsing) and translate findings into diagnoses (i.e., diagnostic reasoning). Current VLMs have shown insufficient performance to support clinical integration. Objective: To evaluate the separate contributions of visual parsing and diagnostic reasoning toward GPT-based VLMs' performance in generating correct diagnoses for thoracic imaging. Methods: This retrospective study included...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the gap between point-of-care and laboratory standards: comparative evaluation of MedSenso and DSA glucometers against Cobas analyzers for accurate diabetes monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetes mellitus remains a major global health burden, with effective management relying heavily on accurate blood glucose monitoring. Personal glucometers are widely used for daily self-checks, yet their performance must be rigorously validated against laboratory standards to ensure reliability. This study undertook a diagnostic evaluation of three glucometers, DSA, MedSenso, and the laboratory-based Cobas systems (C503 and Pro analyzers), to assess their precision and clinical applicability....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of machine learning models for prediction of current and future dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dementia is among the most distressing and burdensome health challenges in aging populations. Treatment efficacy is limited; however, early diagnosis can delay or prevent disease progression. Previous machine learning-based prediction models have limitations (e.g., they are based on clinical parameters or are not generalizable). Thus, in this study, prediction models were developed for current and future dementia solely based on demographic, socioeconomic, and health-related features....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between changes in self-esteem and smartphone dependency among Korean adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Increasing smartphone ownership across all age groups has raised concerns about the rising risk of smartphone addiction, particularly during adolescence when self-esteem development is critical. This study aimed to investigate the association between changes in self-esteem and smartphone dependency over a five-year period using data from the Korean Children and Youth Panel Survey (2018-2022). A total of 1,971 participants from the middle school 1st grade cohort were analyzed. Self-esteem was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fractal-shaped droplet microfluidics for highly scalable cell mechanoporation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emerging non-viral gene delivery platforms provide alternatives to viral methods. However, they remain limited in scalability and efficiency for clinical translation. We present a fractal-shaped droplet microfluidic system that achieves approximately 98% efficiency and 80% viability at throughputs exceeding 10⁷ cells per min, enabling efficient, large-scale, and clinically relevant cell engineering.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Assessment of Focus Quality in Whole-Slide Imaging of Thyroid Liquid-Based Cytology Using Laplacian Variance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plyometric training enhances jump, sprint, and agility performance across different surface types: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PT significantly enhanced physical performance outcomes, regardless of the surface type. Practitioners may not need to prioritize the specific surface type when implementing PT programs aimed at improving jump, sprint, and agility performances.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of diode laser versus conventional scalpel in labial frenectomy: a systematic review and meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High labial frenum attachments may cause diastema, gingival recession, and hygiene difficulties. Conventional scalpel frenectomy is effective but may cause pain and bleeding. This meta-analysis compared the use of a diode laser versus a conventional scalpel for maxillary labial frenectomy, focusing on postoperative pain, swelling, intraoperative bleeding, and operative time. PubMed, Scopus, Web of Science, Cochrane Library, and Embase were searched through September 2025 using MeSH and free-text...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HER2CLIMB-05: A Phase 3 Study of Tucatinib Versus Placebo in Combination with Trastuzumab and Pertuzumab as First-line Maintenance Therapy for HER2+ Metastatic Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tucatinib addition to trastuzumab and pertuzumab demonstrated improvement in PFS with no new safety signals identified and may be an option for 1L maintenance therapy in patients with HER2+ MBC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is RAGE Expression in Flexor Tendon Synovium Associated With Carpal Tunnel Syndrome in Patients With Diabetes?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: According to our findings, RAGE-mediated mechanisms may contribute to the pathophysiology of CTS associated with diabetes. Further studies are warranted to elucidate the RAGE-related molecular pathways involved in this association and to determine whether targeting RAGE could be a potential therapeutic strategy influencing disease progression or surgical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Nocardioides secundeburneus</em> sp. nov. and <em>Gordonia aurantiaca</em> sp. nov., isolated from soil]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two strains, B21^(T) and C4-1^(T), were obtained from soil near Sinpung Station, the Republic of Korea. The two aerobic, Gram-negative, rod-shaped bacterial strains were designated B21^(T) and C4-1^(T). Phylogenetic tree analysis based on 16S rRNA and whole-genome sequences suggested that the strains B21^(T) and C4-1^(T) belonged to the genera Gordonia and Nocardioides, respectively. The draft genome of strain B21ᵀ consists of 4.99 Mb with a G+C content of 68.3 mol%, while that of strain C4-1ᵀ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Yaseen, H.M.A.; Park, S. Effect of Various Nanofillers on Piezoelectric Nanogenerator Performance of P(VDF-TrFE) Nanocomposite Thin Film. <em>Nanomaterials</em> 2025, <em>15</em>, 403]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the published paper [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dihydroorotate Dehydrogenase in Mitochondrial Ferroptosis and Cancer Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferroptosis is an iron-dependent form of regulated cell death driven by lipid peroxidation. Since the identification of dihydroorotate dehydrogenase (DHODH) as a mitochondrial suppressor of ferroptosis in 2021, increasing evidence has highlighted its role in linking nucleotide metabolism, redox regulation, and tumor progression. We conducted a comprehensive review of publications on DHODH, ferroptosis, and cancer. Relevant studies were analyzed to synthesize mechanistic insights, translational...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cellular and Molecular Roles of Human Odorant-Binding Proteins and Related Lipocalins in Olfaction and Neuroinflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Olfactory perception depends on soluble proteins in the perireceptor environment that support odorant transport, mucosal protection, and tissue homeostasis. In insects, odorant-binding proteins (OBPs) in the sensillum lymph are indispensable for odor detection, whereas in humans the indispensability of OBPs (OBP2A/2B) remains unclear because they are inconsistently detected in nasal mucus. Consequently, it remains unclear whether other soluble proteins compensate for this function or how they...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cellular and Molecular Mechanisms of Wound Repair: From Biology to Therapeutic Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wound repair preserves tissue integrity through four overlapping phases-hemostasis, inflammation, proliferation, and remodeling-coordinated by platelets, neutrophils, macrophages, fibroblasts, keratinocytes, endothelial cells, and stem/progenitor cells acting with growth factors, chemokines, extracellular matrix, and intracellular signaling. Disruption of these programs results in chronic non-healing wounds or fibrotic scarring. Recent work delineates microbial influences, epigenetic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-derived orthogonal minimum joint space width improves radiographic assessment of knee osteoarthritis severity and progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Orthogonal minimum joint space width, automatically quantified by deep learning, enhances both sensitivity and specificity for assessing knee osteoarthritis severity and progression. This metric may serve as a robust and reproducible structural imaging endpoint for clinical trials and longitudinal research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asiatic acid inhibits NF-κB signaling and ameliorates experimental acute and chronic colitis in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AA alleviates intestinal inflammation by suppressing NF-κB signaling in vitro and exhibits therapeutic efficacy in both acute and chronic colitis models, suggesting its potential as a therapeutic candidate for inflammatory bowel disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Cardiovascular Safety of Duloxetine and Gabapentin in Patients with Hip Osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Duloxetine was generally associated with increased CV risks, while a lower risk of AMI and no significant increase in mortality were observed compared to gabapentin. Our subgroup analysis further suggests that when potential confounding from preexisting CVDs was minimized, duloxetine was associated with incident CV complications in patients without prior CVDs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychological Resilience and Quality of Life in Family Caregivers of Patients with Terminal Cancer Across Levels of Spiritual Well-Being: A Multicenter Cross-Sectional Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among the FCs of patients with terminal cancer, resilience reflects QoL, in which SWB may play an important role.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Text Network Analysis of Research on the Bereaved After Sudden Death Since 2000]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Research addressing those left behind after sudden death is scarce, and only 108 studies were identified. These five clusters suggest that the research topics related to sudden bereavement represent distinct grief experiences characterized by unique psychological, social, and contextual features.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Disease: The Current and Emerging Treatment Approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a chronic progressive neurodegenerative disease characterized by amyloid β (Aβ) plaques and neurofibrillary tangles (NFTs) as its main pathological features. It mainly manifests as cognitive dysfunction, and its pathological process may occur before symptom onset. However, the current drugs and methods for treating AD have unsatisfactory therapeutic outcomes. Therefore, finding a treatment that can inhibit the progression of AD by targeting its pathological features...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Based Clustering Algorithm for Pulse Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results suggest significant alignment between data-driven pattern identification and expert diagnoses, especially for the "Floating-Sinking" pattern. Further refinement with diverse populations is necessary, but data-driven diagnostic tools hold potential for standardizing and quantifying traditional pulse diagnosis, moving it toward a scientifically robust practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robotic right lower lobe sleeve lobectomy using the single-port robotic system: Challenging case after immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-lung Fontan operation in a child with a double inlet left ventricle, pulmonary atresia, and absence of the left pulmonary artery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[White matter tracts involved in complex regional pain syndrome after subcortical stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Post-stroke complex regional pain syndrome (CRPS) is a challenging complication that impairs recovery during stroke rehabilitation, particularly during the subacute phase. Despite its clinical significance, the neural substrates underlying post-stroke CRPS, specifically following subcortical stroke, remain unclear. This retrospective observational study included 40 patients with first-ever subcortical stroke diagnosed with CRPS via a three-phase bone scan, and 40 propensity score-matched...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical decision-making after neoadjuvant chemotherapy in pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-term external biliary drainage in living donor liver transplantation using duct-to-duct anastomosis: a single-center experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A single institutional experience showed the effectiveness and safety of short-term EBD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of advanced bipolar <em>versus</em> conventional monopolar energy device in single incision laparoscopic total extraperitoneal hernia repair (SILTEP): a retrospective comparative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AB energy devices may offer advantages for SILTEP, including reduced intraoperative blood loss. AB energy devices may be useful and viable options for SILTEP. Further prospective studies are warranted to validate these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of job satisfaction and determinants between medical and surgical hospitalists in South Korea: a nationwide cross-sectional online survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Surgical hospitalists experienced higher workloads but maintained comparable satisfaction levels to their medical counterparts. Enhancing academic opportunities and tailoring financial incentives may be effective strategies to improve job satisfaction and support workforce retention across specialties.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting prognosis and optimal timing for surgery using CA 19-9 in patients with pancreatic cancer who underwent FOLFIRINOX-based neoadjuvant therapy: a retrospective single-center cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Timing of surgery after NAT should be decided considering post-NAT tumor size and CA 19-9 levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neurophysiological and cognitive enhancements in autonomous sensory meridian response identified using heart rate variability and electroencephalography connectivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Autonomous sensory meridian response (ASMR) is a sensory-emotional phenomenon characterized by tingling sensations and relaxation, typically elicited by auditory or visual stimuli. Although anecdotal reports suggest potential cognitive and physiological benefits, empirical evidence remains limited. Furthermore, objective physiological monitoring of ASMR-related responses has yet to be systematically explored.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of COVID-19 on Adaptive Skills and Psychiatric Symptoms in South Korean Children With Autism Spectrum Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The majority of South Korean children with ASD demonstrated stability despite the lack of consistency or structure during the pandemic. A 2-year longitudinal follow-up study is underway.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiplex Magnetic Biosensor Microarrays Facilitate Personalized Vaccination Schedules for SARS-CoV-2 Variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rapid, sensitive, multiplexed antibody detection technologies are essential for assessing vaccine efficacy and recipient immunity against viruses. As severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) variants continue to emerge and novel viruses may pose potential threats in the near future, personalized vaccines can be precisely tailored to an individual's measured immunity to help mitigate the symptoms of infection and viral spread. Here, we present giant magnetoresistive (GMR)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convergent Complex Quasi-Newton Proximal Methods for Gradient-Driven Denoisers in Compressed Sensing MRI Reconstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In compressed sensing (CS) MRI, model-based methods are pivotal to achieving accurate reconstruction. One of the main challenges in model-based methods is finding an effective prior to describe the statistical distribution of the target image. Plug-and-Play (PnP) and REgularization by Denoising (RED) are two general frameworks that use denoisers as the prior. While PnP/RED methods with convolutional neural network (CNN) based denoisers outperform classical hand-crafted priors in CS MRI, their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative modeling of longitudinal cell-free DNA and tumor volume dynamics: a multimodal quantitative prognostic framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Therefore, our study demonstrates that integration of longitudinal cfDNA and tumor volume dynamics yielded improved assessment of treatment response and prognosis in NSCLC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the clinical impact of plasma-only mutations in non-small cell lung cancer: a Korean multicenter experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Plasma-based ctDNA analysis broadens detection of actionable genomic alterations and facilitates access to targeted therapies in NSCLC, particularly when tissue biopsy is limited. These findings support integrating liquid biopsy into routine practice to optimize patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Foreign Body-Induced Duodenal Perforation Complicated by Retroperitoneal Abscess and Necrotizing Pancreatitis: A Report of a Rare Case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Duodenal perforations are rare but critical conditions that often present with significant morbidity and mortality. These injuries may result from peptic ulcer disease, trauma, or foreign bodies, with posterior perforations posing particular challenges due to their retroperitoneal location. Such perforations may lead to complications, including retroperitoneal abscesses, necrotizing pancreatitis, and fistula. The management of these cases often requires a multidisciplinary approach. This case...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Web-based high-intensity bodyweight interval training improves metabolic health and physical fitness outcomes in middle-aged men with obesity during the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reduced opportunities for physical activity during the COVID-19 pandemic have heightened obesity-related health risks, emphasizing the need for effective, scalable, and remotely deliverable exercise interventions. This randomized controlled trial examined the efficacy of an 8-week, real-time, supervised, web-based high-intensity interval training (HIIT) program in improving metabolic health and physical fitness in middle-aged men with obesity. Twenty-two men (age <45 years; BMI >30 kg/m²; waist...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative inverse design for microstructure control in precursors for Li- and Mn-rich layered-oxide cathodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microstructures often dictate materials' performance, yet they are rarely treated as an explicit design variable because microstructures are hard to quantify, predict, and optimize. We built an image-centric, closed-loop framework that makes microstructural morphology a controllable objective and demonstrate its use case with precursors for Li- and Mn-rich layered oxide cathodes. This work presents an integrated, AI-driven framework for the predictive design and optimization of lithium-ion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CpG-induced immune responses <em>via</em> DNA micelles, gold nanoparticles, and liposomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CpG oligodeoxynucleotides (CpG ODNs) are well-known adjuvants that induce innate immunity, particularly dendritic cell activation, by stimulating Toll-like receptor 9. However, the stimulatory efficacy of CpG ODNs is limited by their negative charge, which causes electrostatic repulsion from the cell membrane and hinders cellular uptake. In addition, CpG ODNs are rapidly degraded by nucleases under physiological conditions. To address these challenges, various nanoparticle (NP)-based delivery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adult-onset Familial TUBB4A-related Leukodystrophy Caused by c.286G&gt;A (p.Gly96Arg) in a Korean Family: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining Optimally Safe and Effective Blood Levels of Hydroxychloroquine in Lupus: An Important Step toward Precision Drug Monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The therapeutic reference range for HCQ blood level monitoring is 750-<1150 ng/ml. HCQ level monitoring could optimize HCQ use, particularly in patients with CKD stage ≥3. Future longitudinal studies are needed to validate the use of HCQ blood level monitoring in optimizing dosing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Weather and Sudden Sensorineural Hearing Loss: A Nationwide Study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides evidence that hot and humid weather conditions are associated with increased SSNHL risk. These findings offer scientific support for developing preventive strategies and public health guidelines, particularly amid increasing climate variability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoscale Mapping of Relativistic Carrier Mobility and Photoconduction Properties in Graphene/MoS<sub>2</sub> Heterostructure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this paper, relativistic carrier mobilities and photoconduction properties in graphene/MoS(2) heterostructure (GM-HS) are mapped via photoconductive scanning noise microscopy with a conducting nanoprobe. Graphene on MoS(2) (HS) regions shows two-times reduced sheet conductance (G(Sh)) without a significant increase in trap densities (N(T)) compared to that in graphene on SiO(2) (Gr) regions, due to the electron-doping in graphene by underlying MoS(2). Interestingly, both regions exhibit G(Sh)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing Condition-Specific Adverse Event Profiles of Modafinil for Labelled and Off-Label Uses: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Modafinil is approved for excessive daytime sleepiness in narcolepsy, obstructive sleep apnoea (OSA), and shift work sleep disorder (SWSD), but its widespread off-label use raises safety concerns. We evaluated the risk of adverse events (AEs) associated with both labelled and off-label use of modafinil. A systematic search of PubMed, Embase, and Cochrane identified 54 studies that met the inclusion criteria. In labelled uses, narcolepsy patients had significantly elevated risks of diarrhoea...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41367108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term trends in anemia prevalence before and after COVID-19 among non-pregnant adults in South Korea, 2010 to 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anemia is a global public health concern, yet its long-term trends in the general adult population, particularly during the COVID-19 pandemic, remain unclear. This study analyzed long-term trends and risk factors for anemia among non-pregnant adults including the pandemic. We analyzed data from the Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey conducted on non-pregnant adults. Anemia was defined as a hemoglobin level of <13 g/dL in males and <12 g/dL in females. The prevalence of anemia...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the femoral neck system and dynamic hip screw for femoral neck fracture: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FNS demonstrated shorter operative time, reduced blood loss, and improved functional outcomes compared to DHS, with comparable complication rates. These findings suggest that FNS may serve as a viable alternative to DHS for the treatment of FNFs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The immediate effectiveness of a multi-channeled oral irrigator in reducing dental plaque and oral malodor: A preliminary single-blind clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tooth brushing typically removes approximately 42% to 60% of the initial dental plaque in healthy adults. A single cycle of MCOI use reduced plaque by approximately 25% and significantly lowered CH₃SH, a compound associated with periodontal disease. These findings suggest that the MCOI may serve as a useful adjunct to tooth brushing, particularly for individuals with limited motor skills, and could help reduce the risk of plaque-related oral diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global, regional, and national burden of kidney cancer, 1990 to 2021, and projections to 2050: A Global Burden of Disease Study 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the Global Burden of Disease Study (GBD) 2019 offered important insights into kidney cancer, no research has yet examined the updated GBD 2021. Therefore, utilizing the GBD 2021, this study provides updated estimates of kidney cancer burden, identifies attributable risk factors, and projects future trends through 2050. Data on the global and regional burden of kidney cancer from 1990 to 2021 were extracted from the GBD 2021, stratified by age, sex, Sociodemographic Index (SDI), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transgenerational Dynamics of Endophytic Microbiome in Soybean Seeds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seeds harbor diverse microbial communities, including endophytes, some of which are vertically transmitted and may contribute to plant health and productivity. However, the temporal dynamics of seed endophytic communities remain poorly understood in many crop species. In this study, we monitored the composition of bacterial and fungal endophytes in soybean (Glycine max) seeds, along with rhizosphere microbiomes, across three plant generations using a culture-independent approach. Our results...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Planta Application and Efficacy of FireFighter-A Phage Cocktail for Combating Fire Blight]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fire blight, caused by Erwinia amylovora, poses a significant threat to Rosaceae crops and has caused substantial damage to South Korea since its emergence in 2015. Traditional control methods, including antibiotic- and copper-based treatments, have shown limitations, underscoring the necessity for alternative solutions to enhance efficacy while addressing the concerns associated with antibiotics. This study evaluated the efficacy of FireFighter-A, a novel phage cocktail, in managing fire...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Degenerative pathologies on cortical biopsy, dopaminergic depletion, and shunt efficacy in iNPH]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Coexisting degenerative pathologies may influence the efficacy of ventriculoperitoneal (VP) shunting in idiopathic normal pressure hydrocephalus (iNPH).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stress, Social Isolation Profiles, and Depressive Symptoms Among Older Adults in a Low-Income Community in Singapore]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Subjective loneliness, more so than objective structural isolation, is pivotal in shaping older adults' mental health and stress vulnerability within low-income settings. Interventions should consider decoupling loneliness from social isolation, tailoring support to the specific needs associated with different social isolation profiles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence-powered oocyte evaluation: Correlating cytoplasmic features with blastocyst development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings underscore the value of cytoplasmic features as objective indicators of developmental competence. This artificial intelligence-driven approach may improve embryo selection by providing a standardized, non-invasive method for evaluating oocytes, ultimately contributing to enhanced clinical outcomes in assisted reproductive technologies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How pre-pregnancy body mass index influences health-related quality of life during pregnancy: a serial multiple mediation analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: To promote HRQOL during pregnancy, healthcare professionals should educate women of reproductive age on the importance of maintaining a healthy BMI before conception. Additionally, prenatal care should incorporate simultaneous screening for sleep disturbances and depressive symptoms, particularly among women with elevated pre-pregnancy BMI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41366752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light and metabolism: label-free optical imaging of metabolic activities in biological systems [Invited]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic imaging is critical for understanding cellular functions beyond morphology, offering significant insights into various biological processes and disease states. Label-free optical imaging techniques stand out by providing high-resolution, molecularly specific, and/or non-invasive assessments of metabolic activity without relying on exogenous contrast agents. This review discusses the key photon-tissue interactions-absorption, emission, and scattering-that underpin label-free optical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41368095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma expression levels of microRNA-101 are downregulated in patients with Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41373032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Parkinson's disease (PD) is a neurodegenerative disorder characterized by the loss of dopaminergic neurons. Endoplasmic reticulum (ER) stress contributes to PD pathogenesis, with the ER-associated degradation (ERAD) system playing a protective role. HRD1, an ER-resident ubiquitin ligase, and its stabilizer SEL1L are involved in ERAD and neuronal survival. This study investigated alterations in the plasma levels of microRNA-101 (miR-101), which targets SEL1L, in patients with PD, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41373032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards "Zero by 30", the Kenyan case: a systematic exploration of barriers to rabies policy implementation through systems thinking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Stakeholder-validated causal-loop diagrams show that Kenya's rabies-control bottlenecks - such as vaccine stock-outs, fragmented surveillance and fluctuating political will - form self-reinforcing cycles that stall progress toward "Zero by 30". By exposing these dynamics, the study identifies policy entry-points that can break the cycles - shifting the conversation from what fails to why it persists. Therefore, the study offers decision-makers a structured systems map for turning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expression and Functional Evaluation of ABC and SLC Transporters in Human Choroid Plexus Papilloma (HIBCPP) Cells: A Human Blood-Cerebrospinal Fluid Barrier Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Various nutrient and drug transporters are functionally expressed in HIBCPP cells. Therefore, HIBCPP cells could serve as a useful human BCSFB model to evaluate nutrient and drug transport between the CSF and blood.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A mixed methods study comparing video based and paper based diagnostic error education for medical students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diagnostic errors, which can negatively impact patient outcomes, require better prevention strategies. Simulated patient case studies can be useful educational tools for medical students to reduce diagnostic errors. We compared the effectiveness of video- and paper-based diagnostic error case studies as teaching modalities for medical students. In this mixed-method, non-blinded randomized controlled trial, we recruited Japanese medical students. The participants (N = 113) received either video-...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A patient-centric approach to chronic rhinosinusitis with nasal polyps (CRSwNP): developing tools to improve disease management and outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372530/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The PMP could support patient-HCP education and communication, supplement management guidance, enhance shared decision-making, and ensure a timely, personalized, long-term treatment and management approach, including follow-up, for patients with CRSwNP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372530/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a nomogram incorporating YpT stage for predicting ypN0 using multicenter data in clinically node-positive breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have demonstrated that breast pathological complete response (pCR) can be accurately diagnosed preoperatively using image-guided needle biopsy after neoadjuvant chemotherapy (NAC), underscoring the value of incorporating ypT stage into prediction models for axillary response (ypN0). Based on this evidence, we developed and externally validated a nomogram to predict ypN0 in patients with clinically node-positive (cN+) breast cancer treated with NAC. This retrospective, multicenter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deformed wing virus affects foraging success and foraging specialization of honeybee workers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deformed wing virus (DWV) is a major driver of honeybee colony losses, yet its sublethal effects on adult foraging behaviour remain underexplored. Building on evidence that covert DWV infections impair sucrose responsiveness and associative learning, we tested whether infection changes foraging success and specialization in worker bees. Using a controlled experiment, we marked 1,000 newly emerged workers that were either inoculated with DWV lysate or injected with an RNA-interference control...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artifact-free preparation of biological samples for SEM by optimized water freeze-drying]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Water freeze-drying has traditionally been considered an inappropriate drying method for biological samples for scanning electron microscopy (SEM) because ice crystals can potentially form and damage cell structures. Chemical fixation is also considered essential for the SEM observation of soft cells, such as protozoa and animal cells. We succeeded in preparing specimens of freshwater protists for SEM using simple water freeze-drying without chemical fixation. Specifically, a suspension of live...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In-situ total X-ray scattering reveals the structural evolution of SrIrO<sub>3</sub> during the oxygen evolution reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the importance of oxygen evolution reaction (OER) catalysts in energy conversion applications, the time-resolved dynamics of their amorphous phases remain elusive. Understanding the structural evolution of OER catalysts is pivotal to improve their design and sustainability and increase the energy conversion efficiency. SrIrO(3) is a promising OER catalyst for achieving high energy conversion efficiencies, but it has not been sufficiently characterized in terms of its phase dynamics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying topological phases through global and local symmetries of the quantum transfer matrix]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The 1-form symmetries in two-dimensional topological systems are "shadowed" as global symmetries in their one-dimensional quantum transfer matrices. In this work, we introduce a distinct shadow effect arising from the pair-creation of anyons, which manifests as a local symmetry of the quantum transfer matrix. The interplay between these two shadow effects provides a powerful framework for characterizing topological phases without extensive numerical simulations. Specifically, we derive the phase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic and functional changes in vascular endothelial cell monolayers under combined hypoxic and inflammatory stimuli]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In sepsis, dysregulated inflammatory responses cause microthrombi formation, leading to organ hypoxia. While endothelial cell (EC) responses to inflammation are well-studied, the combined effects of hypoxia and inflammation remain unclear. We investigated EC dynamics and function under simultaneous hypoxia and lipopolysaccharide (LPS) exposure using microfluidic devices with controllability of oxygen concentration. Collective cell migration was measured by particle image velocimetry, while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vasopressin-to-oxytocin receptor crosstalk in the preoptic area underlying parental behaviors in male mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The transition to parenthood brings significant changes in behavior toward offspring. For instance, in anticipation of their offspring, male mice shift from infanticidal to caregiving behaviors. While the release of oxytocin from the paraventricular hypothalamus (PVH) plays a critical role in paternal caregiving, it does not fully account for the entire behavioral shift. The specific downstream neurons and signaling mechanisms involved in this process remain obscure. Here, we demonstrate that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chromosome-scale, haplotype-resolved genome of Bighead catfish for conservation and aquaculture]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The first haplotype-resolved chromosome-scale genome assembly for the bighead catfish (Clarias macrocephalus), a freshwater species native to Thailand and Vietnam, which has importance in aquaculture and conservation, is presented here. The 880 Mb genome was assembled using high-fidelity long-read sequencing from Pacific Biosciences and Oxford Nanopore Technologies, which was scaffolded using high-throughput chromosome conformation capture data, and polished with Illumina short-read sequencing....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Publisher Correction: A red fluorescent genetically encoded biosensor for in vivo imaging of extracellular l-lactate dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MAASTY: a (dis)ordered copolymer for structural determination of human membrane proteins in native nanodiscs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amphiphilic copolymers capable of extracting membrane proteins directly from cellular membranes into "native nanodiscs" offer a simplified approach for preparing membrane proteins in lipid nanodiscs compared to approaches that rely on detergent. Copolymer amphiphilicity, length, and composition influence their performance, in addition to the protein itself and the purification conditions used. Here, we report a copolymer composed of methacrylic acid and styrene, which we term MAASTY, leveraging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antitumor Activity of Death Receptor 5-Targeted Camptothecin-Loaded Nanoparticles in Murine Syngeneic Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Death receptor 5 (DR5) is a key mediator of the extrinsic apoptotic pathway that is often upregulated in tumors, rendering it an attractive target for cancer therapy. Activation of DR5 requires oligomerization, which can be achieved through multivalent presentation of DR5 ligands on nanoparticles. DR5-targeted nanoparticles can efficiently agonize DR5 to inhibit the growth of human xenografts, although it remains unclear whether these effects would translate to a syngeneic tumor model with an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41372101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in Stimuli-Responsive Peptide-Polymer Carriers for Mitochondrial Therapeutics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondria are essential organelles that govern energy metabolism, redox balance, and cell survival; their dysfunction is implicated in a wide range of pathologies, including neurodegenerative disorders, cardiovascular diseases, metabolic syndromes, and cancer. Despite their significance as therapeutic targets, the unique structural and electrochemical properties of mitochondria, particularly the impermeable inner mitochondrial membrane and high membrane potential pose major challenges for the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Violet light-transmitting intraocular lens increases choroidal thickness: 1-year prospective, randomised controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The choroidal thickening after cataract surgery was associated with the VL-transmitting IOL and longer time spent outdoors with exposure to abundant VL. Despite these findings, this study has several limitations, including a relatively short follow-up period, and it did not assess postoperative lifestyle, VL exposure or actual peripheral defocus in the patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A water-soluble β-cyclodextrin polymer reduces cholesterol accumulation and autophagy dysfunction in vitro and in Niemann-Pick type C disease model mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Niemann-Pick disease type C (NPC) and Alzheimer's disease (AD) are characterised by cognitive dysfunction and neurological impairment. In both diseases, the abnormal accumulation and disruption of cholesterol homeostasis in the brain may contribute to the pathogenesis and exacerbation of symptoms. Cyclodextrins (CDs) are attracting attention as therapeutic agents that can reduce free cholesterol in the brain. A water-soluble β-CD polymer (β-CDP) consisting of multiple β-CDs cross-linked by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coagulation and Fibrinolysis Profiles in Mouse Breast Cancer 4T1 Tumor-Bearing Mice: A Characterization of Neutrophil-Associated Prothrombotic States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer-associated thrombosis is the second leading cause of death in patients with cancer. The highly metastatic triple-negative mouse breast cancer cell line 4T1 induces thrombus formation that is dependent on neutrophil extracellular traps (NETs) in transplanted mice when exposed to certain stimuli, such as lipopolysaccharide (LPS) injection. These findings suggest that 4T1 transplantation into mice increases the susceptibility to NET release, followed by thrombus formation in response to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationship between the salience network and facial emotion recognition in social anxiety disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Social anxiety disorder (SAD) is thought to involve the negative evaluation of facial emotions. Although imaging studies have examined this aspect, no study has investigated the relationship between resting-state functional connectivity (rsFC) and facial emotion recognition in SAD. Hyperconnectivity in the salience network, particularly involving the anterior cingulate cortex (ACC), has been reported to be associated with facial recognition and SAD. This study aimed to identify the association...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Femoral Morphology and Range of Motion After Eccentric Rotational Acetabular Osteotomy in Males with Hip Dysplasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Eccentric rotational acetabular osteotomy (ERAO) enhances acetabular coverage and optimizes joint contact pressure in patients with hip dysplasia (HD); however, postoperative range of motion (ROM) may be restricted due to bony impingement. The impact of this procedure on anterior ROM in males remains unknown. ROM depends on both acetabular morphology and femoral neck anteversion (FNA); hence, this study aimed to address the following questions: (1)Does sex affect the achievement of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of Epithelial Lining Fluid Drug Concentrations to MIC<sub>i</sub>-Based PK/PD Modeling of Cefepime/Nacubactam in a Murine Model of CPE Pneumonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings support the utility of MIC(i)-based PK/PD analysis for optimizing combination antibiotic therapy in pneumonia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming construction waste into low-carbon cementitious materials through co-calcination of recycled concrete fines and kaolinite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explores a sustainable route to synthesize a novel supplementary cementitious material (SCM) through co-calcination of recycled concrete fines (RCF)-a secondary powder waste from recycled aggregate production-with kaolin clay. The co-calcination process effectively utilizes the overlapping temperature ranges of cement hydrate decomposition and kaolinite dehydroxylation, enabling the formation of a limestone calcined clay (LC(2))-type SCM. Co-calcination promotes the formation of α-...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustained diabetes remission induced by FGF1 involves a shift in transcriptionally distinct AgRP neuron subpopulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In rodent models of type 2 diabetes, a single intracerebroventricular (icv) injection of fibroblast growth factor 1 (FGF1) induces sustained remission of hyperglycemia. Overactive agouti-related peptide (AgRP) neurons, located in the hypothalamic arcuate nucleus, are a hallmark of diabetic states, and their long-term inhibition has been linked to FGF1's antidiabetic effects. To investigate the underlying mechanism(s), we performed single-nucleus RNA sequencing of the mediobasal hypothalamus at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Duloxetine-induced inhibition of voltage-gated K<sup>+</sup> 3.1 (Kv3.1) channels and underlying electrophysiological mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Duloxetine is a serotonin-norepinephrine reuptake inhibitor that has been widely used to treat major depression; however, it has also been associated with severe neuropsychiatric side effects, including hallucinations, confusion, and suicide attempts. Nevertheless, the electrophysiological mechanisms underlying these adverse effects remain poorly understood. In this study, we investigated the effect of duloxetine on cloned neuronal rat voltage-gated K^(+) (Kv) channel subunit Kv3.1, stably...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondrial Dynamics in Neurodegenerative Diseases: Research Hotspots and Trends from 2005 to 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This bibliometric study maps the intellectual structure and evolutionary trajectory of mitochondrial dynamics research in neurodegenerative diseases. It documents a field-wide paradigm shift toward a translational agenda centered on the MQC framework. Furthermore, the findings highlight the necessity of integrating pharmacological interventions with lifestyle modifications and precision medicine approaches to overcome translational barriers and develop effective disease-modifying...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary supplementation with silkworm pupae prevents growth retardation in broilers under heat stress conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Global warming poses a major challenge to livestock production, particularly in broiler chickens. They are highly sensitive to heat stress due to their elevated metabolic activity associated with rapid growth and high productivity. Pupae of the silkworm (Bombyx mori) are known for their immunostimulatory properties. In this study, we investigated the effects on broiler performance of dietary supplementation with defatted silkworm pupae (DSP) under elevated ambient temperatures (neutral, days...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification and characterization of peptidyl-prolyl isomerase Pin1 as a new regulatory component of BCR::ABL1 degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While tyrosine kinase inhibitors (TKIs) can effectively counteract BCR::ABL1 activity, resistance by BCR::ABL1 overexpression is a significant challenge in combating chronic myeloid leukemia, making down-regulation of BCR::ABL1 a promising anti-cancer strategy. We previously reported that the ubiquitin ligases c-Cbl and CHIP mediate BCR::ABL1 protein degradation. Bag1, a nucleotide exchange factor for Hsc70, senses immature structures of Hsp90-unchaperoned BCR::ABL1 protein and stimulates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41371165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative modelling of biomolecular dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Much of our mechanistic understanding of the functions of biological macromolecules is based on static structural experiments, which can be modelled either as single structures or conformational ensembles. While these provide us with invaluable insights, they do not directly reveal that molecules are inherently dynamic. Advances in time-dependent and time-resolved experimental methods have made it possible to capture the dynamics of biomolecules at increasingly higher spatial and temporal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Factors associated with pulmonary function decline in patients with rheumatoid arthritis-associated interstitial lung disease" [Respir. Investig. Volume 63, Issue 5, Pages 857-865]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying the Initiation of Oshikatsu and Health-Promoting Activities Through Oshikatsu Among Older Adults: A Trajectory Equifinality Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oshikatsu, supporting a specific individual or group, has been linked to enhanced well-being and physical activity motivation. However, few studies have explored how this practice begins, particularly among older adults. This study applied the Trajectory Equifinality Approach (TEA) to investigate how individuals aged 50 and above initiate oshikatsu and subsequently engage in health-promoting activities, and to identify influencing factors. Semi-structured interviews were conducted with nine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EEG-Based meditation decoding: Tackling subject variability with spatial and temporal alignment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective. Meditation and mindfulness are increasingly recognized as important in improving mental well-being. However, Electroencephalography (EEG)-based neurofeedback systems supporting these practices typically fail to generalize to unseen subjects. This study investigates the application of both spatial and spectral alignment to EEG to improve the classification of meditation and rest states for new subjects without any model retraining.Approach. Two unsupervised domain adaptation techniques...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal social network modeling of mobile connectivity data with graph neural networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have emerged as a state-of-the-art data-driven tool for modeling connectivity data of graph-structured complex networks and integrating information of their nodes and edges in space and time. However, as of yet, the analysis of social networks using the time series of people's mobile connectivity data has not been extensively investigated. In the present study, we investigate four recently proposed snapshot - based temporal GNNs in predicting the phone call and SMS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41370318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methane oxidation and C1 metabolism in a propane-utilizer Gordonia sp. strain TY-5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gordonia sp. strain TY-5 utilizes propane, but not methane, as the sole carbon source. In this strain, propane is oxidized to 2-propanol by propane monooxygenase (Prm), and 2-propanol is further metabolized to methyl acetate, which is subsequently converted into acetate and methanol. However, methane and methanol metabolism in strain TY-5 has remained unclear. In this study, draft genome analysis revealed that strain TY-5 possesses the one-carbon (C1) dissimilation pathway, in which methanol is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term clinical control in acromegaly patients with postoperative discordant nadir growth hormone during oral glucose tolerance test and insulin-like growth factor 1 levels: a retrospective observational study and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Most patients achieved a mid- to long-term disease-controlled state without additional treatment. Given the potential risk of GH deficiency from further treatment, it may be reasonable to consider patients clinically controlled as long as IGF-1 levels remain normalized, with careful long-term monitoring recommended.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DC-STAMP and OC-STAMP cooperatively regulate osteoclast and foreign body giant cell cell-cell fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DC-STAMP and OC-STAMP cooperate to promote osteoclast and FBGC cell-cell fusion. DC-STAMP and OC-STAMP doubly deficient mice exhibit increased osteogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Irrigation Flow Rate and Silent Cerebral Events During Pulsed Field Ablation With a Variable-Loop Catheter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41369638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251211024156&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>