<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:21:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-Halogenated Solvent Processed Shortwave Infrared Organic Photodetectors Using Sub-1 eV Bandgap Acceptor with Cyano Substitution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shortwave infrared (SWIR) organic photodetectors (OPDs) offer significant potential but face persistent challenges such as limited responsivity and high noise under reverse bias. This work presents the development of high-performance OPDs for SWIR sensing, leveraging a newly designed non-fullerene acceptor (NFA) named 6CN. The 6CN molecule, featuring a fused-cyclopentadithiophene (fCPDT) core and cyano-substituted π-bridges, exhibits an ultra-narrow optical bandgap of ≈0.98 eV, enabling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging Evidence and Practice: A Consensus Statement from the Korean Diabetes Association on Diabetes Screening, Pharmacological Treatment and Severe Diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This Korean Diabetes Association (KDA) consensus statement bridges global evidence with the Korean clinical context, where large randomized and real-world data remain limited. Recommendations required ≥80% agreement by the committee of clinical practice guideline and approval by the board of directors. The statement comprises three domains: diabetes screening aligned with Korean epidemiology; pharmacologic management guided by pathophysiology and comorbidities; and a severity construct of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative efficacy of seed biopriming and soil drenching with Bacillus altitudinis TM22 and Bacillus atrophaeus MCM61 on the suppression of Fusarium wilt of cotton]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study highlights the potential of Bacillus strains TM22 and MCM61 applied via seed biopriming and soil drenching in suppressing Fusarium wilt and enhancing biomass of cotton plants. © 2025 The Author(s). Pest Management Science published by John Wiley & Sons Ltd on behalf of Society of Chemical Industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DICER1-Associated Gynecologic Neoplasms: An Update and Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DICER1 plays a crucial role in the biogenesis and maturation of microRNAs. Germline mutations in the DICER1 gene are associated with an increased risk of developing a wide range of benign and malignant neoplasms. The same tumors may also arise sporadically due to somatic DICER1 mutations. In syndromic patients, a germline loss-of-function DICER1 mutation is usually followed by a somatic hotspot mutation in the tumor as a second hit. In the gynecologic tract, DICER1-associated neoplasms include...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A MOF-derived iron oxide nanorod platform for multiplexed detection of ovarian cancer extracellular vesicle biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-grade serous ovarian cancer (HGSOC) is a highly aggressive malignancy often diagnosed at an advanced stage due to the absence of early symptoms and effective diagnostic tools. Extracellular vesicles (EVs) secreted by tumour cells carry disease-specific biomarkers, offering potential for early detection. However, their low concentration in biological samples poses challenges for isolation and detection, necessitating highly sensitive and specific multiplexed assays for subsequent detection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid Brain/Neural Exoskeleton Enables Bimanual ADL Training in Routine Stroke Rehabilitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the compatibility of the novel B/NE with existing clinical workflows and its feasibility to enable B/NE-supported stroke neurorehabilitation by facilitating seamless integration into clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic Insights of Bipolar Redox Cathodes for Organic Rechargeable Batteries: LUMO Anti‒Bonding Contributions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The search for sustainable organic cathode materials has been constrained by intrinsically low redox potentials and limited understanding of p‒type redox chemistry. In this study, we establish a rational design framework for bipolar cathodes by combining p‒type functionalities (‒NH(2), ‒OH, ‒SH) with carbonyl backbones and elucidating their structure‒property relationships using the first-principles calculations. We find that redox potentials and resultant discharging behaviors are governed by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CELLama: Foundation Model for Single Cell and Spatial Transcriptomics by Cell Embedding Leveraging Language Model Abilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Large-scale single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq) and spatial transcriptomics (ST) have transformed biomedical research into a data-driven field, enabling the creation of comprehensive atlases. These methodologies facilitate detailed understanding of biology and pathophysiology; however, the complexity and sheer volume of data present analytical challenges, particularly in robust cell typing, integration, and understanding complex spatial relationships of cells. To address these challenges,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasmonic Nanolenses with Tunable Thickness: Enhanced Near-Field Focusing via Rim-Localized Light Absorption and Energy Transfer to a Central Nanochannel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, the rational design and implementation of a modular chemical toolkit involving on-demand synthetic steps are reported, enabling the fabrication of plasmonic gold (Au) nanolenses consisting of 2D hexagonal nanoplates (NPLs) with central porous domains. These nanostructures exhibit tunable thickness along the z-axis and enable precise control over the ratio between the internal porous region and the surrounding smooth rim. The latter is designed to maximize the absorption of light, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Purification of Tin Iodide through Solid-State Reaction for Efficient Tin-Lead Mixed Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tin-lead (Sn-Pb) mixed perovskite solar cells (PSCs), which serve as the rear subcell, have achieved significant advancements, largely driving the remarkable power conversion efficiency (PCE) seen in recent all-perovskite tandem solar cells (TSCs). However, the efficiency of Sn-Pb mixed PSCs is limited by the oxidation susceptibility of Sn^(2+), which induces the formation of Sn vacancies in the perovskite thin films, leading to an increase in defect densities. To address this issue, a novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regiodivergent and Stereoselective Hydrothiolation of Ynamides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a regiodivergent and stereoselective hydrothiolation of ynamides, enabling access to α- or β-aminovinyl sulfides with complete stereocontrol under mild and sustainable conditions. Notably, this study introduces the first example of the hydrogen-bond-mediated umpolung β-addition of ynamides, employing ionic liquids (ILs) as bifunctional hydrogen-bond activators. This conceptually distinct approach expands the reactivity of ynamides beyond canonical keteniminium pathways. Mechanistic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colonoscopy Quality and Strategies for Improvement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colonoscopy plays a pivotal role in colorectal cancer (CRC) screening and reduces CRC incidence and mortality. Its effectiveness depends on colonoscopist performance, which can vary. Missed lesions during colonoscopy can lead to post-colonoscopy CRC (PCCRC), making high-quality colonoscopy essential for maximizing the preventive benefit of CRC screening. This review highlights the significance of colonoscopy quality indicators and practices for improvement. Bowel preparation, cecal intubation,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Silver Ions as Ambipolar Dopants in InAs Nanocrystal Solids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The precise control of semiconductor polarity in nanocrystals (NCs) is crucial for optimizing device performance in various optoelectronic applications. In this study, it is shown that Ag⁺, added post-synthetically to InAs NCs using an AgNO(3) solution, can induce either n-type or p-type doping of the solid, depending on the intrinsic polarity of the host and the dopant concentration. In n-type InAs NCs, Ag⁺ consistently acts as an interstitial n-type dopant, shifting the conduction band minimum...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of carbon nanocomposites consisting of nanocellulose-derived carbon and reduced graphene oxide for high-performance captive deionization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several types of nanocellulose-derived carbon/reduced graphene oxide (rGO) nanocomposites are synthesized using three nanocellulose types: cellulose nanofibers (CNF), long cellulose nanocrystals (CNC-L), and short cellulose nanocrystals (CNC-S). The nanocomposites achieve a large surface area due to the small nanocellulose fibers acting as spacers. For the capacitive deionization (CDI) test, the CNC-L/rGO is selected and compared with the rGO prepared without nanocelluloses. It achieves a high...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reference Intervals for Whole-Blood Viscosity Measured Using the Fully Automated Scanning Capillary Tube Viscometer RHEOVIS 200 in Korean Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate interpretation of whole-blood viscosity (WBV) requires population-specific reference intervals (RIs), as WBV is influenced by sex, age, and Hct. This study is the first to establish RIs for WBV using a fully automated scanning capillary tube viscometer, RHEOVIS 200 (Biorheologics, Jeonju, Republic of Korea), in Korean adults. WBV was measured in 438 adults at shear rates of 1 s^(-1) (diastolic WBV) and 300 s^(-1) (systolic WBV). RIs were determined using the non-parametric method...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Disulfide Chemistry for Functional Polymers: Self-Healing, Vitrimer Behavior, and Biochemical/Electronic Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dynamic covalent disulfide bonds offer a powerful strategy for engineering polymeric materials with self-healing, recyclability, and programable degradation. Unlike traditional polymers with static covalent networks, disulfide-based systems respond to mild stimuli, such as heat, UV irradiation, or pH changes, through reversible bond dissociation and exchange. This allows structural rearrangement without compromising integrity, supporting repeated reuse and extended service life. Owing to their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Phenotypes of Diabetic Peripheral Neuropathy: Implications for Phenotypic-Based Therapeutics Strategies (Diabetes Metab J 2025;49:542-64)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between Fatty Liver Index and Incident Diabetes according to Alcohol Consumption Status in Young Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anthropometric Changes and Risk of Visual Impairment in Patients with Newly Diagnosed Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A New Era in Islet Transplantation: Stem Cell-Derived and Gene-Edited Islet Therapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preventing End-Stage Kidney Disease in Older Adults with Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus: Optimal Blood Pressure Targets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Physical Activity Strategies for Older Adults with Diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing prevalence of diabetes among older adults has emerged as a major socioeconomic burden. This population is highly heterogeneous, ranging from functionally independent to severely impaired individuals, making it difficult to establish standardized recommendations. Physical activity (PA) is a cornerstone of diabetes management; however, current exercise guidelines do not adequately address the wide spectrum of functional capacities observed in older adults. For those with physical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Synthesis of WS9326B <em>via</em> a Bioinspired Macrolactonization Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[WS9326B (1) is a cycloheptadepsipeptide isolated from Streptomyces sp. SNM55 and is distinguished by its rare (Z)-pentenyl cinnamic acid side chain and notable antiangiogenic activity. Herein, we report its total synthesis through a bioispired macrolactonization strategy. Sequential amide couplings followed by Shiina esterification delivered WS9326B in 13 longest linear steps. This bioinspired synthesis provides a versatile platform for producing WS9326B and offers a distinctive perspective on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quaternized Lignin-Loaded Electrospun Fish Gelatin Nanofibers for Active Food Packaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study proposes quaternized lignin (QL) as a sustainable and multifunctional additive for active food packaging applications and presents the development of fish gelatin (FG)-based nanofiber packaging materials. Cationic QL was synthesized via glycidyltrimethylammonium chloride (GTMAC) modification of kraft lignin to enhance its water dispersibility and antimicrobial properties. The resulting QL derivatives were incorporated into FG-based nanofibers via electrospinning, which were stabilized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Where Can Aluminum Go When Batteries Die?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[By 2030, the European Union (EU) is expected to have over 30 million electric vehicles (EVs), making the environmental challenges of end-of-life batteries a significant concern. While repurposing extends battery use in less demanding applications, recycling reclaims materials for new products, conserves metal resources, and lessens environmental impact. However, most recycling follows a "shred-first, sort-later" approach, which mixes components and makes separation difficult, leading to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermal Shielding and Vapor Transport Enhancement in MOF-Enabled Membranes for Membrane Distillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Desalination via membrane distillation (MD) powered by low-grade or waste heat is an emerging approach to energy-efficient water purification. However, conventional membranes suffer from significant conductive heat loss, which limits their thermal performance. Developing membranes with low thermal conductivity is crucial for enhancing thermal efficiency. This study introduces a metal-organic framework-enabled membrane (MEM) by embedding zeolite imidazole framework 8 (ZIF-8) onto Poly(vinylidene...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light-Mediated Electrification Enabled Noncontact Mode Quasi-2D Perovskite Triboelectric Nanogenerator for Motion Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid expansion of the Internet of Things (IoT) has intensified the demand for durable, self-powered systems that can simultaneously harvest energy and sense environmental stimuli. Triboelectric nanogenerators (TENGs) have gained significant attention for their versatility in harnessing various environmental energy sources. However, conventional TENGs suffer from interfacial wear and lack photoresponsiveness, limiting their wide applicability. We report a photoenhanced, noncontact TENG based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LC-MS/MS Assay for Quantification of DA-1241, a Novel GPR119 Agonist, in Animal and Human Plasma: Application to Preclinical Pharmacokinetic Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DA-1241 is a novel GPR119 receptor agonist under development as a therapeutic candidate for metabolic dysfunction-associated steatohepatitis. To enable precise quantification of DA-1241 in mouse, rat, dog, and human plasma, a simple and highly sensitive LC-MS/MS approach was designed and thoroughly evaluated. Plasma samples were processed using protein precipitation with acetonitrile, followed by chromatographic separation on a reverse-phase C(18) column (3.0-mm i.d. × 50 mm, 2.7 μm). Isocratic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The emergence of object play in young children at elevated likelihood for autism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This prospective study investigated object exploration and combination play, in addition to (pre-)symbolic play in children at elevated likelihood for autism (EL; younger siblings of autistic children and very preterm children). Play of EL-children with (n = 22) and without (n = 61) a best-estimate research diagnosis of autism at 36 months was measured using detailed coding of direct observations at the (corrected) age of 10 and 14 months. As expected, autistic and non-autistic EL-children...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating Sorbents in CO<sub>2</sub> Electroreduction: A Model System to Disentangle Layer Contributions in Membrane Electrode Assemblies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Membrane electrode assemblies (MEAs) are crucial in high-performance CO(2) electrolysis, reducing iR losses and overcoming low solubility issues by supplying CO(2) in the gas form. However, liquid anolyte permeation to the cathode causes salt precipitation, stability issues, and parasitic H(2) evolution, hindering industrial implementation. Full gas-phase operation could mitigate these problems, but a model system to study gas-phase concepts is lacking. This study presents a planar bimetallic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nb-Promoted Pt/MoO<sub>x</sub>/TiO<sub>2</sub> Catalysts for Low-Temperature CO<sub>2</sub> Hydrogenation to Methanol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The catalytic hydrogenation of carbon dioxide (CO(2)) to methanol under mild conditions presents a sustainable route for carbon recycling and chemical energy storage. However, the inert nature of CO(2) and high activation energy barrier for methanol formation remain major challenges. In this study, we developed a series of Nb-promoted Pt/MoOx/TiO(2) catalysts for efficient CO(2) hydrogenation at temperatures below 200 °C. Among these, Pt(5)/Mo(10)-Nb(1)/TiO(2) exhibited superior performance,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of an Equilibrium between a Betaine and a 1,2-Oxaphosphetane in a Phosphaboratatriptycene System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The deprotonations of β-hydroxyalkylphosphonium salts containing a phosphaboratatriptycene skeleton with MHMDS (M = Li, Na, and K) were monitored by variable-temperature (VT) ^(31)P{¹H} NMR spectroscopy. Upon using LiHMDS, the corresponding betaines were observed at 25 °C, whereas the betaines were detectable below -40 °C, upon using NaHMDS. In contrast, the corresponding 1,2-oxaphosphetanes were observed upon using NaHMDS in the presence of crown ether and KHMDS. The results indicated that the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient Thorium/Barium Separation by Quaternary Ammonium Functionalized Silica Composite toward Sustainable Production of <sup>212</sup>Pb for Targeted Alpha Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[^(212)Pb has become a critical parent isotope for ^(212)Bi, which is an alpha-emitting radionuclide utilized in targeted alpha therapy (TAT) for oncology; however, its limited availability impedes broader clinical use. To tackle this significant challenge, this study focuses on a strategic approach to separate ^(228)Th (a precursor to ^(212)Pb) from its parent isotope ^(228)Ra within the decay chain of naturally occurring ^(232)Th. A novel porous silica composite, functionalized with quaternary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Titanate Nanosheets/Cellulose Composite Showing Improved Crystallinity and Decreased Water Wettability by Gamma-Irradiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While molecularly thin nanosheets have been increasingly studied as functional coatings, their use as a hydrophobic and γ-irradiation-tolerant component in biologically derived matrices is to be demonstrated. Herein, simple dip-coating was employed to fabricate titanate nanosheets/cellulose composites, which were subjected to γ-irradiation up to 50 kGy. Their surface chemistry was evaluated by water contact angle (WCA) measurements and X-ray photoelectron spectroscopy (XPS). Upon irradiation,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac Structure and Function Among Patients With Heart Failure With Reduced Ejection Fraction and Kidney Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among HFrEF patients, future onset of KD and prevalent KD were increasingly associated with impaired GLS, LVEF, TAPSE, and E/e' ratio. Furthermore, LVEF, TAPSE, and E/e' ratio were independent predictors of incident KD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The obestrung personality: A clinical confounder of obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This communication defines and describes the obestrung personality trait, which can be a clinical confounder of obesity. Obestrung (based upon high-strung) personality can be defined as a trait characterized by excessive preoccupation with weight, weight loss, weight loss strategies and weight loss outcomes. Timely identification and alleviation of such attitudes and behaviour is important. This is because excessive stress, through release of cortisol and proinflammatory cytokines, can hamper...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medical termination of unplanned pregnancies in women with diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Women living with diabetes may experience unplanned pregnancies. This poses challenges and risk to both maternal and foetal health in case glycaemia and other associated comorbidities are not optimized. This may lead to doubts regarding continuation of pregnancy, given there are no clear guidelines or position statement for decision regarding termination or continuation of pregnancy. Multiple biomedical, psychosocial and environmental factors determine the course and outcome of such pregnancies....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Full marathon after bilateral total hip arthroplasty: case report with magnetic resonance imaging findings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Long-distance running is not a recommended form of exercise after total hip arthroplasty (THA). However, younger and more active patients often wish to return to sport after THA. We present the case of a 38-year-old man who underwent bilateral THA for osteonecrosis. Three months after surgery and rehabilitation, the patient returned to his normal life. He returned to sport one year after surgery when he engaged in long-distance running and documented his daily exercise status. In the fourth year...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Viral hemorrhagic fevers - therapeutic trial advances and challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Viral hemorrhagic fevers (VHFs) represent a group of severe diseases caused by RNA viruses with high fatality rates, posing significant global health threats. These diseases are prioritized by the World Health Organization due to their epidemic potential, geographical restrictions, and limited therapeutic options.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tuning Polyacrylate Composition to Recognize and Modulate Fluorescent Proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Molecular definition is usually regarded as a prerequisite to achieve protein recognition and functional modulation, particularly for macromolecular interactions. Herein, we report that polymers with specific combinations of monomers arranged into random sequences [random hetero oligomers (RHOs)] can selectively bind to a model protein. Using green fluorescent protein (GFP) as a target, polyacrylates were developed that bound with nanomolar affinity and enhanced fluorescence by >100%....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seeing Beyond the Coronaries: Pairing Echocardiography With Targeted Carotid Ultrasound After Percutaneous Coronary Intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synovial histopathology in common orthopaedic joint conditions assessed with a modified krenn synovitis score]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While maintaining the concept and basic elements of the Krenn synovitis score, MKSS incorporated more details of synovial pathology, particularly inflammatory infiltration and fibrosis. It could provide a more comprehensive evaluation of synovial pathology in common orthopaedic joint conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Vitro Activity of Nitroxoline (5-Nitro-8-Hydroxyquinoline) Against Aspergillus Species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results correspond to excellent in vitro activity against Aspergillus spp.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Streptococcus mutans and Cariogenic Biofilms: Mechanisms, Disruption Strategies, and Future Therapeutic Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dental caries, a significant global health concern, is intricately linked to the development and persistence of cariogenic biofilms on tooth surfaces. These complex microbial ecosystems orchestrate a multifactorial process of decay, adhering to teeth, producing acids that erode enamel, and exhibiting resistance to traditional therapies. This review delves into the intricate mechanisms of cariogenic biofilm formation and pathogenesis, exploring adhesion, acid production, extracellular polymeric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Population Genetic History and Evolutionary Dynamics on the Eastern Tibetan Plateau]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The origins of Tibeto-Burman populations on the eastern Tibetan Plateau (TP), especially within the Tibetan-Yi Corridor, remain unresolved. We sequenced whole genomes of 293 individuals from 21 Tibeto-Burman-speaking groups and genotyped 799 individuals from 60 Sino-Tibetan-speaking groups to reconstruct regional population history. Our analyses reveal fine-scale substructure and extensive admixture along the underrepresented Tibetan-Yi and Hexi corridors, driven by gene flow from Eastern...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to: Utility of Progression Rate Since Symptom Onset in Predicting Subsequent Survival in Progressive Supranuclear Palsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lattice Hydrogen Engineering Unlocks Inert TiO<sub>2</sub> for H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub> Electrosynthesis in Neutral Media]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical H(2)O(2) production through the two-electron oxygen reduction reaction (2e^(-) ORR) represents a transformative route for sustainable and decentralized chemical synthesis. Nevertheless, conventional catalysts struggle to achieve optimal intermediates adsorption and efficient proton-coupled electron transfer (PCET) under neutral conditions, as the sluggish dissociation of water imposes a severe kinetic bottleneck. Herein, we introduce a lattice hydrogen engineering strategy that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cooperative Au<sub>vertex</sub>-Au<sub>shoulder</sub> Pair Sites of Biicosahedral Au<sub>25</sub> Cluster for Highly Oxidative Carbonylation of Diamine to Cyclic Urea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The realization of target reactants completely transformed on the designed active sites toward desired products remains a challenge. Here, we report that the [Au(25)(PPh(3))(10)(SCH(2)CH(2)Ph)(5)Cl(2)]^(2+) cluster in the library of metal clusters is unique for the oxidative carbonylation of diamine to cyclic urea. Our studies reveal that the ligand on-off dynamics in the presence of solvent coupled with diamine can invoke the active function of the vertex and shoulder Au of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between pre-pregnancy cardiovascular health and singleton birthweight after in vitro fertilization/intracytoplasmic sperm injection: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Better maternal pre-pregnancy CVH is associated with more favorable neonatal birthweight outcomes after IVF/ICSI. Improving maternal CVH, particularly BMI, might reduce the risk of abnormal birthweight and improve assisted reproductive technology outcomes. These findings have implications for clinical practice in terms of pre-pregnancy health management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OSA Initiates Histone Lactylation That Drives PDE4B/FUS/AGT Axis to Pulmonary Hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) is strongly associated with an increased risk of hypertension; however, the molecular mechanisms linking these two conditions remain incompletely understood. In this study, we identified phosphodiesterase 4B (PDE4B) as a key mediator in the development of OSA-related hypertension. Using integrated bioinformatics analysis and experimental validation, we found that PDE4B expression was significantly elevated in both cell and animal models of OSA combined with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Vitro Inhibitory Effect of Isorhapontigenin on Cytochrome P450 Enzymes (CYP3A4, 2C9, and 2D6) and Its Characteristics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Isorhapontigenin is a polyphenol that is predominantly found in Gnetum cleistostachyum. It has been demonstrated to possess pharmacological effects, including anticancer and anti-inflammatory properties. The objective was to examine the impact of isorhapontigenin on cytochrome P450 (CYP450) enzymes, thereby establishing a theoretical foundation for drug-drug interactions and clinical prescriptions. The impact of isorhapontigenin (0, 2.5, 5, 10, 25, 50, and 100 µM) on CYP450 enzyme activity was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discontinuation of the ACURATE transcatheter heart valve platform: loss or reckoning?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes and durability of balloon-expandable TAVI in small and large annuli]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Annular size differences were not found to influence long-term outcomes or valve durability following TAVI with a BE-THV, suggesting that other factors warrant further investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence, predictors, and clinical impact of hypoattenuating leaflet thickening following SAPIEN 3 Ultra RESILIA implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The incidence of HALT for the S3UR was comparable with the already reported incidences for the previous-generation SAPIEN 3 THV. Given the haemodynamic impact of HALT severity and multiplicity, strategic planning to avoid deformation of the implanted THV might be required. (Clinical trial registration: UMIN000020423).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deciphering the Novel Photoreactivity of β-Enaminones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mechanism of a newly discovered photochemical reaction of β-enaminones is examined by femtosecond transient absorption spectroscopy and multistate multiconfigurational quantum chemical calculations. Our study reveals that this photochemical reaction features a previously undocumented excited-state-proton-transfer (ESIPT) process. We show that this process is structurally and dynamically gated, occurring in ultrafast time domain with complex progression of β-enaminone along three potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic ultrasound examination for postoperative intermittent irritation of the infrapatellar branch of the saphenous nerve]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Printable Potentiometric Ion-Selective Electrodes Based on Carbon Fiber and Ti<sub>3</sub>C<sub>2</sub>T<sub>x</sub> MXene Nanoflakes: Eliminating Complex Modifications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Portable electrochemical sensors are essential for real-time ion detection in environmental and clinical analysis, with ion-selective electrodes (ISEs) serving as a key platform due to their reliance on polymer membranes (ISMs) and conductive materials for selective recognition. This study compares traditional carbon fiber ISEs (CF-ISEs) with MXene-based alternatives. CF-ISEs use Ag/AgCl with polyelectrolyte transducers (PSS/PEI), while MXene-modified CF-ISEs (MXCF-ISEs) replace polyelectrolytes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Difference in the Motor Unit Firing Behavior During Submaximal Isometric Ramp Contraction Between Healthy Children Aged 6-12 Years and Young Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION/AIMS: Although nervous system maturation is a key factor underlying the difference in muscle strength between children and adults, specific neural strategies for modulating motor unit (MU) firing during graded force production remain largely unexplored. This study aimed to clarify the differences in MU firing behavior between children and young adults during submaximal isometric ramp contractions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Efficacy Change among Diverse Family Caregivers in Dementia Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: To determine whether changes in caregiver self-efficacy (beliefs about one's ability to manage dementia-related problems and access help) differed by caregiver race and ethnicity across all participants enrolled in a large pragmatic trial of comprehensive dementia care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced CO Oxidation on PtO<sub>x</sub> Raft Species Synthesized via Citric Acid-Assisted Electrostatic Adsorption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platinum-based catalysts have attracted considerable attention for CO oxidation, with their activity critically dependent on the nanostructures of Pt species. Herein, raft-structured PtO(x) species on CeO(2) support (Pt/CeO(2)-CA) were successfully prepared via a citric acid-assisted strong electrostatic adsorption (SEA) method, which leveraged competitive adsorption between noble metal precursors and organic compounds. The Pt/CeO(2)-CA catalyst exhibits a T(50) (temperature for 50% CO...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydraulic In Vitro Characterization of MR-Conditional Blood Pumps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: All three pumps meet basic MR-conditionality and flow requirements, supporting their potential for use in MRI-guided studies during neonatal cardiac surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Phenotypic and Genotypic Features of ADAMTSL4-Related Ocular Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pathogenic variants in ADAMTSL4 are an important cause of isolated ectopia lentis with an increasing number of genetically confirmed cases internationally. We sought to better describe ocular features seen with pathogenic variants in ADAMTSL4. We performed a retrospective, multicenter study examining the phenotypic and genotypic spectrum of ADAMTSL4-associated ocular disease. We identified 41 individuals from 32 families with genetically confirmed ADAMTSL4-related disease across six tertiary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioinspired Janus Spider-Web Nanofibrous Membranes Integrating Triboelectric Energy Harvesting, Adaptive Thermo-Moisture Regulation, and Bactericidal Activity for Multifunctional Wearables]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of multifunctional membranes integrating asymmetric wettability, breathable waterproofing, antibacterial activity, and energy-harvesting capabilities is critical for smart textiles and medical protective equipment, yet balancing robustness, environmental adaptability, and energy conversion efficiency remains challenging. Here, we engineer a bioinspired Janus nanofibrous membrane with a spider-web-like hierarchical architecture via synchronous electrospinning-electrospraying of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomics of Prostate Cancer Tissue Small Extracellular Vesicles Reveal Alteration of Metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prostate cancer (PCa) is a leading male malignancy worldwide, with metabolic reprogramming being a critical hallmark of its progression. Extracellular vesicles (EVs) derived from tissues directly reflect the tumor microenvironment, offering unique insights into cancer pathophysiology that are unattainable through cell line or biofluid-derived EVs. However, the functional roles of tissue-derived EVs in PCa metabolism remain poorly understood. Leveraging our expertise in murine PCa model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In-Situ Observation of Atom Motion and Manipulation of Structural Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precisely controlling structural transformations is essential for realizing novel functionalities in crystal materials, as these transformations often result in significant changes in physical and chemical properties. However, such structural control at the atomic scale remains a formidable challenge. Here the direct observation and realization of atomic scale structural transformation is demonstrated from KTaO(3) to K(6)Ta(10.8)O(30) via high-energy electron beam manufacturing in scanning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Renal anatomy review activity using 3D digital models and clinical cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decreased contact hours have led to investigation of new visualization methods for anatomy education. As a result, novel methods of three-dimensional modeling continue to proliferate. Photogrammetry has been utilized recently to construct 3D digital models from human body donors. The purpose of this study was to explore the benefits of photogrammetry and its potential in improving student performance in a first-year preclinical medical renal and genitourinary systems course. All 166 students...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Conventional Cooling: Advanced Micro/Nanostructures for Managing Extreme Heat Flux]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The surge in device integration has escalated thermal losses, compromising performance and safety, necessitating advanced thermal management solutions with extraordinary heat flux capabilities to address power and heat dissipation challenges in high heat-flux electronics. Micro/nanostructures have emerged as promising solutions for targeted heat dissipation in electronics due to their outstanding performance, miniature footprint, and design flexibility. However, a comprehensive review of recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validity of Weighed and Digital Photography Diet Estimation Study in a Childcare Setting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Weighed and digital photography plate waste methods yield similar results, and both are valid methods to assess food intake in pre-school aged children to aid in intervention studies along with evaluating menu quality. Choice of assessment methods depends on budget, time, equipment, expertise, and training.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxygen Vacancy-Driven Asymmetrical Charge Distribution on Bi-O-Sn Sites in Sn-Doped Bi<sub>2</sub>MoO<sub>6</sub> for Efficient Photocatalytic CO<sub>2</sub>-to-CH<sub>4</sub> Conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient proton-coupled electron transfer (PCET) at tailored active sites is beneficial for photocatalytic CO(2) reduction, yet the relationship between catalytic sites and performance remains unclear. Herein, p-block Sn is introduced into the Bi(2)MoO(6) lattice (Sn-BMO) via Bi site substitution to construct a novel oxygen vacancy (Ov)-Bi-O-Sn structure, where high-valence Sn induces Ov formation by lowering the Bi valence state, thereby creating a charge-asymmetrical region. This unique...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First-Order Phase Transformation in Highly Concentrated Electrolyte for High-Rate and Long-Cycle Aqueous Zn-Ion Battery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Concentrated electrolyte offers a promising approach to enhance aqueous batteries, yet its influence on electrode phase transformations and mechanical properties remains largely unknown. This work shows that salt-concentrated electrolyte induces a first-order phase transformation, rather than the conventional conversion reaction of VS(4) cathode typically observed in dilute electrolyte. This transformation results in a semi-coherent phase boundary, reducing strain and improving energy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling Size Dependent Bi- and Tri-Exciton Characteristics in CdSe/CdS Core/Shell Quantum Dots via Ensemble Time Gated Heralded Spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiexcitons in quantum dots (QDs) manifest many-body interactions under quantum confinement and are significant in numerous optoelectronic and quantum applications. Yet, the strong interactions between multiexcitons leading to rapid non-radiative Auger decay introduce challenges for their characterization. While so far, the measurement techniques rely either on indirect methods or on single particle studies, herein a new method is introduced to study multiexcitons in QD ensembles utilizing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are i-Motif Structures in DNA Compatible with Cytosine-Ag(I)-Cytosine Base Pairs?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To evaluate whether the protons of hemi-protonated C:CH^(+) base pairs in DNA i-motif structures can be replaced by silver ions, an i-motif/duplex junction (IDJ) known to be stable at pH 7 was investigated. Interestingly, only the most accessible out of five C:CH^(+) pairs in the structure can be converted into a C-Ag^(I)-C base pair, as was derived by ¹H NMR spectroscopy, luminescence spectroscopy, temperature-dependent UV spectroscopy, and isothermal titration calorimetry (ITC). When more than...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Fall-Related Fracture Risk by Possible Fall-Risk Increasing Drugs in Japanese Older Adults Using Municipal Linked Medical and Long-Term Care Claim Data: A Nested Case-Control and Case-Crossover Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Long- and short-term use of specific medications is associated with increased fracture risk in older adults. Therefore, attention should be paid to prescription of these drugs in older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Underlying conditions associated with adverse COVID-19 treatment outcomes in selected Kenyan hospitals, October 2020 to December 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with underlying conditions hospitalized for COVID-19 were more likely to die than those without. Hypertension was independently associated with disease severity, while heart disease and diabetes were independently associated with death during COVID-19 treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nature-Inspired Innovation in Electrical Engineering Technologies and Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving field of science and technology, biomimetic design has emerged as a transformative force in electrical engineering. Leveraging insights from natural evolution, biomimetic methodologies significantly enhance equipment performance and overall system efficiency. This review explores several key functional mechanisms, such as multimodal sensing, energy conversion, and adaptive drive, and showcases state-of-the-art applications. These include biomimetic sensors and detection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling Hydrogen Coverage on Ru Nanoparticles Through Modeling and Experiments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding metal-hydrogen interactions is essential in catalysis research. Hydrogen activation on metal catalysts is crucial in industrially catalytic processes, and measurements of hydrogen uptake are widely used to estimate the dispersion of supported metal catalysts. Here, advanced computational strategies, including density functional theory (DFT), ab initio phase diagrams, ab initio molecular dynamics (AIMD), and deep potential molecular dynamics (DPMD) simulations, are combined with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding Potassium Ion Desolvation States for Enhanced Electric Double-Layer Capacitance in Actual Porous Carbon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Porous carbon (PC) electrodes store energy mainly via electric double-layer formation, governed by ion adsorption on pore surfaces and strongly influenced by ion desolvation states in PC, potassium ions can exist in five distinct desolvation states, denoted as [K(H(2)O)(0-4)]^(+). However, the mechanisms and thermodynamics and kinetics of individual desolvation states remain poorly understood. In this study, a methodology is developed to resolve and characterize the distinct desolvation states...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conformation-Driven Circularly Polarized Luminescence Sign Inversion in Chiral Bispyrene Based Cocrystals with Optical Waveguide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circularly polarized luminescence (CPL) materials hold great promise for advanced photonic applications, yet achieving dynamic control over both the luminescent dissymmetry factor (g(lum)) and wavelength remains a substantial challenge. Conventional approaches to CPL inversion often require the intricate synthesis of enantiomers or depend on specific crystal orientation effects. Herein, we propose a supramolecular cocrystal engineering approach to achieve conformation-driven CPL inversion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chiral Nanoagonist Targeting EGFR for Nerve Injury Repair]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nerve injury repair is limited by the incapacity to regenerate neurons in the nervous system. Epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR) plays an important role in the development of the nervous system, but its potential in nerve regeneration and repair has remained underappreciated. Herein, a chiral nanoagonist, D-Histidine ZnO nanorods (NRs), is reported to effectively activate EGFR and initiate multiple downstream cascade signaling pathways, promoting nerve cell proliferation, differentiation,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Click-Cyclized Cell Penetrating Peptides Containing Hydrophobic Proline Derivatives for Efficient Intracellular Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Targeting intracellular organelles with macromolecules is challenging due to cell membrane impermeability. Innovative approaches to direct intracellular delivery have been developed, including nanoparticles, as a promising method for protein delivery; however, with limited efficiency. Cell-penetrating peptides (CPPs) provide a versatile alternative for intracellular cargo delivery. We suggest substituting hydroxy- or amino prolines in β-turns in cyclic CPPs with hydrophobic residues to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trace Oxygen-Assisted Synthesis of High-Quality Graphene with Improved Electrical Performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Point defects and amorphous carbon contamination, which are almost inevitable during the high-temperature chemical vapor deposition growth process, are demonstrated to severely degrade the intrinsic properties of graphene films, particularly their electronic performance. This study puts forward a trace oxygen-assisted strategy for synthesizing high-quality graphene by effectively eradicating amorphous carbon contamination and then promoting the repair of underlying lattice defects. Both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[4.5-V-Class Safe Lithium-Ion Batteries with Silicon-Majority-Graphite Anodes Enabled by Self-Limiting Interphase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[4.5 V-class lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) pairing LiNi(0.8)Mn(0.1)Co(0.1)O(2) (NMC811) cathodes with silicon-majority graphite (SmG, >1500 mAh g^(-1)) anodes can surpass 400 Wh kg^(-1), but their cycling stability, safety, and low-temperature operation are constrained by the difficulty in constructing stable interphase. This study reports a hybrid-sulfonamide electrolyte (HSE) that can survive the aggressive chemistry of high-voltage NMC811 and programs a self-limiting inorganic interphase on Si...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light-Up Nanostructures with Allosterically Controlled Fluorogenic DNA Aptamers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a systematic approach is presented for the rational design of synthetic allosteric DNA aptamers. This methodology enables precise control over the allosteric ON-OFF transition in fluorescent DNA aptamers, allowing for the engineering of aptamers with highly tunable fluorescent properties. When combined with toehold-mediated strand displacement, a series of allosteric aptamers is developed in which the target sequence functions as a specific allosteric modulator. Furthermore, these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Catheters for Diagnosis, Monitoring, and Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review explores smart catheters as an emerging class of medical devices that combine embedded sensors, robotics, and communication systems with increasing functionality and complexity to enable real-time health monitoring, diagnostics, and treatment. Evolving from traditional catheters used as drains or entry ports, smart systems are now able to track blood pressure, temperature, biochemical signals, and mechanical forces within the body with a high degree of accuracy. Advances in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monosaccharide-Derived Enantioselectivity in SWCNT Chemoresistive VOC Sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Semiconducting single-walled carbon nanotubes (sc-SWCNTs) are of great potential for vapor sensing. However, sc-SWCNTs lack recognition features for discriminating between sparsely functionalized moieties, molecules with similar structural features, and enantiomer pairs. This becomes a major setback in discriminating between volatile organic compounds (VOCs). Here, we used two galactosides decorated with aromatic groups as a recognition layer in chemoresistive sc-SWCNT sensors to produce chiral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk-Stratified Phase II Clinical Trial for Epstein-Barr Virus-Associated Hemophagocytic Lymphohistiocytosis in Pediatric, Adolescent, and Young Adult Patients in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Risk-stratified treatment for EBV-HLH guided by DEX response and plasma EBV-DNA levels after 2 weeks of treatment was safe and effective.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Porcine Cell Line Stably Expressing Ephrin-B2 for Nipah Virus Research and Diagnostic Testing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nipah virus (NiV) is a highly pathogenic zoonotic virus transmitted from bats to humans through pigs as a crucial intermediate host. NiV outbreaks pose significant public health and economic threats, especially for pig farmers. Although the World Organization for Animal Health recommends African green monkey-derived Vero cells for NiV isolation, pig-derived cell lines could represent an optimal platform for propagating pig-origin NiV, as signs and symptoms of NiV infection differ among different...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optically Driven Eutectogel Pyroelectric for Efficient Deformable Photodetectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionic gels are emerging stimuli-response elastomers for biomimetic sensors in diverse fields. Photoresponse ionic gels can detect light as a photoreceptor to emulate biological vision for artificial retina and skin. However, the existing ionic gel-based photosensors face limited response speeds and detecting sensitivity due to inefficient ion transport. Here, a high-performance elastomeric photodetector made of polyvinyl alcohol-based pyroelectric eutectogels, containing polar ions and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MOFs-Derived Oxygen-Vacancy-Rich Cu-Cu<sub>x</sub>O/TiO<sub>2</sub> with Dynamic Redox Cycling for Steering Hole-Driven PMS Activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The efficiency of peroxymonosulfate (PMS) activation in photocatalytic processes critically depends on the regulation of electron transfer from generation to utilization. Herein, a holistic electron transfer pathway is constructed within a metal-organic frameworks (MOFs)-derived Cu-Cu(x)O/TiO(2) composite to achieve superior PMS activation. The incorporated Cu species serve as dynamic redox mediators, enabling an efficient non-photoinduced electron transfer pathway via Cu⁰&Cu^(n+) cycling....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultralong Room-Temperature Phosphorescence Achieved by Microcapsule Rupture-Triggered In-Situ Polymerization for High-Contrast Damage Visualization and Advanced Anti-counterfeiting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymer materials with mechano-responsive ultralong room-temperature phosphorescence (RTP) are highly desired but challenging to achieve. Herein, a microcapsule (MC) rupture-triggered in-situ polymerization strategy is proposed to achieve such RTP with full-color tunable emissions. It involves co-encapsulating organic phosphors and moisture-reactive hexamethylene diisocyanate (HDI) in MCs, which are dispersed into a polymer matrix. Mechanical damage ruptures MCs, releasing HDI that undergoes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomimetic Spring Effect Construction to Stabilize Electrode/Electrolyte Interface for High-Performance Lithium Metal Anodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lithium (Li) metal anode is the most promising anode for the next-generation high-energy storage batteries due to its high theoretical specific capacity and low redox potential, while its commercial application is plagued by notorious dendrite formation and instable electrode/electrolyte interface degradation. Inspired by the spring effect of cholesterol (Ch) in phospholipid bilayers to maintain cytomembrane structure, a self-assembled biomimetic spring (SABS) layer is constructed as an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cu-Catalyzed Aerobic Oxidative C─C Cleavage in Lignin-Derived Oligomers and Biological Funneling of the Monomeric Products]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Existing methods for lignin deconstruction to aromatic monomers primarily cleave carbon-oxygen bonds within the polymer, resulting in sub-optimal monomer yields and formation of oligomers that retain intact carbon-carbon bonds. Here, we demonstrate that copper-catalyzed aerobic oxidation under aqueous alkaline conditions promotes oxidative cleavage of carbon-carbon bonds in lignin oligomers derived from reductive catalytic fractionation (RCF) of pine and poplar biomass. Fundamental insights are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[All-in-One Molecule Regulated Buried Interface and Crystallization of Tin-Lead Perovskite for Efficient All-Perovskite Tandem Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mixed tin-lead (Sn-Pb) perovskite solar cells (PSCs) are critical for advancing all-perovskite tandem solar technologies, as they resolve the efficiency limitations of single-junction devices. However, the widely used hole transport layer (HTL) poly(3,4-ethylenedioxythiophene):poly(styrenesulfonate) (PEDOT:PSS) restricts performance and durability due to its acidic nature and moisture absorption. Additionally, the rapid crystallization of Sn-containing perovskites hinders the fabrication of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bond-Discretization in Nickel Oxide to Boost Capacity for Rechargeable Nickel─Zinc Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aqueous Ni─Zn batteries are highly attractive for grid-scale energy storage due to their safety, low cost, and environmental friendliness. However, their energy density is limited by the underutilization of nickel-based cathode materials. Here, a bond-discretization strategy in NiO is developed to overcome this challenge. By designing a low-symmetry crystallographic structure with a reduced Ni-Ni coordination number of 9, the NiO cathode achieves a near-theoretical capacity for the one-electron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging the Fragment Merging Approach for Synthetizing Novel Selanyl Phenyl Acetamide Thiazolidinedione Hybrids Endowed With Apoptotic Potential for Cancer Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Designing novel selenium-containing compounds (organoselenium compounds, OSe) has shown growing interest owing to their chemoprotective and antioxidant properties. Consequently, by harnessing a fragment merging approach, a series of novel OSe hybrid compounds bearing selanyl phenyl acetamide and thiazolidinedione scaffolds were designed and synthesized (8-10, 11a-c, 12a-c, 13a-c, and 14). The growth inhibition percentages (GI%) of the newly afforded OSe were evaluated using seven human cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial Transcriptomic Characteristics of the Aging Human Ovary]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ovarian aging is a complex process that compromises fertility and elevates the risk of reproductive disorders. To elucidate its spatiotemporal dynamics, we integrated single-nucleus RNA sequencing and spatial transcriptomics to construct a comprehensive aging atlas of 12 human ovarian tissues spanning ages 12-54 (prepubertal, age 12, n = 1; young, ages 23-29, n = 4; middle-aged, ages 32-34, n = 2; and older-aged, ages 42-54, n = 5). Our analysis revealed aging-related transcriptomic shifts,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Field Work Experience in the Delayed Period of Earthquake Response in Syria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: During disasters, the needs of the population for various types of medical care vary significantly. The main causes of variability, in our opinion, are the time period of work from the disaster onset; the situation in the country and in the healthcare system, preceding the disaster; the climatic conditions during work; and the local endemicity of diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Neoadjuvant Chemotherapy on Early Postoperative Anxiety and Depression in Patients With Gastric Cancer: An Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: NACT is independently associated with increased anxiety and depression in the early postoperative period, especially if chemotherapy cycles are prolonged.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brown Adipose Tissue and Metabolic Markers Differ Between Greenlanders and Danes with Cold-Activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The larger increase in BAT activity in response to cooling and the dampened response in metabolic parameters in Greenlanders compared to Danes, leads to a hypothesis of preparedness for rapid thermogenic response to cold exposure in populations with active BAT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synovial Fluid-derived Micrococcus Luteus G18 Exacerbates Osteoarthritis Progression by Promoting Chondrocyte Degradation via TLR2/JNK/AP-1 Signaling Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditionally considered a sterile environment, the articular cavity has this perception overturned with advances in multi-omics technologies-microbial communities are increasingly identified in once-thought sterile tissues, making the articular cavity a potential microbial niche. However, the presence and role of intra-articular microbes in osteoarthritis (OA) remain rarely studied. Synovial fluid microbiomes of OA patients at different stages are analyzed via 16S rRNA high-throughput...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of pulmonary physical exam skills by internal medicine interns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Medicine interns had variable skills in performing the pulmonary PE. Improving PE skills would lead to increased identification of relevant pulmonary findings, inform clinical decision making, and improve overall patient care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of planar chiral ferrocene diketone derivatives <em>via</em> a cascade Pd-catalyzed asymmetric C-H arylation/α-arylation reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Planar chiral ferrocenes are extensively used in catalytic asymmetric transformations in both academic research and industry. Here, we present a Pd-catalyzed cascade approach involving asymmetric C-H arylation and α-arylation to synthesize planar chiral ferrocene diketone derivatives with high efficiency (88% yield) and enantioselectivity (99% ee). Mechanistic studies, including kinetic analysis and in situ^(31)P NMR analysis, clarify the sequence of the cascade reactions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational roadmap of stable Mo-S nanoclusters: atomic structures and magic compositions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanoparticles exhibit unique properties that are harnessed in various technological fields, yet their atomic structure remains complex and challenging to determine experimentally, especially for nanoclusters. This study explores the stability and crystal structures of molybdenum-sulfur (Mo-S) nanoclusters using the evolutionary algorithm USPEX and density functional theory (DFT) calculations. We used a selection method based on "magic" clusters, whose stability is evaluated through second-order...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial Photopatterning of Substrate Stiffness in Dual-Cure Silicones for Cardiac Mechano-Regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mechanical properties of the extracellular matrix play a key role in regulating cellular functions, yet many in vitro models lack the mechanical complexity of native tissues. Traditional hydrogel-based substrates offer tunable stiffness but are often limited by instability, porosity, and coupled changes in both mechanical and structural properties, making it difficult to isolate the effects of stiffness alone. Here, we introduce a spatially patterned dual-cure polydimethylsiloxane (DC-PDMS)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Morinda citrifolia</em> L. (noni) and its potential in the management of systemic metabolic disorder (SMD)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Morinda citrifolia L. (noni) is a tropical plant containing over 200 phytochemicals, including terpenoids, anthraquinones, coumarins, flavonoids, lignans, and polysaccharides, with demonstrated biological activities such as antioxidant, anti-inflammatory, hypoglycaemic, hepatoprotective, and cardioprotective effects. Studies indicate that noni and its bioactive components, such as scopoletin, quercetin, rutin, ursolic acid, and polysaccharides, exert beneficial effects on systemic metabolic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiology of nummular eczema - methodological approaches and outcomes from nationwide claims data analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite differences in methodological approaches leading to some variation, the prevalence of NE in the German population can be reasonably estimated at approximately 0.26%. Overlaps and miscoding may have occurred, particularly with other forms of eczema, underscoring the need for reliable diagnostics and standardized coding.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NH<sub>3</sub>-Guided Low-Temperature Nanostructural Refinement Boosts Visible-Light-Driven H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub> Synthesis in Ionic Carbon Nitrides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solar-driven oxygen reduction on ionic carbon nitride frameworks presents a compelling strategy for sustainable hydrogen peroxide (H(2)O(2)) production. Herein, a nanostructural engineering strategy is presented to tailor the morphology and defect chemistry of potassium poly(heptazine imide) (KPHI), enabling extended solar coverage and enhance photocatalytic performance. By incorporating NH(4)Cl into a molten KCl/LiCl eutectic medium, simultaneous nanoscale fragmentation of KPHI crystals and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2'-Fucosyllactose supplementation results in a transient improvement in gut microbial resilience after vancomycin use in adults with overweight or obesity: a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibiotic-induced perturbations of the gut microbiome can be long-lasting and potentially affect host metabolic health. Strategies supporting microbial resilience are needed to mitigate the negative impact of antibiotics. We investigated the potential of 2'-fucosyllactose (2'-FL) supplementation after vancomycin use in a double-blind placebo-controlled randomized intervention among adults with overweight/obesity. Participants received oral vancomycin for seven days followed by 2'-FL or placebo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered bacteria for cancer therapy: Advancements, challenges, and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in cancer therapeutics, including targeted therapies and immunotherapies, have significantly improved treatment outcomes but remain limited by challenges such as off-target toxicity, poor penetration into deep tumor tissues, and the emergence of drug resistance. Engineered bacteria-based cancer therapies present a novel and versatile approach to address these limitations. Leveraging their ability to selectively colonize tumor microenvironments, bacteria can elicit antitumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-national risk factors for childbirth-related PTSD: Findings from the INTERSECT study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings support a stress-diathesis framework, showing that while pre-existing vulnerabilities contribute, birth-related stressors exert the strongest influence. Trauma-informed maternity care should prioritize these factors, with attention to women's appraisals of birth.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping Core Memory Networks in Cognitively Impaired Adults Aged 75 and Older: Insights From a WMS-R-Based Symptom Network Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Visual memory and delayed recall emerged as pivotal components in the cognitive network of older adults with impairment, suggesting that interventions focusing on these domains may enhance overall cognitive function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Burden of Breast Cancer and Its Attributable Risk Factors in the Belt and Road Initiative Countries, 1990-2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although mortality has fallen, BC incidence continues to rise in BRI countries, especially in low- and middle-SDI regions. Expanded screening, improved healthcare infrastructure, and targeted interventions on modifiable risks are urgently required.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differences in peak oxygen uptake in heart failure patients with and without cachexia: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic heart failure (CHF) is characterized by reduced peak oxygen consumption (VO(2peak)). Cachexia may exacerbate the decline in VO(2peak) from reductions in muscle mass and strength. We sought to assess differences in VO(2peak) between patients with CHF and cachexia and those without. A systematic literature search of cohort studies via databases (PubMed, Web of Science, Scopus, and Cochrane Library) was conducted from inception until April 2025. A meta-analysis using a random-effects model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment of isolated injuries of the posterior cruciate ligament (PCL)-A 2025 Delphi-based structured expert statement by the ligament injury committee of the German Knee Society (DKG)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: By providing structured treatment protocols, this Delphi-based structured expert statement can support clinicians in day-to-day decision-making and ultimately improve patient care and outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Functional Connectome Mediates Associations Between Fitness and Cognition Across the Adult Lifespan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardiorespiratory fitness (CRF) is increasingly recognized as essential for improving neural and cognitive function, especially in older age. Here, we examined a cross-sectional sample of the Human Connectome Project (HCP) Aging dataset (ages 36-100; N = 378) to test the hypothesis that functional connectivity profiles that are related to CRF are also associated with episodic memory and executive function across middle age and older adults. To test these hypotheses, we first used...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of intrathecal therapy in the treatment of familial haemophagocytic lymphohistiocytosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cutaneous Vegetating Candidiasis in Keratitis-Ichthyosis-Deafness Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D Body Scanning-Derived Normative Values of Appendicular Circumferences: A Novel Tool for Sarcopenia Screening in Chinese Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study establishes the first age- and sex-stratified percentile references for ACs in Chinese adults. These results reveal significant sex disparities in absolute and BMI-adjusted measures, providing essential tools for sarcopenia screening, lifestyle intervention evaluation and high-risk population identification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfering Transposable Elements: ISXoo15 Transposase as a First-in-Class Antibacterial Target Against Xanthomonas oryzae pv. oryzae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current challenges in controlling phytopathogenic bacteria lie in widespread chemical resistance, biosafety concerns, and the scarcity of novel biomacromolecule targets. While transposable elements have emerged as critical drivers of genetic variability and virulence in plant pathogens, their potential as druggable targets remains unexplored. Here, we report the first discovery of ISXoo15 transposase in Xanthomonas oryzae pv. oryzae (Xoo) as the bactericidal receptor for J9, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward Personalized Neuroscience: Evaluating Individual-Level Information in Neural Mass Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macroscale brain modeling using neural mass models (NMMs) offers a framework for simulating human whole-brain dynamics. These models are pivotal for investigating the brain as a complex dynamic system, exploring phenomena like bifurcations, oscillatory patterns, and responses to stimuli. While connectome-based NMMs allow for the creation of personalized NMMs, their utility in capturing individual-specific neural characteristics remains underexplored, with current studies constrained by small...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shaping Ultrafast Pulses for Enhanced Resonant Nonlinear Interactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coherent control with shaped ultrafast pulses is a powerful approach for steering nonlinear light-matter interactions. Prior quantum control studies show that, beyond transform-limited pulses, antisymmetric spectral phases can efficiently drive nonresonant multiphoton transitions. However, resonant multiphoton transitions experience dispersion from the material's spectral-phase response, which lowers nonlinear efficiency. Preshaping the pulse to compensate for this response can restore and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Histamine mediates food intake, but not muscle adaptations, following 10 weeks of resistance training in humans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Histamine receptor antagonists, commonly used for allergies, block histamine signalling and can impair adaptations to high-intensity and endurance exercise. Because it remains unclear whether this is a universal mechanism of muscle adaptation, this study investigated histamine receptor blockade effects on resistance training adaptations. Acute study: Eight men performed three resistance training sessions with intake of either placebo, H(1)-receptor antihistamine (180 mg fexofenadine) or combined...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrostatically Enhanced Self-Assembled Monolayers Anchoring for Scalable and Stable Inverted Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Self-assembled monolayers (SAMs) have substantially advanced the efficiency of inverted perovskite solar cells (PSCs), yet weak interfacial adhesion to transparent conductive oxide (TCO) substrates and perovskite compromises both scalability and thermal stability. Here, an electrostatically enhanced anchoring strategy (EEAS) is presented using sulfadiazine (SDZ) molecules to deprotonate phosphonic acid groups in SAMs, generating phosphate anions that strengthen electrostatic interactions with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variation in trabecular bone microarchitecture across rhesus macaque (Macaca mulatta) load-bearing joints]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Globally, human population structure is quickly trending older, increasing the prevalence and systemic burden of age-related skeletal disorders such as osteoporosis. Osteoporosis is characterized by the loss of bone mass, including trabecular bone tissue, leading to skeletal fracture. Although clinically important, fundamental questions remain about normal trabecular bone variation and age-related bone loss. In this study, we use free-ranging rhesus macaques (Macaca mulatta) from the Cayo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A 3D Atlas of Visceral and Somatic Pelvic Motor Neurons in Whole Mounts of Female and Male Rat Spinal Cords]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The sexually dimorphic genitourinary organs and specialized striated muscles in the pelvis are controlled by a spinal cord motor neuron (MN) subsystem that produces reflexogenic and psychogenic (conscious) visceral and somatic motor activity during urinary continence and voiding, scent marking (in some species), defecation, reproduction, and sexual activity. To produce a three-dimensional (3D) atlas of the pelvic MN system, we performed whole-mount immunostaining and advanced 3D microscopy on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A posterior hypothalamic to midbrain circuit orchestrating nociceptive behaviours in male mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND IMPLICATIONS: Our results define a functional PH^(Glu) → VTA^(DA) → NAc circuit that contributes to chronic pain processing. Hyperactivity in this pathway facilitates nociceptive behaviours, while its inhibition exerts analgesic effects. Modulating this circuit may offer new therapeutic strategies for treating chronic pain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The triad of maternal gut-breast milk-infant gut microbial transmission in early life as a critical pathway for microbial inheritance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although maternal microbial inheritance is recognized, the temporal dynamics of how the maternal gut microbiota shapes the infant gut microbiota via specific routes remain unexplored. We performed longitudinal, multi-site microbiota sampling in 30 mother-infant pairs (including 14 exclusive breastfeeding and 16 mixed breastfeeding) from birth to one month, stratified by lactation stages. To trace the origin of breast milk microbiota, we also analyzed colostrum and gut samples from 8 postpartum...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting the Hyperglycemic Pre-Metastatic Niche to Prevent Breast Cancer Bone Metastasis: Mechanisms and Therapeutic Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The recent pioneering study by Ye et al. (Adv Sci. 2025;12(37):e0504924) provides compelling evidence that systemic hyperglycemia orchestrates a pre-metastatic niche (PMN) in bone, promoting breast cancer metastasis and identifying Receptor for Advanced Glycation End-products (RAGE) inhibition as a viable therapeutic strategy. While this work represents a significant conceptual advance by linking systemic metabolism to organotropic metastasis, the analysis identifies several substantive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plant-derived peptides: from identification to agronomic applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Global agriculture faces critical challenges due to the overreliance on chemical pesticides, driving an urgent need for eco-friendly biopesticides and biostimulants (BioP&S). Plant-derived peptides, evolved as natural regulators of growth, development, and stress adaptation, offer immense potential as biodegradable and biocompatible alternatives. However, their commercialization remains constrained by limited exploration of diversity and activity, high production costs, incomplete ecological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-effectiveness of a corticosteroid injection versus exercise therapy for shoulder pain in general practice (SIX-Shoulder Study): a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: For patients with shoulder pain, the exercise therapy group has a probability of 70% to be cost-effective compared to the injection group over a 12-month follow-up with an ICER of €14 489 (95% CI: -1 698 053 to 1 727 032) at a willingness-to-pay threshold of €50 000 per QALY.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MXene Membrane as Multifunctional Interface for Vapor Splitting via Photothermal-Catalytic Membrane Distillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advancements in solar-driven processes are fundamentally transforming the production of freshwater and energy into a more sustainable manner. Realizing such potential requires developing highly efficient solar responsive materials and advanced solar systems. Here, an MXene-based membrane is reported as a multifunctional interface capable of simultaneously producing freshwater and hydrogen through a strategically designed photothermal-catalytic sweeping gas membrane distillation (PTC-SGMD)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermophilic composting of dewatered sewage sludge under subzero temperatures using a full-scale pre-fermentation reactor: A 10-day valorisation strategy for year-round operation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermophilic composting of sewage sludge under subzero temperatures remains a significant operational barrier to sustainable waste management. In this study, we report a full-scale composting process that treats 180 t of dewatered sewage sludge per day, achieving complete compost maturation within 10 days, even during freezing winter conditions. The system integrates a pre-fermentation reactor equipped with internal heating and aeration, enabling rapid thermophilic activation and maintaining...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoplasmonic real-time RT-RPA and CRISPR/Cas12a detection for rapid point-of-care molecular diagnostics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid and precise detection of nucleic acids is crucial for effective disease diagnosis and management at the point-of-care (POC) level. Here we report a palm-sized plasmonic photothermal platform for real-time on-chip recombinase polymerase amplification (RPA) and CRISPR/Cas12a detection. An ultrathin photothermal nanoplasmonic cavity (PNC) of Au nanoislands (AuNIs) and an aluminum reflector delivers uniform and efficient photothermal heating under white LED illumination. The configuration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Orbital-Based Correlated Electron-Nuclear Dynamics for Extended Systems with Exact Factorization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a practical orbital-based framework for simulating correlated electron-nuclear dynamics in extended systems within the exact factorization (XF) formalism. Building on our earlier derivation of time-dependent Kohn-Sham (TDKS) equations that merge real-time time-dependent density functional theory with XF, we apply the classical path approximation and incorporate pairwise XF-derived decoherence corrections in the Kohn-Sham basis. This leads to a new efficient algorithm...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of fabrication methods and build orientation on Candida albicans adhesion on 3D-printed and conventional denture resin: an in vitro comparative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insomnia as a risk factor for temporomandibular disorders: a nationwide population-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Clinically diagnosed insomnia was found to be associated with an increased risk of developing TMD. However, as this study was based on the NHIS database, causality cannot be definitively established. Nonetheless, these findings suggest that incorporating sleep disturbances assessments into the evaluation and management of TMD may be beneficial. Further prospective studies are warranted to clarify this association and assess the potential benefits of integrated care strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41243088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to "Optimizing FeNO and blood eosinophil stratification in eosinophilic asthma study: Adjusting for smoking history and blood sampling time"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AEG-1 on cancer drug resistance: From molecular insights to therapeutic challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astrocyte elevated gene-1 (AEG-1), also known as metadherin (MTDH), has emerged as a multifunctional oncogene implicated in cancer progression, metastasis, immune evasion, and notably, drug resistance across diverse malignancies. AEG-1 exerts its effects by modulating key signaling cascades, including PI3K/Akt, NF-κB, and Wnt/β-catenin, and by regulating genes associated with epithelial-mesenchymal transition, apoptosis suppression, cancer stemness, and multidrug resistance. Its interactions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CPAP Therapy Alters Monocyte Activation and Immune Phenotype in Obstructive Sleep Apnea in Relation to Hypoxic Burden]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION.: CPAP alleviates systemic inflammation in OSA by reducing hypoxic burden and reprogramming monocytes toward an anti-inflammatory phenotype. The magnitude of immune modulation was more closely linked to ODI than AHI, suggesting that oxygen desaturation burden serves as meaningful adjuncts to AHI in assessing monocyte-driven immune dysregulation in OSA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Printing accuracy and post-mounting dimensional stability of 3D-printed hollow dental models with varying shell thicknesses and cross-arch bars]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Shell thickness and reinforcement significantly affected the trueness and stability of 3D-printed hollow dental models. Thicker shells with a cross-arch bar demonstrated the highest accuracy and stability, supporting their use in prosthodontic applications requiring articulator mounting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Paraprobiotic Levilactobacillus brevis WB2357 attenuates TNF-α/IFN-γ-induced inflammation via NF-κB/p38 MAPK, STAT3 and HO-1 signaling pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atopic dermatitis is a persistent inflammatory skin condition with consistently increasing prevalence. Among the possible intervention options, paraprobiotics, which are widely used in the food industry, have gained substantial attention because of their immune regulatory effects. The objective of this study was to assess the effects of heat-inactivated paraprobiotic Levilactobacillus brevis WB2357 isolated from kimchi in tumor necrosis factor (TNF)-α/interferon (IFN)-γ-stimulated HaCaT cells....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental health emergencies and mortality following public fine particulate matter alerts: A Nationwide case-crossover study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Issuance of PM(2.5) alerts in South Korea was associated with a modest reduction in emergency visits for mental disorders but did not correspond with lower mortality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum to "Report from the World Health Organization's Immunization and Vaccines-related Implementation Research Advisory Committee (IVIR-AC) meeting, virtual gathering, 1-5 September 2025" [Vaccine 68 (2025) 127903]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When the air feels heavy: How visceral stuffiness shifts well-being priorities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[When the air feels heavy and breathing becomes strained, the resulting visceral state may cause our motivational compass to quietly tilt. This study investigates whether the experience of visceral stuffiness can temporarily recalibrate individuals' well-being priorities by increasing the salience of hedonic (pleasure-oriented) over eudaimonic (meaning-oriented) motivation and whether this motivational shift is reflected in subsequent decisions involving a trade-off between hedonic enjoyment and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exogenous application of hydrogen sulfide combined with blue light improves the quality of pepper fruit minimizing oxidative stress during postharvest storage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While the roles of hydrogen sulfide (H(2)S) as a source of supersulfide and blue light (BL) in overall plant growth are established, their precise involvement in fruit ripening is still obscured. We focused on the specific roles of the combination of those (H(2)S + BL) treatments that might delay the ripening of pepper fruit for better postharvest storage. In this experiment, harvested fruits were treated with H(2)S from 1 mM sodium hydrogen sulfide (NaHS) solution following storage under BL...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Annual Averages: Rethinking Metrics For Emergency Department Crowding And Capacity Planning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: HPBO overcomes the limitations of AA by capturing short-term occupancy fluctuations, providing accurate estimates of additional bed needs. This offers healthcare administrators a reliable tool for addressing ED overcrowding and optimizing resource allocation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41242069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carboxylate polystyrene nanoplastics disrupt mitotic progression and induce chromosomal instability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The widespread use of plastics has raised serious concerns regarding environmental pollution and human health. Although exposure to nanoplastics induces significant toxicities, the mechanisms underlying their genotoxicity, particularly chromosomal instability, remain poorly understood. In this study, we used a non-lethal dose of carboxylate polystyrene nanoplastics (cPS-NPs), which have high reactivity with biological molecules due to enhanced surface reactivity. cPS-NPs accumulated near the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design of a dual-responsive system based on ferrocene and porous Fe<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub> microspheres for therapeutic applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper reports the development of an advanced dual-stimuli-responsive drug-delivery system designed to enhance the precision and efficiency of targeted therapies. The system integrates the unique properties of ferrocene and porous iron oxide microspheres (P-Fe(2)O(3)) to respond to reactive oxygen species and external magnetic fields. Ferrocene, with its well-known redox properties, facilitates selective drug release in oxidative environments commonly found in tumor tissues, while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glutinol, main component of <em>orostachys japonica</em>, inhibits <em>in vitro and in vivo</em> TGF-β-induced epithelial mesenchymal transition of human cancer cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glutinol (GT), a major triterpenoid component of Orostachys japonica, suppresses TGF-β-induced epithelial-mesenchymal transition (EMT) in human cancer cells. GT treatment restored epithelial characteristics by upregulating E-cadherin and downregulating Snail, thereby reducing cancer cell migration and invasion in A549 and MCF-7 cells. In vivo, GT significantly inhibited lung metastasis of TGF-β-treated A549-luc cells in mice. These findings demonstrate that GT exerts potent anti-metastatic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An O<sub>2</sub>-Independent Copper(II) Phototherapeutic Agent for Photoactivating H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub> to Enhance Antitumor Immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The characteristics of tumor cells and their microenvironment, including high rates of recurrence and metastasis, insufficient oxygen (O(2)) supply, and the immunosuppressive microenvironment, severely limit the effectiveness of conventional photodynamic therapy for hypoxic tumors. Herein, we report an O(2)-independent nano-photocatalyst (NanoPcCu), rationally designed to provide near-infrared light induced self-adaptive photodynamic processes, enhancing the generation of type I reactive oxygen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41241839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251117142138&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>