<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 07:36:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable Production of Tailor-Designed MXene-Hydrogel Core-Shell Fibers via Dual Stress-Guided Alignment during Thermal Drawing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Large-scale production of two-dimensional MXene-based functional fibers, while preserving their outstanding material properties, remains challenging. Here, we present highly aligned Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXene fibers integrated into tens of meters-long fibers via in situ stress-induced alignments during thermal drawing. In the proposed liquid injection-assisted thermal drawing, MXene flakes in aqueous dispersion are continuously injected into hollow channels of fibers and subsequently aligned by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning enables scalable and systematic hierarchical virus taxonomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although virus ecogenomics has expanded access to and understanding of the virosphere, existing classification tools lack taxonomic resolution and are unable to scale to modern discovery-based datasets or classify previously unknown sequence space. Here we develop vConTACT3-a machine learning-based tool that improves scalability and accuracy of virus taxonomy. By optimizing gene-sharing thresholds and leveraging adaptive, realm-specific cut-offs, vConTACT3 expands classification to both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A quantum chemical dataset of interacting molecular pairs for chemical reaction studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding molecular interactions beyond single-molecule properties is critical for studying real-world chemical systems. Quantum chemical calculations of molecule-molecule interactions are computationally demanding, making large, publicly available datasets scarce. Here, we present an efficient framework for generating initial configurations of molecular interaction systems and construct a molecular interaction dataset, containing 49,620 individual molecules and 247,741 molecular pairs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Dataset of Lipid Nanoparticle Compositions and Properties for Nucleic Acid Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipid nanoparticles (LNPs) have emerged as the leading delivery platform for nucleic acid therapeutics, with clinical success demonstrated in mRNA vaccines and therapeutic applications. However, rational design of LNP remains challenging due to the complex relationships among LNP composition, physicochemical properties, and biological performance, as well as the scattered experimental data across the literature. Here, we present LNP Atlas, a comprehensive dataset containing LNP formulations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring potential of Turing pattern classification through convolution maps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the classification potential of nonlinear Turing patterns by employing convolutional features. Classifying spatial heterogeneity caused by Turing instability, observed in natural phenomena such as animal coat patterns and neural models, remains a challenging problem due to the difficulty in learning the parameters governing such pattern formation. We consider a minimal structure of a convolutional neural network including convolutional layers, activation functions, and pooling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal changes in each retinal layer thickness in diabetic retinopathy patients treated with pan-retinal photocoagulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The thickness of each retinal layer of patients who underwent PRP changed differently over time, and these changes were significantly associated with changes in visual acuity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural configuration of sustainable sports industry based on deep learning and genetic algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To address the structural imbalances and sustainability challenges faced by the sports industry in its high-quality development transformation, and to overcome the shortcomings of existing research in dynamic modeling, multi-objective optimization, and quantitative solutions, this paper constructs an intelligent optimization framework integrating deep learning (DL) and genetic algorithms (GA). This framework uses a one-dimensional convolutional neural network to extract deep features and predict...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum electrodynamics of photonic time crystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photonic time crystals host a variety of intriguing phenomena, from wave amplification and mixing to exotic band structures, all stemming from the time-periodic modulation of optical properties. While these features have been well described classically, their quantum manifestation when coupled to an atomic electric dipole has remained elusive. Here, we introduce a quantum electrodynamical model of photonic time crystals that reveals a deeper connection between classical and quantum pictures: the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Limits on WIMP Dark Matter with NaI(Tl) Crystals in Three Years of COSINE-100 Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report limits on weakly interacting massive particle (WIMP) dark matter derived from three years of data collected by the COSINE-100 experiment with NaI(Tl) crystals, achieving an improved energy threshold of 0.7 keV. This lowered threshold enhances sensitivity in the sub-GeV mass range, extending the reach for direct detection of low-mass dark matter. Although no excess of WIMP-like events was observed, the increased sensitivity enabled a model-insensitive comparison between the expected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[β-Decay Half-Lives of Neutron-Rich Sulfur to Potassium: Evolution of the N=32 and 34 Subshell Closures below Calcium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The half-lives of 24 isotopes ranging from sulfur to potassium were measured using the ZeroDegree Advanced Decay Station at the Radioactive Isotope Beam Factory, including six of the most neutron-rich-^{47}S, ^{48,49}Cl, ^{51,52}Ar, ^{55}K-for the first time, while the precision for ^{48}Ar and ^{53,54}K was significantly improved. Two prominent features are found: First, a half-life drop at ^{54}K_{35} relative to ^{52,53}K, supporting the persistence of the N=34 subshell closure in potassium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growth hormone is required for hippocampal engram cell maturation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memory is stored in specialized cells known as engram cells, but the molecular mechanisms underlying this process remain unclear. We discovered that the initial translation leading to growth hormone (GH) synthesis in engram cells is required for their maturation in the mouse dentate gyrus. Time-course experiments with a translation inhibitor suggested that the key molecule is immediately translated during learning. We identified GH as the crucial factor, specifically translated within the first...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined Outerbridge-Kashiwagi Procedure and Supercharged Anterior Interosseous Nerve Transfer for Elbow Arthritis With Ulnar Neuropathy: Refinements in Surgical Aspects of the Combined Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This combined approach addresses both mechanical impingement and motor deficits, offering a feasible and effective strategy for restoring upper extremity function in this patient population. Preoperative electrophysiologic assessment plays a key role in optimizing candidate selection and outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Maribacter algae</em> sp. nov., <em>Maribacter spongiae</em> sp. nov., <em>Maribacter corallii</em> sp. nov., <em>Maribacter aquimarinus</em> sp. nov. and <em>Maribacter taeanensis</em> sp. nov., isolated from marine habitats in the Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Five novel bacterial strains, designated as 2210JD10-5^(T), 2304DJ31-5^(T), 2307UL18-2^(T), 2307ULW6-5^(T) and 2308TA10-17^(T), were isolated from diverse marine samples in the Republic of Korea, including algae, sponge, coral and seawater. The five novel strains affiliated with the genus Maribacter were taxonomically characterized using a polyphasic approach. The cells were catalase- and oxidase-positive and rod-shaped. The five novel strains were revealed as mesophilic, neutrophilic in pH and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasensitive Detection of Multiple Foodborne Pathogens Using CRISPR-Cas12a on a Finger-Actuated Microfluidic Device Integrated with a Modular Pressurizing Pump]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Foodborne pathogens pose a serious threat to global health and the economy, causing gastrointestinal illnesses and potentially leading to fatalities. Here, we present a recombinase polymerase amplification (RPA)-CRISPR-Cas12a-based method for the detection of foodborne pathogens using target-specific CRISPR RNAs (crRNAs) on a reusable, reconfigurable finger-actuated microfluidic device. Unlike previous finger-actuated pushbutton-based microfluidic devices, the device incorporates a modular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coffee Consumption and Colorectal Cancer Survival: A Dose-Response Meta-Analysis by Coffee Type and Disease Stage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Coffee consumption is associated with improved survival and reduced recurrence in CRC patients in a dose-dependent and stage-specific manner.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamical dark energy in light of the DESI DR2 baryonic acoustic oscillations measurements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding whether cosmic acceleration arises from a cosmological constant or a dynamical component is a central goal of cosmology, and the Dark Energy Spectroscopic Instrument (DESI) enables stringent tests with high-precision distance measurements. Here we analyse measurements of baryon acoustic oscillations in DESI Data Release 1 and Data Release 2 and consider type Ia supernovae and a distance prior for the cosmic microwave background. With the larger statistical power and wider redshift...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Report: Temporary supratrochanteric plating for the management of subtrochanteric femoral fracture in an immature dog]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This case report describes the successful management of a subtrochanteric femoral fracture in a 2-month-old dog using temporary supratrochanteric plate fixation, performed prior to the development of the greater trochanter apophysis. A tibial plateau leveling osteotomy plate was applied to the proximolateral femur and subsequently removed following radiographic evidence of bridging callus formation. At the 21-month follow-up, the dog exhibited normal limb function, symmetrical femoral length,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world treatment outcome and toxicity analysis of inotuzumab ozogamicin in adult patients with relapsed or refractory B-cell precursor acute lymphoblastic leukemia: multicenter prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: INO represents a potent salvage option for R/R BCP-ALL. However, substantial toxicities highlight the critical need for careful patient selection and dose optimization strategies to maximize its therapeutic benefit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeepKinome: quantitative prediction of kinase binding affinity by a compound using deep learning based regression model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DeepKinome offers a promising approach for understanding kinase inhibition and compound binding.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a dual-purpose 60K SNP chip for simultaneous genotyping of chicken and duck]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We successfully developed and validated the first poultry SNP chip incorporating chicken-duck pooled samples. This chip provides reliable genotyping performance for both species and offers a cost-effective solution for large-scale SNP chip development in the livestock industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancements in the molecular understanding of major depressive disorder uncovering novel targets with therapeutic promise: focus on recurrence of illness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Major depressive disorder (MDD) is a neuro-immune-metabolic-oxidative stress (NIMETOX) disorder. A significant proportion (50%) of individuals with MDD experience recurrence of episodes and suicidal behaviors. Recurrent MDD is characterized by greater severity of depression and increased functional impairments. Recently, the recurrence of illness (ROI) index was introduced as a quantitative metric for assessing this recurrence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soil organic matter dynamics under changing precipitation regimes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current and predicted changes in global precipitation regimes, characterized by increasing extreme events and wet-dry cycles, present critical uncertainties for terrestrial biogeochemical cycling and soil organic matter (SOM) dynamics. Here, we highlight individual and interactive effects of abiotic and biotic factors on SOM dynamics under changing precipitation amount, timing, and frequency. Particularly, we identify the mechanisms and magnitude by which changes in precipitation regimes alter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychometric evaluation of a Korean-language version of the Nursing Home Survey on Patient Safety Culture (K-NHSPSC)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aldolase a coordinates macropinocytic nutrient scavenging and lysosomal degradation in lung cancer by interacting with V-ATPase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study identifies a novel, non-enzymatic function of ALDOA as a critical regulator of lysosomal degradation of macropinocytosed proteins via interaction with V-ATPase. This mechanism is essential for metabolic adaptation and growth of KRAS-mutant tumors under stress conditions. Targeting ALDOA offers a promising therapeutic strategy for cancers that rely on extracellular nutrient scavenging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a laboratory-scale apparatus and experimental investigation of fluid property effects on pipe wear in slurry shield TBM operations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Managing pipeline wear is critical for maintaining excavation efficiency during slurry shield tunnel boring machine (TBM) operations. Yet, the effects of carrier fluid properties on pipe wear in slurries containing coarse particles remain insufficiently understood. To address this gap, this study developed a laboratory-scale test apparatus to simulate slurry flow in the discharge pipelines of a slurry shield TBM, focusing on the influence of carrier fluid viscosity and density on pipe wear....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pressurized intraperitoneal aerosol chemotherapy enhances cisplatin efficacy in colorectal cancer organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pressurized Intraperitoneal Aerosol Chemotherapy (PIPAC) is an emerging method that delivers chemotherapeutic agents as aerosols directly into the peritoneal cavity to overcome poor tissue penetration. Although early clinical outcomes are promising, challenges remain, such as variable patient responses and the lack of appropriate preclinical models. In this study, we investigated the efficacy of PIPAC combined with three cytotoxic agents (Cisplatin, Oxaliplatin, and Paclitaxel) using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MIDAS: rapid, multiplexed molecular profiling for integrated host-pathogen analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Addressing the need for integrated molecular analysis in complex infectious conditions requires technologies that rapidly quantify both pathogens and host responses. This is particularly relevant in sepsis research, where existing tools typically measure either microbial or host biomarkers. Here, we present MIDAS (Multiplexed Intelligent Diffraction Analysis System), a proof-of-concept platform that integrates shape-encoded hydrogel particles with lens-free diffraction imaging and deep...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trajectories of post-discharge cognitive function and associated risk factors in ICU survivors: a secondary analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[USP11 promotes colorectal cancer progression by stabilizing EGFR and TRAF6: a potential therapeutic target in EGFR- and TLR-driven tumorigenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ubiquitin-specific proteases (USPs) are key regulators of protein homeostasis and have been implicated in various aspects of cancer development, including colorectal cancer (CRC). In this study, we investigated the role of USP11 in CRC pathogenesis. RNA-seq analysis of tumor and matched normal tissues from 35 CRC patients identified USP11 as significantly overexpressed in tumor samples. Elevated USP11 expression was correlated with reduced patient survival, suggesting its prognostic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The São Paulo International Consensus on Minimally Invasive Pancreatic Surgery for Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Although minimally invasive surgery is widely accepted across surgical disciplines, its role in pancreatic cancer continues to be debated. The objective of the São Paulo Consensus on Minimally Invasive Pancreatic Surgery (MIPS) was to establish consensus statements on the use of MIPS for pancreatic cancer, integrating contemporary evidence and recent advances.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Specific glutamatergic projection to claustrum for regulating methamphetamine abstinence anxiety-like behaviors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Methamphetamine (METH) abstinence anxiety is a common METH abstinence symptom, which drives METH relapse. Our previous study found that claustrum (CL) is involved in coding abstinence anxiety-like behaviors caused by adolescent cocaine experiences. Here, we aim to investigate the role of CL in the development of METH abstinence-induced anxiety, especially exploring the related glutamatergic projections to CL. We found that 14 days of METH abstinence heightened anxiety-like behaviors in male...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International consensuses and guidelines on multifocal intraocular lenses (IOLs) by the Academy of Asia-Pacific Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intraocular Lenses (IOLs) have revolutionized cataract surgery, evolving from simple monofocal designs to advanced multifocal technologies that aim to reduce dependence on glasses after surgery. However, multifocal IOLs remain one of the most debated topics in ophthalmology, with passionate advocates and critics. This controversy stems from the balance between their potential benefits and limitations. The Asia-Pacific Academy of Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO) formed an international panel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunohistological characterization of minced dental pulp transplant in an ectopic mouse model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This preliminary in vivo mouse study suggests the feasibility of MP transplantation and its potential for dentin-pulp complex regeneration, though further studies are needed to assess long-term outcomes and clinical applicability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence, Progression, and Clinical Impact of Stem Notching in Ceramic-on-Ceramic Total Hip Arthroplasty: A Minimum 15-Year Follow-Up Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Stem notching in CoC THA is a relatively common, but often overlooked phenomenon. Most notches remained stable over time and were not associated with inferior functional outcomes. Although hips with notches showed a higher rate of ceramic-related noise and head fractures, these differences were not statistically significant. Clinicians should recognize this finding, maintain routine follow-up, and reassure patients that a notch alone does not pose any immediate problem.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Good clinical outcome of nonoperative treated low grade medial collateral ligament injuries combined with primary anterior cruciate ligament reconstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Similar patient-reported, functional, and return-to-sport outcomes were found for nonoperatively treated grade I and II MCL injuries combined with ACL reconstruction compared to those of isolated ACL reconstruction at the 2-year follow-up.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Levan-stabilized Prussian blue nanoparticles targeting the CD44 receptor for the effective treatment of acute kidney injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute kidney injury (AKI) is a prevalent disease characterized by sudden loss of renal function. Nanozymes have emerged as promising therapeutic candidates because of their intrinsic reactive oxygen species (ROS)-scavenging capabilities and anti-inflammatory efficacy. However, their clinical translation has been hindered by limited bioavailability and lack of targeted tissue specificity. In this study, ROS-scavenging Prussian blue nanozymes were stabilized with levan polysaccharide (L-PB) to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liver cancer chronically exposed to palmitate acquires ferroptosis resistance via the downregulation of glutamine-driven hepcidin expression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study uncovers a previously unrecognized type of palmitate-induced metabolic reprogramming that confers resistance to ICB-induced ferroptosis on HCC, and propose a therapeutic strategy to overcome ferroptosis resistance under free fatty acid-rich conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex Differences in Platelet Reactivity and Five-Year Outcomes With Extended Dual Antiplatelet Therapy After Drug-Eluting Stent Implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Female patients with HPR tended to have lower ischemic event rates than males, without an increase in bleeding events; however, this finding should be interpreted as hypothesis-generating.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell-surface RNA forms ternary complex with RNA-binding proteins and heparan sulfate to recruit immune receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent discoveries have shown the presence of ribonucleic acid (RNA) on the cell surface, defying the view that RNA only functions intracellularly. However, how RNA is presented on the cell surface and what its biological relevance is are poorly understood. We established Toll-like receptor 7 (TLR7) as a cell-surface RNA (csRNA) probe. Employing it in a genome-wide knockout screening, we identified heparan sulfate (HS) as a crucial factor for csRNA presentation. Cell-surface proximity labeling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morphological changes of the preserved discoid lateral meniscus on serial magnetic resonance imaging following partial meniscectomy and repair: A comparison between immediate and 2-year postoperative findings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The meniscal width of the anterior and posterior horns of DLM in the sagittal plane increased from the immediate postoperative state through to 2 years following partial meniscectomy and meniscus repair. Although the height of the anterior horn, midbody, and posterior horns remained consistent, the mid-height of these structures decreased at the 2-year follow up compared with the immediate postoperative status.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of NIRS-based models for predicting quality and gas production traits of fresh alfalfa silage via machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Near-infrared spectroscopy (NIRS) prediction models offer an expeditious method for assessing the nutritional value of feedstuffs, however, developing high-performance models using undried and unground samples remains challenging. This study aimed to explore strategies to improve NIRS models for predicting silage quality and gas production of fresh alfalfa using machine learning approaches. A total of 348 spectral samples were collected for modeling 15 parameters of alfalfa silage. The modeling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutralizing endocan reduces blood pressure and improves endothelial function in angiotensin II-induced hypertensive mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endocan (endothelial cell-specific molecule-1) has emerged as a potential biomarker of endothelial dysfunction in hypertension. This study investigates the role of endocan in blood pressure regulation and vascular dysfunction, aiming to clarify its contribution to the pathophysiology of hypertension. Eight-week-old male C57BL/6 mice were treated with saline, endocan (0.6 mg/kg), or angiotensin II (Ang II, 1000 ng/kg/min) for 4 weeks. Ang II-induced hypertensive mice were further treated with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantification differences between supine and prone CT in interstitial lung disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Prone CT measurements demonstrated high reproducibility and comparable correlation with PFT parameters, relative to supine CT measurements, with fibrosis extent variability of approximately 2 %. Prone CT may be reliable for single-time-point assessment; however, caution is warranted for longitudinal comparisons in advanced or GGO-dominant ILD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of oil droplet detachment by cavitation bubbles in ultrasonic cleaning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient removal of oily contaminants from solid surfaces remains a significant challenge in various engineering applications. While ultrasonic cleaning mechanisms for solid particles are well established, the detachment of oil droplets is less understood due to the distinct interfacial and viscous characteristics of oils. Here, we experimentally investigate oil droplet removal under ultrasonic excitation, focusing on the role of cavitation bubble dynamics. High-speed visualizations reveal that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental health, coping and related risk factors during the first 2 years of the COVID-19 pandemic in children: Nationally representative, multi-wave, cross-sectional results from 12 countries from the global COH-FIT study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Few multinational studies have assessed risk factors and coping strategies associated with the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on children's mental health over time. The Collaborative Outcomes study on Health and Functioning during Infection Times (COH-FIT) is the largest transcontinental, multi-wave, cross-sectional survey collecting multi-nation data on well-being and psychopathology during the pandemic. We analyzed country-specific, general-population-based, representative COH-FIT data of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interferon-γ-responsive theranostic nanoplatform for adaptive antibacterial therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing intelligent theranostic strategies capable of real-time infection assessment and adaptive treatment remains a significant challenge in wound management. Here, we present a smart theranostic nanoplatform (Apt-Ag^(+)-GNR) that integrates fluorescence-guided detection, real-time adaptive silver ion (Ag^(+)) release, and photothermal therapy (PTT) for the precise treatment of infections. This system utilizes interferon-γ (IFN-γ), an inflammation-specific biomarker with high detection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent short-term and long-term outcomes of massive pulmonary hemorrhage in extremely low birth weight infants: A nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The incidence and in-hospital deaths of massive pulmonary hemorrhage in ELBW infants have decreased in recent years. However, improved survival may be accompanied by increased in-hospital morbidity and adverse neurodevelopmental outcomes, underscoring the need for ongoing monitoring and strategies to mitigate short- and long-term complications in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal analysis of mangrove vegetation changes in Cà Mau, Vietnam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mangrove ecosystems provide essential coastal ecosystem services, including shoreline protection, carbon sequestration, and biodiversity conservation, but are increasingly affected by climate change, aquaculture expansion, and coastal development. These pressures have intensified marine pollution, which alters water chemistry, reduces oxygen levels, and disrupts root-sediment interactions that are crucial for mangrove survival and regeneration. This study examined spatiotemporal changes in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of anti-inflammatory constituents of <em>lindera glauca</em> using cell extraction coupled with lC-QTOF MS/MS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lindera glauca, an edible medicinal plant native to Northeastern Asia, has been reported to possess various pharmacological activities. This study employed cell extraction (CE) in conjunction with LC-QTOF-MS/MS to identify bioactive components that bind to target cells. The 80% MeOH extract of L. glauca exhibited significant nitric oxide (NO) production inhibitory activity in BV2 cells and was applied to the CE coupled with the LC-QTOF MS/MS method. New compound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Search for New Physics in Jet Multiplicity Patterns of Multilepton Events at sqrt[s]=13 TeV]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A first search for beyond the standard model physics in jet multiplicity patterns of multilepton events is presented, using a data sample corresponding to an integrated luminosity of 138 fb^{-1} of 13 TeV proton-proton collisions recorded by the CMS detector at the LHC. The search uses observed jet multiplicity distributions in one-, two-, and four-lepton events to explore possible enhancements in jet production rate in three-lepton events with and without bottom quarks. The data are found to be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Underutilization of GIS in health research in Pakistan: A literature review of Pakistani medline indexed journals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the spatial dimension of place, alongside time and personal characteristics, is essential in epidemiology. The current narrative review was planned to analyse articles from all three Medline-indexed general medical journals in Pakistan that reported on the use of Geographic Information System or the Global Positioning System. From 2011 till October 2024, a total of 20 studies were published; 18(90%) of them in the Journal of Pakistan Medical Association, including the first article...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and Psychometric Testing of the Self-Efficacy for Heart-Healthy Lifestyle Behaviors (SE-HeartLife) Scale in Cardiovascular Disease Prevention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The 35-item SE-HeartLife scale is a psychometrically robust instrument for assessing self-efficacy in the integrated practice of multiple heart-healthy behaviors aimed at preventing cardiovascular disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reconstruction after distal gastrectomy and alkaline gastritis: a multi-center three-arm randomized trial comparing Billroth-II, Billroth-II Braun, and Uncut Roux-en-Y (SDR-02)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Uncut R-Y is superior to B-II and B-II Braun in reducing bile reflux and related symptoms after distal gastrectomy. These findings support the adoption of uncut R-Y as a preferred reconstruction method for long-term QOL improvement in gastric cancer patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in Transmission Electron Microscopy to Image Nanocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in transmission electron microscopy (TEM) have substantially expanded our capability to observe nanocrystals at unprecedented spatial and temporal resolutions. Innovations in TEM instruments, specimen preparation, and imaging modality have overcome historical limitations related to radiation damage, weak contrast for light elements, 2D projection limitations, and high-vacuum constraints. Additionally, advanced image processing techniques, particularly those incorporating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Cognitive Function and Somatic Psychological Symptoms Are Correlated with Greater Risk of Delirium After Total Knee Arthroplasty: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study comprehensively evaluated preoperative cognitive function and psychological symptoms in patients undergoing TKA. Even subclinical cognitive and somatic symptoms were linked to POD, emphasizing the need for preoperative identification of high-risk patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How similar should collaborators be in inter-organizational learning: Optimal cognitive proximity and knowledge complexity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Effective knowledge exchange is critical for innovation in knowledge-intensive sectors, yet the relationship between cognitive proximity and collaborative innovation remains underexplored in complex knowledge environments. While prior studies confirm a non-linear, inverted U-shaped relationship where moderate similarity balances absorptive capacity and novelty, how this relationship changes with increasing knowledge complexity is poorly understood. This study investigates how knowledge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Vertical Molecular Synaptic Transistor with Redox-Induced Analog States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a three-terminal, ion-gel-gated, redox-active molecular transistor that exhibits synaptic plasticity and analog conductance states. The device was composed of a ferrocene-terminated alkanethiolate self-assembled monolayer as the active channel, vertically sandwiched between a monolayer graphene source and a Au drain, and the channel conductance was modulated by an ion-gel gate. Gate voltage pulses induce an electric double layer at the ion-gel/graphene interface, triggering dynamic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toxicity and Safety of Nanomaterials in Food Packaging Applications: A Dimension-Based Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanomaterials are increasingly used in food packaging polymers to enhance barriers, strength, and antimicrobial properties, raising important questions about their migration into food and potential health risks. Driven by these concerns, this review evaluates the toxicity and safety of nanomaterials in food packaging from a dimensional perspective. It explores how dimensionality (0D, 1D, 2D, and 3D) influences nanoparticle transport, gastrointestinal transformation, biological fate, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of combining empagliflozin in people with type 2 diabetes mellitus uncontrolled with metformin and sitagliptin: A randomised, double-blind, multicentre, therapeutic confirmatory phase 3 clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results suggest that coadministration of empagliflozin safely improves glycemic control in Korean patients with T2DM uncontrolled by sitagliptin and metformin.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacological inhibition of Ubiquitin-Specific Peptidase 10 (USP10) with spautin-1 attenuates adipogenesis through CCAAT/Enhancer-Binding Protein Beta (C/EBPβ) destabilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pharmacological control of lipid accumulation in white adipose tissue (WAT) is a key area of focus in obesity research, yet the role of deubiquitination in adipocyte lipid storage remains underexplored. We found that spautin-1, an inhibitor of the deubiquitinases ubiquitin-specific peptidase 10 (USP10) and 13 (USP13), suppressed lipid accumulation during adipogenesis. Therefore, we investigated whether blocking deubiquitination restricts adipogenesis and acts as the underlying mechanism....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chainmail catalysis for advanced water treatment: overcoming the stability-reactivity tradeoff in Fenton-like oxidation of micropollutants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent developments in chainmail catalysis present a promising solution to the longstanding challenge of catalytic deactivation in traditional advanced oxidation processes (AOPs) for water reuse. This strategy involves encapsulating nanocatalysts within protective carbon shells, which significantly improves their stability and enhances the degradation kinetics of micropollutants. The unique architecture of these materials promotes efficient electron transfer between the transition metal core and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal IFN-γ Priming and Therapeutic Efficacy of 3D-Cultured Human Umbilical Cord-Derived Mesenchymal Stem Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MSCs were enhanced using cytokine priming and 3D spheroid culture. We successfully established the effective priming conditions for the therapeutic application of IFN-γ-primed 3D spheroids. The findings suggest their potential benefits in the treatment of TMJOA which is currently incurable and inform further advancements in regenerative medicine.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Climate research towards sustainable development: contributions of the Brazilian Science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Promoting sustainable development depends on addressing the challenges generated by climate change. The nature of these complex and interconnected challenges requires knowledge generation and the strengthening of interdisciplinary research networks. Research developed by the National Institute for Science and Technology for Climate Change Phase 2 (INCT-MC2) project, with its six thematic lines (or subcomponents) and three integrative (crosscutting) topics, provides a deep understanding of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Initial Distance-Dependent Mean Force Drives Synaptic Vesicle Motion Toward Fusion Sites in Stimulated Hippocampal Neurons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuronal communication occurs through transport and exocytosis of synaptic vesicles (SVs). However, their dynamics during neuronal stimulation remains poorly understood. Here, real-time, 3D motion of individual SVs undergoing exocytosis in presynaptic terminals is quantitatively investigated. SVs are categorized into two types: Type I showing confined motion near fusion sites until exocytosis and Type II SVs exhibiting unconfined motion before tethering and exocytosis. Type II SVs have a broader...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Croceiramulus getboli</em> gen. nov., sp. nov., a marine bacterium isolated from the tidal flat]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A Gram-stain-negative, non-motile and golden-yellow pigmented bacterium, designated strain YJPT1-3^(T), was isolated from a tidal flat sediment collected in Yongyu-do, Republic of Korea. The strain grew optimally at 30 °C, pH 7.0, and with 2% (w/v) NaCl. Phylogenetic analysis based on 16S rRNA gene sequences placed strain YJPT1-3^(T) within the family Flavobacteriaceae, with the closest relatives being Arenibacter nanhaiticus NH36A^(T) (90.3%), Sediminicola luteus CNI-3^(T) (90.2%), Muriicola...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photopolymerized helical acrylate networks enable stable and full-color circularly polarized luminescence in perovskite nanocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photopolymerized chiral polymer frameworks offer an unexplored strategy to couple structural confinement with optical activity in hybrid materials. Here, we introduce a confinement-driven design in which a photopolymerized hydrophobic helical acrylate network (DPAHA) simultaneously stabilizes and imparts chirality to all-inorganic CsPbX(3) (X = Cl, Br, I) perovskite nanocrystals. The polymer forms rigid, non-centrosymmetric cavities that asymmetrically confine the nanocrystals, generating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of vagus nerve stimulation and epilepsy surgery on antiseizure medication usage in pediatric patients with drug-resistant epilepsy in the real world: A retrospective nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: The long-term effects of epilepsy surgery (ES) or vagus nerve stimulation (VNS) on antiseizure medication (ASM) usage and status epilepticus (SE) diagnosis in real-world pediatric drug-resistant epilepsy (DRE) populations remain unclear. This study aimed to provide a more comprehensive understanding of how VNS and ES affect ASM usage and SE manifestations in pediatric DRE.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biology-driven stratification of advanced biliary tract cancer treated with nab-paclitaxel plus gemcitabine-cisplatin: A prospective observational cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrated the clinical activity of Gem/Cis/nab-P in advanced BTC and highlighted that biology-driven patient stratification based on genomic and transcriptomic features may provide important prognostic information.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of clofazimine-bedaquiline combination as a candidate regimen for macrolide-resistant <em>Mycobacterium avium</em> complex infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Mycobacterium avium complex (MAC) is the primary cause of pulmonary disease (PD) among nontuberculous mycobacteria, presenting a significant treatment challenge on a global scale. A long-term (≥12 months) three-drug regimen, typically including a macrolide, such as clarithromycin (CLR) or azithromycin, along with rifampicin and ethambutol, is recommended. However, many patients fail to respond adequately to therapy, and some eventually develop macrolide resistance, making the disease even...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seropositive Rheumatoid Arthritis and Polyhexamethylene Guanidine/Oligo(2-(2-Ethoxy)ethoxyethyl)guanidinium Chloride Exposure Are Associated With a Synergistic Effect on the Risk of Developing Interstitial Lung Disease: Registry Based Cohort-Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PHMG/PGH exposure was not associated with increased incidence of seropositive RA. PHMG/PGH and seropositive RA each independently raised ILD risk, with more-than-additive association when combined. Given the retrospective, internally compared design, mechanistic work is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetic smartphone microflow cytometry enables rapid CD4/CD8 T cell quantification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate enumeration of CD4+ and CD8+ T lymphocytes is essential for HIV management, yet conventional flow cytometry remains largely inaccessible in resource-limited settings. Current point-of-care testing (POCT) approaches, including lateral flow assays and fluorescence-based imaging methods, offer improved accessibility but typically compromise accuracy and yield semi-quantitative results. Here, we present a magnetic-activated smartphone microflow cytometry (MACC) platform that enables rapid,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the Letter to the Editor: Methodological Reflections on the Development of Breath VOC Models in Colorectal Cancer Screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychological Benefits of Vagus Nerve Stimulation for Children and Adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Charting the way forward for HTA in Asia-Pacific: HTAsiaLink's strategic plan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Health Technology Assessment (HTA) informs resource allocation and policy decisions, particularly to achieve Universal Health Coverage (UHC). Recognizing the increasing demand for evidence-informed decision-making, the HTAsiaLink network was established in 2011 as a regional platform to strengthen individual and institutional capacity in HTA research and facilitate the integration of HTA evidence into policy decisions across the Asia-Pacific.Over the years, HTAsiaLink has expanded to over fifty...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing emergency medical system governance in Japan and South Korea: lessons for high-income countries from a multisource comparative health systems analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The contrasting systems suggest that hybrid governance that combines centralized standard settings with local operational flexibility may optimize EMS performance. These findings provide lessons for EMS reform, cross-border collaboration, and disaster preparedness in high-income nations facing similar demographic and healthcare challenges.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of an automated phenotyping platform and identification of a novel QTL for drought tolerance in soybean]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep understanding of slow-wilting is essential for developing drought-tolerant crops. Existing approaches to measure transpiration rates are difficult to apply to large populations due to their high cost and low throughput. To overcome these challenges, we developed a high-throughput phenotyping system that integrates a load cell sensor and an Arduino-based microcontroller device. The system tracked the transpiration rate in real time by measuring changes in the pot weight in 224 recombinant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De-occlusion models and diffusion-based data augmentation for size estimation of on-plant oriental melons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate fruit size estimation is crucial for plant phenotyping, as it enables precise crop management and enhances agricultural productivity by providing essential data for growth and resource efficiency analysis. In this study, we estimated the size of on-plant oriental melons grown in a vertical cultivation system to address the challenges posed by leaf occlusion. Data augmentation was achieved using a diffusion model to generate synthetic leaves to cover existing fruits and create an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KDOSS-net: Knowledge distillation-based outpainting and semantic segmentation network for crop and weed images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Weed management plays a crucial role in increasing crop yields. Semantic segmentation, which classifies each pixel in an image captured by a camera into categories such as crops, weeds, and background, is a widely used method in this context. However, conventional semantic segmentation methods rely solely on pixel information within the camera's field of view (FOV), hindering their ability to detect weeds outside the visible area. This limitation can lead to incomplete weed removal and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid diagnosis of herbicidal activity and mode of action using spectral image analysis and machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herbicide screening requires a substantial amount of time, effort, and cost, making a new herbicide discovery expensive and time-consuming. Various diagnostic methods have been developed, but most of them are destructive and require significant time and effort to identify herbicide activity. Therefore, this study was conducted to apply spectral image analysis for early and rapid diagnosis of herbicidal activity and modes of action (MOAs). RGB, chlorophyll fluorescence (CF), and infrared (IR)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of Ambient Multipollutant Exposure and Health Impacts Over India Using the Novel Satellite-Based Multi-Pollutant Index]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ambient air pollutants are reported to have adverse health impacts, which could be better assessed by examining human exposure to multiple criteria pollutants or through a multi-pollutant Air Quality Index (AQI). As compared to AQIs developed using in situ measurements of pollutants across sparse monitoring stations, satellite-based products such as ambient PM(2.5) or NO(2) provide better spatiotemporal patterns. Here, we examine the long-term (2005-2019) air pollution exposure and health...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pre-symptomatic diagnosis of rice blast and brown spot diseases using chlorophyll fluorescence imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rice blast and brown spot are two of the most significant fungal diseases affecting rice production. Although the leaf symptoms of both diseases are distinct, they manifest as similar brown-black lesions, complicating differentiation and effective management. Traditional diagnostic methods predominantly rely on DNA-based molecular techniques, which are not well-suited for rapid, large-scale applications. This study aimed to identify reliable chlorophyll fluorescence (ChlF) indicators for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Cochlear Implant Position for Magnetic Resonance Imaging of Vestibular Schwannoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Optimal positioning of the CI magnet, particularly maintaining a distance greater than 90 mm from the EAC, is crucial for achieving clear postoperative MRI visualization of the IAC in patients undergoing VS treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomically refined entorhinal cortex segmentation improves MRI-based early diagnosis of Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The entorhinal cortex (EC) is one of the earliest cortical regions affected in Alzheimer's disease (AD) and serves as a key target for magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) biomarkers. However, conventional segmentation pipelines based on the Desikan-Killiany atlas do not clearly distinguish the EC from the adjacent perirhinal cortex, leading to mixed labels and reduced diagnostic sensitivity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Processed silkworm powder (Hongjam) ameliorates metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease via GPR35/PKA and SIRT1/AMPK pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) is a chronic metabolic disorder linked to obesity, insulin resistance, and type 2 diabetes. This study aimed to investigate the preventive effects of Hongjam, a processed silkworm powder, in a high-fat diet-induced MASLD mouse model and to explore its underlying mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[조영증강 유방촬영술: 현재의 임상적 활용과 미래 방향에 대한 종합적 고찰]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Contrast-enhanced mammography (CEM) is an advanced imaging technique that combines morphological and functional information to enhance breast cancer detection, similar to MRI. Using dual-energy X-rays and iodinated contrast agents, CEM highlights enhancing abnormalities and is highly sensitive in detecting malignancies, particularly in dense breasts. Its advantages include rapid image acquisition and cost-effectiveness, making it useful in screening, diagnosis, staging, and monitoring of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Current Landscape and Commercialization of AI Models in Musculoskeletal Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article on p. 624 in vol. 86, PMID: 41113373.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Practice Guideline for Stroke Rehabilitation in Korea-Part 2: Rehabilitation for Motor and Sensory Function (2024)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This clinical practice guideline (CPG) is the second part of the fourth edition of the Korean Stroke Rehabilitation Guidelines, following the first part published in 2023. While, the first part addressed rehabilitation for motor function, while this second part focuses on both motor and sensory rehabilitation. Beginning with the fourth edition, significant methodological advancements have been introduced, transitioning from a consensus-based approach to an evidence-based framework using the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, POSTECH, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complementary strategies in pancreatic cancer precision medicine: therapeutic prediction and immune modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The development of patient-derived organoids for drug sensitivity testing, personalized mRNA vaccines for immune activation, and precision diagnostic and therapeutic technologies represents complementary advances in PDAC. While each approach has demonstrated independent clinical value, their integration remains an important future direction that may provide a comprehensive framework for improving outcomes in PDAC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Administration of 2-deoxy-D-glucose induces pyroptosis in murine breast cancer cells via cAMP/PKA/HK2 to impair tumor survival]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings identified a novel metabolic-inflammatory axis (cAMP/PKA-HK2-caspase-3/GSDME) in breast cancer. Furthermore, study highlights the in vivo efficacy and safety of 2-DG and its ability to induce pyroptosis, thereby providing a basis for targeting drug resistance in breast cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and associated factors of intimate partner violence against women in Ghana: a secondary analysis of the 2022 Demographic and Health Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: IPV is associated with multiple complex factors. About 1.8 women out of every five women in Ghana have experienced IPV in their lifetime. These findings emphasize the urgent need for effective public health and economic strategies to reduce this preventable form of violence for women in Ghana.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Socioeconomic Inequalities in the Continuum of Suicidal Ideation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Suicidal ideation changes over time. Few studies have examined socioeconomic inequalities in suicide ideation regarding interrelated indicators of incidence, persistence, and remission. Aim: We aimed to investigate how socioeconomic characteristics are related to the incidence, persistence, and remission of suicidal ideation in South Korea. Methods: We assessed the incidence of suicidal ideation at the 1-year follow-up among individuals without prior suicidal ideation and its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developmental Brain Age Estimation From MRI Data: A Systematic Review of Deep Learning Approaches and Open Datasets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brain age is an emerging concept that reflects complex, time-dependent changes in brain structure, identifying departures from expected neurodevelopmental patterns. In the developing brain, accurate MRI-based age estimation is a quantitative biomarker for detecting atypical neurodevelopment, facilitating early diagnosis, guiding clinical decision-making, and potentially improving long-term outcomes. Data-driven models applied to neuroimaging have provided valuable insights into the pathogenesis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physician experience and perceptions of tetrabenazine for the treatment of tardive dyskinesia and Huntington's chorea: a survey of neurologists and psychiatrists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although most physicians were moderately satisfied with TBZ, they also reported that TBZ side effects prevented reaching optimal clinical effectiveness and often led to discontinuation, suggesting a need for additional effective treatment options with favorable benefit-risk profiles for TD and HD-related chorea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prioritizing maternal sleep: a public health strategy for preventing childhood allergic diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nitrogen balance and yolk corticosterone levels of laying hens fed low protein diets from 33 to 64 weeks of age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: It is concluded that decreasing dietary protein levels fortified with limiting amino acids can be applied to mitigate nitrogen excretion without affecting nutrition-mediated stress in laying hens.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cohort profile: the KDCA-Tuberculosis-NHIS Cohort linking tuberculosis surveillance and health insurance data in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite a steady decline in incidence, tuberculosis (TB) remains a substantial public health burden in South Korea, particularly among older adults. Existing national TB surveillance systems lack sufficiently comprehensive data to assess long-term outcomes and health disparities. The K-TB-N cohort integrates data from 3 national sources: the Korean Tuberculosis Surveillance System (2011-2022), the National Health Insurance Database (2010-2022), and mortality data from Statistics Korea...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Secular trends in grip strength among Korean adults according to socioeconomic factors: the 2014-2022 Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings provide descriptive evidence of grip strength trends and socioeconomic disparities in Korea. They may serve as baseline information to guide future longitudinal studies and inform public health strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pervasive environmental contaminant acrolein compromises myocardial geometry and function through the induction of cuproptosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acrolein, a highly reactive α,β-unsaturated aldehyde found in cigarette smoke, automobile exhaust, industrial emissions, combustion byproducts, cooking and cyclophosphamide chemotherapy, has raised serious health concerns, although the precise mechanism remains unclear. This study is designed to examine the impact of this pervasive environmental pollutant on myocardial geometry and function alongside the underlying cellular mechanisms. Adult C57BL/6 mice are challenged with acrolein (2.5...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunosuppressive Tumor Microenvironment in Colorectal Cancer Lung Metastases: Implications for Recurrence After Metastasectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Immunosuppressive features including enrichment of SPP1+ TAMs and depletion of effector T and NK cells contribute to recurrence after CRC lung metastasectomy. Therapeutic strategies targeting both TAMs and T cells may enhance clinical outcomes in this patient population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redefining HER2 in Breast Cancer: From Conventional Positivity to Low and Ultralow in the New Era of Antibody-Drug Conjugates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human epidermal growth factor receptor 2 (HER2) has evolved from a poor prognostic factor to one of the most impactful predictive biomarkers in oncology. The introduction of trastuzumab established HER2 as a binary determinant of therapy, with HER2 immunohistochemistry (IHC) becoming the treatment-guiding diagnostic assay. However, the emergence of antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs), particularly trastuzumab deruxtecan, has challenged this paradigm by demonstrating activity in tumors with low and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilization, Reimbursement, and Barriers to Accessing Sequencing Tests for Cancer Care in the Asia-Pacific Region: KSMO Initiatives to Address Cancer Care Inequity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings demonstrated a wide disparity in access, funding and reimbursement of sequencing tests across the region. Addressing cost, improving reimbursement mechanisms, and building infrastructure capacity will be critical for the equitable integration of NGS into routine cancer care in the Asia-Pacific.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell cycle-regulated expression of Fam72a from the |Srgap2-Fam72a| master gene leads to Mis18a downregulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The novel |Srgap2-Fam72a| master gene, comprising SLIT-ROBO Rho GTPase-activating protein 2 (Srgap2) and family with sequence similarity 72 member A (Fam72a), has attracted attention for its potential role in regulating brain plasticity and supporting advanced cognitive functions in humans. Moreover, recent studies have identified Fam72a as a new cell cycle-regulated gene. In this study, we investigated the activity of the intergenic region (IGR) between the native Srgap2 and Fam72a gene pair...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[β-Catenin and AMPK/AKT/FOXO Signaling Mediate Doxorubicin-Induced Senescence and Lipid Accumulation in C2C12 Myoblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skeletal muscle atrophy is a major complication associated with aging, chronic disease, and chemotherapy. Doxorubicin (Dox), a widely used anticancer agent, accelerates muscle wasting; however, the underlying cellular mechanisms remain poorly understood. In this study, we examined the effects of Dox on myogenic differentiation, senescence, and lipid metabolism using C2C12 myoblasts. Dox exposure impaired myotube formation without causing overt cytotoxicity. Mechanistically, Dox disrupted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microneedle Patch Loaded with Metabolized Elastin-Complexed Ceria Nanoparticles for Oral Ulcer Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41413932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oral ulcers are prevalent oral health issues with a high recurrence rate that substantially impair oral and systemic health. However, current therapies for oral ulcers are limited to symptom relief without addressing its fundamental pathophysiology. Additionally, their treatment efficacy is limited by reduced bioavailability due to the dynamic environment of oral cavity and reactive oxygen species (ROS)-rich microenvironment of ulcer bed. Here, we develop a microneedle patch system designed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41413932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving 2D-ness to enhance thermopower in oxide superlattices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The thermoelectric performance of a material is determined by the fundamental transport dynamics of itinerant charge carriers and their interactions with the environment. For two-dimensional oxide thermoelectrics, predominantly represented by doped SrTiO3-based superlattices, reduced spatial dimensions and increased effective mass are known to enhance thermopower (S). However, because of their large effective Bohr radius resulting from their high dielectric constant, SrTiO3-based systems have...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EGFR activation requires cholesterol interaction at the inner leaflet of the plasma membrane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Signal transduction by the human epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR) is modulated by its ligands as well as by the various compounds on the plasma membrane (PM), including cholesterol. Here, using single-molecule coimmunoimmobilization, we found that cholesterol in the inner leaflet of PM plays an essential role in ligand-dependent EGFR activation. This was done by direct and quantitative examination of the interaction between EGFR and cholesterol on the PM of a living cell. Structural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: The costs of subsidies and externalities of economic activities driving nature decline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amino acid metabolism in diabetic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amino acids are the building blocks of protein synthesis and play important roles in the generation of adenosine triphosphate (ATP), glucose, and fatty acids as metabolic precursors. Consequently, they serve as both structural components and energy sources for cells, supporting growth, differentiation, and function. Metabolic disorders involving amino acids have been associated with multiple clinical pathologies, including diabetic kidney disease (DKD). Increasing evidence suggests that amino...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Energetic spectra from semi-implicit particle-in-cell simulations of magnetic reconnection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astrophysical observations suggest that magnetic reconnection in relativistic plasmas plays an important role in the acceleration of energetic particles. Modeling this accurately requires numerical schemes capable of addressing large scales and realistic magnetic field configurations without sacrificing the kinetic description needed to model particle acceleration self-consistently. We demonstrate the computational advantage of the relativistic semi-implicit method (RelSIM), which allows for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of the channel on the memory window of HfZrO<sub>x</sub> ferroelectric field-effect transistors with p-type Si-doped InZnO<sub>x</sub> channel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To elucidate the origin of the memory window (MW) of HfZrO(x) ferroelectric field-effect transistors (FeFETs) with a p-type Si-doped InZnO(x) (p-Si:InZnO) channel, we perform a comparative study with thin-film transistors (TFTs) in which the HfZrO(x) ferroelectric layer (FL) of the FeFETs is replaced by an HfO(2) dielectric layer (DL). The TFT is turned on at a threshold voltage (VT) of - 3 V and exhibits a reliable hysteresis-free transfer curve with a subthreshold swing (SS) of 265 mV/dec....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Statistical analysis for heat transfer optimization of magnetohydrodynamics trihybrid nanofluid over a convectively heated Riga surface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Riga plate is arrangement of electrodes and permanent magnets allows for efficient regulation of fluid flow. The Riga surface leverages Lorentz forces to control boundary layers (BL) and improve cooling purposes for effective electromagnetic flow control in nuclear and aeronautical engineering systems. Furthermore, by utilizing synergistic interactions of different nanoparticles, heat transfer rat can be optimized in industrial setup. The primary focus of this work is to investigate the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Galectin-3 in endometrial small extracellular vesicles promotes cytotrophoblast cell fusion during the implantation phase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings demonstrate that endometrial sEVs enriched in galectin-3 during the implantation phase promote CT differentiation into ST, underscoring a novel role for sEV-mediated protein delivery in regulating early placental development and suggesting potential diagnostic and therapeutic applications in reproductive medicine.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic resource optimization: a core collection of tetraploid wheat from 2,254 NBRP-wheat accessions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study provides a valuable core collection that captures the genetic diversity of tetraploid wheat conserved in NBRP-Wheat. The identified genomic regions and trait-associated loci demonstrate the utility of this core set for trait dissection and highlight its potential in future wheat improvement programs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergent collective alignment gives competitive advantage to longer cells during range expansion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacterial competition shapes community architecture, yet a universally conserved determinant remains elusive. We show that cell aspect ratio -a simple morphological feature- confers a competitive advantage. Using growth-based range expansion experiments, we show that longer bacteria conquer the expanding front, even when initially in minority. Using an agent-based model of dividing bacteria, to isolate the effect of aspect ratio, we reveal that the takeover mechanism is collective alignment:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal Machine Learning Integrating N-13 Ammonia PET and Clinical Variables Predicts Major Adverse Cardiac Events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The need for dynamic and static acquisitions under stress and rest in myocardial perfusion positron emission tomography (PET) is burdensome, and the short half-life of N-13 ammonia places additional constraints on scanning protocols. This study investigated whether combining static PET-derived images with clinical parameters via machine learning predicts major adverse cardiac events (MACE) to expand the utility of ammonia PET without dynamic scanning. The cohort comprised 386 patients, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transformer-based Deep Learning Models with Shape Guidance for Predicting Breast Cancer in Mammography Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent breast cancer research has investigated shape-based attention guidance in Vision Transformer (ViT) models, focusing on anatomical structures and the heterogeneity surrounding tumors. However, few studies have clarified the optimal transformer encoder layer stage for applying attention guidance. Our study aimed to evaluate the effectiveness of shape-guidance strategies by varying the combinations of encoder layers that guide attention to breast structures and by comparing the proposed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased ʟ-glutamate production from gaseous nitrogen using Klebsiella pasteurii NG13 with modified citrate synthase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fermentation of nitrogen-containing compounds by biological nitrogen fixation is a sustainable strategy that is independent of the Haber-Bosch process. We previously reported that the nitrogen-fixing bacterium Klebsiella pasteurii (formerly K. oxytoca) NG13 synthesized and excreted large amounts of ʟ-glutamate using gaseous nitrogen when citrate synthase (CS) and citrate transporter (CitS) were overproduced; however, the majority of carbon atoms in ʟ-glutamate were derived from citrate, not...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distance to the spinal canal and vertebral body from the insertion point of percutaneous pedicle screws in the lumbar spine: radiographic anatomy on computed tomography images for a safe and efficient procedure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study can contribute to the safe and efficient insertion of the lumbar PPS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chondrosarcoma organoids reveal SHH pathway activation driven by PTCH1 and BCOR alterations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chondrosarcoma is the second most common malignant bone tumor, characterized by the production of cartilaginous matrix and a high degree of resistance to conventional therapies such as chemotherapy and radiotherapy. Effective treatment options remain limited, highlighting the urgent need for preclinical models to explore novel therapeutic approaches. This study aimed to establish patient-derived organoid (PDO) models of chondrosarcoma and to investigate their utility in elucidating molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraperitoneal immune microenvironment and efficacy of intraperitoneal chemotherapy in patients with gastric cancer and peritoneal metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigated the role of the intraperitoneal immune microenvironment in the therapeutic response of gastric cancer with peritoneal metastasis to intraperitoneal paclitaxel. Gastric cancer with peritoneal metastasis has a poor prognosis, even with systemic chemotherapy. Although intraperitoneal paclitaxel administration has demonstrated clinical benefit, treatment resistance remains a major hurdle. Between 2017 and 2023, 30 patients undergoing staging laparoscopy were prospectively enrolled....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive factors for outcomes of chemonucleolysis with condoliase in lumbar disc herniation: A multi-institutional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identified key factors associated with successful outcomes of condoliase in LDH. Baseline pain intensity, MRI findings (herniation occupancy rate, slip), injection level, and disease duration were significant predictors of treatment outcomes. These findings may aid clinicians in patient selection and improve treatment success.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetically Encoded Ca<sup>2+</sup> Sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cytosolic Ca^(2+) plays a crucial role as a second messenger in cell signaling, regulating a wide range of cellular processes. Hence, studying its spatiotemporal dynamics has emerged as a key area of research, and fluorescence imaging has become an indispensable method. The first attempt to visualize Ca^(2+) in living specimens was made in the 1960s by microinjecting the bioluminescent Ca^(2+)-binding protein aequorin. However, the true breakthrough in Ca^(2+) imaging is often considered to be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient preference survey for attributes of locally advanced or metastatic urothelial carcinoma treatment in Japan: a discrete-choice experiment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this study, Japanese patients with la/mUC were more concerned about reduced quality of life due to adverse events than extending survival by 6 months. Patients, clinicians and other members of the care team need to communicate frequently and candidly about a patient's well-being.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2026 Scientific Advisors to the Editors (SAEs) Appointments and Updates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of interspecies differences in DS-2087b-induced gastrointestinal toxicity using mouse and monkey intestinal organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastrointestinal (GI) toxicity is a common adverse event induced by anti-cancer drugs; however, the information of the correlations in vitro to in vivo regarding GI toxicity is limited. The objective of this study was elucidating the usefulness of animal small intestinal organoids using DS-2087b, a novel epidermal growth factor receptor/human epidermal growth factor receptor 2 exon 20 insertion inhibitor. Mice showed no DS-2087b-related GI toxicities up to 100mg/kg in 28-day repeated oral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[β-Glucans and their roles in immune and metabolic regulation: A review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[β-Glucans are non-starch polysaccharides derived from various natural sources, including cereals, fungi, yeast, algae, and bacteria. Their structures determine their functions: cereal-derived β-glucans from oats and barley have mixed β-(1,3) and β-(1,4) linkages for heart and blood sugar benefits, while fungal and yeast types have β-(1,3) backbones with β-(1,6) branches that confer potent immunomodulatory properties through their interaction with pattern recognition receptors on immune cells....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased 30-day Mortality Risk in Coronavirus Disease 2019 Compared to Seasonal Influenza]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: COVID-19 is associated with markedly higher short-term mortality than influenza across diverse clinical and demographic subgroups. These findings underscore the ongoing need for vigilant prevention efforts, and vaccination. This study represents the first large-scale nationwide analysis, and the first in Asia, conducted in the post-COVID-19 era.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling Immune Lineage Co-Development in Human Pluripotent Stem Cell-derived Liver Organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: FLOs establish a physiologically relevant model for multi-lineage hemato-hepatogenesis and innate immunity in the liver. By recapitulating critical fetal liver tissue functions, FLOs provide a translational platform for studying human fetal liver development, immune-mediated hepatic injury, and regenerative therapies in humans.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dengue serotypes and epidemic dynamics in Brazil: a spatiotemporal perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Changes in the geographic distribution and territorial expansion of Aedes aegypti, the main dengue vector in the Americas, coupled with the concurrent circulation of multiple DENV serotypes, have driven the overall rise in dengue incidence in Brazil. Here, we investigate the spatiotemporal distribution of dengue virus serotypes across Brazil, focusing on dengue epidemiology over the last decade (2014 to 2025). We examine the temporal dynamics of these serotypes and discuss the main strategies to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering the gut microbiome and its impact on human health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The gut microbiome plays a crucial role in maintaining health by supporting digestion, immunity, and overall well-being. Disruptions to the gut microbiome can result in dysbiosis, which is correlated with disease states. Recent advances in engineering the gut microbiome, functional ingredients designed through prebiotics, probiotics, and synbiotics have progressed together with synthetic microbial communities (SynComs), which influence the modulation of microbiome composition and functional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Femorotibial joint rotation in intact joints and following partial medial collateral ligament transection, tibial plateau leveling osteotomy, and cranial cruciate ligament transection - A limb press study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite widespread use of tibial plateau leveling osteotomy (TPLO), the influence of partial medial collateral ligament transection (pMCLX) and physiologic loading on rotational stability remains unclear. This cadaveric study quantified internal and external tibial rotation in canine stifles under simulated weightbearing conditions. Ten unpaired pelvic limbs were mounted in a custom limb press applying axial loads equivalent to 30 % body weight with the stifle fixed at 135°. Quadriceps tension...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acicular berthierine-chamosite in coal and lung cancer tissues of Xuan Wei, China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Xuan Wei has China's highest female lung cancer mortality, attributed to household coal smoke exposure. While coal-derived polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons (PAHs) were previously blamed, persistently rising lung cancer rates despite PAH reductions implicate other carcinogens. Here, we aim to investigate iron-rich minerals in Late Permian coal as potential overlooked drivers. Coal was sampled from Laibin, epicentre of Xuan Wei lung cancer epidemic. Mineral phases in low temperature ash (LTA) were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evidence for the Dimuon Decay of the Higgs Boson in pp Collisions with the ATLAS Detector]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A search for the dimuon decay of the Higgs boson is presented based on pp collision data recorded by ATLAS during Run 3 of the Large Hadron Collider, corresponding to an integrated luminosity of 165 fb^{-1} at sqrt[s]=13.6 TeV. To enhance the sensitivity, the results are combined with those from Run 2. An excess of events over the background is observed with a significance of 3.4σ (2.5σ expected). The best-fit signal strength is μ=1.4±0.4. This result provides evidence for the H→μμ decay with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Observation of the Surface Superconducting Gap in the Topological Superconductor Candidate β-PdBi_{2}]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[β-PdBi_{2} is one of the candidates for topological superconductors with a superconducting (SC) transition temperature (T_{c}) of 5.3 K, in which parity mixing of a spin singlet and spin triplet has been anticipated, being crucial for the further understanding of the relationship with inversion symmetry and parity mixing in the superconductivity. In this Letter, we measured the SC gap in a high-quality single crystal of β-PdBi_{2} by using high-resolution laser angle-resolved photoemission...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analytical Lower Bound on Query Complexity for Transformations of Unknown Unitary Operations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent developments have revealed deterministic and exact protocols for performing complex conjugation, inversion, and transposition of a general d-dimensional unknown unitary operation using a finite number of queries to a black-box unitary operation. In this Letter, we establish analytical lower bounds for the query complexity of unitary inversion, transposition, and complex conjugation, which hold even if the input unitary is an unknown logarithmic-depth unitary. Specifically, our lower bound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adsorption Energy Prediction Model for CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction on Electrocatalysts Containing Previously Unencountered Metal Elements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical carbon dioxide reduction (CO(2)RR) using electrocatalysts has gained attention for its potential to convert atmospheric CO(2) into value-added chemicals. Recently, machine learning (ML) has emerged as a promising approach for catalyst development. In previous studies, catalyst screening using ML performed using adsorption energy databases obtained from density functional theory calculations has yielded successful results. However, the full potential of ML in catalyst discovery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interprofessional collaboration between hospital-based palliative care teams and hospital ward staff: A realist review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This realist review highlights the complexity of interprofessional collaboration between PCTs and ward staff, emphasizing the importance of tailored approaches that address specific contextual needs, expectations, and norms. Strengthening positive attitudes, clarifying roles, and fostering partnerships can enhance interprofessional collaboration, ultimately improving palliative care quality in hospital settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutral theory of cooperative dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mutualistic interactions are widespread in nature, from plant communities and microbiomes to human organizations. Along with competition for resources, cooperative interactions shape biodiversity and contribute to the robustness of complex ecosystems. We present a stochastic neutral theory of cooperator species. Our model shares with the classic neutral theory of biodiversity the assumption that all species are equivalent, but crucially differs in requiring cooperation between species for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imaging findings of intra-articular tumor/tumor-like lesions based on pathologic correlation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proper treatment of intra-articular tumor/tumor-like lesions (tenosynovial giant cell tumor, synovial chondromatosis, synovial hemangioma / intra-articular venous malformations, lipoma arborescens, etc.) depends on an accurate diagnosis. This review highlights the imaging findings of intra-articular tumor/tumor-like lesions and the other synovial diseases (gout, amyloid arthropathy, rheumatoid arthritis, ganglion, and postoperative intra-articular tumor) to determine whether they could help in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unexpected respiratory distress in a CKD patient with vertebral osteomyelitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-deep targeted next-generation sequencing with peripheral blood in patients with vascular malformations: a cohort of 40 patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Liquid biopsy of cfDNA from the peripheral blood enables safe, outpatient-compatible molecular diagnosis, to potentially guide tailored treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A rare case of idiopathic gastric rupture in an elderly female]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hospital procedural costs of surgical aortic valve replacement versus transcatheter aortic valve replacement in low-risk isolated aortic stenosis: a single-center analysis in japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this cohort of low-risk patients with AS in Japan, TAVR was associated with significantly higher in-hospital costs than SAVR, despite shorter postoperative stay.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CT findings of lung injury during breast cancer treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While breast cancer treatment outcomes have improved significantly through multidisciplinary approaches including surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation therapy, the incidence of non-neoplastic pulmonary complications has also increased. Accurate interpretation of chest imaging is essential for managing these adverse events. This review outlines the major radiological findings of pulmonary injury during breast cancer treatment, focusing on two primary categories: drug-associated interstitial lung...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between embolic agent choice and complications after transcatheter arterial embolization for colonic diverticular bleeding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared with coils, GS particles were associated with an increase in both early rebleeding and intestinal ischemia, whereas NBCA was associated with decreased rebleeding and increased ischemia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Th7R predicts chemo-immunotherapy response and survival in small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Th7R is a novel Th1-like CD4^(+) T cell lineage characterized by TCF7 and IL-7 receptor expression, exhibiting distinct transcriptional and epigenetic profiles compared with classical Th1 cells. The clinical significance of Th7R, including the efficacy of immune checkpoint inhibitors and the prediction of postoperative disease-free survival, has been demonstrated in non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) but not in small cell lung cancer (SCLC). In this study, we investigated Th7R expression as a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of an acute inhalation toxicity testing method based on a lung-on-a-chip]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To date, no in vitro test methods for acute inhalation toxicity have been adopted under the OECD Test Guidelines. One major challenge is the difficulty in mimicking the complex physiological and biomechanical environment of the human lung in vitro. Microfluidics can be used to establish extracorporeal lung models with continuous fluid flow and gas exchange. In this study, we aimed to establish the optimal conditions for culturing cells on a lung-on-a-chip (LOC) to identify substances with acute...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of propranolol and its metabolites in postmortem human solid tissues and body fluids: LC-MS/MS approach with the standard addition method applied to a forensic case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A validated LC-MS/MS method for determining propranolol and its metabolites in forensic samples was established, and it could also be applied to the authentic human samples obtained from a propranolol poisoning case. The findings could offer substantial and reliable support for investigating propranolol-related fatalities and contribute to the comprehensive understanding of the metabolism of propranolol in the human body.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EXPRESS: Beyond Sodium Channel Blockade: Flavonoid as Alternative Local Anethetic Candidates of lidocaine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[When conventional drug-based Western medicine proves ineffective, complementary and alternative medicine (CAM), including herbal medicine and acupuncture, often gains prominence. Phytochemicals, plant-derived compounds synthesized for self-protection against environmental stressors like ultraviolet radiation and insects, have also shown numerous physiological benefits in humans. Among these, flavonoid compounds-abundant in fruits and vegetables-have garnered significant research interest due to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AD-related plasma biomarkers in centenarians: links to cognition and neuropathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Whether Alzheimer's disease (AD)-associated plasma biomarkers reflect cognitive performance and neuropathology in the oldest old remains unclear.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220023634&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>