<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:22:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive in silico analysis of Acinetobacter isolates from South Korea reveals genomic diversity, antimicrobial resistance, virulence factors, and evolutionary dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brentuximab vedotin combined with cisplatin, cytarabine, and dexamethasone treatment in transplant-eligible Korean patients with relapsed or refractory Hodgkin's lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite its encouraging early efficacy, the administration of BV-DHAP in Korean patients with RRHL requires careful monitoring due to toxicity concerns.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic substrate design for enhanced mechanical and optical stability in island-bridge stretchable displays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Island-bridge designs are regarded as promising platforms for stretchable displays, but their mechanical and optical reliability is limited by two distinct failure modes: interfacial delamination, driven by localized strain concentration due to mechanical mismatch, and the substrate sagging, resulting from insufficient elastic recovery after repeated stretching. In this study, an island-bridge stretchable display that incorporates a multi-covalently crosslinked polyurethane is presented, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Predictors of Malignancy in Main Duct-Involved IPMN: The Critical Role of MPD Diameter Changes in a Multicenter Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dynamic MPD monitoring is essential for assessing malignancy risk in patients with MPD-involved IPMN. An MPD growth rate of ≥ 2 mm/year was the strongest predictor of malignant transformation, underscoring the value of longitudinal surveillance over static MPD diameter thresholds. Patients with rapid MPD growth should be considered for early surgical intervention or intensified monitoring to improve clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of conserved residues essential for the ciliogenic functions of WDPCP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we report a genetically engineered mouse model expressing a mutant Wdpcp gene that harbors a deletion of two codons encoding D481 and W482 that correspond to N512 and W513 in human WDPCP. Homozygous mutant mice, designated as Wdpcp-Z11, exhibited severe developmental abnormalities, including neural tube defects, craniofacial malformation, anophthalmia and polydactyly. The mutant WDPCP protein was expressed but failed to dock to the apical surface of the cell. Cilia formation and Hh...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NDST3-Induced Epigenetic Reprogramming Reverses Neurodegeneration in Parkinson's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parkinson's disease (PD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder characterized by the loss of dopaminergic neurons (DN) in the substantia nigra and disruption of cellular maintenance. Here, we demonstrate that NDST3-mediated epigenetic reprogramming halts neuronal degeneration and restores motor function in an animal model of PD. Following NDST3 administration, the DN and its associated circuits in the substantia nigra and striatum showed marked revitalization, accompanied by a considerable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optically-Coupled X-Ray Computed Laminography System for High-Speed Inspection of Lithium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional X-ray computed tomography systems for microstructure inspection typically employ a geometrically magnified imaging setup, requiring a micro-focus X-ray source to mitigate image blurring caused by a finite focal spot size. However, due to its low output power, the micro-focus X-ray source results in prolonged image acquisition times. This study presents a novel optically-coupled X-ray computed laminography system for high-speed inspection. In the proposed system, a scintillator is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Policy Inaction Risks Breaching the 2°C Climate Target]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite repeated increases in national climate pledges since the Paris Agreement, a significant gap remains between collective ambition and the action required to meet its temperature goals. Integrating these pledges with global models, we show that full implementation would still lead to approximately 1.7°C of warming, missing the 1.5°C target. When considering ongoing policy inaction, a cumulative shortfall of 505 GtCO(2)e in anticipated mitigation is expected, and this warming increases by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the <em>Panax ginseng</em> Meyer soil metagenome to uncover antagonistic bacteria against ginseng root rot disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Bacillus velezensis ARRI17 is an effective biocontrol agent that promotes ginseng growth and enhances disease resistance. Its natural compatibility with traditional farming practices, especially its presence with rice straw compost, positions ARRI17 as a promising and sustainable alternative.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean red ginseng extract suppresses food allergy by remodeling the gut microbiota and restoring immune homeostasis in IL4ra<sup>F709</sup> mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: KRGE mitigates FA in IL4ra^(F709) mice by restoring gut microbiota balance and immune homeostasis, suggesting its potential as a microbiota-targeted intervention for FA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[pH-activated liquid microdroplet carrier for enhanced phycocyanin oral delivery and sustained bioactivity post-digestion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although C-phycocyanin (PC) possesses various therapeutic functions, it is highly unstable under gastrointestinal (GI) conditions involving digestive enzymes and pH variations, leading to rapid degradation and subsequent loss of bioactivity before absorption. A protective oral delivery system is therefore essential to enhance its bioavailability and delivery efficiency. In this study, a water-immiscible, pH-responsive microdroplet system was developed using fish gelatin (FG) and fucoidan (FC) as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of pexophagy by a novel TBK1-MARCHF7-PXMP4-NBR1 Axis in PEX1-depleted HeLa cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peroxisomes are essential for lipid metabolism and redox balance, with pexophagy playing a critical role in maintaining cellular homeostasis. However, the regulatory mechanisms of pexophagy remain unclear. Through functional screening, we identified MARCHF7 as a novel E3 ligase regulating pexophagy. MARCHF7 depletion impaired pexophagic flux under PEX1 knockdown conditions. MARCHF7 binds to PXMP4 and promotes its ubiquitination at lysine 20 in PEX1-deficient cells. Depletion of PXMP4 impairs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of photobiomodulation therapy for ophthalmic diseases: protocol for a systematic review and meta-analysis of disease-specific and shared physiological outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Photobiomodulation therapy (PBMT)-a noninvasive therapeutic strategy-employs low-level red or near-infrared light to regulate cellular bioenergetics, reduce oxidative stress, and modulate inflammation. It has demonstrated therapeutic potential for several ophthalmic diseases, including age-related macular degeneration, diabetic retinopathy, glaucoma, retinitis pigmentosa, and dry eye disease. However, the clinical evidence remains fragmented due to heterogeneity in study designs,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a health literacy-based hypertension self-management education program using sign language for Deaf individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The H-SMILE program is designed for Deaf individuals with hypertension and may be particularly beneficial for those with limited health literacy who use sign language. The program, validated by experts and evaluated in a pilot test showing high satisfaction scores and strong feasibility, appears to be a promising intervention with the potential to enhance health literacy, promote self-management behaviors, and improve health outcomes among Deaf individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automation of electrothermal cell sheet manipulator for seamless tissue assembly and handling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The manipulation of fragile biological tissues such as engineered cell sheets remains a major challenge for regenerative medicine and tissue engineering. Manual handling with tools like tweezers often induces wrinkling or tearing, compromising tissue integrity. Here, we present an automated cell sheet manipulator that integrates a thermoresponsive microchanneled poly(N-isopropylacrylamide) (PNIPAAm) hydrogel with an embedded microheater, mounted on a programmable three-axis motorized stage. Upon...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differences in symptom experiences and coping strategies based on post-traumatic growth and depreciation in cancer patients undergoing chemotherapy: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study highlights the importance of tailored psychological assessment for cancer patients. Understanding the distinct symptom experiences and coping strategies of different PTG-PTD clusters can guide the development of individualized nursing interventions that enhance patient well-being and recovery. Findings offer practical guidance for effective psychosocial support and holistic cancer care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-based exploration of volatile flavor diversity from food yeast species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Yeast shares a longer than 10 000-year history with humans in food fermentation by producing various volatile flavor compounds that contribute to the final taste and aroma of foods. Yeast-associated volatile flavor compounds include esters, benzenoids, sulfur compounds, and phenolic derivatives, and these enhance the sensory complexity of fermented foods and beverages. Genome-scale technologies have advanced and transformed our understanding of the genetic and evolutionary drivers of volatile...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia as a major comorbidity in late-onset epilepsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epilepsy is more common in the elderly population, with a higher prevalence of epilepsy-related neurological diseases, such as stroke and traumatic brain injury. Although dementia is also known to be a potential cause of epilepsy in the elderly, estimating its accurate contribution is challenging because of its high prevalence in the general elderly population. To characterize the clinical features of patients with comorbid dementia, we compared the characteristics of these patients with those...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obesity phenotypes and atherogenic dyslipidemias]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Atherogenic dyslipidemias are a hallmark of high-risk obesity phenotypes and a major contributor to ASCVD within the CKM framework. Precision medicine approaches that incorporate obesity phenotyping, targeted treatment strategies and population-level interventions are needed to reduce the burden of dyslipidemias and their cardiovascular sequelae.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Two Synthetic Routes to a Benzofuran Intermediate for Fruquintinib]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two practical routes were developed for the synthesis of a key benzofuran intermediate used to prepare fruquintinib, both of which commence from readily available monoprotected resorcinol derivatives. The first route involves constructing a 2-methylbenzofuran-3-carboxylic acid core from 2-bromo-5-methoxyphenol and a 2-butynoic acid derivative using Michael addition chemistry, followed by intramolecular Heck cyclization. Final deprotection afforded the benzofuran intermediate in 45% overall yield...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxygen-free discontinuous dewetting in a degassed mold for anisotropic colloidal hydrogel microparticle synthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anisotropic colloidal hydrogel microparticles offer unique advantages owing to their shape-dependent interactions, and enhanced diffusion and reaction kinetics, which is favorable in solution-based processes. However, their fabrication remains difficult, mainly due to limitations of surface energy and oxygen inhibition. In this study, we present a versatile synthesis platform for anisotropic colloidal hydrogel microparticles using oxygen-free discontinuous dewetting in a degassed mold. By a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Noise Suppression in Organic Photodiodes: A Comprehensive Review of Mechanistic Insights and Design Principles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic photodiodes (OPDs) are emerging as leading candidates for next-generation image sensors owing to their tunable photophysical properties, which enable broadband detection from the visible to X-ray regimes and open new possibilities for intelligent systems such as fingerprint sensing, gesture recognition, and medical imaging. Across these applications, minimizing the dark current density (J(d)) is of paramount importance, as it sets the noise floor, while thermal and low-frequency noises...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Datopotamab deruxtecan versus docetaxel for non-small cell lung cancer: a plain language summary of the TROPION-Lung01 study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Disease Distribution Matters for PCI Outcomes: Lessons From PPG-Based Prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Net Water Uptake With Catastrophic Functional Outcome After Thrombectomy in Patients With Large Infarcts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Elevated ASPECTS10-NWU is strongly associated with catastrophic functional outcome in patients with large infarcts treated with endovascular thrombectomy. Integrating the ASPECTS10-NWU with clinical variables may provide patient-specific prognostication that may assist clinicians in decision-making for endovascular thrombectomy in large infarcts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six Unrecorded Species of Polyporales (Agaricomycetes, Basidiomycota) from Mudeungsan National Park in Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The order Polyporales is a diverse group of macrofungi, comprising approximately 2500 species worldwide. The majority of these species are wood-decaying saprotrophs that contribute to the carbon cycle by degrading lignin, cellulose, and hemicellulose. They also produce valuable enzymes with wide industrial applications. Despite their ecological and industrial importance, the diversity of Polyporales in Republic of Korea remains relatively understudied compared to the global scale. Mudeungsan, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptomic analysis of skin biopsies in Prurigo nodularis patients: with and without atopic dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results provide insight into the molecular mechanisms of PN, particularly in the context of atopic dermatitis, and highlight that immune dysregulation and impaired skin barrier function are key factors in pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Prospective Cohort Study on the Usage, Safety, and Efficacy of Delamanid in Patients With Pulmonary Multidrug-Resistant Tuberculosis in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Delamanid demonstrated favorable safety and efficacy profiles for MDR-TB treatment under programmatic conditions, providing valuable and up-to-date evidence supporting its promising role in MDR-TB management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive review of the effects of <em>Panax ginseng</em> and its constituents against inflammatory diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unresolved inflammation can progress into severe diseases that need safer and more effective therapeutic strategies. The adverse effects of conventional anti-inflammatory agents have evoked interest in natural products as alternatives. Panax ginseng is a traditional medical herb famous for its diverse pharmacological properties. This review comprehensively discusses the anti-inflammatory effects of P. ginseng and its constituents against inflammatory bowel disease, hepatitis, sepsis, gastritis,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetics and pharmacological activities of protopanaxatriol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protopanaxatriol (PPT) is an active metabolite derived from protopanaxatriol-type ginsenosides from Panax ginseng, displaying broad range of pharmacological activities against various diseases with higher efficacy. Since ginsenosides are known to be active components from ginseng, exploring biological activities and functions of the components could be important in terms of understanding ginseng's pharmacological roles. In this review, we aimed to report biological role of PPT by analyzing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of white ginseng on reducing stress and tension by enhancing default mode network connectivity: A randomized, double-blinded placebo-controlled clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings of this study suggest that PGC has the potential to mitigate stress and tension, potentially through the modulation of DMN functional connectivity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean red ginseng mitigates pulmonary injury and enhances antiviral immunity in a low-dose pseudo-type SARS-CoV-2 infection model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Korean red ginseng modulates immune responses and promotes long-term immunity against low-dose PSV infection. Our data also support the potential of Korean red ginseng as a complementary therapeutic strategy for COVID-19 and an enhancer of vaccine efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of the MIND Diet on the Cognitive Function of Older Adults: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Mediterranean-DASH Intervention for Neurodegenerative Delay (MIND) diet is a brain-focused dietary pattern designed to prevent cognitive decline in older adults. This systematic review, conducted in accordance with Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses guidelines, aimed to examine the association between the MIND diet and cognitive function in older adults. Relevant studies published between 2015 and 2024 were identified through comprehensive searches of PubMed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Impact of Nutritional Intervention on Pressure Injury Healing in a Paraplegic Patient: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pressure injuries are common complications in patients with limited mobility, particularly those who are bedridden. These wounds not only cause pain and reduce quality of life but also lead to prolonged hospitalization, increased risk of infection, and higher healthcare costs. Among the various contributing factors, malnutrition plays a crucial role by impairing collagen synthesis, weakening immune function, and delaying tissue repair. Adequate nutritional support-particularly sufficient protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Secular Trends in Dietary Patterns Among Korean Adolescents: Using Data From the 2007-2022 Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to identify major dietary patterns among Korean adolescents, examine their changes over the past 16 years, and evaluate differences by sex. Data were analyzed from 7,679 adolescents aged 12-18 years who participated in the 2007-2022 Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey and completed health, examination, and nutrition surveys. Dietary intake was assessed using a 24-hour recall, and cluster analysis was performed based on the energy contribution of 26 food...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unstable occult scaphoid fracture diagnosed by dynamic point-of-care ultrasound: a case report and review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case report highlights the pivotal role of dynamic musculoskeletal ultrasound as an adjunct in the diagnostic algorithm for acute wrist trauma. It demonstrates its ability not only to identify a radiographically occult scaphoid fracture but, more critically, to provide immediate functional information about mechanical stability. This information is paramount for guiding appropriate and timely management to mitigate the risk of long-term complications. We advocate for the broader...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing musical creativity through AI: a chain-mediation model of self-efficacy and emotional intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The rapid advancement of AI technology is fundamentally transforming traditional music creation and influencing music education. However, whether and how the use of AI genuinely enhances musical creativity remains a subject for further exploration. This study aims to investigate the impact of AI usage on the musical creativity of music majors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[of Asia: Provision of Patient-Centered Care in Oral Cavity Cancer: A Qualitative Study With Patients, Caregivers, and Healthcare Professionals in Five Asia-Pacific Regions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study examined LA-OCSCC care management in five Asia-Pacific countries/territories with varying healthcare systems and infrastructure. Given LA-OCSCC's aggressive nature and high burden from disease and treatment, patients and caregivers require support beyond medical interventions. A multi-stakeholder approach with clinical and community care is essential to ensure a comprehensive and sustainable approach to patient-centered care within the different health systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triple Amperometric Microsensor for Simultaneous Real-Time In Vivo Monitoring of NO, CO, and H<sub>2</sub>S During Epileptic Seizures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitric oxide (NO), carbon monoxide (CO), and hydrogen sulfide (H(2)S) are endogenous gaseous signaling molecules, playing crucial roles in a wide range of biological processes. This study presents the fabrication and evaluation of a triple amperometric microsensor capable of the simultaneous and selective detection of NO, CO, and H(2)S for in vivo applications. The sensor integrates three platinum working electrodes into a single device. Each electrode was independently modified with specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Ultrasound-guided Superficial Cervical Plexus Block on Early Postoperative Recovery in Patients Undergoing Microvascular Decompression: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Superficial CPB did not improve early postoperative QoR in patients undergoing MVD. However, it reduced the incidence of PONV during the early postoperative period, which could potentially enhance patient comfort and satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Influencing Cultural Intelligence Among Nurses in Western Pacific Countries: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings emphasize the need for healthcare institutions to implement structured educational programs to enhance nurses' cultural intelligence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: 2025 position statement on active outdoor play]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Readability and information quality of LLM-Generated HIV content: a methodological content evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41266988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41266988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between psychological disorders and migraine in young U.S. adults with gender-specific analysis and marital status considerations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41266965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights distinct gender-based psychological correlates of migraine and reveals the social context of marital status as a potential modifier. These findings underscore the need for sex-sensitive and psychosocially informed strategies in migraine assessment and intervention, aligning with biopsychosocial models of pain and the goals of integrated headache care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41266965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of spontaneous regression of primary hepatic diffuse large B-cell lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a rare case of spontaneous regression of primary hepatic diffuse large B-cell lymphoma (DLBCL) in an 89-year-old man. A 12 cm solitary hepatic mass was found in the anterior and medial segments. Contrast-enhanced CT showed a hypovascular solid tumor. Serologic markers including hepatitis B virus, hepatitis C virus, human immunodeficiency virus, alpha-fetoprotein, protein induced by vitamin K absence or antagonist-II, carbohydrate antigen 19-9, and carcinoembryonic antigen were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uterus transplants or surrogacy? Exploring the ethics of assisted gestation through incentivization and compensation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of Adult Stem Cell-Derived Organoid Cultures: General Principles from the Mouse Gut]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adult stem cell (ASC)-derived organoid cultures have become an important model system for studying mammalian epithelial tissues in health and disease, including autoimmune conditions. Somatic stem cells are isolated and embedded into basement membrane-like matrix to allow for the in vitro outgrowth of miniature versions of functional epithelium in the presence of supportive growth factor niche. Organoids derived from tissues affected by autoimmune diseases, such as the intestine in inflammatory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recognizing the importance of papers on sustainable radiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surgical outcomes of lung cancer associated with autoimmune disease-related interstitial pneumonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Lung cancer with AD-IP had a poor prognosis, as did lung cancer with IIP, and the frequency of postoperative AE of patients with AD-IP was as high as that in those with IIP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances of cell therapies for AML/MDS: exploring the therapeutic potential of innate immune cells in AML/MDS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immunotherapy has revolutionized cancer treatments, yet checkpoint inhibitors and CAR-T cells have shown limited efficacy in acute myeloid leukemia (AML) and myelodysplastic syndromes (MDS). This limited efficacy is primarily due to the absence of lineage-specific antigens and the presence of suppressive microenvironments. Innate immunity offers a promising alternative, as it acts independently of neoantigens. The key players such as macrophages, dendritic cells, and natural killer (NK) cells...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of host and gut microbiota-altering interventions on sarcopenia or its defining parameters: a systematic review and meta-analysis of nutrition-based intervention studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Specific diets and probiotics offer potential to improve sarcopenia parameters.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Spirometric Lung Age with Survival Outcomes in Elderly Patients Undergoing Radical Surgery for Gastric Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The discrepancy between lung and chronological age may serve as a useful predictor of long-term outcomes, particularly non-GC-related mortality, in elderly patients undergoing curative gastrectomy. This metric may support risk stratification and inform surgical strategies in this vulnerable population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical characteristics and management of dupilumab-associated ocular surface disease in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dupilumab-associated ocular surface disease (DAOSD) is one of the most common adverse events associated with dupilumab (an anti-interleukin-4-receptor-alpha monoclonal antibody) during the treatment of patients with atopic dermatitis (AD). However, it rarely occurs in patients with bronchial asthma or chronic rhinosinusitis with nasal polyps. Adequate understanding of DAOSD is important for proper diagnosis and appropriate ophthalmic intervention. The aim of this review was to summarize and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Involvement of best-corrected visual acuity in sarcopenia: findings from baseline analysis of the Kyotango longevity cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates a significant relationship between lower visual acuity and sarcopenia. These findings support maintaining visual acuity to prevent age-related decline of physical functions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proton Pump Inhibitors Attenuate the Effectiveness of Nivolumab Monotherapy in Patients with Advanced Gastric Cancer: A Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Concomitant use of PPI may reduce the effectiveness of nivolumab in patients with advanced gastric cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seasonal variation in bacterial community composition in the brackish meromictic Lake Suigetsu]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lake Suigetsu, a deep meromictic lake connected to Wakasa Bay, receives freshwater inflow and exchange surface water with intruding seawater. To investigate bacterial community dynamics and substrate transport, we conducted seasonal 16S rRNA gene sequencing across three stratified layers (mixolimnion, chemocline, and monimolimnion) and two size fractions (0.2-0.8 µm for free-living; 0.8-3.0 µm for particle-attached). Community composition differed by depth, fraction, and season. Winter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of orthodontic treatment on front teeth with prior history of dental injury: a 4-year follow up]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION AND CLINICAL RELEVANCE: Injured front teeth are more prone to pulpal complications and RR than those without trauma. Long courses of treatment should be avoided, especially in severe injuries. Incisor extraction led to significantly worse gingival esthetic outcomes, although this didn't influence patient satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Technical note: Quantitative and qualitative analysis of diatom testing in methomyl poisoning case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diatom testing is conducted in forensic medicine primarily to support the diagnosis of drowning. In our previous study, a large number of diatoms, potentially originating from methomyl, were detected in the lungs of a cat found dead under circumstances suggestive of methomyl poisoning, but not involving drowning or submersion. In the present study, we collected human and animal cases suspected of methomyl poisoning, where the bodies showed no evidence of drowning or submersion. Diatom tests were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Speeding up, not slowing down, decreases the metabolic energy needed to stabilize walking in the sagittal plane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is a metabolic cost associated with stabilizing walking, but it remains unclear to what extent stabilizing walking in the sagittal plane contributes to this cost. Furthermore, strategies for stabilizing walking in the sagittal plane vary with speed, but it is unclear whether this also leads to a speed-dependent metabolic cost of stabilizing walking. Here, we explored the metabolic cost of stabilizing walking in the sagittal plane across speeds and its relationship with control strategies....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting Report on the 1st GlyCosmos Symposium &amp; Jamboree -Community-Driven Expansion of Glycan-Binding Molecules Resources]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world outcomes of anthracycline and taxane-based perioperative breast cancer therapy using the Japanese electronic medical record database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RDI was high in all groups. Clinicians should be cautious when administering AC q3w therapy owing to the high likelihood of patients developing Grade 4 neutropenia. For TC, a slightly lower pegfilgrastim administration rate and >20% Grade 4 neutropenia suggest the need for appropriate pegfilgrastim use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Herbicidal Pyridazinone Cyclic Keto-Enol Compounds Inhibit Acetyl-CoA Carboxylase and Homogentisate Solanesyltransferase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Novel aryl cyclic keto-enol (aryl-CKE) derivatives containing a pyridazinone moiety (5-hydroxy-4-phenyl-3(2H)-pyridazinone) exhibit distinct herbicidal symptoms on grass and broadleaf weeds. Herbicide efficacy tests on target-site resistant blackgrass and enzyme inhibition assays revealed that the herbicidal activity in grassy weeds was primarily attributed to ACCase inhibition. The bleaching effect of the representative compounds on broadleaf plants was initially hypothesized to result from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Decade of Mitochondria-Targeting Drugs in Cancer Treatment: Case Review on Mitochondria-Targeting Curcumin or Mitocurcumin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondrial targeting is of particular interest to researchers, as it presents as a personalized medicine approach in cancer cell metabolism and survival. By specifically targeting mitochondria, targeted therapies can disrupt energy production, induce apoptosis, and overcome drug resistance in cancer cells, potentially improving therapeutic outcomes. This review discusses the advancements in mitochondrial drug delivery over the last decade. It explores the potential of mitochondrial targeting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystal Structure of a GDP-bound Bombyx mori RabX6]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rab GTPases are molecular switches that control intracellular vesicular transport by cycling between GDP- and GTP-bound states. Insects encode an insect-specific subset, RabX; Bombyx mori RabX6 (BmRabX6) has been implicated in testis development and neuropeptide secretion, but its structure and mechanism were unknown. Here we report the 3.1 Å crystal structure of BmRabX6 in complex with GDP and Mg2+ (PDB: 9VLB), the first structure of an insect-specific Rab GTPase. BmRabX6 adopts the canonical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative glycomic analysis of Mimiviridae and Marseilleviridae uncovers host-related and lineage-specific glycosylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Giant viruses encode unusual glycosylation machinery distinct from their amoebal hosts, raising fundamental questions about how their glycans are synthesized and diversified. Here we present a comparative glycomic analysis of mimivirus, tokyovirus, and hokutovirus, together with their common host Acanthamoeba castellanii. The main objective of this study was to determine whether giant viruses rely on host-derived N-glycosylation, or alternatively employ virus-encoded pathways to generate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Insights into the Essentiality of Core Autophagy Factors Revealed by Comprehensive Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autophagy is a conserved degradation process delivering intracellular components to lysosomes or vacuoles. Yeast studies have been pivotal in identifying autophagy-related (ATG) genes and defining the core machinery essential for autophagosome formation. A recent comprehensive analysis that systematically examined all atg mutants in S. cerevisiae under autophagy-inducing conditions revealed that mutants lacking Atg13, Atg8-conjugation, or Atg12-conjugation components retain partial activity in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antidepressant-like and neuroprotective effects of pine needle extracts: evidence from behavioral, transcriptomic, and biochemical studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroinflammation is a key characteristic associated with neurological disorders, particularly depression and anxiety. This study aims to evaluate the neuroprotective and antidepressant-like effects of pine needle (PN) extracts in an LPS-induced neuroinflammation mouse model. Following seven days of oral administration of PN, the tail suspension test demonstrated a significant reduction in immobility time in PN-treated mice compared to LPS controls, surpassing the effect of the standard...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spermatocyte injection into meiotic oocytes rescues diplotene, but not pachytene, arrest in azoospermic mutant mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[STUDY QUESTION: At which arrest stage can spermatocytes be rescued by injection into meiotic oocytes?]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41268068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Case of Adrenocorticotropin-dependent Cushing Syndrome with Osilodrostat Exposure in Early Pregnancy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osilodrostat is a novel treatment for adrenocorticotropin-dependent Cushing syndrome; however, its safety during pregnancy has not been reported. This case involves a patient with Cushing disease who became pregnant while on osilodrostat. She was diagnosed at 31 years of age and underwent pituitary tumor removal. After a relapse at 35 years of age, she was initially treated with metyrapone but switched to osilodrostat and hydrocortisone because of nausea, achieving reasonable cortisol control....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of prior chemotherapy on nanoliposomal irinotecan with fluorouracil and folinic acid for unresectable pancreatic cancer: a retrospective analysis of data from the multicenter NAPOLEON-2 study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: NFF may be effective and tolerable, even in patients previously treated with irinotecan-, fluorouracil-, or platinum-based chemotherapy, in the real world.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel Interference-Based Supercritical Angle Fluorescence Biosensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Supercritical angle fluorescence (SAF) is a near-field collection technique used to create surface-sensitive optical transducers. While SAF biosensors require simpler excitation optics compared with total internal reflection fluorescence (TIRF)-based systems, they rely on complex fluorescence collection setups involving large, expensive microscopes to achieve similar sensitivities. In this article, we present a novel interference-based SAF transducer that leverages complementary metal oxide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decline in Human T-Cell Leukemia Virus Type 1 Pregnant Carriers and Emerging Concerns About Horizontal Transmission: A Nationwide Survey in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The prevalence of HTLV-1 among pregnant women in Japan has declined, largely due to effective mother-to-child transmission prevention implemented mainly in HTLV-1 high-prevalence areas. However, horizontal transmission accounts for a notable percentage of cases, highlighting the need to reinforce preventive education and strategies targeting sexual transmission and unsafe medical or cosmetic practices alongside continued perinatal screening and counseling.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Membrane Constriction by Dynamin through GTP-Driven Conformational Changes from Coarse-Grained Molecular Dynamics Simulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dynamin, a GTPase involved in membrane remodeling processes, plays a pivotal role in membrane fission during endocytosis. Understanding the molecular mechanisms of dynamin assembly and its conformational change triggered by GTP hydrolysis on lipid membranes is crucial for elucidating the intricate details of membrane constriction and fission events. However, the size and complexity of the dynamin assembly prevent us from obtaining comprehensive molecular mechanisms. In this study, we performed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvation Entropy as a Lever for Steering the Macroscopic Properties of a Functional Supramolecular Helical Polymer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solvent-solute interactions are utterly important in supramolecular polymers (SPs), yet the high responsivity of SPs to solvent polarity makes it challenging to play on other solvation effects to tune their macroscopic properties in a rational manner. Herein, we report the characterization at various scales of the assembly properties of a C(2)-symmetric benzene-1,3,5-tricarboxamide monomer with two (1S)-methylheptyl moieties and one diphenylphosphino group as lateral chains. Our investigation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of stability and hydrogel properties of type-A gelatin-dextran mixtures via incorporation of whey protein isolate fibrils]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The stability of water-in-water (W/W) emulsions is a hot research topic in food science due to its profound impact on texture and shelf-life of food systems. Recently, the incorporation of protein nanoparticles has emerged as an effective strategy to improve the W/W emulsions stability. However, the effects of such nanoparticle addition on properties of phase-separated hydrogels remained largely unexplored. This work investigated the effects of whey protein isolate fibrils (WPIF) on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-modal spicy enhancement with odour and electrical tongue stimulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spicy substances like chili pepper and wasabi can have both beneficial and adverse effects on human health. In particular, they may help to reduce salt intake and limit fat absorption, when consumed in appropriate amounts. However, excessive consumption of spicy foods could increase the desire for more intense spiciness, potentially leading to overconsumption. To address the challenge of balancing the amount of spicy substances in food and the desired level of perceived spiciness, electrical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbial and seminal traces of sexual intercourse and forensic implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Taken together, this study revealed that the vaginal microbiome is better at predicting recent sexual intercourse, while the victim's underwear has a clear value as additional biological trace evidence for semen detection. These findings are particularly useful in cases with delayed reporting and are obtained with less invasive sampling. Video Abstract.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can public-domain datasets be leveraged to identify factors associated with the occurrence of African swine fever in europe?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The model showed high accuracy for ASF prediction in domestic pigs but low accuracy for wild boars, highlighting the limitations of public domain (a)biotic factors alone. Integrating restricted data on animal movements, migration, and carcass interactions could enhance future predictions and improve disease control strategies. The change in spatial resolution did not affect the associations between (a)biotic factors and ASF occurrence in wild boars but reduced the number of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A quarter of young Japanese women are underweight: thin-ideal internalization and self-esteem mediate exercise habits and body satisfaction, but different mechanisms with normal-range weight]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results highlight that the pathways through which exercise habits affect body satisfaction differ according to body mass index. For underweight women, reducing thin-ideal internalization and enhancing self-esteem through exercise habits is crucial. In contrast, interventions directly boosting self-esteem may be more effective for women with normal-range weight. These findings clarify the distinct roles of exercise habits in influencing body satisfaction for underweight and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41267007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Considerations for Patient Privacy of Large Language Models in Health Care: Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We propose comprehensive recommendations across 3 phases-study design, implementation, and reporting-to strengthen patient privacy protection and transparency in PHI-LLM. This study emphasizes the urgent need for the development of stricter regulatory frameworks and the adoption of advanced privacy protection technologies to effectively safeguard PHI. It is anticipated that future applications of LLMs in the health care field will achieve a balance between innovation and robust...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioinspired Cascade-Catalytic Scaffold to Prevent Adverse Remodeling of Heart Valve under Pathological Conditions via Conversion of •O<sub>2</sub><sup>-</sup> into NO]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In situ tissue-engineered heart valves (TEHVs) face significant challenges in patients with compromised endogenous repair capacity, particularly those with diabetic comorbidities. To address this issue, we developed a bimetallic nanozyme-functionalized scaffold capable of restoring •O(2)^(-)/NO homeostasis through a bioinspired cascade catalytic reaction that modulates the adverse repair microenvironment. The nanozyme, composed of polyphenol-coordinated iridium (Ir)/ruthenium (Ru), exhibited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adaptation and validation of the Chinese version of the Fear of Alzheimer's Disease Scale]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study confirms the FADS as a valid and reliable instrument to assess dementia-related fear among middle-aged and older adults in the Chinese population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neonatal hyperoxia exposure does not exacerbate hypertension programmed by maternal obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maternal obesity increases risk of preterm delivery and rapid transition of offspring from hypoxemic environment to a normal or elevated oxygen environment, especially if the baby receives oxygen therapy. Maternal obesity may also increase offspring risk of developing hypertension. Thus, we examined whether neonatal hyperoxia (HO) leads to elevated blood pressure (BP) in offspring from lean mothers and exacerbates adverse impact of maternal obesity on offspring BP regulation. Male and female...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Methadone Use for Pain and Opioid Use Disorder Among Medicaid Enrollees]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Enduring Impact of the National Institute of Nursing Research and Why We Still Need It]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective Whole-Genome Sequencing to Identify Bacterial Transmission and Its Modifiers in Neonates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This cohort study involving infants in the NICU suggests that bacterial sequencing can accurately detect bacterial transmission events. Multivariate analysis suggests that the bacterial transmission risk on a NICU can be modified.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Walking Aids and Locomotion Training in the Emergency Department: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this randomized clinical trial, training and provision of walking aids for older adults in the ED improved mobility and fear of falling as long as 90 days after discharge. The addition of telemonitoring did not result in additional benefits. This study highlights the role of a specialized physiotherapy intervention to optimize outcomes in older adults in the ED.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive Outcomes of Children Exposed to Selective Serotonin Reuptake Inhibitors Through Breast Milk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study including children prenatally exposed to SSRIs, additional exposure to SSRIs through breastfeeding was not associated with reduced IQ scores. Although measures of performance other than IQ were not evaluated, these findings suggest that breastfeeding can be encouraged during treatment with SSRIs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alzheimer Disease Blood Biomarker Concentrations Across Race and Ethnicity Groups in Middle-Aged Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort of middle-aged adults, the use of appropriate statistical estimation to ensure population representation indicated that blood-based AD biomarker concentrations were not distinguishable among race and ethnicity groups. Common medical conditions were associated with plasma biomarker concentrations similarly across race and ethnicity groups. These results highlight the importance of considering population representation and comorbid conditions in AD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling Photoprotection of Ultraviolet C Radiation by Ferric Ions and Implications for the Habitability of Ancient Martian Lakes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[On Mars, the amount of ultraviolet C (UVC) radiation that reaches the surface is sufficiently deleterious for life as we know it. However, it has been predicted that some ancient lakes on Mars had high concentrations of Fe^(3+), an ionic species known for a high absorption of UVC radiation. Some models of UV attenuation have already been established; however, there is a lack of reliable simulations that make the connection between this radiation absorption in an aqueous medium and its impact on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A transdiagnostic structural brain signature of Parkinsonian and Essential Tremor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parkinson's disease (PD) and Essential Tremor (ET) are heterogeneous, yet distinct disorders. At the same time, PD and ET show overlapping features such as tremor-predominant phenotypes. These heterogeneities and overlaps pose challenges for clinical management and research and may indicate shared, transdiagnostic mechanisms of tremor. We hypothesized that MRI-derived volumetric differences relate to tremor phenotypes rather than diagnostic labels. We compared regional brain volumes among three...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delirium: a modifiable risk factor for dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: As of yet, ample evidence exists that delirium is an independent modifiable risk factor for dementia. More research is needed to further elucidate neurobiological and protective mechanisms underlying this association.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-rate trickling filter with natural ventilation: diagnosis in a full-scale WWTP set in southern Brazil]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The upflow anaerobic sludge blanket (UASB) reactor effectively removes organic matter from wastewater but does not remove ammoniacal nitrogen, which harms aquatic life in water bodies when in excess. The trickling filter (TF) has been used in Brazil mainly as post-treatment of anaerobic effluents to remove organic carbon and residual solids. Information on N-ammonium removal in UASB-low-rate TF systems at full treatment scale is scarce. Therefore, this work aims to evaluate the performance of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical components of electric vehicle and internal combustion engine vehicle fire smoke and their mutagenic effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lithium-ion (Li-ion) batteries have become the primary power source for electric vehicles (EVs) around the world. However, this technology comes with important risks during EV fires if the batteries are damaged, improperly overcharged, or overheated, leading to intense heat and considerable amounts of smoke, which may have different properties than those from fires in internal combustion engine vehicles (ICEVs). Chemical components of smoke emissions from EV fires and their potential health...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in adamantane-linked heterocycles: synthesis and biological activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Last decade grabbed tremendous scientific attention towards the novel synthetic strategies for the synthesis and derivatization of adamantane core. Adamantane, owing to its unique chemical structure and high biological activity, has always been a subject of perpetual interest for medicinal chemists. The current review deals with the elucidation of the traditional and conventional methods as well as the application of novel methodologies for synthesizing the adamantane derivatives incorporating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nitroquinolones and nitroquinolines: syntheses and antitrypanosomal activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitroaromatic small molecules are established anti-infectives, including against trypanosomal diseases. Inspired by our previously identified suicide inhibitors of Mycobacterium tuberculosis (Mtb) decaprenylphosphoryl-β-d-ribose 2'-epimerase (DprE1), we report the synthesis and in vitro antitrypanosomal activity of six novel nitroquinoline derivatives (4a-4f), as well as the antitrypanosomal activity of 13 previously described nitroquinolone anti-Mtb compounds, 8a-8 m. Two compounds exhibited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovering the world's most endangered great whale species did not advance an issue-attention cycle in news media: Implications for Rice's whale conservation and management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Issue-attention cycles (IACs) follow the predictable rise and fall of media and public attention to topics through five defined stages. Using content analysis and critical discourse analysis, we analyzed 35 newspaper texts (2021-2024) about the Rice's whale, a newly discovered and Critically Endangered species exclusive to the Gulf of Mexico. We investigated whether this discovery was enough to advance an IAC and found that, while Rice's whale science, conservation, and policy has the elements...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Puerarin Regulates Gut Homeostasis in T2DM Rats Involving Structural and Functional Alterations of Gut Microbiota and Paneth Cell Function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Puerarin administration significantly ameliorates glucose metabolism, modulates gut microbiota toward a beneficial profile, and improves Paneth cell function and epithelial integrity in T2DM rats. These findings highlight puerarin's potential as a multi-target therapeutic agent for T2DM by modulating the gut-pancreas-immune axis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Macrophage Cell Culture and Characterization by Serum Human AB in Health and Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This chapter focuses on generating macrophages from monocytes and highlights their crucial role in the immune system, particularly their involvement in the pathogenesis of rheumatoid arthritis (RA), the most frequent systemic autoimmune disease. It addresses the limitations of traditional in vitro models, which often rely on high-dose cytokines, and introduces human AB serum as a more physiological option for monocyte-to-macrophage differentiation. Monocyte-derived macrophages (MDMs) by SAB are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[T Cell Antigen Discovery Using Cell-Based Epitope Libraries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[T cells carry out their functions by specifically recognizing antigens through their T cell receptors (TCRs), making the identification of TCR specificities crucial for understanding health and disease. Over the past decade, several antigen discovery methods have been developed to deconvolute TCRs. Our laboratory has established a cell-based antigen discovery platform based on chimeric receptors termed "SABRs" (Signaling and Antigen-presenting Bifunctional Receptors). SABRs are extracellular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biosimilar Uptake in Spain from 2016 to 2023: Analysis Based on Official Data Collection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Even though the use of biosimilar medicines is increasing across European countries, detailed and regularly published official data on biosimilar uptake are not publicly available except in Italy and Portugal. The main objective of this study was to provide a nationwide assessment of biosimilar consumption and uptake patterns in Spain between 2016 and 2023. Data were provided by the Ministry of Health and included the defined daily dose (DDD) of biosimilars (N = 17) dispensed through both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-omics strategies for biomarker discovery and application in personalized oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multi-omics strategies, integrating genomics, transcriptomics, proteomics, and metabolomics, have revolutionized biomarker discovery and enabled novel applications in personalized oncology. Despite rapid technological developments, a comprehensive synthesis addressing integration strategies, analytical workflows, and translational applications has been lacking. This review presents a comprehensive framework of multi-omics integration, encompassing workflows, analytical techniques, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiology of Invasive Escherichia coli Disease in Adults Using Routine Healthcare Records from the United States, 2002-2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These observations demonstrate that IED is a substantial and growing global health concern that disproportionally affects older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services Screening Mandate on Inpatient Z-Code Documentation of Social Drivers of Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tocilizumab as a treatment tool for ROSAH syndrome: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Tocilizumab showed significant anatomical benefit in this ROSAH syndrome patient, suggesting a role for IL-6 in disease pathophysiology. Although vision could not be restored, the response supports the use of targeted biologics in managing ROSAH. Broader clinical studies are needed to confirm efficacy. This case also highlights the importance of including ALPK1 in genetic panels for optic neuropathies, retinal disorders, and unexplained arthropathies to improve diagnosis and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methylprednisolone Restores Cognitive Impairment in mdx Mice by Inhibiting NF-κB/CCL5-mediated Neuroinflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Duchenne muscular dystrophy (DMD) is an X-linked recessive hereditary neuromuscular disease. In addition to movement disorders such as muscle weakness, it can also show varying degrees of cognitive impairment and behavioral problems. While glucocorticoids are the first-line treatment for DMD, their effects on cognitive function remain unclear. This study aims to investigate whether glucocorticoid therapy can improve cognitive impairments in DMD and to explore the potential underlying mechanisms....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbon market price prediction in the Yangtze River Basin based on improved deep learning ensemble model with CEEMDAN and Attention-RNN]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate carbon price prediction can help the government establish an effective and stable carbon trading market mechanism, which researchers are increasingly focusing on. However, much research on carbon price prediction has ignored the impacts of multiple factors on the carbon price. A novel ensemble deep learning prediction model, termed CEEMDAN-Attention-RNN, which considers multiple influencing factors, has been proposed to improve the accuracy of carbon price prediction. Firstly, raw data...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surface Problem: Unveiling Extracellular Vesicles Surface Markers and Their Implications for Central Nervous System Diseases' Diagnosis and Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles (EVs) are a broad category of small vesicles released by cells in the central nervous system (CNS) that facilitate intercellular communication and contribute to various diseases. In neuroscience, one of the most important and well-characterized EV subtypes is exosomes. However, current issues with EV nomenclature make it difficult to draw firm conclusions due to variability in usage across different studies. One solution to overcome this challenge is to use established...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining the Integration of Biofeedback Treatment in Inpatient Mental Health Care, Specialized in Psychosomatic Medicine and Psychotherapy: A Mixed Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although biofeedback (BFB) treatment has been well researched for different outpatient settings, relatively little information exists on the implementation process or the difficulties of applying this form of therapy in an inpatient setting. This study, therefore, focuses on the implementation of BFB in the inpatient setting and the potential barriers to its implementation and use. A mixed methods approach was chosen. Medical professionals in hospitals for inpatient mental health care,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reliability of a Spinal Cord Injury-Specific Extension of the Work Rehabilitation Questionnaire (WORQ-SCI)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The WORQ-SCI showed good internal consistency and test-retest reliability. The test-retest results provide insight into measurement error, emphasizing the robustness of the instrument over time. The WORQ-SCI could be used reliably to assess work-related functioning in persons with SCI, although limits of agreement suggest caution when interpreting change at the level of the individual.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Role of B-Cell Biotherapy in Myasthenia Gravis from a Genetic Perspective: A Mendelian Randomization Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Myasthenia gravis (MG) is an autoimmune disease caused by dysfunction at the neuromuscular junction. Current studies on MG are increasingly focusing on the involvement of B cell immunophenotypes in the development of the disease. Nonetheless, the specific correlation between B cells and MG still needs to be fully clarified. From published GWAS studies, we gathered summary results on B cell immunophenotypes and MG. We performed a Two-sample Mendelian randomization (MR) analysis to investigate the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychometric properties and factor structure of the Children's Eating Behavior Questionnaire in a Danish sample of children with overweight and obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Danish CEBQ is a valid tool to assess eating behavior traits in Danish children with overweight and obesity; although, generalizability may be limited due to a relatively small sample size. Future studies should further validate the Danish CEBQ by assessing test-retest reliability, construct validity, and factor structure in a generalizable sample across weight categories.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Worse survival despite indolent features for triple-negative invasive lobular carcinoma: a Swedish nationwide registry-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TNBC-ILC is a distinct subgroup with older age, lower grade and Ki-67, undertreatment, and poorer survival, emphasizing the need for age- and subtype-specific treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of genes related to excitotoxicity in glioma prognosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our bioinformatics analysis reveals a significant association between an ERGs signature and glioma prognosis, providing a novel prognostic risk model with strong predictive capabilities. The identified pathways and immune cell infiltration patterns highlight potential therapeutic targets and suggest a role for the tumor microenvironment in glioma progression. These findings warrant further in vitro and in vivo validation to translate bioinformatics discoveries into personalized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PSMD4 Alleviates Aβ₁₋₄₂-Induced Mitochondrial Dysfunction and Oxidative Stress via the PGC-1α/Nrf Axis in Alzheimer's Disease Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate the role of 26S proteasome non-ATPase regulatory subunit 4 (PSMD4) in regulating mitochondrial function and oxidative stress in Alzheimer's disease (AD) and to explore its potential molecular mechanism in Aβ-induced neurotoxicity. An in vitro AD model was established by treating Neuro-2a cells with Aβ₁₋₄₂, and PSMD4 was overexpressed using a lentiviral vector. Flow cytometry was employed to assess reactive oxygen species (ROS) generation and mitochondrial membrane...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations Between APOE Polymorphisms, Neurological Symptoms, and Cognitive Assessments in Long COVID Patients: An Analysis of SNPs rs7412 and rs429358]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Long COVID has been associated with persistent neurological symptoms that impair cognitive function and quality of life, raising questions about the role of genetic factors in symptom severity and persistence. Apolipoprotein E (APOE) polymorphisms, known for their relevance in neurodegenerative diseases, may significantly influence neurological outcomes in long COVID patients. This study aimed to investigate the relationship between APOE polymorphisms, specifically single nucleotide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Racial and ethnic disparities and socioeconomic determinants of male breast cancer mortality in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings highlight elevated mortality risks of mBC among Black patients, among Asian or Pacific Islander patients with TNBC, and associations with household income and insurance status. Interventions addressing socioeconomic inequities that impact access to cancer care programs and services may help reduce racial/ethnic disparities and improve mBC survival outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trofinetide Improves Cognitive Function in APP/PS1 Mice by Suppressing Inflammation and Apoptosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder characterized by cognitive impairment, neuroinflammation, and neuronal apoptosis. Trofinetide, an analog of insulin-like growth factor 1 (IGF-1), has shown neuroprotective effects in various neurological disorders, but its role in AD remains unclear. Six-month-old APP/PS1 transgenic mice received intraperitoneal trofinetide for 2 months. Cognitive function was assessed using the Morris water maze (MWM) test....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive value of neutrophil-to-albumin ratio for the incidence of acute kidney injury in intracerebral hemorrhage patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute kidney injury (AKI) is a severe complication in patients with intracerebral hemorrhage (ICH), however, effective biomarkers combining systemic inflammation and nutritional status for early AKI prediction are still needed. This study aimed to evaluate the association between NAR and AKI and to assess its predictive value in ICH patients. This multicenter retrospective cohort study included 8,016 ICH patients. NAR was calculated using routine laboratory data, and AKI was defined based on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of olive leaf extracts on nutrient digestibility, rumen fermentation, blood parameters, and antioxidant capacity in sheep: an in vitro and in vivo study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chronic inflammatory diseases and survival among breast cancer patients in the U.S. military health system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Chronic inflammation, characterized by chronic inflammatory diseases, was independently associated with increased all-cause death among breast cancer patients in MHS. Future research with cancer-specific death as the outcome is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of lactoferrin administration as an antibiotic alternative growth promoter: impacts on rabbit's growth, meat quality, blood biochemical parameters, immune status, antioxidant status, and tissue histology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibiotic-resistant microbes have emerged because of the widespread misuse of antibiotics in modern animal production. To overcome antibiotic resistance, the name lactoferrin (Lf) is promising since it is a naturally safe alternative to antibiotics. Considering the few sources available, this study evaluated the effects of Lf administration as a possible alternative to antibiotics on the growth, meat quality, blood hematology, hepato-renal function, antioxidant, and immune status of rabbits. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Divergent responses of seed banks and aboveground vegetation to drought and deluge in grasslands across an elevational gradient]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Increased variability in precipitation associated with climate change creates extreme conditions of drought and deluge that can have profound effects on the abundance and composition of plant communities. Responses to these extremes likely vary across climatic gradients and depend on local plant community composition, which includes the emergent, aboveground vegetation as well as belowground seed banks. Because seed banks can both buffer the effects of environmental change and influence the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A portable colorimetric biosensor using MOF-Pt@Cu for Salmonella detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel bimetallic nanozyme (Pt/Cu-loaded MOF, MOF-Pt@Cu) has been synthesized and integrated in immunomagnetic beads (IMB) for Salmonella detection. Through the integration of bimetallic catalytic effects and portable instruments, this approach demonstrates unique advantages in the rapid detection of Salmonella. The enhanced peroxidase activity of bimetallic nanoenzymes, combined with their high stability, significantly improves detection sensitivity, with a detection limit as low as 2.4 CFU/mL...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early trajectory of inflammatory cytokines following tarlatamab administration in three advanced SCLC patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tarlatamab, a bispecific T-cell engager (BiTE), effectively activates the immune system but often causes cytokine release syndrome (CRS). To understand the early in vivo cytokine dynamics of post-BiTE therapy, we analyzed serum from three SCLC patients before and after tarlatamab administration using the Bio-Plex Pro Human Cytokine Screening Panel, 48-Plex. CRS occurred once in case 1, twice in case 2, and not at all in case 3. During the initial CRS in cases 1 and 2, IL-6, IL-1Ra, IL-10,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graphene-based dual-mode electrochemical-FET aptasensor for rapid zeptomolar detection of CEA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An electrochemical (EC) sensor has been developed integrated with a field effect transistor (FET) based on reduced graphene oxide (rGO) for ultrasensitive, rapid, and selective detection of carcinoembryonic antigen (CEA) over a wide dynamic range of up to eight orders of magnitude. An aptamer receptor was immobilized on the rGO surface, which had an initial hole mobility of 7 cm²/(V·s). Cyclic voltammetry and transfer curves measurements were used to monitor the biosensor assembly and to detect...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a machine learning-based prognostic model for gastric cancer: a multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The integrated machine learning model outperformed both traditional TNM staging and deep learning approaches, offering improved predictive accuracy for survival outcomes in patients with gastric cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Severe toxicity following genotype-guided reduced 5-FU dose in a heterozygous DPYD c.2846A&gt;T carrier with stage III anal carcinoma: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case report supports the clinical utility of pre-emptive DPYD genotyping to guide initial 5-FU dosing in intermediate metabolizers, and it suggests that all patients still require close monitoring and some (particularly carriers of c.2846 A > T) may require an initial dose reduction greater than the recommended 50% to prevent severe toxicity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost‑effectiveness analysis of indocyanine green fluorescence imaging-guided laparoscopic lymphadenectomy for gastric cancer in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared to conventional laparoscopic lymphadenectomy, ICG fluorescence imaging-guided laparoscopic lymphadenectomy for GC appears to be a cost-effective option in China.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experience of the endoscopist mediates the association between weekend effect with rebleeding after endoscopic treatment for Dieulafoy's lesion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The weekend effect was significantly associated with the higher rebleeding rate in patients with DL of the upper gastrointestinal tract, and less-experienced endoscopists on weekends might be playing a mediating role in this relationship.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: VZV IE4 downregulates cellular surface MHC-I via sequestering it to the golgi complex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of emotional intelligence in schizophrenia: ability-based vs. self-reported assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results suggest that that MSCEIT-ME and WLEIS may differ in their associations with clinical and neurocognitive profiles, and their impacts on functional outcome. Longitudinal studies in other populations are warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fine-mapping methods for complex traits: essential adaptations for samples of related individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fine-mapping causal variants from genome-wide association studies (GWAS) loci is challenging in populations with substantial relatedness, such as livestock, as standard methods often assume unrelatedness, leading to poor fine-mapping accuracy. Here, we introduce a comprehensive Bayesian framework to address this. Our approach features BFMAP-Shotgun Stochastic Search for individual-level data, which uses a linear mixed model (LMM) and shotgun stochastic search with simulated annealing. For...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrarenal pelvic pressure and renal temperature during 6.3Fr disposable digital flexible ureteroscope surgery: an in vitro experiment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A chromosome level genome assembly of the marine flowering plant, Torrey's surfgrass (Phyllospadix torreyi) reveals an exceptionally large Y-chromosome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phyllospadix spp. (surfgrass) are flowering plants and keystone species in the rocky intertidal and subtidal environments of the North Pacific Ocean. Here we report a chromosome level assembly for P. torreyi, which occurs along the coast of California, sometimes in sympatry with P. scouleri. Both of these species and their putative hybrids are being studied as part of the California Conservation Genomics Project (CCGP). Phyllospadix are dioecious, and males are exceptionally rare compared to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating the Expected Health and Economic Benefits of Price Increases via Taxation to Counter the Dual Combustible and Smokeless Tobacco Epidemics in India]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tobacco use remains a major health and economic burden in India. Both combustible and smokeless tobacco cause high mortality and morbidity. Taxation emerges as a potentially effective tool to reduce deaths, life years lost, and economic losses, with economic benefits reported exclusive of additional tax revenue.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glycoregulation of E3(SCF) ubiquitin ligases in unicellular eukaryotes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skp1 is an essential adaptor within the Skp1/Cul1/F-box (SCF) class of E3 polyubiquitin ligases that regulate protein degradation in all eukaryotes. Skp1 is also a target of a 5-enzyme glycosylation pathway in parasites and other unicellular eukaryotes. Glycosylation of Skp1 is contingent upon oxygen-dependent hydroxylation of a critical Pro residue by a homolog of the HIFα PHD2 oxygen sensor of animals. The resulting hydroxyproline is modified by a series of soluble, cytoplasmic, sugar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enzyme-Induced Nanocavity Formation in Leaf-Shaped Zeolitic Imidazolate Frameworks for Functional Entrapment of Carbonic Anhydrase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immobilizing carbonic anhydrases for CO(2) hydration holds great promise for efficient carbon capture. However, understanding how immobilization affects enzyme activity and host material structure is crucial for advancing this strategy. Here, we investigate the structural and functional consequences of entrapping Persephonella marina carbonic anhydrase (PmCA) within leaf-shaped zeolitic imidazolate frameworks (ZIF-L). Our results reveal that PmCA retains its activity - and, therefore, its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutations of SOX30 are identified in azoospermic human patients and reduce sperm in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sox proteins constitute a family of transcription factors now thought to play essential roles in cell fate decisions and tissue regeneration. SOX30 is a testis-specific transcription regulator for activating postmeiotic haploid gene program, and knockout of Sox30 results in defects in meiotic exit with an arrest at the early stage of round spermatids. Here, we aim to investigate the impact of human SOX30 mutagenesis on this transcriptional regulatory axis and its contribution to male...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Get Up, Stand Up-Are We Sitting Ourselves to an Early Death?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling the role of PEGylation in the anti-aggregation stability of lipid nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PEGylation is a key strategy to increase the storage stability and prolong the in vivo circulation time of lipid-based drug delivery systems by enhancing the anti-aggregation stability of nanocarriers, yet the relevant molecular mechanism remains unrevealed. This study employs multiscale approaches integrating molecular dynamics (MD) simulations and experimental characterization to comprehensively elucidate the quantitative structure-activity relationship (QSAR) between colloidal stability and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research progress of technology for exocytosis detection in the nervous system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vesicular exocytosis and neurotransmitter release play a key role in regulating various fundamental signal transmission and higher-order capacities in the nervous system. A slight variation in the process of exocytosis may change neuronal communication, plasticity and even whole nervous activity; moreover, disorder in neurotransmitter release may cause severe nerve diseases. Therefore, monitoring exocytosis processes and quantifying relevant parameters have been essential for ulteriorly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bottom-Up Fabrication of Graphene Nanoribbons with Nonalternant 5/7/5 Ring Motifs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonbenzenoid carbon nanostructures have attracted increasing attention because of their unique electronic, magnetic, and optoelectronic properties. However, their precise synthesis has remained challenging for both conventional solutions and on-surface synthetic approaches. In this work, we demonstrate the successful fabrication of graphene nanoribbons (GNRs) incorporating 5/7/5 ring motifs on Au(111) via surface-assisted Wurtz couplings followed by cyclodehydrogenation of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to letter to the editor: "What constitutes an adequate sample size for monitoring hand hygiene adherence?"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutrition Practices Reported by Families of Children with Down Syndrome, Autism, and Without an Intellectual or Developmental Disability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND IMPLICATIONS: Disparities in nutrition practices and education across groups highlight the need for tailored interventions to support diverse families.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Susceptibility to E-Cigarette and Cigarette Use Among U.S. Adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: This study aimed to assess the risk and protective factors associated with susceptibility to e-cigarette and cigarette use among U.S. adolescents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Studying Youth Well-Being Through Minecraft Digital Construction: A Visual and Thematic Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: To study adolescent gamers' representations of well-being using a Minecraft construction challenge as an innovative research tool.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Letter:</em> Buprenorphine Receipt Is Uncommon in Older Adults with Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bidirectional Relationships between Pain and Alcohol Use among Older Adults: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings provided convergent evidence that pain can motivate alcohol use in older adults. The effects of alcohol use on longer-term pain outcomes are less clear in this population. Major gaps and directions for future research are described.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selective Iodide Recovery from Saline Water Using Electrodeposited Layered Organo-MnO<sub>2</sub>: Elucidation of the Sorption Mechanism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organo-manganese dioxide (MnO(2)) thin films intercalated with cetyltrimethylammonium chloride (CTAC/MnO(2)) were successfully fabricated via electrochemical deposition and applied for selective iodide (I^(-)) recovery from aqueous solutions. The CTAC/MnO(2) thin films exhibited high sorption capacities for I^(-), following Langmuir-type monolayer sorption behavior with a maximum sorption capacity of 211 mg g^(-1). X-ray photoelectron spectroscopy revealed that iodide sorption proceeded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41269118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251121142237&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>