<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:00:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research on enhancing short-term wind power forecasting through feature fusion in a hybrid deep learning framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wind power generation is a vital component of renewable energy, and achieving high-accuracy power forecasting is crucial for grid stability and sustainable operation. To address the highly nonlinear and complex temporal characteristics of wind power, this paper investigates a hybrid deep learning model, TCN-SENet-BiGRU-Global Attention. The model integrates a Temporal Convolutional Network (TCN), Squeeze-and-Excitation Network (SENet), Bidirectional Gated Recurrent Unit (BiGRU), and a Global...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Topology optimization of thermoelectric generator for maximum power efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermoelectric generators offer a promising approach for harvesting waste heat from both natural and human-made sources, enabling sustainable electricity generation. While geometric design plays a crucial role in optimizing device performance, conventional approaches remain confined to simple configurations, limiting efficiency improvements. This constraint arises from the complex interplay of multiphysical interactions and diverse thermal environments, which complicates structural optimization....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, POSTECH, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trimodal single-cell profiling of transcriptome, epigenome and 3D genome in complex tissues with scHiCAR]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The three-dimensional (3D) organization of cis-regulatory elements (CREs) is critical in transcription control. However, capturing transcriptome, epigenome and 3D genome from the same single cells remains challenging. Here we present scHiCAR (single-cell Hi-C with assay for transposase-accessible chromatin and RNA sequencing), a plate-based combinatorial barcoding method that simultaneously profiles mRNA, open chromatin and chromosome conformation capture from the same cells. Compared to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[London Dispersion and Acido-Basicity of Ni-Rich Cathode Materials Using Inverse Gas Chromatography at Infinite Dilution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The accelerating electrification of energy systems has positioned lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) as essential for high-efficiency storage. Yet, the surface energetics of Ni-rich layered cathodes remain poorly understood despite their critical role in interfacial stability. Here, inverse gas chromatography (IGC) at infinite dilution quantifies the surface free-energy components of two benchmark cathodes, NCM (LiNi(0.95)Co(0.04)Mn(0.01)O(2)) and NCMA (LiNi(0.95)Co(0.02)Mn(0.02)Al(0.01)O(2)). NCM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Trends in Cardiogenic Shock Complicating Acute Myocardial Infarction in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The decline in mortality rates of overall and ba-CS but not that of da-CS emphasizes the need for enhanced prevention strategies, early identification of development of CS after admission, and alternative therapeutic strategies for patients at high risk of CS in the acute stage of AMI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of the Implantation Angle on the Durability of a Bio-Prosthetic Pulmonary Valve in the Tetralogy of Fallot]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The risk for early PVF was relatively lower when the implantation angle was between 30° and 45°. We should be careful to implant a prosthetic valve with an adequate angle to maintain a laminar flow in the pulmonary position for better durability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Outcomes of Deep Sedation Versus General Anesthesia in Cryoablation for Atrial Fibrillation: Insights From the Korean Heart Rhythm Society Cryoablation Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DS provides a comparable safety and efficacy profile to GA for cryoablation in patients with AF. These findings support the use of DS as a feasible and practical alternative to GA in routine clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of CR6-Interacting Factor 1 (Crif1) in Cardiac Mitochondrial Structure and Stress-Induced Functional Decline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that Crif1 is critical for maintaining the structure and function of mitochondria in cardiomyocytes. Additionally, mitochondrial abnormalities in the heart impair stress adaptation, leading to aggravated cardiac dysfunction under stress.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Challenges and Controversies in Perioperative Immunotherapy in Early-Stage Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer: An Optimistic Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immune checkpoint inhibitors have transformed the treatment landscape of non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC), extending their role from metastatic to resectable disease. While neoadjuvant and adjuvant immunotherapies have each shown clinical value, recent evidence suggests that a perioperative strategy-incorporating both preoperative and postoperative immune-based treatment-may provide more consistent and durable survival benefits, especially in stage IIIA and high PD-L1-expressing tumors....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rehabilitation protocols after arthroscopic rotator cuff repair: A survey of active members of the Korean Shoulder and Elbow Society]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite variations in detailed protocols, the structured framework based on tear size and physical demands observed among the active members of the KSES, coupled with the preference for patient-directed rehabilitation and multimodal pain control, may suggest future efforts toward developing evidence-based and culturally adaptable rehabilitation guidelines. Further studies with higher levels of evidence are required to establish standardized and effective rehabilitation protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput heart rate monitoring in Daphnia magna for sublethal ecotoxicological assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monitoring Daphnia magna heart rate provides significant potential as a sensitive physiological indicator for ecotoxicological assessment, yet its broader application has been limited by low-throughput, high variability, reliance on mean-based interpretation, and difficulties in analysing multiple individuals simultaneously. Here, we present an integrated methodology combining stress-minimised immobilisation, high-speed imaging, and Fourier-based analysis to monitor 150 individuals per hour....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heat-killed Bacteroides fragilis SLAM_BAF01 alleviates weaning-induced stress responses and cognitive impairments by modulating the gut-brain-microbiome axis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Weaning transition in porcine industry is marked by nutritional, microbial, and psychological stresses that can impair growth and development. Accumulating evidence indicates that weaning-related stress not only disrupts gut microbial homeostasis but impairs gut-brain axis signaling through activation of stress-related neuroendocrine pathways. However, current interventions have largely focused on improving growth performance or enteric symptoms, while integrated strategies targeting the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying Predictors of Gambling Episodes and Craving Using Ecological Momentary Assessment and Smartwatch-Based Physiological Measures: Protocol for a Longitudinal Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Incorporating the relevant predictors found in this study into digital intervention programs and providing just-in-time individually tailored intervention elements could improve program engagement and effectiveness. The approach used in this study is transferable to other digital interventions for addictive behaviors and holds promise to exploit their potential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Montelukast Modulates MPTP-induced Ferroptosis and Neuroinflammation Linked To the GPX4/ACSL4/5-LOX Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferroptosis, an iron-dependent form of regulated cell death, has been increasingly linked to neurodegeneration in Parkinson's disease (PD). The lipid-peroxidizing enzyme 5-lipoxygenase (5-LOX) contributes to ferroptotic stress, while montelukast, a leukotriene receptor antagonist widely used for asthma, indirectly interferes with this pathway. Here, we investigated whether montelukast protects against dopaminergic injury in a mouse model of PD induced by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Receptor-Free Cellular Internalization of DNA Micelles Driven by Membrane Interaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cellular uptake of nanoparticles is essential for significant therapeutic effects at the target site in drug-delivery applications. Various endocytosis pathways have been reported; however, the internalization of nanoparticles depends on their physical and chemical properties. We previously developed nucleic acid-based micelles (DNA micelles) as a drug-delivery system and observed that the presence of lipid moieties in amphiphilic lipid-modified DNAs plays a crucial role in cellular uptake. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Acupuncture and Moxibustion for Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) Patients Undergoing Standard Treatment: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Acupuncture and moxibustion improve QoL, reduce CINV, and modulate immune function in NSCLC, supporting their complementary role.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ATP release mediated by TRPM3 enhances invasion in glioblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma (GBM) is the most aggressive and lethal form of primary brain tumor, characterized by uncontrolled proliferation and invasion into surrounding brain tissue. Mechanical stimulation (MS) in the tumor microenvironment (TME) has been correlated to tumor progression, partly via ATP release. However, the underlying molecular mechanisms remain poorly understood. In this study, we found that transient receptor potential melastatin 3 (TRPM3) channel mediates MS-induced ATP release from GBM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Juvenile-to-adult refinement of thalamic reticular circuits via LRRTM3 enables high-resolution sensory encoding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sensory processing enables adaptive behavior by accurately encoding dynamic environmental stimuli. Within thalamocortical (TC) circuits, the thalamic reticular nucleus (TRN) functions as a key inhibitory gate that regulates cortical access to sensory input. While classical models posit that sensory circuits stabilize after early critical periods, we uncover a previously unrecognized phase of synaptic refinement in TRN circuitry extending from the juvenile period into adulthood. This late-stage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Taltirelin Hydrate in Patients With Ataxia Due to Spinocerebellar Degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hierarchical deep learning pipeline for robust cervical parameter measurement in radiographs with C7 obscuration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We developed and externally validated a hierarchical deep learning pipeline that automates cervical sagittal measurements, explicitly addressing C7 obscuration on lateral radiographs. The model combines a global keypoint detector with C2/C7 specialists localized via a multilayer perceptron to refine landmarks on high‑resolution patches. Trained on 5604 images and tested internally and on a challenging external cohort enriched for C7 obscuration (82%), it achieved excellent agreement with ground...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large language models in systematic review and meta-analysis of surgical treatments for vaginal vault prolapse]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Systematic reviews provide the highest level of evidence but remain resource-intensive. We evaluated the performance of a large language model (LLM; ChatGPT, OpenAI) in a PRISMA-guided review of randomized controlled trials on vaginal vault prolapse surgery. Prompts were carefully designed to minimize errors, and outputs were verified. Each task was completed within minutes. For title/abstract screening, recall was 69.8% and precision 85.7% (κ = 0.77); full-text agreement 94.1-100% (κ = 0.82-1);...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Not All Child-Pugh B Is the Same: Refining Immunotherapy Eligibility in Hepatocellular Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Studies on intellectual disability identify variants in established genes as well as confirm candidature of new genes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intellectual disability (ID) is a neurodevelopmental disorder, characterized by congenital cognitive and adaptive behavioral issues. We studied multiple patients with ID born to consanguineous parents. Exome sequencing was completed for selected patients and the data were filtered using an allele frequency of less than 0.01. All exonic and splice-site variants were considered. Segregation analyses were performed using allele-specific PCR and Sanger sequencing. Expression analyses of candidate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ambipolar thin-film transistors and inverter circuits based on mixed-dimensional bilayer heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Among a large number of layered materials family, molybdenum disulfide (MoS(2)) has been the most representative semiconducting channel material for electronic devices due to its exceptional electrical performance with a monolayer thickness. However, quite complicated fabrication processes, such as multiple transfer and alignment of individual flakes, have usually been required to implement integrated complementary circuits with MoS(2) which typically exhibits n-type behavior. In particular,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early developmental intervention and neurodevelopmental trajectories in preterm infants without severe brain injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Early intervention was associated with more favorable motor outcomes, highlighting the importance of timely support for high-risk preterm infants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uneven transition risks from multi-scope carbon flows: a nationwide regional assessment for South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Global climate regulations increasingly extend carbon responsibility beyond direct emitters to the supply chains that sustain regional economies. Yet little is known about how these disclosure regimes redistribute transition risks across regions within a country. This study provides the first nationwide, multi-scope assessment of South Korea's regional carbon flows by integrating production-based (Scope 1), energy-related (Scope 2) and supply chain embedded (Scope 3) emissions into a regionally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum-secured routing in drone communication for 6G-enabled smart mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of artificial intelligence identified ipratropium bromide for the treatment of coronavirus disease 2019]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving predictive reliability and automation of smart grids using the StarNet ensemble model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ensuring predictive reliability and automation in smart grids is vital for stable and efficient electricity distribution. This study introduces the StarNet Ensemble Model, a web-based intelligent framework designed to enhance grid stability through a stacking-based ensemble learning approach. The system integrates a machine learning-driven graphical user interface (GUI) that enables automated, real-time monitoring and prediction of grid performance. A synthetic dataset, generated from a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A spatially resolved human glioblastoma atlas reveals distinct cellular and molecular patterns of anatomical niches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma is an aggressive brain cancer with limited treatment options and poor patient survival, driven in part by cellular diversity within tumors. While individual cell types have been catalogued, how malignant, vascular, and immune cells are spatially organized inside human tumors remains incompletely understood. Here we show a spatially resolved, multi-modal atlas of human glioblastoma that integrates gene expression profiling across tissue sections with matched single-cell and protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergent giant topological Hall effect in twisted Fe<sub>3</sub>GeTe<sub>2</sub> metallic system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The topological Hall effect, driven by the exchange interaction between conduction electrons and topological magnetic textures such as skyrmions, is a powerful probe for investigating the topological properties of magnetic materials. Typically, this phenomenon arises in systems with broken global inversion symmetry, where Dzyaloshinskii-Moriya interactions stabilize such textures. Here, we report the discovery of an emergent giant topological Hall effect in the twisted Fe(3)GeTe(2) metallic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Could Predict Chest Tube Drainage Necessity for Spontaneous Pneumothorax]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is increasingly utilized in the medical field, primarily for diagnostic purposes. Although AI has demonstrated efficacy in pneumothorax detection using chest X-rays (CXR), it has yet to be applied for decision-making regarding subsequent treatment. This study aims to develop and evaluate an AI-based system capable of predicting the necessity of chest tube drainage (CTD) in spontaneous pneumothorax patients based on CXR and clinical data. A two-stage AI model was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Classification of dysphagia severity after lateral medullary infarction with deep learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dysphagia is a common and debilitating complication in patients with lateral medullary infarction (LMI), affecting up to 100% of cases and significantly impairing quality of life. Accurate classification of early dysphagia severity is essential for timely intervention and personalized rehabilitation planning. This study aimed to develop and validate a deep learning algorithm using acute-phase diffusion-weighted MRI to classify dysphagia severity in LMI patients. A retrospective cohort of 163...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Association Between Alpha-Blockers for Benign Prostatic Hyperplasia and Acute Angle-Closure Glaucoma". Am J Ophthalmol. 2026;282:197-205]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sodium glucose transporter 2 inhibitor exposure and the risk of congenital malformations: nationwide birth cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this study, SGLT2 inhibitor use during the first trimester was not associated with an increased risk of congenital malformations. Nonetheless, the observed increased risk of congenital heart defects during the organogenesis period highlights the importance of exposure timing and warrants cautious interpretation. These findings provide evidence to guide clinical decision-making regarding antidiabetic medication use during pregnancy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lenvatinib plus pembrolizumab in previously treated advanced endometrial cancer: 5-year outcomes from the randomized, phase 3 Study 309/KEYNOTE-775]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Results were consistent with the primary analysis despite increased use of subsequent systemic anticancer therapy and crossover to lenvatinib+pembrolizumab in the chemotherapy group. The continued durable benefit, including OS, with lenvatinib+pembrolizumab and no new safety signals lend further support for this regimen as a standard of care therapy for EC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longer-term impact of pesticide bans on suicide in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: South Korea's pesticide bans in 2011-2012 were followed by a sustained decrease in pesticide suicides in the 7-year period (2013-2019) after their implementation. National policies restricting or banning highly hazardous pesticides commonly involved in self-poisoning can prevent many suicide deaths over a sustained period. Additional regulatory efforts could further reduce these unnecessary premature deaths.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Physical Activity Is Better: Applying a Cardiovascular Golden Rule to Cardiac Bradyarrhythmia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atrial Metabolic Profile and Underlying Pathophysiology Across Different Ages: Right Atrial Uptake by 18F-FDG PET/CT in Persistent Atrial Fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Initiation of Evolocumab in Patients with Acute Coronary Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Impact of 1-Year Left Ventricular Mass Regression After Aortic Valve Surgery in Severe Aortic Regurgitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Greater 1-year postoperative LVMi regression was associated with improved outcomes in chronic AR, particularly by reducing HF-related hospitalizations. While hypertension negatively affected remodeling, favorable baseline echocardiographic profiles, including higher LVMi, preserved left ventricular ejection fraction, and a smaller left atrium, were connected to more significant postoperative LVRR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virtual Reality Exercise Alleviates Postprandial Vascular and Metabolic Impairment in Adolescents With Congenital Heart Disease: A Randomized Controlled Crossover Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A single session of VR exergaming attenuated vascular and metabolic impairment induced by an HFM and prolonged sitting in adolescents with CHD. These findings suggest that VR exergaming may serve as an alternative to traditional exercise for vascular health in CHD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2025 Clinical Practice Guidelines for the Management of Fontan Patients in Korea: A Consensus Statement With Graded Recommendations by the Committee for Clinical Practice Guidelines on Fontan Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Over the past 4 decades, significant advances in pediatric cardiology in Korea have led to marked improvements in the prognosis of patients with complex congenital heart diseases, including single ventricle physiology. The number of patients reaching adulthood has steadily increased. In particular, there is a growing need for clinical practice guidelines that reflect the latest medical trends for the long-term management of Fontan circulation patients. Accordingly, a Korean Fontan cohort was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased Right Atrial FDG Uptake in Persistent Atrial Fibrillation: Insights Across Young vs. Old Age Groups]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Atrial FDG uptake patterns did not differ by age in patients with AF. Increased RA FDG uptake in persistent AF was consistently observed, suggesting a shared metabolic alteration underlying AF progression transcending age-related pathological differences.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Acupuncture as a Therapeutic Intervention Targeting Both Skin and Gastrointestinal Symptoms in Patients With Atopic Dermatitis: A Randomised Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-Tuberculosis Health: A Holistic Perspective on Multisystem Sequelae and Long-Term Wellbeing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis survivors often face long-term physical, psychological, and social challenges beyond microbiological cure. Post-tuberculosis disease includes pulmonary damage, cardiovascular and neurological sequelae, and profound impacts on wellbeing and livelihoods. Despite growing recognition, most care remains focused on lung disease, neglecting multisystem and social needs. A holistic, people-centered framework integrating medical, rehabilitative, and community-based strategies is essential to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Small Airway Dysfunction in COPD Pathology: Assessment and Clinical Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease (COPD) is a progressive lung disease characterized by airflow limitation and persistent respiratory symptoms. Small airway dysfunction (SAD) plays a crucial role in the progression of COPD, originating in airways less than 2 mm in diameter. Chronic exposure to smoke and toxins leads to inflammatory remodeling and luminal obstruction, which can be detected through micro-CT studies before spirometric airflow limitation becomes apparent. SAD exacerbates COPD by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-yield DNA-based neurofibromatosis type 1 diagnostics reveals population-specific mutation landscape in 1,917 Koreans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF1) is a common autosomal dominant disorder with extensive allelic heterogeneity. Although RNA-based assays can increase sensitivity, their cost and complexity limit their routine use. We evaluated a DNA-only tiered diagnostic approach in 1,917 unrelated Korean individuals with clinically suspected NF1. The process began with targeted sequencing of blood-derived genomic DNA, followed by reflex MLPA for copy-number variants and lesional tissue test for suspected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stimuli-responsive nanodiamonds for precision pharmacokinetics, pharmacodynamics, and drug delivery applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanodiamonds (NDs) have emerged as versatile and promising nanocarriers in pharmacological applications, attributed to their distinctive physicochemical characteristics such as tunable size, customizable surface chemistry, and outstanding biocompatibility. These properties have allowed NDs to be explored extensively across various nanomedicine and biomedical research domains. Despite the significant promise of NDs, a comprehensive understanding of their biodistribution, pharmacokinetics (PK),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural, quantitative, and functional characterization of N-glycans in porcine pancreatin extract, lipase, and α-amylase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Porcine pancreatin extract (PPE), an enzyme mixture comprising porcine pancreatic lipase (PPL), porcine pancreatic α-amylase (PPA), and proteases, facilitates the digestion of fats, carbohydrates, and proteins and is widely used to treat pancreatic insufficiency. N-glycosylation is a critical post-translational modification influencing enzyme stability and activity. This study presents the N-glycan profiling of PPE, PPL, and PPA to evaluate their structural roles in enzymatic function. N-glycans...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcome in children with infantile epileptic spasms syndrome: a multicenter retrospective study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The IESS imposes a substantial burden on affected children and their families and often leads to chronic epilepsy and impaired cognitive function. Consensus diagnostic and treatment guidelines tailored to the Korean clinical practice are necessary to ensure early diagnosis and timely treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication of electrochemical biosensor with a CD36 aptamer and AuMoS<sub>2</sub> heterolayer for tumor-derived exosome detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer (BC), which is often diagnosed at advanced stages owing to its asymptomatic progression, presents with substantial molecular heterogeneity, leading to diverse therapeutic responses and prognostic outcomes. Among its molecular subtypes, the human epidermal growth factor receptor 2-positive/hormone receptor-negative (HER2^(+)/HR^(-)) phenotype displays pronounced therapeutic resistance and recurrence rate, emphasizing the need for early and accurate diagnostic strategies. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GFASNet: Gait feature attention-driven deep sequential network for dementia-related gait pattern analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models leveraging human activity data, such as gait, have shown promise for dementia prediction. However, their limited interpretability and lack of clinically meaningful insights restrict their translational value in cognitive health research. This study introduces GFASNet, a Gait Feature Attention-driven Deep Sequential Network designed primarily to identify dementia-related gait alterations through model-derived attention mechanisms, which may serve as candidate digital...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoplex cluster-mediated synergistic modulation of dendritic cells and T cells amplifies tumor-specific adaptive immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor immune evasion is greatly impacted by immune checkpoint molecules that impede the activation of costimulatory signals. Inadequate costimulatory molecules restrict the immune system's capacity to generate strong responses to malignancies. This study presents a development of a dual-nanoplex cluster (NC) formulation that effectively overcomes these issues. The formulation comprises a nanoplex (NP) encapsulating CpG ODN 1826 (CpG NP), which stimulates TLR-9 and elevates the levels of CD80/86...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean Practical Guidelines for Geriatric Assessment and Management of Older Adults with Cancer: A Korean Cancer Association Guideline for Geriatric Oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Korean Cancer Association's clinical practice guidelines for geriatric oncology provide an evidence-based, multidisciplinary framework to optimize cancer care for the growing population of older adults. Geriatric Assessment (GA) identifies multidimensional vulnerabilities often missed by standard performance measures, providing critical information to guide individualized treatment planning. This guideline recommends using validated geriatric screening tools, life expectancy prediction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing Radiation Pneumonitis Through Functional Lung Imaging: A Single Photon Emission Computed Tomography (SPECT)-Based Approach in Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SPECT-based dosimetric parameters derived from perfusion and ventilation are significantly associated with the risk of SRP. Incorporating SPECT may improve risk stratification and enable lung-sparing strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-based estimation of lung collapse in electrical impedance tomography: A simulation and phantom study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inhomogeneity of air volume distribution in the lungs of mechanically ventilated patients can lead to lung collapse and overdistention, increasing the risk of ventilator-induced lung injury. While Electrical Impedance Tomography (EIT) enables bedside monitoring of regional ventilation, traditional Degree of Lung Collapse (DoLC) assessment using the Global Inhomogeneity (GI) index is limited by lung segmentation. We propose a deep learning framework that directly estimates the DoLC from EIT...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Genomic Landscape of Korean Gastric Cancer: Integrating Biomarker Associations and Clinical Outcomes in Metastatic Gastric Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings provide a comprehensive genomic landscape of Korean gastric cancer and underscore the clinical relevance of integrating genomic and established biomarkers to advance precision oncology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pediatric snakebite in Sub-Saharan Africa: Clinical predictors, outcomes, and gaps in care-A systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pediatric SBE in SSA is characterized by substantial preventable morbidity and mortality, mainly due to delays in care and inconsistent access to essential emergency care and safe antivenom. Improved health system capacity, rapid referral, and standardized management are urgently needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knowledge flows from science to AI technology: Identifying core and brokerage technological roles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence (AI) technologies has not only driven convergence with diverse technological domains but also swiftly spread across various industrial sectors. As a knowledge-intensive field, AI is particularly shaped by the flow of knowledge from scientific research to technological development, yet remains insufficiently examined in a systematic and structural way. This study addresses this gap by investigating science-to-technology knowledge flow that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic diversity of Ligularia revealed by complete plastid genomes and nuclear ribosomal DNAs from 16 collections in Korean Peninsula and Mt. Hallasan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plastid genome (plastome) and nuclear ribosomal DNA (nrDNA) sequences were assembled from 16 Ligularia accessions, including L. fischeri, L. fischeri var. spiciformis, and L. stenocephala. The assembled lengths ranged from 150,889 bp to 151,173 bp, while the 45S nrDNA transcription units varied from 5,846 bp to 5,848 bp. Comparative analyses revealed 0-106 SNPs and 0-60 InDels among the plastomes, and 1-50 SNPs and 0-4 InDels within the 45S nrDNA regions. Although the three taxa are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of patient experience with nurses and ward type on intention to recommend: Focusing on integrated nursing and caring service wards and general wards, 2020-2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although recommendation intention was slightly higher among INCSW patients in unadjusted comparisons, ward type was not independently associated with willingness to recommend after adjustment. In contrast, all nurse experience domains were positively and significantly associated with patients' willingness to recommend the hospital. Strengthening nurse communication competencies, supported by ward-level monitoring and feedback-based training, may enhance patient experience and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Osteoporosis and fracture incidence and risk factors among individuals with traumatic spinal cord injury: A nationwide cohort study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results provide nationwide evidence supporting age - and sex-specific screening and prevention strategies for osteoporosis and fractures in patients with TSCI, which may help improve long-term outcomes and reduce secondary complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optoelectronic Characterization of Trap Density of States in Indium Gallium Oxide Thin-Film Transistors and Their Impact on Bias Stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amorphous oxide semiconductors have become the industry standard for display backplanes, but their limited mobility necessitates complex low-temperature polycrystalline oxide (LTPO) stacks, increasing cost and reducing yield. To realize a practical oxide-only backplane that can serve as both drive and switching transistors, a channel combining high mobility, low off current, and robust stability is required. Here, we report zinc-free crystalline indium-gallium oxide (IGO) thin-film transistors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Longitudinal Relationship Between Self-Efficacy and Job Satisfaction Among Workers with Disabilities in South Korea: An Autoregressive Cross-Lagged Panel Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight the necessity of developing practical strategies and bidirectional interventions aimed at enhancing both self-efficacy and job satisfaction among employees with disabilities in South Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pilot-scale assessment of slag reactors for manganese removal from mine drainage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Manganese (Mn) is a common water contaminant in mining areas and one of the most challenging metals to treat. This study assessed Mn removal efficiencies of pilot-scale slag reactors using steelmaking slag mixed with limestone as the reactive material. Three different reactor configurations of baffle-type, weir-type, and vertical flow-type were installed and tested over a 316-day operational period with initial, middle, and final phases. Geochemical modeling indicated that most effluents were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residual congestion at discharge assessed by bioelectrical impedance and its prognostic value in acute heart failure: a multi-centre, prospective registry study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The EI and PA measured at discharge independently predicted short-term WHFs in patients with AHF. The suggested thresholds for identifying patients at high-risk of residual congestion were EI ≥ 0.4 and PA < 4.5°. As a non-invasive and accessible modality, BIA holds promise as a complementary tool to established biomarkers for evaluating congestion at discharge.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Major Tragal Malformations: Structural Feature, Classification, and Reconstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Major congenital tragal malformations are characterized by structural anomalies involving both the tragal and external auditory canal (EAC) cartilages, associated with the accessory auricle (AA). Despite their prevalence, previous classification systems and surgical techniques have focused primarily on the outer framework, particularly the AA cartilage. This retrospective study included 258 ears in 247 patients who underwent surgical reconstruction between 2013 and 2023. The structural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning for Predicting Stroke Risk Stratification Using Multiomics Data: Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Multiomics ML models showed high apparent discrimination for stroke risk stratification, but current evidence remains methodologically limited. Small sample sizes, heterogeneous designs, and incomplete reporting currently hinder the reproducibility and generalizability of multiomics ML models for stroke risk prediction. To advance the field, future studies should adopt leakage-resistant evaluation frameworks, conduct site-specific external validations, and benchmark against both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NanoScript-Enabled Nonviral Transient Repression of Phosphatase and Tensin Homolog for Axonal Regeneration and Central Nervous System Injury Repair]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spinal cord injury (SCI) remains a debilitating neurological disorder with limited therapeutic options, as existing treatments primarily address symptoms rather than address the complex interplay of cellular and molecular barriers to regeneration. These barriers collectively hinder functional recovery, including inhibitory glial scarring, chronic neuroinflammation, intrinsic neuronal regenerative deficits, and disruption of the blood-spinal cord barrier (BSCB). To address these limitations, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrocarbon Frameworks with Long-Range Order Synthesized via Olefin Metathesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Introducing long-range order into hydrocarbon covalent organic frameworks (COFs) remains a fundamental challenge because carbon-carbon bond-forming reactions are typically irreversible and lack effective error-correction mechanisms. Here, we demonstrate a molecular approach to enhance the crystallinity of a hydrocarbon framework. A fully hydrocarbon two-dimensional (2D) COF, HKU-50, was synthesized via reversible olefin metathesis. Polymerization of a vinylene-bearing monomer using the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polydatin as a Multifunctional Anticancer Agent: Cellular Mechanisms, Therapeutic Potential and Future Clinical Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer remains one of the leading causes of death worldwide, with conventional treatments often facing limitations such as toxicity, drug resistance, and reduced effectiveness over time. Polydatin (PD), a natural glycosylated derivative of resveratrol, has emerged as a promising therapeutic compound due to its ability to induce apoptosis, regulate the cell cycle, modulate oxidative stress, and inhibit angiogenesis. Additionally, PD plays a key role in shaping the tumor microenvironment and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Risk Associated with Polypharmacy in Heart Failure: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Polypharmacy in patients with HF was associated with increased risk of composite CV outcome and HF hospitalization, reflecting the complexity of managing multiple medications. These findings underscore the need for individualized medication reviews to minimize inappropriate prescribing and ensure continued delivery of evidence-based therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevated skin perfusion pressure 48 hours after endovascular therapy predicts early wound healing in chronic limb-threatening ischemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High SPP within 48 hours post-EVT was a significant predictor of early wound healing in CLTI. Although TcPO(2) was not predictive of early wound healing, it was linked to other favorable limb outcomes. Further studies are required to validate our findings and define the complementary roles of SPP and TcPO(2) in managing CLTI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[O<sub>2</sub>-assisted methane oxidation on single-atom Pd@SSZ-13: a combined first-principles and microkinetic study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Complete catalytic oxidation of methane is an effective strategy for greenhouse gas mitigation and clean energy conversion. Yet, ensuring both high catalytic activity and stability using palladium (Pd)-based catalysts remains a challenge. In the present work, we performed a theoretical investigation of methane oxidation over single-atom Pd supported on the SSZ-13 zeolite (Pd@SSZ-13) using density functional theory (DFT) calculations, combined with climbing-image nudged elastic band (CI-NEB)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indole-3-propionic Acid Is an Endogenous Agonist of TAS2R38]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bitter taste receptor 38 (TAS2R38) is increasingly recognized for its extra-oral roles in metabolic and immune regulation but remains incompletely understood due to limited endogenous ligands. Therefore, we aimed to discover a novel TAS2R38 agonist from food- and microbiota-derived metabolites of aromatic amino acids. Using AI-based molecular modeling, a promising ligand-binding pocket and key interactions for TAS2R38 activation, including π-π stacking via aromatic rings and hydrogen bonding via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychiatric, Cardiovascular and Skeletal Risks of Codeine versus Oxycodone in Hip Osteoarthritis: A Population-Based Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Codeine use in patients with hip osteoarthritis was associated with a higher risk of psychiatric disorders and distinct fracture patterns. The observed risks varied according to patient characteristics, comorbidities, and concomitant medications, emphasizing the need for individualized opioid prescribing strategies that incorporate psychiatric monitoring, fracture risk assessment, and patient-specific factors. Further controlled studies integrating clinical, lifestyle, and genetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sequential Monopolar-Bipolar Pulsed Radiofrequency for Non-Invasive Periorbital Rejuvenation: A Case Series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sequential monopolar-bipolar pulsed RF (DENSITY NOIR) demonstrated clinically meaningful outcomes for periorbital skin tightening and wrinkle reduction after a single session. This technology may be a non-invasive option for patients seeking subtle, natural rejuvenation with minimal discomfort and downtime.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Double-Blinded, Split-Face Clinical Trial Evaluating the Effects of a Vitamin C, E, and Ferulic Acid Serum Combined with Microneedling on Facial Photoaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Combining topical antioxidant serum with microneedling provides superior outcomes for facial rejuvenation than microneedling alone. This combination protocol significantly improves clinical signs of photoaging, including skin elasticity, rhytides, and dyspigmentation, suggesting an optimized treatment protocol with minimal recovery time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-task deep learning models for mechanism-based prediction of developmental and reproductive toxicity (DART) using ToxCast bioassays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developmental and reproductive toxicity (DART) testing has traditionally relied on animal studies, which are costly, time-consuming, and ethically constrained. To advance new approach methodologies (NAMs), we developed a mechanism-informed deep learning framework for predicting DART using in vitro bioactivity data from 23 ToxCast assays mechanistically linked to key developmental and reproductive pathways. Four state-of-the-art (SOTA) deep learning architectures (DGCL, TransFoxMol, MolPath, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced neuroprotective ability of human cerebellum during ageing: the interplay of neuroplasticity, neurodegeneration and life-time trajectory-a pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The neurodegenerative decline of brain with ageing is an acute global demographic problem, as elderly population surges worldwide. However, ageing effect has not been systematically studied for cerebellum, an autonomous part of brain having motor, cognition, language and memory functions. By magnetic resonance investigation, we study brain-ageing process: 177 normal subjects, aged 20-80, with focus on cerebellum, the first larger-scale analysis as we know. We found that for whole brain, both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unperceived First-Time Anterior Shoulder Subluxation: The Role of MRI in Detection and Characterization of Pathoanatomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Anterior shoulder instability is not always recognized by patients, and initial physical examination may be limited in the acute setting. MRI findings of unrecognized first-time subluxations were similar to those of typical subluxations and showed less severe HS morphology than in dislocations. Clinicians should maintain a high index of suspicion in young patients presenting with traumatic shoulder pain, even in the absence of perceived instability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between chronic stress-related amygdala metabolic activity and distant metastasis in colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Elevated amygdala metabolic activity on pre-treatment ¹⁸F-FDG PET/CT, a surrogate marker of chronic stress, was independently associated with distant metastasis in CRC. AmygA might serve as a novel imaging biomarker for risk stratification and offer insight into stress-related neural mechanisms underlying metastatic progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The double-edged sword of regulatory T cells in MASLD: from inflammation control to fibrosis promotion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) and its advanced inflammatory subtype, metabolic dysfunction-associated steatohepatitis (MASH), are becoming increasingly prevalent liver disorders driven by complex interactions between metabolic stress, immune dysregulation, and fibrotic remodeling. Regulatory T cells (Tregs), traditionally recognized for their immunosuppressive functions, have emerged as key modulators of hepatic inflammation, fibrosis, and systemic metabolic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supersonic Cryogenic Jet Delivery of Polynucleotides Compared With Manual Intradermal Injection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Transdermal drug delivery devices are a safe and effective alternative to traditional PN injections, with similar skin improvement outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early postnatal changes in thyroid-stimulating hormone and subsequent neurodevelopment in preterm infants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preterm infants with persistently low or decreasing TSH trajectories showed reduced odds of neurodevelopmental impairment. In contrast, persistently high or increasing TSH levels may instead reflect alternative patterns of postnatal HPT-axis adaptation. Corresponding group differences in fronto-limbic regions at discharge provide neurobiological support that altered thyroid function may contribute to atypical brain connectivity underlying later neurodevelopmental outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolomic Clusters and Their Association with Small Airway Disease in Asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Systemic metabolic profiles are associated with small airway inflammation and structural remodeling through bidirectional interactions between circulating metabolites and airway pathophysiology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[15 years of longitudinal genetic, clinical, cognitive, imaging, and biochemical measures in DIAN]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Dominantly Inherited Alzheimer Network Observational Study (DIAN Obs) is a longitudinal, global cohort study investigating brain aging and autosomal dominant Alzheimer's disease (ADAD), a rare monogenic form of Alzheimer's disease (AD). Established in 2008 with support from the National Institute on Aging (NIA), DIAN Obs is designed to collect comprehensive and uniform data with the aim to characterize brain biology and clinical trajectory of individuals at risk for ADAD. Mutations in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ruxolitinib in treatment-naive or corticosteroid-refractory pediatric patients with chronic graft-versus-host disease: final analysis of the phase 2 REACH5 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Not available.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reconsidering the graphical representation of propensity scores in causal diagrams]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reproducibility of OCT Radiomics after Cataract Surgery: Effects of Media Opacity, Signal strength, and ROI selection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Radiomics features in OCT respond variably to media opacity, signal-to-noise ratio, and ROI definition: most are susceptible to these factors, yet a small subset remains stable across them. Limiting analysis to an anatomically precise retina-bounded ROI and enrolling eyes with comparable cataract status and signal-strength scores may therefore improve reproducibility. Implementing these standardizations will help future OCT-radiomics studies identify the most reliable biomarkers for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mild Photoperiod and Temperature Fluctuations Elicit Tissue-Specific DNA Methylation Changes in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STOML2 Maintains Pluripotency and Cell Cycle Integrity in Human Pluripotent Stem Cells via PHB-ERK Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human pluripotent stem cells (hPSCs) can self-renew indefinitely and differentiate into all three germ layers. However, the primary regulators of hPSC cell cycle dynamics remain unclear. To identify novel regulators of hPSC proliferation, transcriptomic profiling of undifferentiated hPSCs and somatic cells was performed via next-generation sequencing. Stomatin-like protein 2 (STOML2) and prohibitin (PHB) were among the upregulated genes in hPSCs and were closely associated with the extracellular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of the plant-derived prenylated flavonoid icariin on acne vulgaris and atrophic acne scars]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: A prospective cohort study on progestin-primed ovarian stimulation vs. GnRH antagonist in IVF-ICSI cycles: effects on clinical pregnancy and neonatal outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the effectiveness of insecticide-treated net use in preventing malaria among children under five: a quasi-experimental study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ITN use provides meaningful but limited protection against malaria infection among young children in Ghana. Strengthening malaria control will require attention to behavioral and contextual drivers of exposure and improved alignment of interventions with local transmission patterns.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploiting the role of milk extracellular vesicles: a comprehensive analysis on isolation methods, characterization, surface modifications, and their therapeutic applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Milk EVs (MEVs) are a class of extracellular vesicles (EVs) that have attracted significant attention for their potential as natural nanocarriers in drug delivery. These nanosized vesicles (30 - 150 nm) are composed of a lipid bilayer that encapsulates proteins, nucleic acids, and lipids. The biogenesis of EVs involves a tightly regulated "endocytosis-fusion-secretion" pathway, and they are secreted by diverse cells into physiological fluids (blood, urine, and saliva). The isolation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Postoperative Chronic Back Pain Syndrome on the Incidence of Psychiatric and Brain Disorders, and All-Cause Mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PCBPS is associated with increased risks of psychiatric disorders, brain diseases, and mortality. These findings emphasize the need for early identification and integrative management in patients with chronic postsurgical pain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41710284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell assays in microcompartments driven by droplet microfluidics and hydrogel technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microcompartments are miniaturized, uniform units designed to isolate and analyze individual cells, cell pairs, spheroids, or organoids, enabling massive parallel assays. This technique overcomes key limitations of traditional plate-based methods, including limited scale, high cost, and labor-intensive processing. This review highlights technologies that create these compartments, primarily leveraging droplet microfluidics and hydrogel techniques for high-throughput cellular analysis. These...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydration, water requirements, and energy balance from spring to summer in free-living older adults: a doubly labelled water study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The escalating effects of climate change, particularly global warming, are posing an increasing burden on human health. Older adults are particularly susceptible to the impact of extreme heat. Adequate water intake is essential to prevent dehydration in hot environments. Therefore, it is important to understand water turnover (WT) and intake. WT of older adults in hot environments remains unknown. This study aimed at investigating the seasonal effects on WT, total energy expenditure (TEE), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatially resolved isotopic analysis of a uranium-bearing particle from inside the Fukushima Daiichi unit 2 reactor using high-resolution SIMS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nitric oxide induces p53-mediated cell death in human nasal epithelial cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitric oxide (NO) is a key signaling molecule that plays a vital role in maintaining homeostasis of physiological processes such as immune responses and neurotransmission. However, excessive NO production during inflammatory responses to infection can lead to cytotoxicity and tissue damage. The nasal epithelial barrier is a crucial first line of immunological defense against viral infections, and it is likely exposed to excessive NO levels during chronic inflammation. Therefore, clarifying the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methotrexate-associated gynecomastia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of respiratory function with sarcopenia in older outpatients: cross-sectional analysis of baseline data from the JUSTICE-TOKYO prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Respiratory function, particularly VC (% predicted), was significantly associated with sarcopenia in older adult outpatients. VC (% predicted) demonstrates diagnostic performance comparable to PEFR and may serve as a practical parameter for sarcopenia risk identification in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outpatient Cardiac Rehabilitation and Long-Term Clinical Outcomes After Transcatheter Aortic Valve Replacement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The participation rate in outpatient CR after TAVR remains low, with identifiable barriers in Japan. Participation was associated with improved outcomes, suggesting a beneficial management strategy for older patients post-TAVR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The adverse effects of persistent wound stress on patients with type 2 diabetes. Part 1: Pathophysiological mechanisms and multi-organ impacts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Persistent wound stress is an important but easily neglected driver of chronic nonhealing wounds and organ dysfunction in patients with type 2 diabetes mellitus. This review summarizes how the diabetic internal environment, including hyperglycemia, insulin resistance, oxidative stress, vascular damage and immune dysregulation, reshapes the wound microenvironment and disturbs the orderly sequence of hemostasis, inflammation, proliferation and remodeling. We outline the clinical and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex differences in the effect of childhood adversity and coping strategies on psychosis expression: A TwinssCan study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mouse strain and sex differences in the number and distribution of salivary gland IgA plasma cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The present results reveal distinct strain and sex differences in salivary IgA concentrations and in numbers and distribution of SG IgA PCs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protein behavior of the ligand of Numb-protein X 2 (LNX2) in mouse ameloblasts at the maturation stage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results suggest that LNX2 contributes to the degradation of Numb and claudin-7 in ruffle-end ameloblasts during maturation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-disease transcriptomic screening identifies fibroblast-associated mediators shared across periodontitis and rheumatoid arthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RA-associated pathological factors may influence the responsiveness of periodontal tissue to inflammatory stimuli. Although periodontitis and RA are primarily driven by immune-mediated inflammation, tissue-level molecular expression and sensitivity to stimulus may also be altered, providing complementary insights into shared disease mechanisms and their potential relevance for clinical management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral biosciences: The annual review 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The review articles featured in the Journal of Oral Biosciences provide comprehensive insights into contemporary research themes and emerging concepts in oral biosciences. This editorial discusses their key findings and underscores their significance in advancing the understanding of oral health and disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inflammatory characteristics induced by cellular senescence in the junctional epithelium of aged mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The JE of aged mice had molecular hallmarks of cellular senescence. These findings highlight the role of senescence in the aging of periodontal barrier tissue.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbiota-dependent transcriptional priming of lung innate immune cells in a mouse model of LPS-induced sepsis-associated lung injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Commensal microbiota influence transcriptional activity and maturation of pulmonary innate immune cells under experimental conditions, thereby influencing susceptibility to LPS-induced lung injury. Targeting microbiota-guided immune training pathways may allow modulation of pulmonary host defenses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of pharyngolaryngeal injury on nociceptive swallowing reflexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nociceptive stimuli elicit swallowing via mechanisms that are distinct from those activated by water. Reduced desensitization of capsaicin-evoked swallowing after pharyngolaryngeal injury suggests facilitation through TRPV1-dependent pathways, potentially driven by increased TRPV1 expression in petrosal/jugular-complex afferents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lineage tracing of Twist2-expressing cells in mouse taste buds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings support the hypothesis that mesenchymal cells contribute to the taste bud cell population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultracentrifuged serum fractions reveal promotion of dental epithelial proliferation by lactoferrin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lactoferrin, which was enriched in the FBS-3rd fraction, may contribute to the proliferation of dental epithelial cells via the Lrp1-ERK signaling pathway.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determination of the binding affinity between osteoprotegerin (OPG) and receptor activator of nuclear factor-κB ligand (RANKL) utilizing Gaussia luciferase in living cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This bioluminescence-based method provides a simple and accessible platform for evaluating interactions between soluble and membrane-bound proteins in living cells, with potential application in the development of drugs targeting the RANKL-RANK-OPG axis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Porphyromonas gingivalis-derived lipopolysaccharide on the barrier function of cultured junctional epithelial cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PG-LPS disrupts JE barrier function and alters its immunomodulatory properties, potentially contributing to periodontitis progression. These findings enhance our understanding of the underlying causes of periodontitis and inform targeted treatments to maintain JE defense against periodontopathogenic bacteria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamin 2 is involved in osteoblast migration by regulating the organization of F-actin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that dynamin plays an essential role in osteoblast migration by regulating actin cytoskeletal remodeling, particularly through the formation of lamellipodia and stress fibers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solute carrier family 9 member A5 regulated by TGF-β is necessary for dental enamel formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SLC9A5 is a downstream target of TGF-β signaling, which is indispensable for enamel maturation because it maintains ion transport and extracellular pH homeostasis in ameloblasts. Its deficiency leads to reduced mineral density, altered Ca/P composition, and progressive enamel loss. These findings underscore the essential role of SLC9A5 in the long-term structural stability of enamel.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early senescence in salivary glands: A multimodal analysis across parotid, submandibular, and sublingual glands]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: By middle age, salivary glands exhibit early senescent changes, senescent cell accumulation, altered proliferative capacity, and shifts in Jmjd3-mediated epigenetic regulation, which occur in parallel with histological changes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intracellular mechanisms underlying modulation of inhibitory synaptic transmission by appetite-related peptides in the insular cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Given the involvement of the IC in the processing of sensory, interoceptive, and reward-related information, this peptidergic regulation likely influences a range of behaviors, including feeding, pain perception, and addiction. Elucidating these intricate mechanisms could facilitate the development of novel therapeutic interventions for disorders such as obesity, chronic pain, and substance dependence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41714011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Combustible Cigarette Smoking, Electronic Cigarette Use, and Related Behaviors Among Korean Adults: An 11-Year Analysis of Data from the Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (2013-2023)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While traditional smoking prevalence continues to decline, the increasing prevalence of e-cigarette use and dual use poses new public health challenges. These trends are particularly evident among young males and low-income groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vasopressin and Oxytocin: From Basic to Clinic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inactivation of bio-aerosolized viruses by applying pulsed electric field]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coronavirus disease 19 (COVID-19) pandemic has highlighted the need for effective countermeasures to prevent the transmission of infectious viruses contained in bio-aerosols, particularly in indoor environments with limited ventilation. Pulsed electric fields (PEF) can electrically capture aerosols and inactivate microorganisms within these aerosols. Our study, with the goal of establishing a new spatial purification technology utilizing PEF, aimed to clarify the inactivation effect of PEF on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fundamentals of Neurogastroenterology: Physiological Aspects and Clinical Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The digestive tract plays a key role in maintaining homeostasis and the general well-being of the human body via complex physiological functions. These gastrointestinal functions include motility; mixing of ingesta with pancreatic, biliary, and enteric secretions; absorption of digested nutrients; and disposal of undigested residues. Such processes usually occur without conscious perception. However, about 30-40% of the general population complain of digestive symptoms, often triggered by meal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetic immunoprecipitation assay for the isolation of adalimumab and degradation products in preclinical biological samples]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Evaluation of pharmacokinetics is a cornerstone in the developability assessment of therapeutic monoclonal antibodies (mAbs). For accurate evaluation of mAbs' concentration-time profile, administered mAbs should be isolated from the interfering host proteins in serum samples. While there are multiple approaches to purify and quantify the administered mAb, they are limited by drawbacks such as low specificity, relatively-large plasma volume requirements, and tedious procedures for sample...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Individual level cognitive social capital and subsequent health and well-being among older adults in Japan: An outcome-wide study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cognitive social capital is broadly associated with multidimensional health and well-being in later life, especially within psychological domains. Given the observed heterogeneity, approaches to strengthening social connections may benefit from considering group-specific characteristics. Community efforts to foster social capital may help promote psychological health and healthy aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catalytic roles of two serine residues in flavin-dependent quinone reductase HadB]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[HadB is flavin mononucleotide (FMN)-dependent quinone reductase that plays a key role in preventing quinone accumulation during the biodegradation of halogenated phenols and nitrophenols. Although the reaction mechanism of HadB has been studied, its structure-function relationship remains unclear. In this study, the predicted structure of FMN-bound HadB, generated using AlphaFold version 3.0, revealed that it belongs to the oxygen (O(2))-insensitive FMN-dependent nitroreductase family. FMN is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polysaccharides-protein-based microencapsulation of anthocyanin-rich riceberry rice extract and its incorporation into rice gel matrices via 3D food printing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate the effects of selected extraction conditions, microencapsulation systems, and 3D food printing on the stability and bioavailability of bioactive compounds from riceberry rice. The effects of extraction temperature, solvent type, and solid-to-solvent ratio on total phenolic content (TPC), total anthocyanin content (TAC), and antioxidant activity were evaluated. Among the tested conditions, extraction at 80 °C using 50% (v/v) ethanol and a 1:10 solid-to-solvent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A circadian rheostat drives proton electrochemical gradients to optimize cell-type-specific growth in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant growth relies on the activity of key transcription factors. Here, we uncover a mechanism for organ-specific growth driven by opposing electrochemical signals that propagate in a cell-type-specific manner. Using a genetically encoded pH sensor and a pH-sensitive dye, we show that apoplastic pH in epidermal cells oscillates antiphasically relative to phloem pH. The clock component CCA1 lowers apoplastic pH in hypocotyl epidermal cells while increasing it in companion cells. This opposing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment fidelity in nursing education research: Striking a balance between rigor and real-world relevance as a contemporary challenge]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Reconceptualizing treatment fidelity allows nursing education to prepare researchers who balance consistency with meaningful adaptation. From this perspective, treatment fidelity is understood not only as a procedural requirement but also as an interpretive framework, which increases rigor while remaining responsive to real-world conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moving the antibody: Molecular dynamics for molecular mechanisms and developability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41713226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relational experiences and meaning-making with significant others in patients with hematopoietic malignancies at end of life: A phenomenological study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients actively construct meaning through relationships across multiple contexts while navigating dialectical tensions between dependence and selfhood. This relational model may guide nurses in assessing relational needs and supporting meaningful living at EOL. Limitations include the single-site design in Japan and the cross-sectional nature of data collection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contrast-Associated Acute Kidney Injury After Thrombectomy for Ischemic Stroke: Prognostic Impact and CAN-REST Predictive Score]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Contrast-associated acute kidney injury (CA-AKI) is a potentially preventable complication after exposure to iodinated contrast media. In patients undergoing endovascular thrombectomy (EVT) for acute ischemic stroke (AIS), the incidence and clinical impact are poorly characterized, and no validated prediction tool is currently available. The aim of this study was to assess the incidence and prognostic significance of CA-AKI in EVT-treated patients with AIS and to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging Technologies and Vulnerabilities in Older Adults Without Cognitive Impairments: Systematic Review of Qualitative Evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This systematic review, which focused on the perceptions of older adults without cognitive impairments, enriches the vast literature about the everyday management and care of seniors by exploring the ethical implications of ETs. This research is complementary to another systematic review of qualitative evidence, which analyzed the views of older people with cognitive disorders on the same topic. Although a certain ambivalence in the use of ETs was identified by both population...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of endometrial CD169<sup>+</sup> macrophages essential for Treg cell accumulation and implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Successful pregnancy requires coordinated regulation between the innate and adaptive immune systems. Regulatory T (Treg) cells are essential for establishing maternal immune tolerance to the semi-allogeneic fetus, but the innate immune cells that modulate this process remain poorly defined. Here, we identify CD169^(+) macrophages in the endometrium as critical regulators of Treg cell recruitment and implantation. These CD169^(+) macrophages are endometrial localized, exhibit an anti-inflammatory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intimate partner violence and psychological well-being: Do housing conditions moderate the effects?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prior studies link intimate partner violence (IPV) to poor mental health, especially among those with low socioeconomic status or limited support. However, few have explored how housing conditions may moderate these psychological effects. This study investigates the relationship between IPV and psychological well-being, with a particular focus on two outcomes: depressive symptoms and life satisfaction. It also examines whether housing conditions amplify or mitigate individuals' psychological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electronic Transmission Signatures of Hydrogen-Bond Topology in Model Antiparallel β-Sheet Segments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the electronic conductance of peptide-based molecular junctions modeled on antiparallel β-sheet motifs of H-bonded glycine complexes, using density functional theory (DFT) combined with the nonequilibrium Green's function (NEGF) formalism. Our results demonstrate that distinct hydrogen-bonding topologies, including central versus terminal ring closure and compact versus extended loop geometries, produce characteristic transmission spectra and stepwise, nonlinear current-voltage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationship between lower limb proprioception and balance performance in children with cerebral palsy: a multisystem and multi-joint approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Postural control deficits in children with CP affect multiple systems, and each system is associated with joint-specific proprioceptive impairments (particularly at the hip), rather than overall proprioceptive accuracy. These findings suggest task-dependent and pathology-dependent associations, the latter likely reflecting limitations in compensatory proprioceptive reweighting across lower-limb joints.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of maturity stages on the optimization of fecal sludge and organic waste co-composting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Co-composting fecal sludge and organic solid waste offers a sustainable solution to waste management challenges in developing nations like Bangladesh. This study evaluates the efficacy of co-composting two waste streams- organic solid waste and fecal sludge mixed in a 75:25 ratio using fecal sludge with two different maturity periods: 14 days and 6 months. Using a bench-scale setup, critical parameters such as pH, temperature, moisture content, electrical conductivity, and the carbon-to-nitrogen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An integrated multi-method assessment of toxic element contamination and associated ecological and health risks in heavily contaminated]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Paddy soils in rice-producing developing countries are particularly vulnerable to contamination from battery recycling operations and untreated industrial effluents. This study examined toxic element (As, Cr, Cu, Ni, Pb, and Zn) concentrations in paddy soils across three areas of Bangladesh: a battery recycling area (BRA), an industrial area (IA), and a sustainably managed area (SMA). ICP-OES, XRD, and SEM-EDS were used to confirm the TE concentrations, mineral composition, and spatial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical nodal positive disease is associated with greater surgical complexity in salvage lung resection after tyrosine kinase inhibitor therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41712050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of contact needle technique on cancer-related fatigue in palliative care patients: a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CNT may be a safe, gentle, and potentially effective intervention for managing fatigue and distress in palliative care patients with advanced cancer. Further research is warranted to confirm these findings and assess long-term outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The optimal conditioning intensity of stem cell transplantation for acute myeloid leukemia in complete remission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strength gains and absence of hypertrophy and cross-education in knee extensors following short-term low-volume eccentric training in untrained young men]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multifunctional LepR⁺ skeletal stem/progenitor cells for bone and marrow homeostasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Bone is a multifunctional organ that provides structural support and hosts the bone marrow, a key site for hematopoiesis and systemic homeostasis. These dual features have long attracted the attention of both bone biologists and hematologists. Each field has pursued the identification of stem-like cells responsible for hard tissue formation and the regulatory microenvironment/niche that supports hematopoietic stem cells (HSCs), which give rise to all blood cell lineages. Converging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CSF protein biomarkers are associated with atrophy and symptom severity in genetic FTD: a GENFI study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure function relationship of paracentral visual field impairment in myopic patients with primary open-angle glaucoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting survival in patients with heart failure aged 80 years and older]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The prognostic model developed in this study (JROADHF over 80 Score) demonstrated satisfactory performance in predicting mortality in a cohort of older Japanese patients with heart failure. Estimating prognosis based on factors obtainable in routine clinical practice has the potential for widespread implementation in clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41711736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260220030053&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>