<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:26:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electronic coupling in a synthetic model of the Cu-cofactor unit of the P<sub>M</sub> state in cytochrome <em>c</em> oxidase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A hydroquinone-imidazole-Cu(II) complex reproduces the Tyr-His-Cu unit of cytochrome c oxidase. Laser-induced EPR and DFT reveal a semiquinone radical electronically isolated from Cu(II) by orthogonal orbital alignment. The weak magnetic exchange underscores how geometry governs coupling, providing insight into transient states of metalloenzymes and their synthetic analogues.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FAST-CRISPR: Fusogenic Association and Secured Transfection of CRISPR/Cas9 Ribonucleoproteins Using Lipid-Silica Hybrid Nanoparticles for Therapeutic Genome Editing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clinical translation of CRISPR/Cas9 therapeutics is challenged by inefficient cytosolic delivery and toxicity issues associated with viral vectors and nanoparticle-based carriers. To overcome these concerns, herein we report a lipid-silica hybrid nanoparticle platform for fusogenic association and secured transfection of CRISPR/Cas9 (FAST-CRISPR), designed for rapid cytosolic delivery of CRISPR/Cas9 ribonucleoproteins, followed by efficient gene editing. Through direct fusion with the plasma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of MAO-B Inhibitors on Cognition in Patients with Parkinson's Disease: A Systematic Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Rasagiline may provide global cognitive benefits in PD, but MAO-B inhibitors, including rasagiline, generally did not demonstrate significant effects on individual cognitive domains. These findings suggest limited cognitive impacts of MAO-B inhibitors beyond managing the motor symptoms. Further large-scale, long-term studies using domain-specific cognitive assessments are warranted to clarify their roles in cognitive performance in patients with PD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of <em>Ecklonia cava</em> Kjellman Extract Complex in Respiratory Health: A Randomized, Double-Blind, Placebo-Controlled, Multicenter Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrialization, air pollution, and respiratory infections have highlighted the importance of maintaining respiratory health. Ecklonia cava Kjellman (EC) has anti-inflammatory, antioxidative, and anti-allergic effects and therapeutic potential for respiratory symptoms. We evaluated the efficacy and safety of Ecklonia cava Kjellman extract complex (EEC), composed of EC and Chrysanthemum indicum Linnaeus (C. indicum) extract, in respiratory health. A randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Adolescent Non-Suicidal Self-Injury: A Narrative Review of Theoretical Models and Evidence-Based Psychotherapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DBT is currently the first-line treatment for NSSIs in adolescents. However, the field must move toward personalized care. Future research should focus on validating alternative therapies through head-to-head randomized controlled trials, identifying the core change mechanisms across treatments, and implementing stepwise care models to improve accessibility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virtual lab of artificial intelligence agents accelerating nanobody design against SARS-CoV-2 variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI)-driven research frameworks are reshaping the boundaries of biomedical discovery. The Virtual Lab exemplifies this transformation, assembling large language model (LLM) agents into coordinated scientific teams functioning as investigators, specialists, and critics. The system autonomously designed, scored, and refined nanobody candidates against emerging SARS-CoV-2 variants, and subsequently validated them experimentally. These findings demonstrate how AI can move...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A developmental stage-aware graph transformer framework for automated bone-age assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: By leveraging a skeletal graph structure based on anatomical relationships and incorporating a developmental stage-aware processing mechanism, the DSGTF framework provides an accurate and efficient automated solution for clinical bone-age assessment. The proposed approach exhibits strong stability and consistency across different age groups and sexes, making it a reliable tool for real-world medical applications. This model effectively simulates the clinical assessment process by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A unified framework integrating local effect and DNA damage for the derivation of cell survival model parameters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: When the same energy is delivered to a cellular target, DNA damage and the resulting cellular response may vary depending on the density and distribution pattern of the energy delivered to the critical volume of each cell. DNA damage can be quantitated based on the pattern of dose distribution over the sub-micrometer volumes in nucleus. DNA double-strand breaks (DSBs) are considered the most critical events for cellular effects. Local effect model (LEM), DNA damage model (DDM), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of the synergistic effect of co-gasification of rice husk and cashew nut shell in a dynamic environment of nitrogen and steam in a fixed-bed reactor system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the depletion of energy resources like coal, dependence on cleaner energy carriers like biomass is growing in the present century. Gasification is the most renowned and more energetically efficient technology for extracting this energy via the generation of syngas than other thermochemical conversion processes. It can produce power, liquid fuel, and valuable chemicals like methanol, upon which the present civilization relies. In contrast, other thermochemical processes can produce products...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Versatile applications of LIG-based biosensors: from environmental monitoring to biomedical innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graphene-based biosensors are recognized as one of the most innovative tools in the fields of biological and medical diagnostics. This paper investigates the laser-induced graphene process and its impact on the electrical and chemical properties of biosensors. By employing advanced laser methods, researchers can finely tune both the architecture and functional characteristics of graphene, thereby improving the sensor's ability to detect specific substances with greater accuracy and selectivity....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erythropoietin-derived Non-erythropoietic Peptides Conferring Oxidative Stress Resistance to Keratinocytes and Fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Concentration Type I Atelocollagen Enhances Early Cartilage Regeneration: An In Vivo Comparative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High-concentration atelocollagen-based scaffolds significantly enhanced both the efficiency and quality of cartilage regeneration by providing mechanical support and a favorable microenvironment for chondrogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporary mechanical support in fulminant myocarditis: prognostic factors and clinical implications from the FULLMOON study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite a relatively young cohort, FM requiring t-MCS is associated with a high 1-year mortality rate. Timely recognition and early referral to specialized ECMO centers before cardiac arrest are critical.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reactive oxygen species-mediated inactivation of Listeria monocytogenes and Staphylococcus aureus induced by pulsed plasma treatment: influence of duty ratio and unit time]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reactive oxygen species (ROS) are key mediators of plasma-induced microbial inactivation. This study investigated the influence of pulsed plasma parameters, specifically duty ratio and unit time, on the inactivation of Listeria monocytogenes and Staphylococcus aureus. Pulsed plasma-activated water PAW was generated under controlled discharge conditions, where the unit time, defined as the duration of a single plasma discharge cycle, and the duty ratio, the fraction of the unit time during which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Periungual Bowen Disease Mimicking a Melanocytic Nevus: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Periungual Bowen disease is an uncommon form of squamous cell carcinoma in situ that may mimic benign pigmented lesions, such as melanocytic nevi. We report a case of a 36-year-old man who presented with an irregularly shaped brown macule on the periungual area of the right third finger, with a history of gradual enlargement over 8 years. The patient reported occasional periungual trauma because of nail picking but had no significant medical history. A punch biopsy was performed, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shear-driven finite-velocity diffusion and its generalization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We consider shear-driven finite-velocity diffusion, both normal and anomalous. In the macroscopic description, this leads to a telegrapher's or Cattaneo-like equation. We analyze the probability density function, and the corresponding moments are obtained analytically. We show that the system exhibits a characteristic crossover of the anomalous dynamics. We also explore corresponding processes under stochastic resetting and find that the systems reach non-equilibrium stationary states in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacterial sensing and response for neutralization and detoxification of environmental ammonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ammonia present in the environment is a major source of nitrogen, but it can be toxic to bacteria. While the biochemical mechanisms involved in the metabolic detoxification of cellular ammonia are well understood, little is known about how bacteria manage toxic external ammonia to survive, especially when ammonia is present as a waste product at high concentrations. Here, we demonstrate that a two-component system consisting of the sensor kinase GrtK and the response regulator GrtR is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-effectiveness of female-only and gender-neutral HPV vaccination strategies in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both female-only 4vHPV and 9vHPV strategies are cost-effective under Japan's economic standards. Furthermore, GNV with 9vHPV provides greater health benefits and cost-effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide insights on early childhood neurodevelopment during a global health crisis: evidence from COVID-19 in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The COVID-19 pandemic led to significant developmental declines among young children, particularly in language and social domains and among toddlers. Boys were more adversely affected than girls, especially in language and socioemotional skills, highlighting sex-related vulnerabilities. Prioritising early screening and interventions targeting these key domains, alongside sex-sensitive strategies and caregiver support, will be essential to mitigate developmental disruptions during...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of metal-assisted chemical etching for microscale Si structures using Arrhenius method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-assisted chemical etching (MACE) has emerged as a promising method for fabricating high-aspect-ratio Si microstructures without the damage or complexity associated with plasma-based etching. However, its thermal activation behavior and the role of catalyst morphology remain poorly understood, especially at the microscale. This study systematically investigated the effects of etchant temperature, metal thickness, and pattern geometry on the etching kinetics of MACE. By constructing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between the Duration of Elevated Perfusion Pressure and Neurological Outcomes in Out-of-Hospital Cardiac Arrest Survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The duration of a MAP >80 mmHg during the 0-48 and 25-48 hour periods after ROSC was associated with good neurological outcomes at six months in OHCA survivors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524055/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic effects of <em>Angelica gigas</em> Nakai in experimental rat model of polycystic ovary syndrome with network pharmacology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) is a prevalent endocrine disorder in reproductive-aged women, characterized by disrupted ovarian function due to multiple factors. Angelica gigas Nakai (AG), known for its multi-compound and multi-target properties, was investigated as a potential therapy using an integrated approach combining network pharmacology and experimental validation. Active compounds of AG were matched with PCOS-related genes, and 45 overlapping targets were identified. Network analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lariciresinol and secoisolariciresinol enhance myogenic differentiation and mitochondrial biogenesis in C2C12 myotubes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lariciresinol (LR) and secoisolariciresinol (SLR), phytochemicals found in pine bark and flaxseed, are known for their anticancer effects, risk reduction of cardiovascular disease, hormone regulation, and antioxidant activities. However, researches on their effects on skeletal muscle function are scarce. Therefore, this study aimed to investigate the efficacy of LR and SLR in promoting muscle hypertrophy and mitochondrial function in C2C12 mouse-derived myoblasts. LR and SLR were found to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bi-dimensional health space mapping: machine learning analysis of population health dynamics in Korean and Dutch cohorts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Health spans a broad spectrum, encompassing various biological and lifestyle factors. The complexity of biological systems necessitates for integrating diverse factors into a unified biomarker. We constructed a health space model that highlights metabolism and oxidative stress as key indicators for tracking healthy aging and mapping health trajectories. To ensure cross-ethnic relevance, we used data from the Dutch Nutrition Questionnaires plus and Korean National Health and Nutrition Examination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of <em>Lactobacillus</em>-fermented garlic extract on hangover relief: a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled crossover study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hangovers are a set of unpleasant symptoms following excessive alcohol intake. This study evaluated the effects of Lactobacillus-fermented garlic extract (LFGE) on hangover symptoms in a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled, crossover trial involving 25 participants. Hangover severity was assessed using the Acute Hangover Scale (AHS) at 1, 2, 4, and 15 h post-consumption, while blood alcohol and acetaldehyde levels were measured at multiple time points up to 15 h. LFGE significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of temperature distribution and heat penetration during retort sterilization on the quality characteristics of canned whelk (<em>Buccinum striatissimum</em>)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study analyzed the temperature distribution and heat penetration characteristics during canned whelk production using two retort sterilizers. The quality characteristics of the products were also analyzed. The structural characteristics of the retorts, product loading methods, and product quantity affected various characteristics of the thermal profiles, including the range of secondary sterilization temperatures, the cold and hot locations in the two retorts, and the heat penetration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-obesity effect of <em>Bifidobacterium adolescentis</em> SPM2022, isolated from Korean adult]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to evaluate the anti-obesity effect of Bifidobacterium adolescentis SPM2022 (SPM2022). Culture supernatant of SPM2022 reduced lipid accumulation (p < 0.01) and expression of adipogenic genes (p < 0.001) during 3T3-L1 differentiation. The effects on anti-obesity and lipid metabolism were assessed in the high fat diet (HFD)-induced obese C57BL6 mouse after 4 weeks of obese induction. Experimental groups (n = 6/group): normal diet, HFD, and HFD fed with 10⁹ CFU/day of SPM2022....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of flavonoid, carotenoid, and organic acid profiles in various commercial dried citrus chips]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study analyzes the flavonoid, carotenoid, and organic acid profiles of 18 commercial dried citrus chips, including 6 Korean and 12 imported cultivars, which are categorized into citron, pomelo, and mandarin groups based on their origin. Hesperidin and narirutin predominate in citron and mandarin groups, whereas naringin is prevalent in pomelo group. Green tangerine chip showed the highest contents of hesperidin (3180.24 ± 296.55 mg/100 g) and narirutin (424.98 ± 9.23 mg/100 g), while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking the potential of Contract Research Organizations in Africa's clinical trials ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite representing 18% of the world's population and 20% of the disease burden, only an estimated 2% of global clinical trials include at least one study site in Africa. This underscores the critical need for continued research on how to overcome clinical trial challenges on the continent. In countries with established reputations for clinical trials, Contract Research Organizations (CROs) play a vital role, accounting for half of the research workforce and effectively managing clinical trials...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction Model for Low Bone Mineral Density in Cancer Survivors and Age-Matched Controls Using a Causal Bayesian Network: A Nationwide Population-Based Study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Causal Bayesian network modeling identified muscle mass as a key modifiable factor influencing BMD among cancer survivors. These findings highlight the importance of muscle-preserving lifestyle interventions, including resistance exercise and adequate protein intake, in survivorship care. The CBN approach provides a framework for identifying individualized risk pathways and can support personalized bone-health management strategies in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Exploratory Pilot Study of Brain Functional Connectivity and Heart Rate Variability in Male Children With Autism Spectrum Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Resting-state EEG coherence may be associated with the clinical characteristics of ASD, and vmHRV may exert a moderating effect on this relationship. These preliminary findings suggest that the concurrent evaluation of brain and autonomic functions can be useful for elucidating the pathophysiology of ASD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation-Focused Psychotherapy for Children With Emotion Dysregulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emotion dysregulation is a transdiagnostic risk factor in childhood psychopathology that contributes to externalizing behaviors. To address this, regulation-focused psychotherapy for children (RFP-C) has been developed as a manualized, short-term psychodynamic intervention for 5- to 12-year-olds with externalizing behaviors rooted in underlying emotion dysregulation and affective conflict. The therapy follows a structured protocol comprising 16 child play therapy sessions and 4 parent sessions....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evidence-Based Psychotherapy for Disruptive Behavior Disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Disruptive behavior disorder (DBD), which includes oppositional defiant disorder and conduct disorder, is among the most common externalizing disorders in childhood and adolescence. This review aimed to identify evidence-based psychotherapies for DBD and summarize their empirical foundations and characteristics. We searched for randomized controlled trials and systematic reviews using PubMed, PsycINFO, and Google Scholar, focusing on major evidence-based guidelines from the National Institute...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerebellar subregional structural changes across the Alzheimer's disease continuum: a longitudinal analysis of cognitive and behavioural correlates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although traditionally viewed as relatively spared in Alzheimer's disease (Ad), the cerebellum is increasingly recognized for its contribution to cognitive and behavioural dysfunction. However, longitudinal data delineating subregional cerebellar involvement across the Ad continuum remain limited. In this study, we investigated longitudinal cerebellar atrophy and its clinical correlates in 259 older adults classified via amyloid PET into four biomarker-defined groups: cognitively normal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cortical asymmetry in autosomal dominant Alzheimer's disease progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The cortical asymmetry index evaluates the cortical thickness asymmetry between hemispheres. We investigated cortical asymmetry index in asymptomatic and symptomatic mutation carriers of autosomal dominant Alzheimer's disease to explore the brain asymmetry within the Alzheimer's disease continuum. Sixty baseline T1-weighted MRI scans were obtained from the Clinic Barcelona cohort. Baseline and longitudinal MRI data from 564 participants within the dominantly inherited Alzheimer network...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Marked Reversibility of Functional Small Airway Disease Following Reduction of Hazardous Inhalational Exposure: A PRM CT Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a case illustrating the role of parametric response mapping (PRM) in detecting and monitoring small airway disease (SAD) related to occupational inhalational exposure. A 52-year-old woman, a lifelong never-smoker with chronic occupational exposure to metal cutting-fluid fumes and metal particles, presented with exertional dyspnea and moderate airflow obstruction. PRM CT revealed PRM-functional small airway disease (PRM-fSAD) of 15.7% and PRM-emphysema of 0.2%. After 1.5 years of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tissue-Resident ILC2s Across Organs: Heterogeneity, Niche Crosstalk, and Shared Regulatory Circuits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Type 2 innate lymphoid cells (ILC2s) are an important source of innate cytokines that contribute to allergic inflammation. Recent studies have also suggested that ILC2s play a biological role in peripheral tissues such as lung, fat, intestine and skin, controlled by alarmins, neuropeptides and environmental factors. Furthermore, emerging studies have shown that tissues including the pancreas, uterus and meninges contain ILC2s that contribute to normal biological function. Here, we review recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aging Mediates Inflammatory Transformation of Kidney-Resident Macrophages via Thrombospondin-1 Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kidney-resident macrophages (KRMs) are long-lived immune cells crucial for maintaining kidney homeostasis, with roles that vary depending on kidney condition. Their phenotypes can exert different effects on kidney status, but how the phenotypes of KRMs evolve in aged kidneys and the resulting impacts on kidney homeostasis remain poorly understood. Through single-cell RNA sequencing, we identified a phenotypic shift in KRMs within aged kidneys characterized by increased oxidative phosphorylation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondria Derived From iPSCs Control by Reciprocal Regulation of Th17/Treg and Anti-Fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several studies have reported the immunoregulatory effects of transplanting mitochondria from mesenchymal stem cells. However, whether similar effects can be achieved using mitochondria derived from human induced pluripotent stem cells (iPSCs; iMito) has not yet been investigated. Here, we examined the protective effects of iMito in a dextran sodium sulfate (DSS)-induced colitis mouse model. To address this, we investigated the effects both in vitro and in vivo. First, iMitos were transferred...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cytokine Engineering in CAR-T Cell Therapy: Next-Generation Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimeric Ag receptor (CAR)-T cell therapy has demonstrated success primarily in B-cell malignancies, but efficacy in solid tumors remains limited by Ag heterogeneity, immunosuppressive tumor microenvironments, and restricted infiltration. Cytokine engineering has emerged as a promising strategy to overcome these barriers. Fourth-generation CAR-T cells, known as T cells redirected for universal cytokine-mediated killing, demonstrated the feasibility of localized immune modulation through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IL7-TBRII, a Dual Cytokine Modulator Targeting IL-7 and TGF-β Pathways, Inhibits Tumor Progression and Metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor-infiltrating CD8^(+) T cells are a key determinant of anti-tumor efficacy in immunotherapy. IL-7 has been explored as a cytokine therapy to expand CD8^(+) T cells, showing promising anti-tumor effects in preclinical models. However, clinical outcomes remain limited, likely due to the immunosuppressive tumor microenvironment. To enhance the efficacy of IL-7 therapy, we reanalyzed publicly available single-cell RNA-sequencing (scRNA-seq) data of tumors treated with IL-7, identifying elevated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current practices and considerations in intense pulsed light therapy for meibomian gland dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intense pulsed light (IPL) therapy has emerged as a promising modality for the treatment of meibomian gland dysfunction (MGD), a leading cause of evaporative dry eye disease. However, its clinical application varies significantly across studies, with notable procedural heterogeneity in device selection, treatment intervals, anatomical coverage, and adjunctive strategies. This comprehensive review synthesizes 110 clinical studies to delineate prevailing procedural trends and identify...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current therapeutic landscape of dry eye and meibomian gland disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic outcomes of oral cefcapene in meibomitis-related keratoconjunctivitis: A Propensity-matched cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adjunctive use of short-term oral cefcapene therapy alongside standard eyelid hygiene measures resulted in a significant reduction in CSSs in patients with MRKC. However, this reduction was not accompanied by a statistically significant improvement in subjective symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conjunctival microvascular alterations in dry eye disease: A comparative study of Sjögren's and non-Sjögren's subtypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings reveal distinct conjunctival microvascular signatures in patients with SSDE, and support vessel diameter as a discriminator. The association between hemodynamic changes and MGD parameters in the NSDE group underscores the interplay between MGD and conjunctival microcirculation in NSDE. The differences in microvasculature identified in this study may serve as valuable biomarkers for DED subtype classification and the development of personalized treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the cost-effectiveness of artificial intelligence-enhanced osteoporosis screening in men and women using routine chest radiographs in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[South Korea, now a "super-aged" society, faces a rising burden of fragility fractures, yet underdiagnosis remains a major barrier, with limited DXA access restricting early detection. Artificial intelligence (AI) applied to routine chest radiographs enables opportunistic screening. In March 2025, Osteo Signal, a deep learning model developed in the South Korean population, received regulatory approval for use in both men and women. Unlike prior evaluations in women only, this study assessed its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Korean Colorectal Cancer Reveals Novel Driver Gene and Clinically Relevant Mutations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colorectal cancer (CRC) ranks as the third leading cause of cancer-related deaths worldwide, characterized by genomic heterogeneity arising from ethnic and interindividual differences. Producing region-specific data to characterize ethnic-specific somatic mutations is essential for advancing CRC research. Additionally, accurate somatic mutation detection requires paired tissue analyses to account for interindividual diversity. This study aims to highlight the importance of ethnic diversity in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma GFAP as a mediator and moderator of Aβ, tau, and neurodegeneration in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astrogliosis is increasingly recognized as a critical component of Alzheimer's disease (AD) pathology, but its precise mechanistic contribution to the interplay among amyloid-β (Aβ), tau, and neurodegeneration remains unclear. Glial fibrillary acidic protein (GFAP), a widely used biomarker of astrocytic activation, shows strong associations with both Aβ and tau pathologies; however, its causal and modulatory involvement in disease progression has yet to be fully delineated. In this study, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combination of Atelocollagen Gel With Induced Pluripotent Stem Cell-Derived Tenocyte for Rotator Cuff Tendon Regeneration in a Rat Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study demonstrates that an injection of atelocollagen containing iPSC-TCs into the lesion after rotator cuff repair produced excellent residual effects. The addition of iPSC-TCs embedded in atelocollagen to a surgically repaired rotator cuff could improve tendon quality by increasing type I collagen production.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoptotic Cancer Cell-Primed Cancer-Associated Fibroblasts Suppress Immunosuppressive Macrophages via WISP-1-Integrin α5β3-STAT1 Signaling in Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell death within the tumor microenvironment (TME) plays a pivotal role in shaping tumor-specific immunity. The dynamic interplay between cancer-associated fibroblasts (CAFs) and tumor-associated macrophages (TAMs) is central to tumor progression and immune regulation. Here, we show that conditioned medium (CM) from lung CAFs exposed to apoptotic cancer cells selectively impairs the survival of M2-like macrophages, induces apoptosis, and promotes their reprogramming toward an M1-like phenotype....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AVN944 Elicits Apoptotic Responses and Impedes Tumorigenic Potential in Ewing's Sarcoma Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inosine monophosphate dehydrogenase 2 (IMPDH2) is implicated in survival and proliferation of cancer cells because of its role in guanine nucleotide biosynthesis. This study evaluates the efficacy of AVN944, an IMPDH2 inhibitor, as a treatment for Ewing's sarcoma, a challenging malignancy in pediatric and young adult patients. Gene expression data, as well as clinical outcomes for sarcoma patients, from The Cancer Genome Atlas (TCGA) were analyzed to determine the association between IMPDH2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circulating Branched-Chain Amino Acids are Associated with Higher Odds of Obesity: Findings from the FiLWHEL Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher circulating BCAA profiles, independent of dietary BCAA intake levels, were associated with a higher prevalence of obesity, with no evidence of interaction in the divergent independent associations between dietary and circulating BCAAs and obesity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling scalable ferroelectric-based future generation vertical NAND flash with bonding-friendly architecture: strategies for erase and disturb optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel ferroelectric VNAND (Fe-VNAND) architecture based on a TCAT (Terabit Cell Array Transistor) structure, integrating an amorphous IGZO channel and a band-engineered filler insulator for enhanced erase and disturbance characteristics. To overcome the limitations of poor hole transport in IGZO, a tailored erase (ERS) scheme employing stepped dummy word-line biasing is introduced, which effectively mitigates over-erasure at the bottom of the NAND string and enables reliable bitline...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Timed up and go test as a screening tool for exercise capacity after lung cancer resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TUGT demonstrates significant correlations with both CPET and 6MWT and may serve as a simple, feasible, and clinically valuable screening tool for identifying patients with reduced postoperative exercise capacity. Incorporating TUGT into routine postoperative evaluations may facilitate early detection of reduced functional capacity and guide timely referral for pulmonary rehabilitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors governing tumor penetration of nanomedicines: intrinsic and extrinsic determinants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanomedicine-based drug delivery has shown considerable promise for cancer therapy; however, the efficient transport and deep penetration of nanoparticles within solid tumors remain major challenges for clinical translation. These limitations arise from the combined effects of nanoparticle physicochemical properties and biological transport barriers acting across multiple biological scales, rather than being governed by any single isolated parameter. Accordingly, nanoparticle transport and tumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SABRE Acethydrazide as a Co-Substrate Agent for Quantitative Analysis of Submicromolar N-Heterocyclic Compounds Using Parahydrogen Hyperpolarization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Signal amplification by reversible exchange (SABRE) hyperpolarization is a well-known method for enhancing nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) signals by transferring para-hydrogen-derived polarization to the analyte of interest. However, due to inherent sensitivity limitations, detecting analyte signals at micromolar (μM) or lower concentrations remains challenging. This study proposes acethydrazide (ACH) as a novel co-substrate, which significantly improves SABRE hyperpolarization efficiency and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multicenter Analysis of the Learning Curve for Endoscopic Ultrasound-Guided Gallbladder Drainage: A Cumulative Sum Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Based on CUSUM analysis, approximately 23 procedures may be required to achieve technical proficiency in EUS-GBD with regard to minimizing adverse events, while 27 procedures are necessary to reach proficiency in terms of procedure time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Energy-Based Devices for the Treatment of Cutaneous Lesions in Patients With Lupus Erythematosus and Dermatomyositis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: EBD treatments may provide cosmetic improvement in selected LE and DM patients and are generally safe. Larger controlled studies are needed to confirm efficacy and establish optimal protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fractional Exhaled Nitric Oxide for Diagnosing Eosinophilic Chronic Rhinosinusitis: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FeNO levels are significantly elevated in ECRS patients compared to non-ECRS patients. The high diagnostic odds ratio suggests that FeNO has potential as a noninvasive diagnostic tool for ECRS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nerve Stimulator-Guided Epidural Anesthesia in a Rhesus Macaque (Macaca mulatta)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A male rhesus macaque underwent inguinal hernia repair under general anesthesia, with epidural anesthesia administered at the fourth lumbar vertebral level using a nerve stimulator-guided technique. This method provided effective analgesia and stable hemodynamics, supporting its potential as an objective alternative to landmark-based approaches in nonhuman primates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The intersection of health inequalities and COVID-19: Evidence from National Health Insurance Big Data in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Health inequalities persist along lines of income and wealth, shaped by unequal access to healthcare, differences in health behaviors, and pre-existing chronic conditions. The COVID-19 pandemic further put families in Korea under health strain and worsened their health outcomes. This study investigates how pre-existing socioeconomic disparities intersect with health outcomes. Using the national administrative health big data provided by the Korean National Health Insurance Service, we employ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Super-Resolution" Deep Learning Image Reconstruction in Dynamic Myocardial Perfusion: A Prospective Evaluation of Image Quality and Hemodynamic Parameters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SR-DLR and NR-DLR significantly enhanced image quality by reducing noise and improving SNR and CNR while maintaining hemodynamic quantification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoscopic predictors of iron deficiency in Helicobacter pylori gastritis: a Kyoto classification-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Younger age, female sex, and larger hyperplastic polyps (≥5 mm) are associated with iron deficiency in patients with H. pylori gastritis. These features may help identify patients at higher risk of iron deficiency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomechanical Assessment of IOL Stability and Position Based on Suture and Inlet Variations in the Canabrava Double-flanged Technique]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Caution is advised in patients with a predisposition to iris chafing as the risk may persist regardless of fixation parameters.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Versatile Microfluidic Cryogel Microbead Platform for Modular Biofabrication and Tissue Regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbead-based modular systems offer significant potential for biofabrication strategies in tissue regeneration. In this study, we present a tunable microfluidic cryogel microbead (MCB) platform that enables injectable, modular assembly of cells and tissue-specific regeneration. The MCBs are designed to incorporate diverse ECM compositions, porosities, and bioceramic components tailored to specific tissue types. They support cell viability and function, and when loaded with endothelial cells,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strong Base-Promoted Pd-Catalyzed Asymmetric Hydroalkoxylation of Alkoxyallene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new protocol for the Pd-catalyzed hydroalkoxylation of alkoxyallene is presented that proceeds under strongly basic conditions. Notably, this method accommodates sterically hindered tertiary alcohols and carbohydrate-derived alcohols, which proved unreactive under the previous base-free conditions. This result was rationalized by the outer-sphere addition of alkoxide nucleophile to the syn π-allyl complex. Synthetic utility of the reaction was demonstrated by convergent synthesis of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Adverse Event Reports of Dipeptidyl Peptidase-4 Inhibitor-Associated Pemphigoid in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The number of reported DPP-4 inhibitor-associated pemphigoid events increased after the revised precautions of package inserts for DPP-4 inhibitors were released.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SOD1 deficiency drives ferroptosis-linked oxidative and reproductive aging, mitigated by ginseng root extract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging is accompanied by cumulative oxidative stress that promotes tissue degeneration and reproductive decline. Here, we show that deficiency of superoxide dismutase 1 (SOD1) accelerates oxidative injury and reproductive aging through a ferroptosis-linked redox imbalance, and that ginseng root extract (GR) confers protection across species. Aged hairless Sod1⁻^(/)⁻ mice exhibited markedly elevated skin and plasma oxidative stress markers-including 8-isoprostane, malondialdehyde (MDA), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Exploring Predictive Risk Factors for Myocardial Injury in Children Treated with Anthracyclines: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of Symptoms and Evaluation of Surgical Indications After Birth Based on Tracheal Morphology of Double Aortic Arch]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To establish objective criteria for predicting postnatal respiratory symptoms and determine surgical indications in fetuses with double aortic arch (DAA). This single-center, retrospective cohort study included fetuses diagnosed with DAA using fetal echocardiography and managed perinatally at Kanagawa Children's Medical Center from January 2013-December 2024. Clinical data, fetal echocardiography, postnatal contrast-enhanced computed tomography (CT) findings, surgical intervention, and outcomes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative performance of a 3D CZT and conventional SPECT/CT for Tb-161 imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Quantitative Tb-161 SPECT imaging can be performed using both a conventional and a 3D CZT SPECT/CT. Given its higher sensitivity, the 3D CZT system is preferred, as it achieved better image quality with an 8-min acquisition compared to a conventional system with a 16-min acquisition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Disc-FX versus L'DISQ for percutaneous disc decompression: pilot comparative study using the minimal clinically important difference]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this pilot study, Disc-FX and L'DISQ had comparable short-term pain outcomes. Any apparent QOL advantage with Disc-FX should be interpreted cautiously as exploratory and potentially confounded, and requires confirmation in adequately powered prospective comparative studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customized Face Guards as Protective Devices for Ocular Trauma in Futsal Players: A Case Report and Clinical Efficacy Evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a case involving a futsal player with brain concussions and commotio retinae to protect the affected area and support a safe, prompt return to play custom face guard instead of a commercial face guard and sports goggles. For a better fit, we fabricated a custom face guard, for which a facial impression was taken using dental alginate material and plaster in July 2019. The following month, the custom face guard was set on the player's face so that its outline provided minimal coverage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative functional analysis of papaya leaves at different developmental stages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Papaya (Carica papaya L.), a tropical plant belonging to the Caricaceae family, is widely cultivated in tropical and subtropical countries. Young leaves grow from the stem tips, petioles elongate, and leaf color changes from light green to dark green during development. Papaya leaves are used as therapeutic agents in folk medicine and potential functional food materials; however, the specific associations between the leaf development stage and functional components of papaya remain unknown....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of bZIP60 function through C-terminal region translated after splicing in <em>Arabidopsis</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The unfolded protein response (UPR) is a central regulatory pathway that ensures the proper function of the endoplasmic reticulum (ER) through efficient protein folding and quality control. In Arabidopsis, bZIP60 mRNA is activated by an IRE1-mediated unconventional splicing that excises a 23-nucleotide intron, resulting in the spliced form (bZIP60s mRNA) that encodes the active bZIP60 transcription factor lacking a transmembrane domain. In this study, we investigated the functional role of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A start codon-targeted genome editing strategy for generating hypomorphic mutants of lethal plant genes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In plants, the functional characterization of essential genes is often hindered by the lethality associated with complete loss-of-function alleles. Here, we present a genome editing-based strategy to generate viable hypomorphic alleles through selective removal of the translation start codon. Using Arabidopsis thaliana NON-SMC ELEMENT 1, which encodes a conserved component of the Structural Maintenance of Chromosomes (SMC) 5/6 complex involved in DNA repair and genome stability, as a model, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rye sprout as a host for the rapid transient production of a recombinant protein using a geminivirus DNA-containing expression vector]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The agroinfiltration technique using sprouts as a host is one of the most cost-effective, efficient, and rapid methods for producing recombinant proteins. We previously reported that radish sprouts were the best host for this purpose. To find suitable alternative sprouts comparable to radish sprouts, we investigated rye sprouts using a wheat dwarf virus (a geminivirus) DNA-containing expression vector. Various rye cultivars were tested, and Raitaro and Ryokuhiyo sprouts exhibited the highest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cohort study of sustainable cultivation methods in mandarin orange orchards across Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Variability in environmental conditions and farming practices often leads to discrepancies between experimental results and outcomes in farmers' fields. This gap poses a challenge for understanding the effects of agricultural inputs and methods under real-world conditions, particularly in fruit cultivation systems, where large-scale experimental data are limited. In this study, we applied a cohort study approach leveraging data from farmers' fields to investigate the effects of pesticide and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient expression of human interleukin-15 in <em>Nicotiana benthamiana</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A plant-based expression system provides a cost-effective, scalable, and safe alternative to traditional cell culture platforms. In this study, recombinant human interleukin-15 (IL-15) was transiently expressed in Nicotiana benthamiana plants using agroinfiltration. IL-15 is a cytokine with significant potential in cell engineering, immunotherapy, and cancer therapy. A codon-optimized IL-15 gene was cloned into a binary vector designed for plant expression and introduced into Rhizobium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phenotypic Spectrum of Gastric Adenocarcinoma and Proximal Polyposis of the Stomach (GAPPS) in Denmark: A Case Series Characterizing the First Danish Families With the <em>APC</em> Promotor 1B Variant c.-191T &gt; C]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric adenocarcinoma and proximal polyposis of the stomach (GAPPS) is a rare autosomal dominantly inherited gastric cancer syndrome that is characterized by fundic gland polyposis of the stomach (> 100) and an increased risk of gastric cancer. The genetic cause is recognized as a pathogenic variant in the promotor 1B of the APC gene. Presently, there are no established clinical criteria, and current guidelines are based on limited evidence. In this report, we identified two families with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extraintestinal Manifestations and Cytomegalovirus Reactivation Are Predictors of Difficult-To-Treat in Ulcerative Colitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with UC, the presence of EIM and CMV reactivation was significantly associated with steroid dependence, steroid refractoriness, and resistance to biologic and molecular-targeted therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Miyake Revisited: Validating the Factor Structure of an Open-Source Cognitive Control Test Battery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cognitive control is a prerequisite for achieving goals in daily life. Miyake et al. (2000) distinguished three separable but correlated cognitive control functions in young adults: inhibition, shifting, and updating. This three-factor model was later adapted to a bi-factor model with a common factor and separate updating and shifting factors. Over the years, these models have been replicated in various young adult samples. However, other studies have failed to confirm these models. Furthermore,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41523092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improvement in coronary microvascular dysfunction after transcatheter aortic valve implantation leading to positive fractional flow reserve and percutaneous coronary intervention: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The management of coronary artery disease in patients with severe aortic stenosis is controversial, with no consensus on optimal revascularization strategies. The validity of using fractional flow reserve to assess ischaemia in this population is debated. Conflicting results have arisen regarding the impact of transcatheter aortic valve implantation on fractional flow reserve values. We present the case of a patient with severe aortic stenosis and intermediate left anterior...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of unilateral neck muscle vibration on tilt direction and variability of subjective postural vertical in the frontal plane during seated posture in healthy adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Unilateral neck muscle vibration (NMV) activates the primary endings of muscle spindles and modulates both subjective visual vertical and subjective straight-ahead perception. However, its effects on subjective postural vertical (SPV), crucial for postural balance, remain poorly understood. We aimed to investigate the effects of unilateral NMV-induced proprioceptive stimulation on SPV tilt direction and intraindividual variability in the frontal plane in healthy participants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-sectional comparative shotgun metagenomic analysis of the subgingival resistome in healthy subjects and patients with periodontitis from four countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Subgingival resistome profiles vary significantly by periodontal status and geography, underscoring the influence of clinical and regional factors on antimicrobial resistance in the oral microbiome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No Alterations in ACL Injury Risk Factors in Preadolescent Elite Female Handball Players Following an Eight-Week Targeted Training Intervention: A Randomised Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adolescent female handball players are at elevated risk of anterior cruciate ligament (ACL) injury. Early interventions during preadolescence seem crucial for improving motor strategies and potentially preventing injuries. This randomised controlled trial on preadolescent female handball players investigated the effects of an 8-week ACL injury prevention program (ACL-IPP) targeting modifiable neuromuscular and biomechanical risk factors and assessed retention effects 8 weeks post-intervention....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel Dual-Task Paradigm for Return-to-Sport Screening After ACL Injury: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This pilot study demonstrates the feasibility and preliminary reliability of the dual-task paradigm, particularly within the ACLR group. Poorer cognitive, hop, and upper-body test performances and smaller test-retest improvements for the ACLR group suggest persistent dual-task deficits following injury, supporting the paradigm's utility for ecologically valid ACL rehabilitation and return-to-sport assessment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41522286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemotherapy resistance due to epithelial-to-mesenchymal transition is caused by abnormal lipid metabolic balance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Invasive cancer is defined by the loss of epithelial cell traits resulting from the ectopic expression of epithelial-mesenchymal transition (EMT)-related transcription factors such as Snail. Although EMT is known to impart chemoresistance to cancer cells, the precise molecular mechanisms remain elusive. We found that Snail expression confers chemoresistance by upregulating the cholesterol efflux pump ABCA1 as a countermeasure to the excess of cytotoxic free cholesterol relative to its major...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turn-off fluorescence sensing of benzenediols <em>via</em> guest-induced π-conjugation switching in bisimidazole-based hydrindacene allosteric receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluorescent bisimidazole-based hydrindacene allosteric receptors 1a-c and 2 were synthesized for nonlinear ON/OFF sensing of benzenediols. By tuning their D-π-D conjugation through substituent modification, these receptors were designed to function as turn-off fluorescent sensors based on the cleavage of their π-conjugation accompanied by binding with benzenediols. The cooperative allosteric binding demonstrated selective and efficient nonlinear quenching toward orcinol.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41521702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linking Maternal and Neonatal Circulation in Preeclampsia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hypertensive disorders of pregnancy (HDP), particularly early-onset preeclampsia (EOPE), are major causes of perinatal morbidity and mortality. While impaired placentation has long been recognized as a key mechanism, increasing evidence highlights the contribution of maternal cardiovascular dysfunction. However, how maternal haemodynamics influences neonatal circulatory transition remains poorly understood. In this prospective study, mother-infant pairs from pregnancies complicated by EOPE were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Streptococcus mobilis</em> sp. nov., isolated from a <em>Helicobacter pylori</em>-positive pre-neoplastic human stomach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A facultative anaerobic, catalase-negative, lactic acid-producing, non-endospore-forming, Gram-positive coccoid bacterium, strain MT/JULY 2010^(T), was isolated from the stomach of a Helicobacter pylori-positive Japanese female patient with pre-neoplastic gastric mucosa. This bacterium can form clusters, chains or pairs or occurs singly in liquid media. The growth ranges for temperature, pH and NaCl concentration were 20-45 °C, pH 5.0-7.0 and 1-4%, respectively. Cells exhibited an unusual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Laboratory Parameters with Acute Kidney Injury in Pediatric Patients Undergoing Surgery for Transposition of the Great Arteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preoperative creatinine and CRP are reliable early indicators of AKI risk in pediatric TGA surgery. Systematic postoperative monitoring of laboratory parameters and diuresis allows timely detection and intervention, potentially improving outcomes. Future multicen-ter studies are warranted to validate these predictors and optimize risk stratification protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Central activation of Chaperone-Mediated Autophagy Reduces Appetite by Fine-Tuning Hypothalamic Amino Acid Pools: New Insights from Fish]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chaperone-Mediated Autophagy (CMA) is a key lysosomal proteolytic pathway essential for cellular homeostasis and metabolism, with dysfunction linked to various human diseases. While extensively studied in humans and mice, CMA was only recently identified in fish, paving the way for novel and evolutionary research perspectives. Here, we demonstrate a role for CMA in regulating feed intake (FI) in rainbow trout (Oncorhynchus mykiss), a major aquaculture species and a widely used model in numerous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ablation of Tumor-Derived IGFBP-3 Attenuates Cancer-Associated Skeletal Muscle Wasting in Murine Pancreatic Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC) is the 4th leading cause of cancer-related deaths, and its incidence is expected to rise. Skeletal muscle wasting (SMW) is a debilitating co-morbidity of PDAC with unknown etiology. Previously our lab demonstrated that systemic increases in Insulin-like Growth Factor Binding Protein-3 (IGFBP-3) is associated with SMW and pathologic myocellular lipid accumulation in an orthotopic murine model of PDAC (Ptf1a^(tm1-cre/+);Kras^(tm4Tyj);Muc1^(-/-)(KCKO)). Here...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying Insulin Autoantibodies With Differential Risk in Type 1 Diabetes With a Novel Bridging ELISA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In global type 1 diabetes (T1D) population screening studies, there is an urgent need for a highly sensitive and specific insulin autoantibody (IAA) assay that can be implemented across multiple laboratories. This study aimed to develop and characterize a novel ELISA-based platform for IAA detection. We established a new bridging ELISA for IAA and validated it in cohorts of patients with stage 3 T1D, children positive for with multiple and single islet antibodies, and control children negative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The US Food and Drug Administration's Regulation of Mifepristone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: FDA oversight of mifepristone, developed during key moments from 2011 to 2023, has been shaped by scientific evidence and a cautious regulatory approach led by scientists at the agency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimation of Mortality via the Neighborhood Atlas and Reproducible Area Deprivation Indices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cross-sectional study, the ReADI was correctly calculated and should replace the flawed NA-ADI for future health policy applications. Its open-source methods support transparency, adaptability, and further development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Volunteering and Metabolic Syndrome and Diabetes in Black Adolescents From Low-Income Families]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These results suggest that encouraging adolescents to volunteer may represent a novel approach to improving cardiometabolic health earlier in life and in groups that have been historically marginalized. The notion that volunteering might help not only the recipients of volunteering efforts, but also the volunteers themselves, suggests the possibility of creating a 2-way street of benefits through a single activity that could promote health across groups while also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Dose vs Standard-Dose Influenza Vaccine in Older Adults With Diabetes: A Secondary Analysis of the DANFLU-2 Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The trial results suggest that, among adults 65 years or older, HD-IIV provided consistent benefit for cardiorespiratory, cardiovascular, and influenza hospitalizations compared with SD-IIV, regardless of diabetes status.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Price of Healing-A Growing Barrier for Aspiring Physicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hepatic Response Dynamics in Newly Diagnosed Patients with Light-chain Amyloidosis: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study highlights the importance of monitoring hepatic response dynamics, identifying 3-month CR(H) and 24-month hepatic OR as key treatment milestones. A graphical abstract is also available with this article.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment and characterization of a testicular yolk sac tumor PDX model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We successfully established a TYST PDX model that retains tissue structure and protein expression signature of the patient's tumor tissue. Furthermore, this PDX model demonstrates high sensitivity to standard JEB chemotherapy and represents a valuable resource for translational research in pediatric germ cell tumors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Stimulus Presentation on Skin Conductance and Potential Implications for Neurofeedback Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Real-time fMRI neurofeedback enables individuals to learn self-regulation of specific brain regions, such as the amygdala, which is often targeted for downregulation in trauma-related disorders. However, repeated exposure to emotional stimuli during lengthy sessions may lead to habituation, with amygdala activity naturally decreasing over time independent of self-regulation success. Presentation rate may influence this effect--however, empirical evidence remains limited with that rate varying...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of biological age versus chronological age on clinical outcomes in patients with atrial fibrillation: insights from the COOL-AF registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Because patients with atrial fibrillation (AF) often exhibit heterogeneous risks that are not fully captured by traditional clinical factors, identifying a more accurate measure of physiological ageing could improve risk stratification and clinical management compared to chronological aging.This study aimed to determine the clinical outcome in relation to biological ageing in patients with AF. We used the data from the COOL-AF registry which is a multicentre nationwide registry of AF patients....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Life-course body shape trajectories and cerebral oxygen metabolism in community-dwelling older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity and lifelong body-shape fluctuation are associated with late-life structural brain damage, suggesting the involvement of metabolic pathways. The cerebral metabolic rate of oxygen (CMRO₂) reflects hemodynamic and oxidative stress and precedes structural atrophy, but its role in adiposity-related brain change remains unclear. We examined whether current and life-course adiposity relate to CMRO₂ and to structural change. A total of 303 community-dwelling adults aged 50 years and older were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41525004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI for screening in healthcare: promise and challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is reshaping population screening, yet the translation from laboratory performance to population benefit remains limited. This narrative review describes current uses of AI across major screening pathways. Prospective trials in mammography demonstrate non‑inferior cancer detection with large reductions in radiologist workload. In diabetic retinopathy, the first FDA‑authorized autonomous system extends specialist‑level screening into primary care and improves uptake....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can vegetables intake pattern mediate the relationship between fast-food and cognitive performance in adolescents? The Cogni-Action project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A central role for PINK1 in governing local mitochondrial biogenesis and degradation in neurons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neurons have adapted the transport and positioning of mitochondria to fit their extended shape and high energy needs. To sustain mitochondrial function, neurons developed systems that allow local biogenesis and adaption to locally regulate mitochondrial form and function. Likewise, fine-tuned degradative systems are required to protect the neurons from mitochondrial dysfunction. Throughout both domains of mitostasis, the local synthesis of the mitochondrial damage-induced kinase PINK1 emerges as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of Enantiomeric Monoterpene-Coumarins with Neuroprotective Activities from the Rhizomes of <em>Luvunga scandens</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Twenty-two new monoterpene-coumarins, comprising the initial disclosure of 11 enantiomeric pairings, were isolated from the rhizomes of Luvunga scandens with the aid of LC-MS/MS based on molecular networking. Luvunscandins A-G (1-7) are dihydrofurancoumarins with a furan ring connection, and luvunscandins H-K (8-11) are dihydrofurancoumarins connected through a pyran ring. Chemical structures and absolute configurations were determined by analysis of spectroscopic data and X-ray diffraction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Choline supplementation in preterm infants: effects of four different supplements on choline plasma concentrations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-Sensitive and direct detection of MiRNAs in real samples via duplex-specific nuclease-mediated signal amplification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The expression levels of miRNAs in cells or biological fluids are closely associated with the onset and progression of many diseases, making the detection of miRNAs in serum and plasma increasingly important. However, due to the low levels of miRNAs in biological fluids and the complexity of their surrounding environment, their analysis faces challenges related to accuracy and reproducibility. We developed a duplex-specific nuclease (DSN)-mediated detection method for the direct detection of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convergences and Gaps between Environmental Ethics, Climate Ethics, and Research Ethics: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the Complexities of Peripartum Mood and Anxiety Disorders: A Qualitative Assessment of Current Issues in Management and Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings provide an in-depth insight into the complex underpinnings of PMADs, particularly barriers to accessing care. This information, along with the positive feedback on home-visiting programs, can contribute to the development of innovative programs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning versus logistic regression for propensity score estimation: a trial emulation benchmarked against the PARADIGM-HF randomized trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) algorithms are increasingly used to estimate propensity score with expectation of improving causal inference. However, the validity of data-driven ML-based approaches for confounder selection and adjustment remains unclear. In this study, we emulated the device-stratified secondary analysis of the PARADIGM-HF trial among U.S. veterans with heart failure and implanted cardiac devices from 2016 to 2020. We benchmarked observational estimates from three propensity score...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quality of cancer-related data from the Danish National patient registry (1994-2025) and the Danish cancer registry (2004-2025): a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Danish National Patient Registry (DNPR) and the Danish Cancer Registry (DCR) are central to registry-based cancer research. This systematic review evaluates studies assessing the quality of cancer-related data in these registries under their current data structures. PubMed and Embase were systematically searched on January 24, 2025 (PROSPERO: CRD420251005952). Studies validating cancer-related data in the DNPR or DCR against a gold standard were included. Findings were synthesized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Space-time clustering of childhood high hyperdiploid B-cell precursor acute lymphoblastic leukemia: a nationwide Swedish study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) is the most common childhood malignancy. While space-time clustering of ALL cases has been suggested, only one prior study has examined clustering by genetic subtype. We investigated space-time clustering of childhood ALL in Sweden, both overall and by genetic subtype. The cohort included 1,629 children age 0-18 years diagnosed with ALL between 1992 and 2017, comprising 1,446 B-cell precursor ALL (BCP-ALL) and 183 T-cell ALL (T-ALL) cases. Two BCP-ALL subgroups...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alcohol Use Disorder versus Adverse In-Hospital Outcomes after Radical Cystectomy and Ileal Conduit Urinary Diversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Since AUD significantly predisposes to higher rates of adverse in-hospital outcomes and in-hospital mortality after RC and ileal conduit urinary diversion, precautionary measures prior to admission and during hospital stay may be warranted in patients with AUD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Longitudinal Study on Development and Validation of the Prostate Cancer Scale Among the System of Quality of Life Instruments for Patients with Cancer (QLICP-PR V2.0) Based on Classical Test Theory and Generalizability Theory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The QLICP-PR V2.0 has good psychometric properties in reliability, validity, and responsiveness, and can be used to evaluate the quality of life of patients with prostate cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Proteome of Bilateral Macronodular Adrenocortical Disease (BMAD) Shows Different Profiles Correlating with the Genetic Causes and Reveals Specific Dysregulation of RNA Polymerase II and Cholesterol Biosynthesis Enzymes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Discrimination to Unmet Healthcare Needs and Care (Dis)Satisfaction among Urban-Dwelling Indigenous Taiwanese Adults: A Path Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite universal healthcare coverage in Taiwan, urban-dwelling Indigenous Taiwanese (UDIT) individuals continue to experience significant health disparities. While everyday discrimination's influence on healthcare outcomes has been documented, few studies have empirically tested the mechanisms linking discrimination to unmet healthcare needs and care dissatisfaction. This study examines how everyday discrimination affects healthcare outcomes among UDIT adults through psychosocial pathways,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Environmental Justice in Vulnerable Populations: Climate Change and Congenital Heart Disease in American Indian/Alaska Native Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The health impacts of environmental change are subtle and cumulative. A growing body of evidence demonstrates that exposure to the forces driving climate change, including heat and pollution, is associated with significant morbidity and mortality, including a higher incidence of congenital and acquired heart disease. Due to compounding historical structural inequities subsequently codified by government policy, American Indian/Alaska Native (AI/AN) populations are disproportionately exposed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intersectional Lives, and Ecological Risks: The Association between Criminal Legal System Exposures and Suicide Attempts among Black Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Contact with the criminal legal system -particularly delinquency and policing-are linked to suicide attempts among Black youth. These findings underscore the need for prevention strategies that integrate suicide risk screening with efforts to reduce harmful criminal legal exposures and support youth and families affected by incarceration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physiological Evidence Supporting the Emotional Motivation Account of the Ending Effect: Pupil Diameters Increase Toward the End]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The phenomenon of increased risk-taking in the last round of a set of risky decision-making tasks is called the ending effect. Recent empirical studies proposed an emotional motivation account to explain the ending effect. That is, the pursuit of an emotionally satisfying ending leads to the increase of risk-taking. However, previous studies have mostly examined the ending effect at the behavioral level, there is yet no physiological evidence to examine the emotional motivation account. To fill...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gender-specific Differences in Radiation Oncology Training during the COVID-19 Pandemic: A Subanalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic significantly impacted cancer education across specialties. Radiation oncology, with its highly technical nature and multidisciplinary approach, faced unique challenges in maintaining training quality while adapting to pandemic restrictions. This subanalysis of a nationwide survey on oncological training quality during the pandemic examines gender-specific differences within radiation oncology specialist training. We analyzed survey responses from 85 radiation oncologists...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atypical Femoral Fractures Induced by Anti-Resorptive Medications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: This review evaluates established risk factors, examines pathogenic mechanisms, determines optimal treatment durations, and proposes evidence-based management strategies for Osteoporosis to enhance clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Homocysteine levels do not impact cognitive profile in frontotemporal dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Hcy levels were not significantly associated with cognitive performance in a large sample of individuals with FTD. If replicated, these findings could challenge the hypothesis that Hcy constitutes a risk factor for FTD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Austrian MS database and the Austrian MS cohort : A national effort towards data harmonization and prospective data collection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The AMSD and AMSC will facilitate the evidence-based development of prognostic biomarkers, individualized therapy strategies and treatment sequences based on a high-quality, population-based dataset of more than 8000 people with MS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Excitation/Relaxation Analysis of Electronic Transitions Using Difference Density Natural Orbitals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Characterizing an electronic excitation in terms of its underlying orbital reorganization is central to understanding photochemical and photophysical processes. Here, we introduce an excitation/relaxation framework that separates electron promotion from orbital relaxation contributions within Δ-self-consistent-field (ΔSCF) treatments of electronic transitions. The framework defines the excitation number and the relaxation number, which quantify electron promotion and electron relaxation....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing off-target effects in CRISPR/Cas9: challenges and strategies for precision DNA editing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of CRISPR/Cas9 technology has transformed the landscape of gene editing, allowing for precise alterations in DNA that hold great promise for research and potential therapies. However, a significant concern is the occurrence of off-target effects, which can lead to unintended genetic modifications with potentially harmful consequences. This paper explores the nature of off-target effects in CRISPR/Cas9, discussing how they arise and their implications for the reliability of gene...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[House, Land, and Asset Ownership and Food Security Among Middle-Age and Older Adults in India: Examining the Associations Using LASI (2017-18)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[House, land and asset ownership are crucial indicators of economic security in old age. Food security recognized as a robust social determinant of health and well-being among the older population, ranks highly in the UN's Sustainable Development Goals. This study aimed to examine the association between house, land, and asset ownership, and food insecurity among middle-aged and older adults in India. Data came from a nationally representative survey, the Longitudinal Aging Study in India (LASI)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunotoxic Effects of Oman Crude Oil Water-Accommodated Fractions on Cellular and Humoral Immune Functions in Sea Cucumber (Apostichopus japonicus)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As a key economic marine aquaculture species in China, sea cucumbers (Apostichopus japonicus) were widely cultured in coastal regions, where were susceptible to crude oil pollution threatening their survival and population recruitment, and the impact of crude oil on non-specific immune functions of sea cucumbers was still limited. Therefore, this study exposed sea cucumbers to water-accommodated fractions (WAFs) of Oman crude oil for 7 d to investigate the effects of crude oil on non-specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultraviolet radiation dosimetry using radiochromic film for extended dose range applications and estimating eye exposure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiochromic films are a reliable tool for quantifying ultraviolet exposure dose. When used without modification, these films enable a simple, low-cost measurement of accumulated dose over time which is amenable to personal exposure monitoring. This study presents two methods to expand the utility of these films for dosimetry applications. One approach utilized an ultraviolet radiation attenuator to effectively extend the usable dose range of radiochromic films. The attenuators have the added...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of hands-on versus hands-off assistance on trainee performance in ERCP training: a randomized controlled study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The hands-off training showed non-inferior effectiveness and safety to the hands-on training. The alternative method can be integrated into the traditional ERCP training. Key messages What is already known on this topic: Conventional endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography (ERCP) training relies heavily on direct, hands-on supervision by experienced endoscopists to guide trainees during procedures. While teleguidance (remote supervision using real-time imaging) has been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simple, low-cost in vitro protocol for differentiating mesenchymal stem cells into cardiomyocyte-like cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Congenital heart disease (CHD) remains the foremost cause of mortality in children under 20 years of age. Given their ease of harvest, robust proliferative capacity and multilineage differentiation potential, stem cells (SCs) have emerged as a promising therapeutic alternative. In particular, mesenchymal stem cells (MSCs) derived from Wharton's jelly in the umbilical cord, i.e., an abundant byproduct of childbirth, especially in lowand middle-income settings, can be induced toward a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Sublattice Entropy via Cation-Anion Co-Doping Enables Broadband Solar Absorption and Efficient Photothermal Conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photothermal conversion is a highly efficient pathway for solar energy utilization, requiring coatings with strong absorption in the solar spectrum (0.3-2.5 µm) while maintaining low emissivity in the mid-infrared range (2.5-25 µm). Here, we report a simple bilayer solar selective absorber coating (SSAC) based on a high-entropy boride (HEB) with dual cation-anion site doping. Nitrogen incorporation into the HEB lattice forms B─N bonds and interstitial N─N states, effectively tailoring the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Through-Plane Conductive Hydrophobic Electrodes for CO<sub>2</sub> Electrolysis to Ethylene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Copper catalyst gas diffusion electrodes (GDEs) have demonstrated unique electrochemical selectivity converting CO(2) to C(2)-hydrocarbons such as ethylene and ethanol but have been challenged by their hydrophobic chemical stability and internal electrical resistance leading to low energy efficiency. Carbon-supported GDEs have low electrical resistance but lack sufficient stability at industrially relevant current densities. While polymer-supported GDEs have improved hydrophobicity, they also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Guidelines for Nutritional Management of Sarcopenia and Frailty 2025. Guest Editor: Masafumi Kuzuya. This publication has been supported by The Japan Geriatrics Society and National Center for Geriatrics and Gerontology (NCGG) (Japan)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Statistics in the United States, 2026: JACC Stats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutational Landscape of Colorectal Tumors From Individuals With Unexplained Adenomatous or Serrated Colorectal Polyposis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our results indicate that BRAF-mutated serrated polyps are molecularly more similar to normal colon tissue than APC- and/or CTNNB1-mutated tumors. Overall, molecular tumor profiling of individuals with polyposis contributes to understanding the genetic disease etiology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbon-Bifunctionalized Mo<sub>2</sub>N Coupled Atomic Pb Sites for Efficient Nitrogen Reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electrocatalytic nitrogen reduction reaction (ENRR) offers a sustainable pathway for ambient ammonia (NH(3)) synthesis but suffers from kinetic limitations and competing hydrogen evolution (HER). Herein, a new type of ENRR catalyst is designed consisting of carbon-bifunctionalized Mo(2)N nanoparticles (NPs) embedded in a hierarchical porous carbon matrix with atomic Pb sites (PbNC) through a one-step carbonitridation strategy. The carbon-bifunctionalization effect not only creates nitrogen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domination Versus Sisterhoods in the Blood Microbiota of Migrating Birds: Patterns of Within- and Between-Individual Blood Parasite Diversity Revealed Through Metabarcoding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Avian blood parasites of the genera Plasmodium, Haemoproteus, and Leucocytozoon are typically identified through Sanger sequencing of a partial cytochrome b fragment, the MalAvi barcoding region. This approach limits the detection of mixed infections and the relative frequencies of co-infecting parasites. In contrast, next-generation sequencing (NGS) can resolve these problems but has been underused for haemosporidian lineage identification in samples from the wild. We used an improved PCR...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deficiency of Pdap1 Results in Embryonic Lethality and Diminished Vascularization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platelet-derived growth factor associated protein 1 (PDAP1) is implicated in various biological processes, including tumorigenesis and the apoptosis of mature B lymphocytes. However, its functions in organismal development and homeostasis remain poorly understood. To address this gap, we generated Pdap1 knockout mice to elucidate the physiological functions of PDAP1 in vivo. Notably, our findings indicate that the absence of Pdap1 results in early embryonic lethality by embryonic day 11.5,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell Culture Substrate Variation Alters Extracellular Vesicle Biogenesis Without Affecting Non-Coding Repeat RNA Profile]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tissue stiffening is central to disease progression and aggressiveness in pancreatic adenocarcinoma (PDAC). Here we report how the biomechanical characteristics of the cell culture conditions impact the amount, as well as the cargo, of extracellular vesicles (EVs) produced by pancreatic cancer cells. Cells grown on softer matrices (0.5 kPa) release upwards of 40 times more EVs than those grown on stiffer surfaces (8 kPa) and their cargo is more enriched in protein-coding RNAs related with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[25-Hydroxyvitamin D Deficiency Elevates the Risk of COPD Incidence and Mortality: A Large Population-Based Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study suggests that 25(OH)D deficiency is associated with COPD incidence and survival, providing a basis for preventive strategies and interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In synergy with interferon-gamma, interleukin-17 activates vascular stromal cells towards a pro-inflammatory profile in giant cell arteritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: IL-17 exacerbates vascular inflammation in GCA by activating MFs and synergizing with IFN-γ to increase production of pro-inflammatory cytokines (IL-6, GM-CSF), chemokines (CCL20, CCL2), and angiogenic factors (VEGF, indicating that IL-17 is a key contributor to disease pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[N-Heterocyclic Carbene Monolayers on Nickel, Iron, and Steel by a Radical-to-Carbene Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[N-Heterocyclic carbenes (NHCs) have recently emerged as the next-generation surface ligands with improved stability and molecular flexibility. Despite these premises, research on NHC-enriched flat surfaces is mainly limited to noble metals, while formation of free NHCs often requires the use of vacuum, bases, or strictly air- and moisture-free conditions. We hereby report an unprecedented radical-to-carbene-based approach for fabricating NHC monolayers on earth-abundant and naturally oxidized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Engineering of Polymer Electrolytes for Lithium and Sodium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alkali metal batteries exhibit excellent energy storage potential due to the ultra-high specific capacity and low redox potential of lithium and sodium metal anodes. However, in the process of electroplating and stripping of lithium and sodium metals, the coupling evolution of ion transport, solvation structure, reaction kinetics, and mechanical stress leads to interface instability, which hinders the practical application of alkali metal batteries. Polymer electrolyte provides a unique...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combatting Silicosis Fibrosis: Methyl Gallate Suppresses Pathogenic Fibroblasts Through hnRNPA2/B1-MDM4-P53 Network Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silicosis, an occupational pulmonary fibrosis caused by silica dust exposure, lacks effective treatments. This study investigates the therapeutic potential and mechanism of methyl gallate (MG), a natural polyphenol, in silicosis fibrosis. A silica-induced silicosis mouse model and TGF-β1-stimulated human lung fibroblasts were employed. MG administration significantly ameliorated lung fibrosis in mice, reducing collagen deposition, α-SMA, fibronectin, and TGF-β1 levels. Transcriptomic analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional characterization of the polar organizer protein FimV in <em>Pseudomonas putida</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Homologs of the polar landmark proteins HubP and FimV are widespread among bacterial species. They all share several common features, including a periplasmic LysM-like domain, a transmembrane region, an extensive cytoplasmic domain enriched in acidic amino acids, and a C-terminal tetrapeptid-repeat (TPR) domain referred to as the FimV domain. Apart from these conserved general features, however, the proteins exhibit little homology across different bacterial genera. Here, we characterized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The prognostic value of protein induced by vitamin K absence or antagonist-II in hepatocellular carcinoma patients undergoing surgical resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study confirms that serum PIVKA-II can serve as a prognostic predictor for HCC patients after surgical treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41524590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260112142619&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>