<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:20:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global diversification of coastal Cafius rove beetles (Coleoptera: Staphylinidae) driven by ocean currents since the early Miocene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As our understanding of abiotic factors continues to grow, along with insights into the biological traits of organisms, so too does the sophistication of studies exploring global diversification and spatio-temporal distribution patterns. The global distribution of coastal Cafius rove beetles, combined with the endemic distribution patterns observed in its subclades, suggests repeated colonization of new regions via ocean surface currents, followed by local diversification and speciation. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Myopic Shift Induced by Omidenepag Isopropyl 0.002% in Patients with Primary Open-Angle Glaucoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: OMDI 0.002% eyedrops were associated with a notable incidence of myopic shift in patients with POAG. Ciliary muscle spasm is a possible underlying mechanism of myopic shift.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Copper-Catalyzed Enantioselective Synthesis of <em>N</em>-Heterocycle-Substituted Quaternary Carbon Stereogenic Centers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The enantioselective construction of all-carbon quaternary stereogenic centers adjacent to N-heterocycles remains a long-standing challenge in asymmetric catalysis. Herein we report a copper-catalyzed enantioselective hydropyridylation of 1,1-disubstituted allenes with 2-halopyridines that proceeds via a nucleophilic aromatic substitution (S(N)Ar) pathway. This transformation enables the efficient synthesis of α-quaternary N-heterocyclic compounds with a broad substrate scope in high yields (up...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Halogenases and dehalogenases: mechanisms, engineering, and applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Halogenated organic compounds (HOCs) are essential building blocks in pharmaceuticals, agrochemicals, and advanced materials. However, their conventional chemical synthesis often relies on hazardous reagents and generates significant environmental waste. Harnessing nature's solutions, halogenases and dehalogenases offer selective, eco-friendly alternatives for the biosynthesis and degradation of HOCs. Halogenases, including electrophilic (e.g., haloperoxidases, flavin-dependent), radical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nurses' perceptions of shared decision-making with older adults using home care services in South Korea: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Results highlighted the need for support for nurses to address the difficulties faced by older adults in making healthcare-related decisions about their place of residence and indicated comparable involvement in SDM between nurses working in long-term care centres and hospital home visiting centres.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NRF2 Activation Suppressed Methylglyoxal-Lysine Dimer-Induced Oxidative Stress and Inflammatory Paracrine Interaction between Macrophages and Adipocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macrophage infiltration is closely associated with adipocyte-related inflammatory response in obesity. In this study, we explored methylglyoxal-lysine dimer (MOLD)-induced inflammatory responses and metabolic disorders during macrophage and adipocyte interactions using an in vitro conditioned co-culture medium-based. MOLD significantly increased the levels of advanced glycation end products (AGEs) and receptor for AGEs and induced the levels of nitric oxide and prostaglandin E2 in RAW 264.7...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Cinnamomum longepetiolatum</em> (Kosterm.) Extract Modulates Inflammatory Responses and Oxidative Stress in Lipopolysaccharide-Stimulated RAW 264.7 Macrophages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although inflammation is a protective response to maintain homeostasis, chronic or excessive inflammation is closely associated with various pathological conditions, including autoimmune diseases, cancer, and chronic inflammatory disorders. Therefore, the present study aimed to evaluate the anti-inflammatory activity of Cinnamomum longepetiolatum (Kosterm.), a medicinal plant from Vietnam, at the cellular level. Although C. longepetiolatum is widely used in traditional medicine, its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesized Depside Molecules Suppress the Progression of Colorectal Cancer by Binding VDAC1/PHB/MMP9 Being at the Crossroads of Stemness, Motility, Apoptosis, and Metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lichen secondary metabolites have shown potential in cancer therapy, but strategies to enhance cancer-specific selectivity are needed. Here, we synthesized depside compounds structurally related to tumidulin (TU) and diffractaic acid (DA) and screened them in vitro, identifying SB4 and SB5 as potent hits. Affinity-based proteomics revealed direct binding to voltage-dependent anion channel 1 (VDAC1), prohibitin (PHB), and matrix metalloproteinase-9 (MMP9), which regulate cancer stemness,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the Electrochemical Reversibility of Multielectron Redox in s-Tetrazine Derivatives for Large-Capacity Electrode Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[1,2,4,5-tetrazine (s-tetrazine) is a promising redox center for organic electrode materials due to its low molecular weight and ability to undergo two-electron redox reactions. However, in practice, the irreversibility of the second-electron transfer has often limited the specific capacities of the s-tetrazine-based electrodes in metal-organic cells. Herein, electrochemically reversible two-electron-transfer processes from the s-tetrazine core are demonstrated by introducing electron-withdrawing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical Environment Afforded by Engineered Hydrogel Critically Regulates Survival of Neural Stem Cells Transplanted in the Injured Spinal Cord via Piezo1-Mediated Mechanotransduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neural stem cell (NSC) transplantation is a promising therapeutic approach for spinal cord repair, but poor graft survival remains a critical challenge. This work reports that the mechanical properties of the transplantation environment play a crucial role in NSC survival in the injured spinal cord. While this previously developed engineered hydrogel effectively creates extracellular matrix preventing cystic cavity formation, NSCs transplanted as a complex with 10% hydrogel exhibits poor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practical Guidelines for Smartphone-Based Hearing Aid Application and Personal Sound Amplification Device Usage to Correct Hearing Loss in Korea Based on a Randomized Controlled Trial by the Patient-Centered Clinical Research Coordinating Center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The prevalence of mild-to-moderate hearing loss is increasing due to noise exposure and an expanding elderly population. Despite the benefits of hearing aids, many individuals avoid them due to cost and incomplete awareness, opting instead for smartphone-based hearing aid applications (SHAAs) and personal sound amplification products (PSAPs). However, these devices are currently lacking official approval for medical use. The study results, together with roundtable discussions organized by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generality-Driven Optimization of Enantio- and Regioselective Mono-Reduction of 1,2-Dicarbonyls by High-Throughput Experimentation and Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The longstanding quest for substrate generality stems from the unpredictability of single-model optimization. Leveraging high-throughput experimentation (HTE), we present a practical multi-substrate screening strategy for the general asymmetric mono-reduction of 1,2-dicarbonyls. Quantitative ¹H NMR spectroscopy combined with simultaneous chiral analysis by ^(19)F NMR for pooled crude mixtures accelerated the workflow eightfold. Robust screening of 31 chiral oxazaborolidinium ion (COBI) variants...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Coupling of Host and Electrolyte Achieving 1270 Wh L<sup>-1</sup> in Anode-Free Lithium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anode-free lithium metal batteries (LMBs) represent a promising avenue for maximizing energy density by eliminating excess lithium (Li), yet their practical implementation is impeded by limited Li reversibility and pronounced interfacial instability. Herein, a synergistic coupling strategy is reported that integrates a highly reversible host (RH) with a rationally designed, carbonate-rich electrolyte (DEL) to concurrently address these fundamental challenges. The RH spontaneously induces the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Burden of Central Nervous System Cancer in the United States, 1990-2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These findings provide valuable insights into the CNS cancer burden across the US by age, sex, location, and SDI, enabling better public health status assessments, health care policy restructuring, and resource redistribution for improved care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparisons of optical characteristics between 3D printed dental resins and resin composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: To compare the optical characteristics of 3D-printed resins and conventional resin composites, focusing on color differences, whiteness index, and translucency under varying specimen thicknesses and polishing conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Stratification Strategies and Implementation of Exercise Training in Patients with Multiple Myeloma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: This review aims to explore key clinical considerations for prescribing exercise in individuals with multiple myeloma (MM) and to evaluate current evidence to develop exercise regimens that prioritize both safety and efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors and Incidence of Reoperation in Direct-to-Implant Breast Reconstruction Surgery Among Patients with Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with breast cancer undergoing DTI reconstruction, age, radiotherapy, and lymphedema were significant risk factors for capsular contracture. These findings highlight the importance of individualized preoperative planning and counseling to reduce the risk and improve outcomes. Further research should focus on developing strategies to manage these identified risk factors and prevent capsular contracture.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor microenvironment remodeling across thyroid cancer differentiation states revealed by spatial transcriptomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that dedifferentiation in thyroid cancer is associated with an immunosuppressive TME that promotes tumor progression. Therapeutic strategies targeting JAK-STAT and VEGF pathways, or enhancing NK cell activity, may hold promises for aggressive thyroid cancers. Further studies with larger cohorts are necessary to validate these findings and develop targeted therapies for aggressive thyroid cancers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transitions into and out of child maltreatment: differential effects on depressive symptoms and gender differences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite well-established evidence on the mental health consequences of child maltreatment, prior research is limited by the assumption that changes in maltreatment status have symmetrical impacts. This study investigated the association between child maltreatment and depressive symptoms, distinguishing transitions into and out of abuse and neglect. Potential gender differences were also examined. This study used six waves of longitudinal data from the nationally representative Korean Children...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Swept-source optical coherence tomography analysis of retinal and choroidal structures in school-aged children after laser photocoagulation for type 1 retinopathy of prematurity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: School-aged children treated with laser photocoagulation for ROP showed increased retinal vascular tortuosity and thickness in the central foveal to parafoveal regions, while choroidal thickness and vascularity remained unchanged in the central 1500 μm zone on SS-OCT device. These findings suggest localized retinal changes with preserved choroidal integrity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence in Acupuncture: Recommendations from the Society for Acupuncture Research Special Interest Group Artificial Intelligence and Digital Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Cognitive Trajectories in Isolated REM Sleep Behavior Disorder: Effects of Sex and Longstanding Disease Duration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Gradual cognitive decline in attention/working memory and memory may represent a natural course of neurodegeneration in men with iRBD, without necessarily indicating imminent phenoconversion. Women with iRBD appeared to show greater resilience to cognitive decline compared to men.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resolving falsely elevated vancomycin levels in KIMS immunoassay due to monoclonal IgM interference]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given its narrow therapeutic index and risk of nephrotoxicity, vancomycin requires accurate concentration monitoring. While immunoassays such as the Kinetic Interaction of Microparticles in Solution (KIMS) are widely used for their speed and simplicity, they are susceptible to interference by paraproteins such as monoclonal immunoglobulins. Here, we present the first case of falsely elevated vancomycin concentrations measured by KIMS due to monoclonal IgM interference, indicated by a 'kinetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A systematic review of psychological difficulties among elite sports coaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This systematic review examined the psychological difficulties experienced by elite sports coaches, focusing on their causes, consequences, and potential interventions. Despite increasing recognition of the challenges faced by coaches, limited attention has been paid to understanding their psychological difficulties and available support systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The association between the adenoid microbiome and chronic otitis media with effusion in children differs according to age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Chronic otitis media with effusion (COME) can adversely affect childhood development, and while the adenoid has been considered a reservoir for bacterial pathogens contributing to the pathogenesis of COME, the role of the adenoid microbiome in COME remains unclear. This study analyzed both the adenoid and gut microbiome in children with and without COME to identify their potential roles in the disease's pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum NOTCH3 Extracellular Domain in Patients With CADASIL]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Cerebral autosomal dominant arteriopathy with subcortical infarcts and leukoencephalopathy (CADASIL) is a hereditary small vessel disease caused by variants in the NOTCH3 gene. The extracellular domain of NOTCH3 (N3ECD) has been proposed as a potential serum biomarker for CADASIL. However, its diagnostic utility remains uncertain. The aim of this study was to evaluate serum N3ECD levels in patients with CADASIL and assess their potential as a diagnostic or prognostic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gradient mesoporosity in hierarchical ZIF-8 by temperature-modulated soft-templating]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Engineering hierarchical porosity in metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) is critical for improving mass transport and expanding their utility in catalysis, separation, and adsorption. We report a temperature-controlled soft-templating method for precise tuning of mesopore size in zeolitic imidazolate framework-8 (ZIF-8), employing a single amphiphilic block copolymer as the structure-directing agent. Systematic variation of the synthesis temperature yields a distinctive gradient mesoporous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A20 mRNA therapeutics ameliorate systemic sclerosis by suppressing TRAF-6/NF-KB signaling and DREAM expression and exerting antifibrotic effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Systemic sclerosis (SSc) is a chronic autoimmune disorder characterized by progressive fibrosis, vascular abnormalities, and immune dysregulation. Decreased expression of A20 (TNFAIP3), a key negative regulator of inflammation, has been shown to aggravate SSc pathogenesis by enhancing fibroblast activation and promoting collagen production. This study explores the therapeutic efficacy of A20 mRNA-lipid nanoparticle (LNP) delivery in restoring A20 expression and mitigating fibrosis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum gamma-glutamyl transferase level is associated with the risk of pancreatic cystic neoplasms: A nationwide retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher GGT level is associated with increased risk of PCNs. Therefore, serum GGT levels might have a role as a biomarker for the development of PCNs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isatuximab in combination with chemotherapy for pediatric patients with relapsed/refractory acute lymphoblastic leukemia or acute myeloid leukemia: The ISAKIDS study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Children with relapsed acute leukemia have a poor prognosis; current relapse treatments are toxic, and novel treatments are needed. The anti-CD38 antibody isatuximab is approved for relapsed-refractory multiple myeloma in adults. We present results of the ISAKIDS study (NCT03860844) investigating isatuximab in children with relapsed-refractory acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) or acute myeloid leukemia (AML). This Phase 2, single-arm, multicenter, open-label study enrolled children aged 28 days...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential effects of physical activity on behavioral and prefrontal responses during repetitive inhibitory control in older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Regular physical activity may enhance cognitive adaptability and selective inhibition in older adults. Behavioral improvements were more evident than neural differences between the groups, highlighting the potential of everyday physical activity to support cognitive resilience in aging. This study provides neurophysiological evidence supporting the integration of physical activity into cognitive intervention strategies for older populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure Reduction During Anesthetic Induction with Remimazolam versus Propofol in Elderly Patients: Pharmacodynamic Modeling of Remimazolam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In elderly patients undergoing general anesthesia with remimazolam, the relationship between dose and MBP reduction during induction was well characterized using a modified logistic model, with body weight as a significant covariate. TCI may represent an effective dosing strategy for maintaining hemodynamic stability during anesthetic induction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PKPy: a Python-based framework for automated population pharmacokinetic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present PKPy, an open-source Python framework designed to automate population pharmacokinetic analysis workflows. The framework emphasizes user accessibility by minimizing the need for manual parameter initialization while maintaining analytical rigor. PKPy implements both one-compartment and two-compartment pharmacokinetic models (with and without first-order absorption) with integrated capabilities for parameter estimation, covariate analysis, and comprehensive diagnostics. The framework's...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of predictive and evaluation models for the retro reflectivity performance of pavement lane markings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The developed models are expected to assist in establishing maintenance plans, formulating budgets, and determining repair work, as well as developing relevant regulations and standards in Seoul.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Osseointegration properties of niobia-modified yttria-stabilized zirconia implant surface: an <em>in vivo</em> study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sandblasted (Y,Nb)-TZP implants indicated superior osseointegration in comparison to SLA titanium and smooth-surface 3D-printed 3Y-TZP implants. The enhanced osseointegration observed in this study supports the clinical potential of (Y,Nb)-TZP as a next-generation zirconia implant material.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the accuracy of removable partial denture frameworks fabricated using conventional and digital impressions: a clinical study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Clinically acceptable RPD framework accuracy was achieved in both groups. However, accuracy was significantly better in the IOS group, especially at the terminal abutments of distal-extension RPDs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing impression techniques in the prosthodontic treatment for edentulous patients: a 3D finite element analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Selective pressure trays modified tissue loading locally at the relief site; however, these did not seem to provide a substantial biomechanical advantage, particularly on bone. Their clinical relevance remains limited and needs further supporting evidence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International Statistical Classification of Diseases and data gaps in traditional medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of Modified High-Performance Ion Chromatography Analytical Method for Inositol Phosphates in Soybeans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phosphorus in the form of phytic acid or myo-inositol hexakisphosphate is not absorbable by animals, leading to decreased bioavailability of essential minerals such as iron, zinc, and calcium. This study aimed to develop and validate a simple and efficient method for measuring inositol phosphates in soybeans. The four types of inositol phosphates analyzed were D-myo-inositol-1,5,6-triphosphate, D-myo-inositol-1,4,5,6-tetraphosphate, D-myo-inositol-1,3,4,5,6-pentaphosphate, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of <em>Levilactobacillus brevis</em> KU15159 on Intestinal Function and Bowel Activity in Loperamide-Induced Constipation in Sprague-Dawley Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Constipation is one of the most common gastrointestinal disorders, with an increasing prevalence. Lactic acid bacteria are known to improve the colon microenvironment; however, the ameliorative effect of Levilactobacillus brevis KU15159 on constipation has not been examined. This study aimed to investigate the effects of L. brevis KU15159 administration on improving intestinal function and defecation activity in an animal model of loperamide-induced constipation. Six-week-old Sprague-Dawley rats...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recognizing emotions in music through a computerized method: a novel way of evaluating social maturity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This study used music emotion recognition to evaluate emotion perception and aimed to explore the relationship between social maturity and musical emotion recognition in both autism spectrum disorder (ASD) and controls groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Costs and cost-effectiveness of robotic-assisted surgery in South Korea: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first comprehensive systematic review and meta-analysis specifically assessing the economic implications of RAS in Korea. Our findings indicate that RAS is more costly than other surgical modalities at the time of surgery. However, the current review identified a lack of evidence on post-discharge costs, and no comprehensive cost-effectiveness or cost-utility analyses have been conducted in Korea. Future studies are encouraging to explore the long-term costs across...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preliminary Study on Host Use and Phylogenetic Analysis of <em>Corethrella nippon</em> in Taiwan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated frog-biting dipteran species using newly designed frog-calling traps in Taiwan. The trap effectively collected specimens from both families, Culicidae and Corethrellidae, demonstrating its utility. Host preference analysis revealed that Odorrana swinhoana (Boulenger, 1903) and Kurixalus eiffingeri (Boettger, 1895) were most frequently associated with collected specimens of Corethrellidae. Additionally, the corethrellids were predominantly attracted to a sound frequency...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valorization of Kraft Lignin via Isocyanate Modification for Use in Polylactic Acid Biocomposites with Improved Mechanical and Functional Properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study focused on improving the dispersibility and phase compatibility of kraft lignin (KL) with polymeric matrices by introducing hexyl alkane groups onto its surface through urethane bonds, yielding hexyl isocyanate-modified KL (KL-HIC) with an 82% degree of substitution (DS). The chemically modified lignin was characterized by Fourier transform infrared spectroscopy (FT-IR) and nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR). This modification enhanced thermoplasticity, decreased the glass transition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A GC-MS-Based Urinary Metabolomic Profiling to Identify Potential Biomarkers of Metabolic Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic syndrome (MetS) is a multifactorial condition characterized by central obesity, dyslipidemia, hypertension, and insulin resistance, increasing the risk of cardiovascular disease and type 2 diabetes. Despite its clinical significance, current diagnostic methods rely on invasive blood-based assessments. This study investigates the potential of urinary metabolomics as a noninvasive alternative for MetS diagnosis. Using gas chromatography-mass spectrometry (GC-MS), we analyzed urinary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Additive renoprotective effects of oral calcitriol on patients with IgA nephropathy receiving RAS blockers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The addition of 0.25 μg/day calcitriol to RASBs safely lowered residual proteinuria and slowed the eGFR decline in patients with IgAN, suggesting a potential therapeutic role for calcitriol in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Integration of Frequency-Dependent Impedance and Machine Learning in Semiconductor Metal Oxide-Based Breath Sensors for High-Performance Gas Discrimination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Frequency-dependent impedance spectroscopy in combination with machine learning offers a powerful strategy for discriminating among gas species using mutually interacting semiconductor metal oxide (SMO) gas sensors. In this study, 0.3 at% platinum-loaded SnO(2) sensing materials were employed to breath-based disease detection, with a focus on machine learning-assisted discrimination of mixtures of acetone (0.5-2.5 ppm) and ethanol (0.5-2.5 ppm) under both dry and humid environments (80% relative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Brain Variability in Recent-Onset and Chronic Schizophrenia: Evidence from Person-Based Similarity Index Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with schizophrenia show marked structural brain heterogeneity compared with healthy controls, which is detectable even in the early stages of the illness. Although there were few differences in PBSI scores between the recent-onset and chronic schizophrenia groups and limited correlations between PBSI scores and clinical measures, the PBSI may still provide valuable insights into individual differences contributing to clinical heterogeneity in schizophrenia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolution of Newcastle Disease Virus Subgenotype VII.1.1 in Iran, 2017-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Newcastle disease (ND), caused by Newcastle disease virus (NDV), has posed a continuous threat to Iran's poultry industry since its first detection in the early 1950s, with subgenotype VII.1.1 currently recognized as the dominant circulating strain. To gain deeper insights into the evolutionary dynamics of NDV in Iran, we performed genome sequencing and phylogenetic analysis on 60 viruses isolated from domestic poultry and wild birds between 2017 and 2024. Maximum likelihood and Bayesian...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superior affinity of ubiquicidin peptide united with <em>ortho</em>-borylated acetophenone to an amine-containing model bacterial membrane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial peptides (AMPs) have been considered as potential agents to combat bacterial resistance to conventional antibiotics. It has been shown that modifying the cationic peptides with 2-acetylphenylboronic acid (2-APBA) improves the binding efficacy with these resistant bacterial membranes via the formation of a covalent iminoboronate bond with lipids, such as 1,2-dioleoyl-sn-glycero-3-[phospho-rac-(3-lysyl(1-glycerol))] (Lys PG). In the present study, the cationic peptide UBI (29-41) is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of consultation-based hospice palliative care team on self-determination respect rates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: Despite the increasing implementation of consultation-based hospice palliative care teams in tertiary hospitals of Korea, there is limited research on their impact on self-determination respect rates. Understanding this impact is crucial for improving end-of-life care practices and respecting patient autonomy. The aim of this study is to assess the trends in self-determination respect rates regarding advance care planning before and after the introduction of a consultation-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rare Clinical Presentation of Diffuse Large B-Cell Lymphoma as Otitis Media and Mastoiditis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lymphomas originating in the ear are extremely rare. As with other malignancies of the temporal bone, diagnosis of lymphoma in the middle ear and temporal bone is often delayed, negatively impacting treatment and prognosis. The delay in diagnosis is primarily due to its clinical presentation overlapping with benign infectious conditions of the middle ear. Here, we present a rare case of a 46-year-old woman with prolonged otorrhea, hearing disturbances, intermittent vertigo, and headache. She...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of Minimal Inverted-J Incision for Bone-Anchored Hearing Aid Attract Implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our novel incision technique for BAHA Attract implantation addresses the limitations associated with both the classical and minimal linear incision approaches.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polarity-Controlled Volatile HfO<sub>2</sub> Memristors with Bimodal Conductance for Neuromorphic Synapses and Reservoir Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this work, an HfO(2)-based memristor exhibiting bimodal switching, wherein the device's conductance is modulated not only by the input stimulus but also by the polarity of the read voltage, is introduced. Uniquely, this device demonstrates reliable short-term memory (STM)-like behavior and supports 16 well-separated conductance states through 4-bit pulsed inputs. Remarkably, under the same input conditions, reversing the polarity of the read voltage results in 16 more different conductance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complementary Multi-Resonance Thermally Activated Delayed Fluorescence Design for Blue OLEDs Beyond the Concentration Limit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advances in boron-based organic compounds exhibiting multi-resonance (MR)-type thermally activated delayed fluorescence (TADF) have been primarily driven by their potential as narrowband blue emitters for wide-gamut display applications. Nevertheless, the intrinsically planar architecture of MR-type TADF molecules often leads to pronounced concentration quenching at elevated doping levels, posing a significant impediment to realizing highly efficient organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Purity Single Photon Extraction from Diamond Nitrogen-Vacancy Centers in Low-Numerical-Aperture Optical Systems via Defect-Selective Metalens Printing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solid-state quantum emitters, such as nitrogen-vacancy (NV) centers in diamond, offer a promising route toward scalable quantum technologies. However, their random spatial distribution and inherently broad dipole emission severely hinder high-purity single-photon extraction-particularly in low-numerical-aperture (NA) optical systems, which are essential for compact and scalable quantum photonic systems. Here, a defect-selective metalens integration approach is presented that allows precise and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Progress of Vanadium Oxide and its Hybrid Composites-Based Electrochromic Supercapacitors: An Advanced Future Energy Storage Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Supercapacitors with integrated electrochromic functionality, capable of changing color in response to stored energy levels, represent a promising and emerging technology. These multifunctional devices offer simultaneous energy storage and real-time visual feedback through dynamic color modulation, making them particularly appealing for modern digital applications. When integrated into smart windows, they can contribute to energy savings by reducing the need for artificial heating and cooling....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in Smoking Status in Depressed Patients and the Risk of Dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Changes in smoking behavior after depression diagnosis influence dementia risk, underscoring the need for cessation strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forensic detection of medical image manipulation using PACS and DICOM artifacts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the digitization of medical information, illegal activities such as medical crimes and insurance fraud through tampering have increased. Medical images are particularly vulnerable due to their nature as soft copies and their transmission over networks. National research institutions such as NIST provide guidelines that define security control elements for managing medical images, primarily out of concern for system vulnerabilities. However, there is still a lack of established or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phosphate adsorption by poultry manure biochar impregnated with different sources of magnesium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rise in fertilizer prices and decline in fertilizer availability have prompted concerns about the sustainability and equity of fertilizer use. Utilizing P‑rich feedstocks for biochar production and further enriching them with P recovered from wastewater has the potential to transform conventional industrial P fertilizers. We explored different sources and levels of Mg as impregnation materials for poultry manure biochar production to optimize the retention of dissolved inorganic phosphate....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of suicide in cancer patients: nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In cancer patients, suicide risk remained elevated for several years after diagnosis, but decreased over time and became similar to that of matched controls after 5 years. However, the temporal pattern varied by cancer type, and suicide risk remained high for patients with haematological cancers. Suicide risk screening is necessary from the time of cancer diagnosis, even in long-term survivors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying overtraining biomarkers through proteomic analysis of extracellular vesicles derived from the central nervous system of male mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overtraining, which results in central nervous system (CNS)-fatigue-related symptoms, leads to a long-term decline in performance. This study investigated CNS-derived EV protein content under overtraining conditions to identify potential biomarkers. Eight-week-old C57BL/6J mice were randomly divided into three groups: sedentary (SED, n = 7), exercise control (EX, n = 8), and overtraining (OT, n = 9) groups. The OT group underwent an 8-week downhill treadmill-based overtraining induction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skin barrier as a target for the prediction, prevention, and treatment of atopic dermatitis and food allergy in infancy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atopic dermatitis (AD) and food allergy (FA) frequently manifest during infancy and share skin barrier dysfunction as a critical early pathogenic event. Recent research has elucidated structural, lipidomic, microbial, and immunologic abnormalities that compromise the skin barrier and contribute to disease onset. Filaggrin gene mutations, altered ceramide profiles, and type 2 cytokine-driven inflammation are among the key factors disrupting epidermal integrity. While AD and FA exhibit overlapping...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoscale Au-Si eutectic mixtures formed by dewetting of a Au-Ni film on Si<sub>3</sub>N<sub>4</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251103142050&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Formation of a eutectic AuSi compound was observed during the solid state dewetting and agglomeration in a Ni-Au bilayer thin film grown on a Si(3)N(4) substrate using coherent X-ray diffractive imaging, X-ray diffraction, and scanning electron microscopy. During rapid thermal annealing at 850 °C in vacuum, AuNi films first separate into islands that are composed of a mixture of Au-rich and Ni-rich phases. As the dewetting proceeds, Si and nitrogen dissociate due to the catalytic action of Ni,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251103142050&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cohort profile and representativeness of participants in the Danish monozygotic twin study on migraine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Danish Monozygotic Twin Study on Migraine is a population-based twin study established in 2023-2024. The cohort was created to lay the foundation for innovative studies of the role of environmental, genetic, and epigenetic factors and their complex interactions in the pathogenesis of migraine. The aim of this paper is to describe data collection, content, characteristics of participants and to assess the representativeness of the cohort by comparing participants to non-responders. Danish...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of total arch replacement with frozen elephant trunk for type B aortic dissection involving left subclavian artery-adjacent entry: a strategy for anatomically challenging cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Total arch replacement with a frozen elephant trunk is safe for anatomically challenging type B aortic dissection with an entry near the left subclavian artery and represents a viable treatment option in this setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CD40 transcriptomic expression patterns across malignancies: implications for clinical trials of CD40 agonists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High CD40 expression correlated with liver and bile duct, pancreatic, and ovarian cancers, as well as with CD28 and GITR transcripts. Immune marker co-expression in individual patients merits further exploration for the development of CD40-based and other immunotherapy interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The intensive care medicine research agenda for the management of ICU acquired weakness: a multinational, interprofessional perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intensive care unit acquired weakness (ICUAW) is common in critically ill patients, contributing to substantial morbidity. Major trials and novel mechanistic findings published over the past years have advanced knowledge for the prevention and treatment of ICUAW. To streamline future research priorities, a multinational, interdisciplinary group of ICU clinicians, researchers, and people with lived experience convened to develop this evidence-based research agenda. Using a stepwise process...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the flush: rethinking reactions to ethanol-based disinfectants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interspecific secondary plasmodesmata at parasitic interface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obligate parasitic plants often establish symplastic connections with their hosts. This symplastic continuity is mediated by plasma membrane-lined channels referred to as interspecific secondary plasmodesmata, which develop at the interface between the parasite and its host. However, the molecular mechanisms underlying the formation of these interspecific secondary plasmodesmata remain unclear. In this mini review, we summarize current knowledge of plasmodesmata biogenesis at diverse cellular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differentiation of iPS Cells into Periodontal Ligament Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Periodontal ligament (PDL) is a thin connective tissue that connects the tooth to the bony socket and plays a crucial role in the regeneration and maintenance of homeostasis of periodontal tissues by supplying stem/progenitor cells. Induced pluripotent stem cells (iPSCs) are highly anticipated in regenerative medicine because of their differentiation potential into a wide variety of cell types. In this study, we investigated the effects of humoral factors on iPSC differentiation by culturing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Host-microbiota matching and epigenetic modulation drive Daphnia magna responses to cyanobacterial stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial communities are crucial in host adaptation to stressors, particularly in dynamic ecosystems. In aquatic environments, Daphnia magna is ideal for studying host-microbiome interactions due to its ecological importance and sensitivity. Adaptation to toxins, such as those produced by cyanobacteria, may involve both host and microbial gene repertoires. Yet, the influence of microbiota composition and function on host performance remains poorly understood. Because epigenetic mechanisms such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sterically Stabilized (Zr,Ti)-(Al,Sn,Pb,Bi)-C MAX Phase Solid Solutions with Zn Additions and Enhanced Chemical Complexity on the A-Site]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The MAX phases constitute a family of nanolaminated ternary carbides and nitrides renowned for their compositional versatility, as reflected in the easy formation of solid solutions with variable chemical complexity. Synthesizing MAX phase solid solutions with intentionally tailored chemical complexity can produce materials that are able to meet the property requirements of the targeted application(s). This work presents an effective strategy specifically developed to design and fabricate highly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Representational dynamics of the main dimensions of object space: Face/body selectivity aligns temporally with animal taxonomy but not with animacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Object representations are organized according to multiple dimensions, with an important role for the distinction between animate and inanimate objects and for selectivity for faces versus bodies. For other dimensions, questions remain how they stand relative to these two primary dimensions. One such dimension is a graded selectivity for the taxonomic level that an animal belongs to. Earlier research suggested that animacy can be understood as a graded selectivity for animal taxonomy, although a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Case of Adipophilin-Positive Pancreatic Intraductal Papillary Mucinous Neoplasm (IPMN) With Eosinophilia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adipophilin expression and eosinophilia associated with intraductal papillary mucinous neoplasm (IPMN) are extremely rare in the literature, and the relationship between adipophilin expression and IPMN remains unclear. This study reports the case of a 67-year-old male patient with adipophilin-positive IPMN and eosinophilia, which diminished following R0 surgical resection. The patient underwent pancreaticoduodenectomy for a pancreatic head (Ph) tumor detected by abdominal echo screening....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel water-from-air technology: creeping clathrate desalination of deliquescent salt solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Water scarcity is an escalating global challenge driven by population growth and resource depletion. Conventional fresh water production methods typically require access to liquid water sources, limiting their applicability in remote or arid regions. Water-from-air technologies offer a potential solution but are often hindered by high energy demands and/or climatological conditions. This study introduces clathrate-based desalination of deliquescent salt solutions as a novel approach for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wrapping a single crystal spin-crossover complex with a single crystal non-spin-crossover complex to modulate the spin-transition temperature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The formation of a heterojunction interface between different materials could lead to emergent functions that are not the simple sum of the properties of each component. Here we report the modulation of physical properties due to the lattice mismatch between two molecular crystals. Using metal complexes as a motif, we created a crystalline object that can be referred to as a core-shell crystal, in which a single crystal of one complex (Fe^(II) complex) is wrapped with a single crystal of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Colletotrichum tofieldiae</em> enhances phosphorus uptake and biomass production and alters the microbial interactions in the rhizosphere of komatsuna (<em>Brassica rapa</em> var. <em>perviridis</em>) grown in phosphorus-deficient farm soils]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial bioinoculants should play important roles to achieve sustainable phosphorus (P) management in agriculture. Colletotrichum tofieldiae (Ct), a fungal endophyte, is a promising material that supports phosphorus acquisition in Arabidopsis under low phosphorus (P) conditions and promotes maize and tomato growth in a greenhouse. However, its effects on leafy vegetables such as komatsuna, particularly those with a range of P availability in the soil, remain largely unclear. This study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preface to the special issue "Diverse Symbiotic Relationships between Plants and Microbes in the Phyllosphere and Rhizosphere"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phyllosphere C1-microorganisms: Their interaction with plants and contribution to the global carbon cycle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plants emit a variety of volatile organic compounds (VOCs), including C1-compounds such as methane and methanol, which are major components of plant-derived VOCs. A group of microorganisms called methylotrophs or C1-microorganisms utilize these C1-compounds as a single source of carbon and energy and contribute to driving the global carbon cycle between two major greenhouse gases, CO(2) and methane. C1-microorganisms inhabit the surface of the above-ground part of plants (phyllosphere), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell Raman spectroscopic analysis of bacteroids in soybean nodules to observe the relationship between biomolecular constituents and symbiotic nitrogen fixation activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitrogen fixation in soybean occurs as a result of symbiosis between the plant and rhizobia in the nodules. This process allows both the plant and the symbiont to acquire vital nutrition. To fully understand the symbiosis, many researchers have attempted to attain a deeper interpretation of the biomolecular behavior or enhance the nitrogen fixation activity of bacteroids. However, most studies have focused on forward and reverse genetics approaches to evaluate the contribution of a particular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Various types of mycorrhizal fungi sequences detected in single intracellular vesicles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A diverse range of microbes have been observed to coexist in plant roots in the field, among which arbuscular mycorrhizal fungi (AMFs) are universal and have recently been shown to be of two types: one belonging to the subphylum Glomeromycotina (G-AMF) and the other to the subphylum Mucoromycotina (M-AMF). These two types of mycorrhizal fungi are known to co-occur in roots. This is because, in addition to the morphological evidence, diverse ribosomal RNA (rRNA) gene sequences, including those of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elimination mechanism of vanillin from non-phenolic β-O-4-type terminals formed in guaiacyl lignin: a combined kinetic and theoretical study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The alkaline aerobic oxidation of lignin to vanillin (4-hydroxy-3-methoxybenzaldehyde) has been employed as an industrial method for producing bio-based low-molecular-weight aromatic compounds. To deepen the molecular-level understanding of this reaction, we have been investigating the vanillin formation mechanism from native softwood lignin. One of the major reaction pathways involves oxidative degradation of β-O-4-type internal units, followed by alkaline-induced elimination of vanillin from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimum colonoscopy observation time for colonic diverticular bleeding: A new benchmark based on the 5% plateau time]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although it varied according to the CT findings, the overall 5% plateau time was 40 minutes. This offers a practical benchmark for the minimum observation time without SRH detection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Latent Intrarenal Renin-Angiotensin-Aldosterone System Activation Could Persist Until Early School-Aged in Children with a History of Low Birth Weight]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results indicated that latent intrarenal RAAS activation in children with a history of LBW persists until early school age and may contribute to the progression of CKD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progress in the management of pregnancy in patients with neuromyelitis optica spectrum disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuromyelitis optica spectrum disorder (NMOSD) is an autoimmune astrocytopathy characterized by autoantibodies against aquaporin-4 (AQP) that predominantly affecting women of childbearing potential. Unlike multiple sclerosis, NMOSD poses a higher risk of severe and irreversible postpartum relapse, making pregnancy a significant concern in affected women. Historically, in Japan, immunosuppressive treatments were contraindicated in women who could become pregnant, leading many to discontinue...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meta-representations as representations of processes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we explore how the notion of meta-representations in higher-order theories (HOT) of consciousness can be implemented in computational models. HOT suggests that consciousness emerges from meta-representations, which are representations of first-order sensory representations. However, translating this abstract concept into a concrete computational model, such as those used in artificial intelligence, presents a theoretical challenge. For example, a simplistic interpretation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of different traction devices on colorectal endoscopic submucosal dissection outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: There were no significant differences in ESD therapeutic results between SCTB and SO-C, while the SCTB had a faster deployment time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting Substrate Reactivity in Oxidative Homocoupling of Phenols Using Positive and Unlabeled Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A positive and unlabeled machine learning (PU learning) model was trained to predict substrate reactivity in the oxidative homocoupling of phenols under different conditions. We demonstrated its effectiveness by conducting validation using two descriptor sets: 28-dimensional descriptors considered to influence reactivity and extended-connectivity fingerprints. We performed parameter tuning of the model using our experimental data and determined that the optimized parameters provided excellent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased Antidepressant Prescriptions for Children and Adolescents with Major Depressive Disorder in Japan Based on a Claims Database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The rate of child and adolescent patients prescribed antidepressants increased, while the antidepressant prescription rate among child and adolescent patients with MDD declined, indicating that Japanese physicians have become more cautious about the use of antidepressants. It is critical to generate new clinical data on the efficacy and safety of antidepressants for Japanese child and adolescent patients with MDD and to consider the development of additional pediatric indications for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunable optical properties in the (110)<sub>p</sub>-oriented layered halide perovskite FA<sub>4</sub>Pb<sub>2</sub>I<sub>7.5</sub>(SCN)<sub>0.5</sub> by Br substitution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic-inorganic hybrid halide perovskites have been explored extensively for optoelectronic functional materials. Here, we report (110)(p)-oriented layered halide perovskite thin films with nominal compositions of FA(4)Pb(2)(Br(x)I(1-x))(7.5)(SCN)(0.5) (x = 0, 0.25, 0.5, 0.75, and 1). X-ray diffraction measurements and UV-visible diffuse reflectance measurements demonstrate the successful formation of a solid solution between iodide and bromide. The band gap gradually changes from 2.18 eV to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Giving body to the multitrait framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given its assumption that cognition is embodied, the multitrait framework could benefit from engaging with recent work in embodied cognitive science. Here, we introduce three lines of contemporary research-from ecological psychology, basal cognition, and embodied cognitive neuroscience-which help contextualize the article's "trait-linkage" findings and further support the authors' arguments for evolutionary continuity between simple and complex cognitive traits.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of Exercise Right Ventricular-Pulmonary Arterial Coupling in Primary Mitral Regurgitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Exercise right ventricular-pulmonary arterial coupling, particularly intermediate exTAPSE/sPAP, is a robust and feasible measure independently associated with adverse outcomes, and provides prognostic information beyond resting variables and cardiorespiratory fitness, potentially refining risk stratification and guiding management in patients with primary mitral regurgitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Novel Synthetic Hydrogel Sealant for Effective Prevention of Liver Resection-Associated Bile Leakage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bile leakage is a major complication following hepatectomy; these often lead to surgical site infections, liver failure, and even death. Biomaterials, including fibrinogen-based collagen fleece (TachoSil) and fibrin glue, are ineffective for bile sealing. Synthetic sealants, including cyanoacrylate and polymer-based materials, independent of coagulation, are inadequate for bile leakage management. Therefore, in the present study, a novel hydrogel-based sealant (DCSN_100_25) is developed using 3...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local recurrence after glans-sparing surgery: no impact on penile cancer-specific survival]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients undergoing GSS for PSCC demonstrate excellent survival outcomes, despite LR in 29% of men. These findings support the use of GSS as a safe and effective treatment option for patients committed to adequate follow-up.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Body Mass Index and Surgical Outcomes in Degenerative Cervical Myelopathy: Findings From a Prospective Multicenter Cohort of 935 Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher BMI in DCM was associated with greater operative demands, higher OPLL prevalence, and persistent postoperative alignment and motion deficits. However, neurological recovery and patient-reported outcomes were comparable across BMI categories. In patients with surgical indications based on symptoms and imaging findings, surgery can be performed appropriately regardless of BMI, with favorable outcomes achievable through thorough preoperative assessment and strategic surgical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergy Effects in a Bimetallic Ru ─ Pt Alloy Catalyst for Low-H<sub>2</sub>-Pressure Hydrogenolysis of Low-Density Polyethylene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogenolysis of low-density polyethylene (LDPE) under low pressure of H(2) has been accomplished with a Ru─Pt bimetallic alloy catalyst. Using Ru(5)Pt(1)/CeO(2) (atomic ratio of Ru to Pt is 5:1) as a catalyst, LDPE was efficiently converted (97.6 ± 2.5% conversion) to gas and liquid hydrocarbons under 5 bar of H(2) at 200 °C, whereas Ru/CeO(2) and Pt/CeO(2) showed much lower conversion (45.7 ± 3.7% and < 1%, respectively), under the same conditions. Mechanistic studies suggested that the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of Preoperative Mental Health on Surgical and Clinical Outcomes in Degenerative Cervical Myelopathy: A Multicenter Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preoperative mental health status does not impact neurological improvement but significantly affects recovery in pain and QOL. These findings suggest that evaluating patients' psychological well-being before surgery could enhance perioperative planning and support more accurate prognostic counseling.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of C5 Methylation on Cytidine Photohydration Revealed by Deep-Ultraviolet Transient Absorption Anisotropy Spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[C5 methylation enhances the photostability of monomeric cytidine (Cyd), but the molecular basis of this effect has remained unresolved. Here, we examine the photodynamics of Cyd and its C5-methylated analogue, 5-methylcytidine (5mCyd), using femtosecond deep-ultraviolet transient absorption anisotropy spectroscopy. Recent theoretical and spectroscopic studies have highlighted a metastable ground-state intermediate with a twisted C5═C6 double bond, which plays a key role in the photodynamics of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peptide Mass Fingerprinting of South American Xenarthrans: A New Resource for Zooarcheology and Palaeontology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Xenarthrans─armadillos, anteaters, and sloths─are endemic to the Americas, primarily inhabiting the Neotropics, where they represent a key component of faunal diversity. They have essential functions for ecosystem maintenance, such as insect control and nutrient cycling, playing key roles as ecosystem engineers. Despite their frequent occurrence in archeological and paleontological contexts, their identification is often hindered by the highly fragmented and morphologically indistinct nature of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment of H Pylori in Children to Prevent Gastric Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct polymerization of tyrosine conjugates into melanin-like polymers for efficient protection of photosensitive pesticides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Melanin-inspired materials are being increasingly utilized across diverse areas, with their unique light absorption properties playing a decisive role in multiple domains. However, constrained by the structural complexity, effective strategies for controlling their light absorption properties remain limited, which mainly focus on modulating intramolecular conjugation through molecular doping. Nevertheless, these strategies have hit a bottleneck in regulating the light absorption properties due...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of the visual reasoning test for the NIH Toolbox]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Cognition Battery of the NIH Toolbox (NIHTB) is an iPad-based set of brief assessments with documented test score reliability and validity, covering a range of cognitive functions for ages 3-85+. The construct of visual reasoning (VR) was identified as a measurement gap in previous versions of the NIHTB by a contingent of NIH-sponsored researchers. The VR Test was developed de novo to address this gap across the entire age spectrum. Given the intended brevity of NIHTB measures, VR was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A psychometric examination of computerized adaptive measures of posttraumatic stress disorder among military veterans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brenner et al. (2021) developed and initially tested two computerized adaptive measures of posttraumatic stress disorder (PTSD), one that provides a provisional diagnosis (PTSD computerized adaptive diagnostic screen [CAD-PTSD]) and one that estimates symptom severity (PTSD computerized adaptive severity test [CAT-PTSD]). We expanded on the initial psychometric findings by collecting data regarding test-retest reliability, incremental validity, and respondent burden. A sample of veterans (N =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eppikajutsuto for Treatment of Lymphatic Malformations in Children: A Nonrandomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this nonrandomized clinical trial of children with LMs, eppikajutsuto was associated with a reduction in lesion volume and was well tolerated. Further studies, including randomized clinical trials, are warranted to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of 4 Risk Stratification Tools for Delirium in the Emergency Department]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this prognostic study comparing 4 delirium tools to improve delirium detection and identify high-risk patients, the REDEEM score and the MDP tool had better performance for delirium detection in the ED. These findings lay the groundwork for integrating validated risk stratification into ED workflows to improve early delirium detection and inform prevention strategies for high-risk older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Effectiveness of Cladribine and S1P Receptor Modulators in Treatment-Naive Relapsing-Remitting MS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These findings suggest cladribine was associated with superior effectiveness in reducing disability progression over 25 months, likely due to reduced PIRA, despite comparable short-term NEDA-3 outcomes. However, relapse prevention declined after 36 months, suggesting retreatment or therapy modification within 3 years may be needed to maintain long-term disease control.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Remote, Automated Gamification and Community-Based Physical Activity in Parkinson Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moral pride promotes honesty in preschoolers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study investigated the role of pride in promoting honesty among children aged 3-6. Children (N = 247; 125 boys, 122 girls; middle-income Chinese families) participated in a temptation resistance paradigm, instructing them not to peek at a toy when unsupervised. Subsequently, children were randomly assigned to one of four experimental conditions: a moral pride condition, induced through a compliance task; a nonmoral pride condition, induced through a success task; a happiness...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trajectories of cross-ethnic friendships and their associations with school adjustment in ethnic minority adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cross-ethnic peer relations are pivotal for ethnic minority adolescents. However, there is limited understanding of how their cross-ethnic friendships with majority peers in school develop over time. Addressing this, this study aimed to investigate individual trajectories of cross-ethnic friendship in school and how they predict long-term school adjustment. Our sample consisted of 1,445 Turkish- and Moroccan-heritage minority adolescents in 70 Belgian middle schools (52.6% boys, M(age) = 15.07;...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subjective age in proximal and distal contexts: Both momentary pain and long-term trajectories of physical health shape daily dynamics of subjective age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Subjective age-the age people feel-fluctuates considerably across days and even within days. We investigated how subjective age fluctuations are intertwined with experiences of momentary pain and how the within-person couplings of subjective age and pain are shaped by long-term changes in physical health using data from 139 older individuals participating in the Berlin Aging Study II (age 67-88, 41.3% women). After providing long-term longitudinal data across on average 7 years on central facets...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application potential of therapeutic ultrasound in oral diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: To review the literature on the application potential of ultrasound in the treatment of various oral and dental diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of aging on mechanical and microbiological properties in CAD-CAM-milled and 3D-printed denture base resins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: To evaluate the adhesion of Candida albicans and the mechanical properties of resins in denture bases fabricated using conventional, milled, and 3D printing methods at different aging times.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing behavioral economic and internalizing symptom predictors of drinking trajectories over 3 years during emerging adulthood]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Behavioral economics highlights external influences on alcohol's reinforcing value and suggests life transitions in the mid-to-late 20s may increase costs of drinking, contributing to developmentally mediated drinking reductions among emerging adults. However, higher value for alcohol and fewer substance-free alternatives are theorized to predict persistent risky drinking. The current study compared behavioral economic indices of alcohol value with internalizing symptoms (e.g., anxiety,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in white matter volume and cortical thickness predict internalizing symptoms during early adolescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We sought to examine whether global structural changes in grey and white matter predict adolescent internalizing symptoms using a 3-year longitudinal design. Using secondary data analysis from the Adolescent Brain Cognitive Development Study, 6,564 participants (53% male, 55% White) were included in analyses. We used linear mixed-effects models to predict adolescent internalizing symptoms (measured at ages 12/13 via caregiver report and self-report) from structural brain metrics. Percent change...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abortion Education in U.S. Medical Schools: Curricular Variability by State Law]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Reproductive health, including abortion care, is a critical component of undergraduate medical education (UME) that is inconsistently included in UME. Objective: The objective of this study is to investigate the association between the inclusion of abortion and contraception topics in UME curricula overall and state-level abortion restrictions. Methods: A national cross-sectional survey of medical students was conducted from August 2022 to June 2023 using the American Medical Student...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SEOM-GEICAM-SOLTI clinical guidelines in advanced breast cancer (UPDATE 2025)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advanced breast cancer represents a challenge for patients and physicians due to its dynamic genomic changes, which are associated with resistance to treatments. The main goals of treatment in advanced breast cancer are to improve patient quality of life and to increase patient survival. This is achieved using the most appropriate sequence of treatments based on knowledge of the natural history of the disease. In these guidelines (updated in 2025), we summarize current evidence and available...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic analysis of Androctonus mauritanicus toursvirus: first evidence of Ascoviridae in arachnids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Viruses have long been known to infect various arthropod hosts, playing crucial roles in their ecology and evolution. While viral diversity has been well studied in insects, knowledge of viruses in arachnids remains limited. This study investigated the DNA virome of Androctonus mauritanicus (Moroccan black thick-tailed scorpion) to expand our understanding of viral diversity in non-insect arthropods and explore the evolutionary relationships of scorpion-associated viruses. Samples of Androctonus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Species Typing of Trypanosomatids Using Amplicon-Based Sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amplicon-based sequencing has emerged as an exceptionally powerful tool for the identification and characterization of microorganisms, offering enhanced sensitivity and specificity in molecular diagnostics. In this chapter, we detail the amplification and sequencing protocols for two critical genetic markers: the HSP70 gene, essential for identifying Leishmania species, and the 18S ribosomal RNA gene, a well-established marker for detecting Trypanosoma species. We provide a comprehensive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Effect of Fluoride on the Expression of 8-Hydroxy-2'-Deoxyguanosine in the Blood, Kidney, Liver, and Brain of Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a nomogram for predicting postoperative survival in patients with multifocal hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Postoperative antiviral treatment for patients with M-HCC, aimed at enhancing immune function and protecting liver function, has been shown to extend patient survival. Simultaneously, factors such as Child-Pugh, age, and Cirrhosis in patients with M-HCC have been associated with a decrease in postoperative survival time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Involuntary Psychiatric Commitments among Non-Western Immigrants during the Muhammad Cartoon Controversy in Denmark]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping Health State Utility from Disease-Specific Measures in Spinal Muscular Atrophy and Paroxysmal Nocturnal Hemoglobinuria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These newly developed mapping algorithms enable the estimation of EQ-5D-5L and SF-6Dv2 utilities in the absence of a preference-based measurement, thus supporting health economic evaluations of therapies for spinal muscular atrophy and paroxysmal nocturnal hemoglobinuria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Novel Fluorescence Nanoprobe Based on Molecularly Imprinted Polymer on Cobalt-Carbon Quantum Dots for Rapid Detection of Methamphetamine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In forensic drug analysis, detecting low concentrations of illicit drugs in samples presents a significant challenge. This paper introduces a novel approach for developing molecularly imprinted quantum dot materials (Co-AD QDs-MIPs) capable of efficiently detecting methamphetamine (METH) in artificial urine without the need for extraction or pretreatment. Using free radical polymerization, molecularly imprinted materials were coated onto the surface of quantum dots, forming a Co-AD QDs-MIPs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Re-sensitization of cancer multidrug resistance through P-gp, MRP1 and BCRP modulation: advances in terpenoids based cancer therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Among the most significant risks that many chemotherapeutic drugs currently encounter is the development of multidrug resistance (MDR) in cancerous cells. Numerous critical regulators are thought to be responsible for MDR and render therapeutic strategies inefficient. Several pathways mediate this effect, one of which is the upregulation of ATP-binding cassette (ABC) superfamily membrane transporters. Most of these transporters, which regarded as drug efflux pumps, are embedded in the cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the expression and mechanistic role of SYCP2 in cervical lesions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SYCP2 emerges as a critical biomarker for HPV-driven cervical carcinogenesis, with diagnostic potential for high-grade lesions and prognostic value for metastasis risk. Its regulatory role in IL13RA2-mediated signaling and association with viral response pathways suggest mechanistic involvement in tumor microenvironment remodeling. The dual context-dependent expression (upregulated in cervical cancer vs. downregulated in other malignancies) highlights tissue-specific oncogenic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Established and Emergent Reading Skills in Adults with Cerebellar Stroke: Evidence of Phonological Alexia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the impact of cerebellar stroke on both well-established reading skills and emergent literacy abilities using a combination of static and dynamic assessments. The static component involved a lexical decision task featuring novel orthographic forms (pseudowords) followed by tests of orthographic memory. The dynamic component employed a training protocol in an artificial orthography, requiring participants to learn new grapheme-phoneme correspondences and read in a novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive functioning in multiple sclerosis with focus on brainstem volume]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While no link was found between brainstem volumes and cognitive impairment, this analysis underscores the importance of considering various brain structures in understanding cognitive impairment in MS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunotherapy for Metastatic Pancreatic Neuroendocrine Tumors with High Mutational Burden and Mismatch Repair Alterations Following Treatment with Alkylating Chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alkylating agent-based chemotherapy is one of the main treatment options for patients with metastatic pancreatic neuroendocrine tumors (PanNETs).However, it favors the acquisition of a hypermutator phenotype, suggesting a potential benefit of immunotherapy.We aimed to describe the efficacy of immunotherapy in an international retrospective cohort of patients with metastatic well-differentiated PanNETs pretreated with alkylating therapy. The primary endpoint was progression-free survival (PFS)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal changes in the genetic and environmental influences on DNA methylation linked to obesity measures: a 5-year twin study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The reproducibility of obesity-related DNA methylation (DNAm) sites (CpGs) remains low across studies, and the underlying mechanisms involving genetic and environmental contributions require further investigation. In this study, we systematically searched PubMed, EMBASE, and EWAS catalogue for CpGs associated with BMI, waist circumference (WC), and waist-to-hip ratio (WHR) from previous publications, identifying 29 studies with 2,603/892/28 CpGs for BMI/WC/WHR, respectively. Then, based on 1,074...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The intracerebral hemorrhage checklist]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Aquatic Resource Surveys (NARS): the foundation for long-term aquatic monitoring data across the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is a common saying in business that "what matters gets measured". Environmental protection and sustainability certainly should qualify as important concerns for both businesses and governments. The 1970s marked the genesis of the modern environmental movement, with growing concern about water pollution in the United States (U.S.). In 1972, the U.S. enacted the Clean Water Act (CWA) "to restore and maintain the chemical, physical, and biological integrity of the Nation's waters". In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DSMG-Chip: A High-Throughput Degenerate qPCR Chip for Profiling Microbial DMSP and Related Organic Sulfur Metabolic Genes in Diverse Environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The organosulfur cycle involves active microbial transformations of dimethylsulfoniopropionate (DMSP) to yield the climate active gas dimethyl sulfide (DMS) and other compounds. The lack of rapid and accurate methods to quantify the DMSP metabolic potential hinders a deeper understanding of this cycling. We developed a high-throughput qPCR (HT-qPCR) chip, DSMG-chip, to quantify the absolute abundance of DMSP and related organic sulfur metabolic genes. DSMG-chip contains 42 degenerate primer sets...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic stratification of coronary microvascular dysfunction in STEMI patients with or without diabetes mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Post-PCI angio-IMR is an independent predictor of 2-year MACE in STEMI patients, regardless of diabetes status. Patients with both diabetes and post-PCI angio-IMR > 40 had the highest 2-year adverse event rates, underscoring the need for targeted risk assessment and management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cysteine-mediated structural stabilization of the tetrameric GlpF]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The stability of membrane proteins depends on amino acid-specific interactions within the protein structure, its surroundings, e.g. the lipid membrane and ionic solutions, and their substrates. A molecular understanding of the factors affecting protein stability is essential for comprehending the respective structure-function relationships. This study aims to investigate the influence of native cysteine residues, ions, and glycerol on the stability of GlpF, the aqua(glycerol)porin of E. coli,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing CIK cell immunotherapy: highlights from the second international conference on DC-CIK and CAR-CIK approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[On April 7, 2025, the 2nd International CIK Cell Conference was held in Monza, Italy, marking the establishment of the International Society for CIK Cells (ISCC). The conference, kindly supported by Fondazione Tettamanti (Italy), featured cutting-edge advancements in cytokine-induced killer (CIK) cell immunotherapy, used alone and in combination with dendritic cells (DC-CIK) and chimeric antigen receptors (CAR-CIK). The event also provided a valuable opportunity for young investigators to engage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of the clinical characteristics and prognostic factors of multicenter childhood Burkitt leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Burkitt lymphoma (BL) is a B-cell malignancy with a rapid doubling time, originating in follicular germinal centers. We aimed to explore the characteristics and prognosis of childhood Burkitt leukemia. A total of 124 children with Burkitt leukemia enrolled during the 6-year period of China Net Childhood Lymphoma- mature B-cell lymphoma 2017 regimen (CNCL-B-NHL-2017) were assessed. The median age at onset was 7 years (1-15 years), with a male-to-female ratio of 4.17:1. Of the total, 50.8%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment outcomes of zanubrutinib-based regimen in newly diagnosed patients with MYC/BCL2 double-expressor diffuse large B-cell lymphoma: a retrospective multicenter real-world study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diffuse large B-cell lymphoma (DLBCL) patients with co-expression of MYC (≥ 40%) and BCL2 (≥ 50%), classified as double-expressor DLBCL (DE-DLBCL), consistently exhibit poor prognosis with traditional first-line therapies. In order to address the unmet therapeutic needs in this high-risk population, this real-world study retrospectively reviewd 46 newly diagnosed DE-DLBCL patients from two centers to evaluate the efficacy and safety of zanubrutinib-based regimens. Key outcomes included complete...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Marked sex differences are observed in heroin acquisition and affective states in rats but converge to similar levels of footshock stress-induced reinstatement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings indicate sex-specific vulnerabilities to development of heroin use disorders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum L-ornithine-derived polyamines as indicators of Parkinson disease progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prior studies reported that biospecimen concentrations of L-ornithine-derived polyamines (ODPAs) and their metabolites differentiated Parkinson disease (PD) from healthy controls. We investigated ODPA metabolism in CSF and serum specimens from well-characterized, unmedicated PD patients to explore correlations with disease severity, progression, and PD clinical subtypes using data from Unified PD Rating Scale (UPDRS) assessments. We developed targeted assays for L-ornithine and the ODPAs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating UHPLC-MS, Network Pharmacology, and Molecular Docking techniques to explore the neuroprotective effect of Mirificin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ischemic stroke (IS) is a complex cerebrovascular disease with a high global incidence, recurrence rate, and disability. Despite the limited availability of clinical therapies for IS, further research is essential to develop traditional Chinese medicine (TCM)-based neuroprotective treatments. This study aims to investigate the neuroprotective properties of mirificin against neuronal damage and uncover the pharmacological mechanisms involved. Mirificin levels in rat cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A corus line: nanophase diagrams of miscible bimetallic nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To this day, the variety in chemical ordering within gas-phase deposited nanoparticle (NP) samples is not fully understood. On the one hand, energetic arguments point toward specific, uniquely defined configurations. On the other hand, kinetically controlled phenomena (NP coalescence, adatom decoration, ripening) account for emergent energetically unfavourable orderings but cannot capture all cases. Here, we present a simple, fundamental nanothermodynamics argument that can potentially explain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update in Cardiovascular Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The goal in selecting these recent articles was to help identify literature that may change the clinical practice of women's health for practitioners in the primary care setting. Articles were identified by reviewing the high-impact medical and women's health journals, national guidelines, ACP JournalWise, and NEJM Journal Watch. In this Clinical Update, we selected recent publications relevant to the cardiovascular health of women.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soft Tubular-Surface Rolling Robots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soft creatures like Drosophila larvae can quickly ascend tubular surfaces via rolling, a capability not yet replicated by soft robots. Here, we present a single-piece soft robot capable of rolling along tubular structures by sequentially actuating its built-in axial muscles. We reveal that the sequential actuation generates distributed spinning torques along the robot's curved axis, enabling continuous non-coaxial rolling-distinct from current gravity-dependent rolling solutions. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Couple's orgasm as a dyadic experience: a scoping review of dyadic data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Future research might focus on orgasm as a dyadic experience, include individuals with diverse gender identities and sexual orientations, and adopt daily-diary designs to capture the unique orgasm experiences as they unfold in couples' daily lives.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Middle-Down Nuclear Magnetic Resonance for Therapeutic Monoclonal Antibody Glycan Profiling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recombinant monoclonal antibodies (mAbs) are widely used across therapeutic areas, and their glycosylation plays a critical role in product quality, manufacturing consistency, and biosimilarity assessment. A middle-down nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) method has been developed to profile mAb glycan distribution while preserving the covalent bond between glycan and mAb domains, e.g., the fragment crystallizable (Fc) domain. The workflow uses the immunoglobulin-degrading enzyme from Streptococcus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal Biomarkers of Consciousness in Acute Severe Traumatic Brain Injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Predicting outcome for patients with acute severe traumatic brain injury (TBI) is imprecise, relying on neurological examination, structural neuroimaging, and resting-state electroencephalography (EEG) to serve as proxies for brain function. We implemented a multimodal assessment protocol to determine whether detection of consciousness using advanced tools, including standardized behavioral evaluation, advanced EEG, and functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI), is associated with functional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Past Genomes Guide Future Conservation: Insights from Extinct Populations of the Endangered Pacific Pocket Mouse]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efforts to recover endangered species often rely on restoring populations to their historical range, yet reestablishing lost genetic variation is challenging when the ancestral genetic landscape is poorly understood. The Pacific pocket mouse (Perognathus longimembris pacificus), a federally endangered heteromyid rodent, has been extirpated from most of its range in coastal southern California. Recovery efforts call for establishing new populations in their historic range through translocation,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protoplast technology in woody plants: Current advances and potential applications in genetic improvement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Woody plants have garnered significant attention in recent years for their essential ecological and economic contributions. Protoplasts, isolated from plant cells, exhibited remarkable totipotency and offered immense potential in a broad array of biological and biotechnological fields. These included, but were not limited to, protein gene expression regulation, functional gene analysis, subcellular localization, interaction studies, gene editing, and single-cell sequencing. This review offered a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epigenetic landscape underlying plant-microbiome chemical communication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chemical communication, a universal mode among the interactive members within dynamic plant-microbiome systems, fundamentally drives coevolutionary trajectories. Emerging evidence suggests the critical role of epigenetic regulation in chemical communication, though its mechanistic insights are yet not well understood, a gap that has limited the precise mining of microbiomes function in modern agriculture. Here, we synthesize recent findings from chemistry to epigenetics to illuminate the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251103142049&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>