<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 19:21:49 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CoBRA: compound binding site prediction using RNA language model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA performs a variety of functions within cells and is implicated in various human diseases. Because druggable proteins occupy a small portion of the genome, considerable interest has been increasing in developing drugs targeting RNAs. Thus, precise prediction of small-molecule binding sites across different classes of RNAs is important. In this study, a lightweight deep learning program for predicting RNA-drug binding sites, called compound binding site prediction for RNA (CoBRA), is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that APOE genotype significantly modulates the relationship between plasma p-tau217 and amyloid burden in Alzheimer's disease. Plasma p-tau217 showed stronger correlations with amyloid burden in individuals with APOE E2 and E3 genotypes compared to those with the E4 genotype, highlighting its potential as a sensitive biomarker for amyloid pathology in non-E4 carriers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into clinical large language models and their barriers to translational readiness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Clinical LLM research remains exploratory, marked by limited generalizability across languages, data types, and clinical environments. To bridge this gap, future studies must prioritize multilingual and multimodal training, prospective study designs with rigorous external validation, and hybrid evaluation frameworks combining quantitative performance with qualitative clinical usability metrics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Large-Scale Genome-wide Association Study of Blood Pressure Accounting for Gene-Depressive Symptomatology Interactions in 564,680 Individuals from Diverse Populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gene-environment interactions may enhance our understanding of blood pressure (BP) biology. We conducted a meta-analysis of multi-population genome-wide association studies of BP traits accounting for gene-depressive symptomatology (DEPR) interactions. Our study included 564,680 adults from 67 cohorts and 4 population backgrounds (African (5%), Asian (7%), European (85%), and Hispanic (3%)). We discovered seven previously unreported BP loci showing gene-DEPR interaction. These loci mapped to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When Clocks Go Rogue: Circadian Rhythms and the Rise of Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review summarizes recent insights into the roles of the circadian clock in regulating cancer hallmarks, with a focus on its impact on the tumor microenvironment, and highlights the translational promise of circadian-informed strategies for cancer therapy. The circadian clock is a 24-hour biological timekeeping system that aligns physiological processes with cyclic environmental cues, such as light-dark cycles. Disruptions of circadian rhythms caused by lifestyle factors, including shift...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gas-Producing Bacteria Causing Package Swelling in Hubei Broad Bean Paste: Isolation, Identification, and Control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The problem of swollen canned Hubei broad bean paste, a traditional fermented food, leads to significant quality degradation and economic loss. This study aimed to isolate and identify the causative gas-producing bacterium and develop an effective control strategy. A dominant strain, designated Clostridium tyrobutyricum strain LG12 (accession number MT265221.1), was isolated from swollen cans and identified via 16S rDNA sequencing. Physiological studies revealed that this isolate grew optimally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Lacticaseibacillus Rhamnosu AFY02 on AOM/DSS-Induced Inflammation-Associated Colon Cancer in Mice and the Mechanism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of this study was to explore the effects of Lacticaseibacillus rhamnosu AFY02 (LR-AFY02), which was obtained from traditional fermented yogurt, on mice with inflammation-related AOM/DSS-induced colon cancer and the associated processes. The pathological results of the colon tissue of mice, the indicators of serum and tissue, and their expressions in the tissue were detected. The results showed that the use of LR-AFY02 significantly improved intestinal histopathological injury, decreased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MACFIV: a novel framework for nonlinear causal inference in the body mass index-hypertension relationship with many weak and pleiotropic genetic instruments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Causal inference is an essential approach for understanding biological processes. Traditional causal inference methods assume a linear relationship between different biological traits, whereas their true causal relationship may be nonlinear, such as U-shaped. Moreover, when the instrument set includes weak and pleiotropic genetic instruments, accurately capturing the shape of these relationships becomes challenging. To address these issues, we propose model-averaged control function-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling Supports Combinatorial Effects Between Pharmacological and Non-Pharmacological Interventions to Prevent Opioid-Induced Cardiac Arrest]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Few studies have quantified the effects of non-pharmacological interventions (e.g., rescue breathing) in the setting of community opioid overdose. We extended a previously validated model for opioid antagonists by incorporating the mechanism of rescue breathing, and quantified combinatorial effects between rescue breathing and various formulations of naloxone under different fentanyl overdose scenarios in a virtual patient population suffering from opioid-induced respiratory failure. We defined...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IL-18 metabolically reprograms CAR-expressing natural killer T cells and enhances their antitumor activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Invariant natural killer T cells (NKTs) have intrinsic anti-tumor properties that make them promising candidates for chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) immunotherapies. Transgenic cytokine expression can enhance cellular therapy potency, and we hypothesized that co-expressing IL-18 alone or with IL-15 would boost CAR-NKT therapeutic potential. To test this, we generated retroviral constructs expressing IL-15 and/or IL-18 with an inducible caspase 9 safety switch and co-transduced them with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Trial Results Provide the Rationale to Protect Dual HIV-specific T Cells with a Signaling-Defective HIV Fusion Inhibitor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coupling the HIV fusion inhibitor C34 with CXCR4 (C34-CXCR4) protected CD4 T cells from all strains of HIV. Escape from C34-CXCR4 expression proved difficult, requiring more than 21 serial passages, mutations at conserved gp41 sites, and a complete loss of Vpu activity. A dose-escalation, Phase I clinical trial was performed in which up to 10 billion C34-CXCR4 expressing T cells were infused into people with HIV (PWH). While these infusions were safe, we observed limited persistence of these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene therapy for Bietti crystalline corneoretinal dystrophy: a phase 1/2 clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bietti crystalline corneoretinal dystrophy (BCD) is an inherited retinal degeneration caused by biallelic variants in the CYP4V2 gene. Here, we report a phase 1/2, dose-escalation clinical study to assess the safety and efficacy of ZVS101e, an adeno-associated viral (AAV) mediated gene augmentation therapy (rAAV2/8-hCYP4V2), in 11 BCD patients with up to 365 days of follow-up (NCT05832684). ZVS101e showed a favorable safety profile, with no dose-limiting toxicities or drug-related serious...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Quadruple Immunotherapy for Colorectal Cancer (QuICC) Trial for Mismatch Repair-Proficient Metastatic Colorectal Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Quadruplet therapy produced one objective response in unselected mCRC patients (n = 20). There were no responses with triplet therapy (n = 12). The role of ICB-based combination immunotherapy in pMMR CRC remains unclear. NCT04491955.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An attention enhanced CNN ensemble for interpretable and accurate cotton leaf disease classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precise and timely identification of cotton leaf diseases is essential for sustaining crop yield and quality, yet manual inspection remains time-consuming, labor-intensive, and prone to error. Existing automated approaches are limited by insufficient dataset diversity, inconsistent evaluation practices, limited use of explainable AI (XAI), and high computational cost. To address these challenges, we propose an attention-enhanced CNN ensemble, namely CottonLeafNet, which integrates lightweight...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serological and molecular evidence of canine enteric coronavirus in southern Italy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canine enteric coronavirus (CECoV) is one of the most common viruses in dogs, causing gastrointestinal disorders and, in severe cases, death. Despite being a main pathogen, research on its distribution is limited, particularly in some geographical locations, such as Campania region (southern Italy). This study investigated the serological and molecular prevalence of this virus, as well as the risk factors associated with higher exposures. A total of 258 blood and 154 fecal samples from 71...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wearable textile-based phototherapy platform with customized NIR OLEDs toward non-invasive hair loss treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hair loss presents a widespread clinical and psychological challenge, yet conventional pharmacological treatments often incur systemic side effects such as hormonal imbalance and mood disturbances. To provide a non-pharmacological alternative, a wearable textile-integrated near-infrared (NIR) organic light-emitting diode (OLED) platform was developed with emission closely aligned with the action spectrum of human dermal papilla cells (hDPCs). By employing a top-emitting microcavity structure, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biological mediation of microplastic aggregation and sedimentation by a harmful dinoflagellate Prorocentrum minimum in a simulated marine environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coastal estuaries are hotspots of microplastics (MPs) and harmful algal blooms (HABs), yet the role of dinoflagellates in MP sinking remains unclear. We examined aggregate formation between Prorocentrum minimum and polyethylene (PE; 1.0 and 1.4 g cm^(-3), 10-20 μm) and polypropylene (PP; 0.91 g cm^(-3), 45-75 μm) using roller-shaker incubations. Growth, aggregate morphology, sinking velocity, and stability were evaluated microscopically and statistically. P. minimum growth was not inhibited by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A 3D Astrocyte Microenvironment Model Enables Rapid Ca<sup>2</sup> <sup>+</sup>-Resolved Analysis and Therapeutic Modulation of Oxidative Neuroinflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astrocytes orchestrate key neuroinflammatory processes, yet conventional two dimentional (2D) cultures distort Ca^(2+)signaling and elevate inflammatory noise. Here, we introduce the Astrocytic Reactive-Calcium 3D microenvironment (ARC-3D), a tunable methacrylated gelatin (GelMA)-based 3D astrocyte microenvironment that enables stable long-term culture, improved transcriptional fidelity, and rapid Ca^(2+)-resolved functional assessment under perfusion. The optimized 3.5 wt% matrix supported...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Re: Comments on "Potentially Inappropriate Medication Use in Patients With Parkinson's Disease: Analysis of Korean National Health Insurance Claims Data"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of Frailty in Community-Dwelling Older Adults Using Smartphone-Based Digital Lifelogging: A Multi-Center, Prospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Frailty in older adults is a multidimensional syndrome characterized by reduced physiological resilience and heightened vulnerability to adverse outcomes, yet conventional assessments remain largely clinic-based. This study evaluated the feasibility and explanatory utility of smartphone-based digital lifelogs for assessing frailty in community-dwelling older adults. In a prospective observational study, 300 participants (mean age 73.30, SD 5.37 years) from three sites in Seoul, South Korea, used...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Expression of UBE2Z, a Target Protein of miR-500a, Is Associated with Poor Prognosis in Triple-Negative Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC) exhibits diverse histological and molecular characteristics. TNBC patients also have the poorest prognoses among those with various breast cancer subtypes, and no effective treatment strategy has been established for TNBC beyond non-specific chemotherapy. Recent studies have reported that the dysregulation of miRNAs is associated with tumor behavior, prognosis, and treatment responses in TNBC patients. Therefore, this study was conducted to identify miRNAs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting Adipocyte Enhancer-Binding Protein 1 to Induce Microglial Phenotype Shift for Immunotherapy in Alzheimer's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroinflammation, a key contributor to neurodegenerative diseases, results from excessive microglial activation. Microglia that respond to pathogenic molecules switch to the M1 type and secrete various immune cytokines, which can cause neuronal damage. Therefore, our study focused on molecules that can enhance the neuroprotective role of microglia and reduce neuronal damage. The adipocyte enhancer-binding protein 1 (AEBP1) gene is known for its role in regulating immune responses in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilizing Carbonated Reclaimed Water as Concrete Mixing Water: Improved CO<sub>2</sub> Uptake and Compressive Strength]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41515742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the carbonation degree of reclaimed water (RW) and its potential use as mixing water for cementitious materials under controlled laboratory conditions using a simplified CO(2) injection method. To reproduce the chemical environment of actual RW, a synthetic reclaimed water (SRW) system with a cement-to-sand ratio of 8:2 was prepared and used throughout the evaluation. Thermogravimetric analysis revealed that the cementitious solids suspended in SRW exhibit high reactivity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41515742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hole-Patterned Pellicles: A Structural Approach for Improved Extreme Ultraviolet Transmittance and Mechanical Behavior]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41515722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To sustain high-throughput extreme ultraviolet (EUV) lithography, pellicles with high transmittance are essential. As conventional methods-such as material optimization and membrane thinning-have reached their practical limits, alternative strategies are now required. In this study, we investigate an alternative hole-patterned pellicle architecture that introduces a geometric degree of freedom beyond that of continuous-film architectures. EUV transmittance measurements show that transmittance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41515722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic Identification and Biochemical Characterization of Methyl Jasmonate (MJ)-Inducible Terpene Synthase Genes in Lettuce (<em>Lactuca sativa</em> L. cv. Salinas)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41515001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Terpenes are diverse plant metabolites with essential ecological and physiological functions, yet their biosynthetic regulation in lettuce (Lactuca sativa L.) remains poorly understood. By integrating volatile profiling, genome-wide identification, and biochemical characterization of terpene synthase (TPS) genes, we elucidated how methyl jasmonate (MJ) induces terpene formation in lettuce seedlings. Headspace analysis of 10-day-old seedlings revealed that while mock-treated tissues emitted no...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41515001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Device-driven cyclic compression of the superior vena cava as a preload reduction strategy to improve cardiac function in heart failure: a pilot feasibility study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We evaluated the physiological efficacy and safety of a novel device-based preload reduction strategy that applies external cyclic compression to the superior vena cava (SVC) in a preclinical heart failure model. Heart failure was induced in eleven pigs using ischemia-reperfusion injury, and a 3D-printed SVC compression device was tested under varying compression ratios (70%, 85%, and 100%) and protocols. Hemodynamic responses were monitored using right-heart catheterization and pressure-volume...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41520006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal weight gain to reduce obesity risk in preterm infants in a National cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental investigation on mechanical properties of iron metal matrix reinforced with MAX phase V<sub>2</sub>AlC-GO]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of high-quality composites has become increasingly crucial due to rapid modernization and technological advancements, particularly as traditional iron-based materials face significant limitations such as high density, low strength-to-weight ratios, and susceptibility to corrosion and wear. This research focuses on fabricating a metal matrix composite (MMC) from a pure iron matrix reinforced with vanadium aluminum carbide (V₂AlC) and graphene oxide (GO) using the powder metallurgy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LncRNA Wee1-AS coordinates oxidative fatty acid metabolism through the activation of mitochondrial CDK1/CYCLIN B1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) is steadily increasing with life-threatening complications, underscoring the need for new therapeutic targets. In this study, we identified a novel long noncoding RNA, Wee1-AS, which is transcribed from the antisense strand of the Wee1 gene locus. The expression of Wee1-AS was greater in hepatocytes, particularly in the region around the central vein, and it was induced in response to high-fat diet challenge. Adeno-associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elasto-magnetic instabilities for amplified actuation and mechanical memory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Instabilities can generate fast and amplified motion in mechanical systems. Here, we present an elasto-magnetic instability that combines magnetic attraction and elastic tension to create bistable dynamics. To demonstrate this, we built a coupled elasto-magnetic vibration system that produces amplified motion and greater displacement and force than a control system across a wide frequency range. We also establish design principles that can be applied to different configurations by studying the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptional stratification of necrotizing enterocolitis identifies distinct disease subtypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Necrotizing enterocolitis (NEC) is a severe inflammatory disorder of the intestine that affects neonatal babies, with a mortality rate of 30-50%. Despite the severe nature of the disease, its rare incidence and early onset prevent further understanding of its etiology and the development of treatment strategies. To further understand the pathogenic mechanism of this disease, we subjected intestinal tissues from ten NEC patients and three control individuals to RNA-sequencing. Clustering of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetically predicted susceptibility to dust-induced lung diseases and risk of autoimmune diseases: a two sample Mendelian randomization study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of overweight and obesity on gastric and colorectal cancer incidence in the older adults: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In situ engineering of synthetic yeast consortia for cross-species metabolic conversion of crude glycerol and byproducts into circular renewable bioenergy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of biodiesel production generates large amounts of crude glycerol, a low-value byproduct with environmental and economic challenges. Here, we present an engineered yeast coculture system combining Saccharomyces cerevisiae and Yarrowia lipolytica to convert crude glycerol into isopropanol, a liquid organic hydrogen carrier. The system integrates metabolic engineering, cell surface display pairing, immobilization, and continuous cultivation in fibrous bed bioreactors. In S....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Response to the Letter to the Editor: "Lazertinib Versus Osimertinib in EGFR-Mutant NSCLC: Efficacy, Toxicity, and Unaddressed Clinical Gaps"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intravitreal aflibercept 8 mg versus 2 mg in Asian patients with neovascular age-related macular degeneration: 48-week analysis of the Phase 3 PULSAR trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Aflibercept 8mg was effective and well tolerated in Asian patients with nAMD, with demonstrated improvements in functional and anatomic outcomes comparable to aflibercept 2mg at W48. Aflibercept 8mg outcomes were achieved with fewer injections than with aflibercept 2mg, consistent with overall PULSAR results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tankyrase-1-mediated PARsylation directs TFEB partner switching to regulate selective Wnt target gene expression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wnt/β-catenin signaling coordinates developmental and oncogenic programs by modulating transcriptional networks. In addition to β-catenin, we previously identified TFEB-a master regulator of lysosomal biogenesis and autophagy-as a Wnt-inducible co-regulator for a subset of Wnt target genes. However, the molecular mechanism underlying this selective transcriptional engagement remained unknown. Here, we show that Wnt3a stimulation promotes TFEB's interaction with TCF-1/LEF-1 without altering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nontuberculous Mycobacterial Pulmonary Disease Risk in Tuberculosis Survivors: A Nationwide Korean Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Individuals with prior pulmonary TB have a markedly elevated risk of NTM-PD. Targeted surveillance and early diagnostic strategies for NTM-PD in TB survivors may improve outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advance Care Planning in Adults with Congenital Heart Diseases: current practices, preferences and needs of 8,281 adults from 32 countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: When looking at global ACP practices, needs and preferences, much room for improvement of ACP provision could be noticed. Also, a notable variation in ACP was observed worldwide.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seasonally Adaptive Data-Driven Ozone Prediction in Megacity Environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ground level ozone (O(3)) concentrations have shown a persistent upward trend in urban megacities over the past decade, despite substantial reductions in primary pollutant emissions through regulatory and technological interventions. Unlike primary pollutants, O(3) is produced via nonlinear photochemical reactions that are highly sensitive to meteorological and environmental conditions, posing challenges for control through traditional precursor-based strategies. Here, we present a comprehensive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Fine-Tuning: Leveraging Domain-Aware In-Context learning with large language models for clinical named entity recognition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: With optimized domain-aware demonstration selection, open-source LLM-based ICL can match or surpass encoder fine-tuning for clinical NER. Its ease of adaptation and ability to update knowledge via demonstration pools-without retraining-enable continuous improvement in dynamic, resource-limited healthcare settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Levels and associations of borderline personality features and early maladaptive schemas in bipolar disorder: A comparative network analysis of patients with and without severe borderline personality features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Clinicians treating patients with bipolar disorder should note that patients with severe BPFs tend to have high EMS levels and mind the similarities and differences in the relationships among EMSs and BPFs across BPF levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex differences in the association between chronotype and anxiety: A nationwide population study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Differences in the chronotype-anxiety association were observed between men and women. Specifically, having a morning chronotype may reduce the risk of anxiety in men, whereas this protective effect was not observed in women. These findings suggest the need for sex-specific chronotype-targeted approaches for the prevention and management of anxiety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Benefit of residential greenness on visual acuity among 3-year-old children through reduction of exposure to ambient air pollutants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A growing body of evidence highlights the health benefits of green space, but underlying mechanisms remain unclear. We hypothesized that the benefits of greenness on children's visual acuity may be mediated through reduced air pollution exposure. This study examined the mediating role of air pollutants in the association between greenness and visual acuity in 3-year-old children. We used data from the Korean Children's Environmental Health Study. Of 5458 cohort participants, 794 children were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nocturnal enteral feeding and mechanical ventilation risk in intensive care unit patients: A deep Learning-Based causal inference study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among non-intubated ICU patients, night-time enteral feeding may increase the risk of mechanical ventilation, particularly at very large feeding volumes. These findings suggest reconsidering overnight continuous feeding practices and support prospective trials of circadian-aligned nutrition to reduce respiratory complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecularly imprinted polymer-based field-effect transistor for real-time, highly selective, and sensitive aflatoxin B1 monitoring in food]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In food, the simple and on-site quantitative detection of aflatoxin B1 (AFB1), a known human carcinogen, remains a significant challenge. Shelf-stable detection methods compatible with portable electronics are scarce. This study proposes a cost-effective and promising field-effect transistor (FET) sensor technology as a potential solution. In tandem with a molecularly imprinted polymer (MIP) biomimetic antibody, we fabricated an FET-type sensor that uses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The emergence and validation of these new tau PET tracers have opened new opportunities for the development of more accurate diagnostic and management tools for AD. In our study on post-mortem sections, [^(18)F]MK-6240 and [^(18)F]Flortaucipir showed similar binding profiles with preference to middling tangle maturity levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Internal Capsule Involvement Explains the Prognostic Impact of ASPECTS after Endovascular Thrombectomy for Large-Core Infarction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The prognostic implications of Alberta Stroke Program Early CT Score (ASPECTS) subscores in patients with large-core ischemic stroke undergoing endovascular thrombectomy (EVT) remain uncertain. We hypothesized that specific ASPECTS regions substantially influence functional outcomes after EVT and therefore sought to identify which individual subscores are associated with outcome and whether any of them account for the association between total ASPECTS and functional outcomes. We retrospectively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microvascular Resistance Reserve vs Coronary Flow Reserve to Assess Age-Related Trends in Coronary Microvascular Dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Structural CMD increases with age regardless of obstructive CAD, while functional CMD prevalence increases only in nonobstructive CAD. CFR may overestimate CMD in epicardial disease, whereas MRR provides a more consistent assessment regardless of obstructive CAD, underscoring the need for prospective studies on their clinical relevance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Prognostic Impact of Changes in Coronary Angiography-Derived Index of Microcirculatory Resistance Following PCI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: An elevated Δangio-IMR correlates with a heightened risk of TVF in vessels with intermediate coronary stenosis underwent PCI. ΔAngio-IMR could be used as a valuable risk stratification indicator, particularly in patients with high post-PCI angio-IMR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of shift work on cortisol levels among nurses: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shift work is essential in nursing to ensure continuous patient care; however, it is associated with adverse health outcomes. Cortisol, a key stress hormone regulated by the circadian rhythm, is often disrupted by shift work. This systematic review aimed to examine the association between types of shift work and cortisol levels in nurses. The systematic review was conducted following Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses guidelines, and the study protocol was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of neoadjuvant chemotherapy on surgical outcomes in patients with HPV-positive oropharyngeal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: NAC + S achieved comparable survival outcomes to upfront surgery and allowed omission of adjuvant therapy in selected patients, supporting its role in treatment de-intensification for HPV+ OPSCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microfluidic-Based Analysis of Trichomonas Vaginalis Attachment and Drug Response Using AI-Based Imaging Algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[T. vaginalis is a protozoan parasite responsible for the most common non-viral sexually transmitted infection worldwide. Effective therapeutic evaluation is essential, particularly with rising concerns over drug resistance. In this study, we developed a microfluidic culture platform integrated with an AI-based imaging algorithm to quantify parasite attachment dynamics and assess drug efficacy. The platform enabled controlled exposure of T. vaginalis to human cancer cell lines (HeLa and BFTC905)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Control to Conversion: Optimizing Systemic Therapy for Curative-Intent Conversion Surgery in Metastatic Gastric Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conversion therapy enables curative-intent resection in patients with initially unresectable or metastatic cancers after effective systemic therapy. Recently, advances in systemic therapy with molecular targeted agents and immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) have renewed clinical and research interest in this approach, particularly for metastatic gastric cancer (GC). This review aimed to summarize the international guidelines and expert consensus informed by contemporary evidence on conversion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neoadjuvant Chemotherapy for Gastric Cancer: Evolving Approaches and Supporting Evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neoadjuvant and perioperative therapy have emerged as promising strategies for managing locally advanced gastric cancer (LAGC). Landmark phase III studies, such as PRODIGY and RESOLVE, have established neoadjuvant chemotherapy as a viable therapeutic option in Asia. More recently, the MATTERHORN trial demonstrated the potential of incorporating immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) into perioperative treatment. However, the use of fluorouracil, leucovorin, oxaliplatin, and docetaxel in Asian...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Imaging in Gastric Cancer: [¹⁸F]FDG and Fibroblast Activation Protein-Targeted PET/CT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric cancer remains a major global health burden, and accurate staging and response assessment are essential for optimal management. 2-[¹⁸F]-Fluoro-2-deoxy-D-glucose ([¹⁸F]FDG) positron emission tomography (PET)/computed tomography (CT) is widely used in oncology. However, it exhibits variable sensitivity in gastric cancer, particularly in poorly cohesive, mucinous, and signet ring cell carcinomas with low glucose metabolism. These limitations have prompted interest in fibroblast activation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiology of Gastric Cancer in Korea (1999-2022): Incidence, Survival, and 5-Year Conditional Relative Survival]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The incidence and mortality rates of gastric cancer in Korea have declined over the past two decades, accompanied by improved survival outcomes. The CRS analysis suggests that long-term follow-up is warranted, with the optimal duration varying according to patient characteristics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Journal of Gastric Cancer</em>'s Ascent and the Enduring Contributions of Dr. Keun Won Ryu]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural Distribution-Guided Botulinum Toxin Injection for Platysma muscle: A Split-Neck Comparison With Conventional Technique]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Motor innervation-guided BoNT-A injections may achieve equivalent clinical outcomes while reducing injection burden, toxin dose, and complication risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We propose novel differential scores based on AD signature features, incorporating high-order attention mechanism learned from amyloid/tau pathology predicting model and inter-feature relationships. The proposed high-order attention mechanism enabled extraction of precise features with higher predictive power for AD pathologies, while capturing feature importances reflecting their mutual relationships.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comments on: "Potentially Inappropriate Medication Use in Patients With Parkinson's Disease: Analysis of Korean National Health Insurance Claims Data"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Re: Comments on "Efficacy and Safety of Pregabalin for Restless Legs Syndrome in Korean Adults: A Randomized, Double-Blind, Placebo-Controlled Trial"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Korean Case of <em>C9orf72</em>-Related Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis With Progressive Supranuclear Palsy-Like Features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HLA-A*2402 May Be Associated With Antiseizure Medication-Induced Severe Mucocutaneous Adverse Events in Korean Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global Incidence and Prevalence of Trigeminal Neuralgia, 1945-2024: A Systematic Review and Meta-Regression Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights substantial global variations in TN incidence and prevalence, with how the evolving diagnostic criteria affects the epidemiological features of TN.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Otolith Deterioration: Factors Affecting Microvascular and Structural Integrity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings of this study suggest that various systemic factors beyond age and sex are related to otolith function via effects on the microvasculature and structural constituents. These findings provide new insights into potential mechanisms of otolith degeneration and highlight the impact of systemic factors on otolith function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Oral Microbiome in Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis Shows Differentially Abundant Organisms in Limb Versus Bulbar Onset Disease: A Binational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite the cohort and household effects, our study identified differentially abundant organisms that may be important to the phenotypic variability of ALS and should be considered for future study. Our study provides novel insights into design for future multi-site microbiome research in ALS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Verification of Efficacy of Cognitive Function Test Using the Cognitive Impairment Screening Test]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study supports the validity and utility of the CIST as a screening tool for cognitive impairment. The CIST outperformed the PST in predictive accuracy. However, direct score conversion between the two tests should be approached with caution.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concurrent Use of Contact Aspiration and a Stent Retriever Is Associated With Successful Recanalization in Patients With Cancer-Associated Stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The combined technique was associated with successful recanalization in patients with cancer-associated stroke and emergent large vessel occlusion.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Ablation to Neuromodulation Platform: The Evolving Role of Magnetic Resonance-Guided Focused Ultrasound in Functional Neurosurgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance-guided focused ultrasound (MRgFUS) has rapidly evolved from an experimental concept into a versatile platform in functional neurosurgery. Initially pioneered as a noninvasive thermal ablation modality for essential tremor, MRgFUS has since gained regulatory approval and demonstrated durable long-term efficacy. Its clinical applications have expanded to include Parkinson's disease, chronic pain, psychiatric disorders, and investigational use in dystonia, epilepsy, and brain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eight Decades of Data Reveal a Far Greater Global Burden of Trigeminal Neuralgia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuropathy of the infraorbital area following rapid palatal expansion: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RATIONALE: Neuropathic pain in the orofacial region, although relatively uncommon, can occur after dental procedures performed in trigeminally innervated areas. Miniscrew-assisted rapid palatal expansion (MARPE) is widely adopted to correct maxillary transverse deficiency in adults and is generally safe; however, neurosensory complications are rarely documented. This case highlights infraorbital neuropathy following MARPE, underscoring the need for clinical vigilance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Initial compliance as a predictor of therapeutic outcomes in chronic tinnitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tinnitus treatments incorporate various strategies, yet substantial challenges remain. Sound therapy (ST) is cost-effective and self-administered, but its efficacy and standardization continue to be debated. This study aimed to evaluate treatment outcomes and associated factors of ST combined with reinforced directive counseling (DC) in patients with chronic tinnitus. From January 2020 to August 2023, 53 patients underwent one year of ST-based self-training, with reinforced DC provided every 6...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current status of family physicians' practices in geriatric medicine and associated factors in the Republic of Korea: A cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The importance of geriatric medicine has grown significantly in recent years. This study aims to assess the current practices of family physicians in geriatric medicine in the Republic of Korea. This cross-sectional study employed online surveys targeting family medicine physicians. The questionnaire focused on the primary treatment areas of the physicians and the percentage of elderly patients in their practices. Descriptive statistical analyses were performed to interpret the data. The average...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving muscle function and quality of life in women with chronic low back pain through combined self-myofascial release and Pilates: A randomized clinical trial (CONSORT)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that incorporating the self-myofascial release with Pilates may enhance the therapeutic benefits for individuals with CLBP. The use of both targeted myofascial release and structured exercise regimens could be considered a viable strategy for the rehabilitation of CLBP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early prophylactic pancreatic stent dislodgement increases the risk of pancreatitis after endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate the association between post-endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography (ERCP) pancreatitis (PEP) and early pancreatic stent dislodgement. A retrospective analysis was conducted on patients who underwent ERCP with prophylactic pancreatic stent placement at 3 academic institutions between January 2010 and December 2022. We evaluated the association between early stent dislodgement (≤24 hours) and PEP as well as the risk factors for early stent dislodgement. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective observational study on the application of an integrative medicine program for the enhanced recovery of patients undergoing spinal surgery: Effects and survey-based analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enhanced recovery after surgery (ERAS) protocols have been widely adopted in various surgical disciplines to accelerate recovery and improve patient outcomes. However, the application of these programs in spinal surgery, particularly with an integrative medicine approach, remains limited. This study aimed to evaluate the effects of a customized integrative medicine-based program on postoperative recovery and to analyze patient-reported preferences for future protocol refinement. This study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term follow-up of vertebral compression fractures in inpatients treated with integrative Korean medicine: An observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conservative management is the recommended first-line treatment for thoracolumbar vertebral compression fractures (VCFs), with integrative Korean medicine (IKM) being widely used for treatment in Korea. However, evidence regarding long-term treatment outcomes is lacking. We aimed to investigate the effectiveness of IKM treatment for thoracolumbar VCFs. Data from inpatients with thoracolumbar VCFs who received IKM treatment, comprising acupuncture, pharmacopuncture, electroacupuncture, Chuna...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of clinical prognostic factors between adult and pediatric patients with Bell's palsy: An eighteen-year single center retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Identifying the clinical prognosis factors of Bell's palsy in adults and children is important to provide an early and accurate treatment for a better outcome. The aim of this study was to compare the clinical prognostic factors of Bell's palsy in adults and children and to identify specific factors that can predict recovery. This retrospective cohort study involved 1433 patients diagnosed with Bell's palsy (1355 adults and 78 children) who attended the outpatient clinic of a university hospital...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Jo et al. Protective Effects of Orexin A in a Murine Model of Cisplatin-Induced Acute Kidney Injury. <em>J. Clin. Med.</em> 2022, <em>11</em>, 7196]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the original publication [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effect of Cognitive Training After Heart Valve Surgery: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Neurocognitive complications are common after cardiac surgery, and postoperative cognitive decline remains a clinically relevant concern in patients undergoing heart valve surgery. This impairment may persist over time and negatively affect quality of life and increase mortality risk. This review aimed to explore the potential benefits of cognitive training in patients after heart valve surgery. Methods: We systematically searched PubMed, Embase, Cochrane Library, and Scopus to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Affecting Postoperative Satisfaction After Presbyopia-Correcting Intraocular Lens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Presbyopia-correcting IOLs have revolutionized cataract surgery by enabling functional vision across multiple focal distances, thereby reducing dependence on spectacles. These lenses-ranging from multifocal to extended depth-of-focus (EDOF) and hybrid designs-incorporate advanced optical technologies to address the limitations of traditional monofocal IOLs. Despite their clinical promise, patient satisfaction remains variable, with a substantial subset experiencing postoperative visual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive Tracheobronchial Morphometry in Korean Adults: Clinical Implications for Double-Lumen Tube Sizing and Right Upper Lobe Alignment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Accurate knowledge of tracheobronchial anatomy is essential for safe airway management, particularly during one-lung ventilation using double-lumen tubes (DLTs). However, population-specific morphometric data in Asian adults remain limited. We aimed to establish a comprehensive morphometric profile of the tracheobronchial tree in Korean adults using 2D and 3D computed tomography (CT), and evaluate the clinical implications for DLT sizing and right upper lobe (RUL)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Trends and Outcomes of Amyloidosis in Korea: A 14-Year Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The diagnostic and therapeutic landscape of amyloidosis has evolved significantly with the introduction of non-invasive imaging and novel agents. However, contemporary real-world data reflecting these recent changes-particularly regarding the burden and prognostic impact of cardiac involvement-remain limited. We aimed to evaluate up-to-date temporal trends in the incidence, prevalence, and outcomes of amyloidosis using a nationwide cohort spanning the recent era. Methods:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concordance Analysis Between Sputum and Bronchoscopic Specimens on Nontuberculous Mycobacteria Pulmonary Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study evaluated the concordance between sputum and bronchoscopic specimens in diagnosing nontuberculous mycobacteria (NTM) pulmonary disease. Methods: We retrospectively analyzed patients with NTM isolated from respiratory specimens between 2010 and 2022. Our analysis assessed species concordance across the two diagnostic methods and compared clinical outcomes between patients with multiple positive cultures and those with a single positive culture. Results: A total...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient and Observer Scar Assessment of Facial Keystone Flap Reconstruction in Korean Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Facial reconstruction using keystone flaps (KFs) provides reliable outcomes; however, few studies have evaluated postoperative scarring using patient-reported outcomes. We assessed scar outcomes after facial KF reconstruction using the Patient and Observer Scar Assessment Scale (POSAS) and explored associations with clinical and sociodemographic factors. Methods: In this retrospective observational cohort study, 43 Korean patients (27 males, 16 females; mean age: 49.95 ±...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined Impact of Mean and Variability of Non-HDL Cholesterol on Myocardial Infarction in Hemodialysis Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: The aim of this study was to stratify cardiovascular risk based on the mean and variability of non-high-density lipoprotein cholesterol (non-HDL-C) in patients undergoing hemodialysis. Methods: Data were analyzed for 453 hemodialysis patients without a history of myocardial infarction (MI) or stroke, who underwent at least five lipid profile measurements at any one of seven university hospitals in the Republic of Korea between March 2009 and December 2020. Visit-to-visit non-HDL-C...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Socially Assistive Robot <em>Hyodol</em> for Depressive Symptoms of Community-Dwelling Older Adults in Medically Underserved Areas: A Preliminary Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Socially assistive robots effectively support elderly care when they incorporate personalization, person-centered principles, rich interactions, and careful role setting with psychosocial alignment. Hyodol, a socially assistive robot designed for elderly people, embodies a grandchild's persona, emulating the grandparent-grandchild relationship. Based on the behavioral activation principles and a human-centered approach, this robot continuously supports users' emotional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes of Surgery Versus Radiotherapy in Bilsky Grade 3 Metastatic Epidural Spinal Cord Compression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Surgery is generally recommended for higher Bilsky grade metastatic epidural spinal cord compression (MESCC); however, Bilsky grades 2-3 are often grouped together, leaving limited evidence for managing patients with Bilsky grade 3 MESCC who have not developed neurological deficits. This study aimed to evaluate whether, and when, surgery should be performed in Bilsky grade 3 MESCC. Methods: This retrospective cohort study included patients diagnosed with Bilsky grade 3...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cetirizine and Dexamethasone in Sepsis: Insights into Maresin-1 Signaling and Cytokine Regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Sepsis remains one of the leading causes of mortality, yet its etiopathogenesis is still not fully understood. This study aimed to investigate the effects of cetirizine and dexamethasone (alone and in combination) on serum levels of Maresin-1 (MaR-1), TNF-α, IFN-γ, IL-1, IL-2, IL-6, IL-8, and IL-10 in a rat model of sepsis induced by the cecal ligation and puncture (CLP) method. Methods: Male Sprague Dawley rats aged 8-10 weeks were used and randomly divided into 7 groups,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Usefulness of Lateral Arm Free Flap in Heel Reconstructions After Malignant Skin Tumor Excision: An Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Heel reconstruction is a complex procedure that requires soft tissue reconstruction resistant to weight, pressure, and shear stress. Various flap reconstruction methods have been reported; among them, free fasciocutaneous flaps have advantages in terms of function and aesthetics, but also have challenges due to the longer operation time required and the possibility of failure. The primary aim of this study was to examine the functional outcomes of heel reconstruction using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hump Nose and Coexisting Deviation in Rhinoplasty: Their Association and Surgical Considerations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Dorsal humps and nasal deviation are common deformities in rhinoplasty. While existing classification systems characterize these deformities individually, their concurrent presentation complicates surgical planning. The aim of this study was to examine the association between dorsal humps and nasal deviation in rhinoplasty patients and assess their influence on surgical decision-making. Methods: This retrospective study analyzed 90 consecutive patients who underwent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Alternative Surgical Technique for Managing Proximal Tibia Chronic Osteomyelitis: Anterior Approach with Establishment of Bone Marrow Communication via Intramedullary Reaming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Surgical treatment of chronic osteomyelitis of the proximal tibia is challenging due to limited soft tissue coverage, poor blood supply, and the weight-bearing function of the bone. Moreover, structural instability following curettage may necessitate fixation with metallic implants, which carries a risk of biofilm formation and often requires multi-stage surgeries. Methods: To address these challenges, we developed a new surgical technique combining an anterior approach...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to Malik et al. How to Define High-Flow Arteriovenous Fistula? Comment on "Kim et al. Hemodynamic Adaptation and Cardiac Effects of High-Flow Arteriovenous Access in Hemodialysis Patients: A Prospective Study. <em>J. Clin. Med.</em> 2025, <em>14</em>, 4556"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The comment raised by Malik et al [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Forward and Reverse Suturing Techniques in Enhancing Neural Regeneration and Motor Function Recovery Following Facial Nerve Axotomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Facial nerve injury from conditions such as Bell's palsy, trauma, surgery, and infection leads to facial asymmetry and motor deficits. Axotomy models reproduce peripheral nerve disruption and consequent motor impairment. To compare the effects of forward versus reverse autologous nerve suturing on neural regeneration and motor recovery within the facial nucleus after axotomy. Methods: In rats subjected to facial nerve axotomy, motor recovery was assessed at 8 weeks using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Clinical Experience with the Novel A-Stream Glaucoma Shunt Combined with Mid-Posterior Tenon's Capsule Advancement Flap]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: The aim of this study was to evaluate the clinical outcomes and surgical techniques of A-stream Glaucoma Shunt (A-stream; MICROT Inc.) implantation. Methods: A retrospective review of 59 eyes from 59 patients who underwent A-stream implantation was conducted. Eyes were divided into two groups: group A (25 eyes), where the distal tip of the ripcord was left exposed and the device was covered with conjunctiva, scleral flap, pericardium patch graft, or mid-posterior Tenon's capsule...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Safety of Cyproheptadine-Based Appetite Stimulants: An Electronic Health Record-Based Retrospective Cohort Study in Adult Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Cyproheptadine-based appetite stimulants (CAS) have been safely used in Korea for over 30 years. However, in older adults who are vulnerable to malnutrition, sarcopenia, and fall-related morbidity, safety of CAS in nutrition care remains uncertain due to limited evidence and its antihistaminic effects. This study aimed to assess the real-world safety of CAS compared with megestrol and other antihistamines to inform safe pharmacologic support within clinical nutrition practice....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current Perspectives on Balloon Pulmonary Angioplasty for Chronic Thromboembolic Pulmonary Hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Balloon pulmonary angioplasty (BPA) has become an established treatment modality for patients with inoperable chronic thromboembolic pulmonary hypertension (CTEPH), particularly in those with distal pulmonary artery lesions or significant comorbidities precluding pulmonary endarterectomy. BPA provides significant improvement in pulmonary hemodynamics, right ventricular function, exercise tolerance, and quality of life. Recent randomized controlled trials, including the RACE and MR-BPA trials,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying Neurobehavioral Biomarkers of Anxiety and Treatment Response Using Virtual Reality, Electroencephalography, Magnetic Resonance Imaging, and Related Multimodal Assessments: A Longitudinal Study Protocol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Anxiety disorders are highly prevalent and impairing psychiatric conditions. Conventional diagnostic approaches based on symptom checklists lack biological specificity and often fail to guide treatment decisions effectively. This study protocol outlines a multidimensional, prospective investigation designed to identify behavioral and neurobiological biomarkers predictive of treatment response in individuals with anxiety-related symptoms, grounded in the Research Domain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enzyme-Assisted Tenderization and Vitamin E-Loaded Liposome Coating for Garlic Scape Quality Enhancement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Older adults and patients with masticatory and deglutition disorders often experience difficulties consuming tough, fibrous vegetables. The enzymatic and liposomal conditions for softening garlic scapes were optimized while simultaneously enhancing their nutritional value through vitamin E fortification. Enzymes (Plantase UF and Plantase PT) were applied at varying concentrations and incubation times to determine optimal tenderization conditions, followed by the application of vitamin E-loaded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Explainable Artificial Intelligence for Rehospitalization and Financial Burden of Fertile Women in Orthopedic Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Fertile women represent a socially and medically significant patient group, yet little research has examined their rehospitalization behavior and financial burden in clinical settings. This study develops predictive and explainable artificial intelligence for rehospitalization and medical costs among reproductive-age orthopedic patients. Methods: Electronic health records of 83 women (aged 15-49) at a major university hospital in Korea were analyzed. Six machine learning models were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medical Service Utilization for Carpal Tunnel Syndrome in Korea (2010-2017): A Retrospective, Cross-Sectional Study Using a Nationally Representative Sample from the HIRA-National Patient Sample Database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Carpal tunnel syndrome (CTS) is a common peripheral neuropathy with increasing prevalence and economic burden. This study aimed to analyze recent trends in CTS treatment patterns, healthcare utilization, and costs within the dualized healthcare system in Korea, using nationwide claim data. Methods: This cross-sectional study used data from the Korean Health Insurance Review and Assessment Service National Patient Sample (HIRA-NPS) between 2010 and 2017. Patients with a primary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gendered Social Construction of Adolescent Health Practices Through Digital Detox and Physical Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Despite growing concerns about the impact of excessive digital media use on adolescents' health, few studies have examined how digital detox practices and physical activity interact to influence it, particularly from a gender perspective. Purpose: This study investigated the effects of digital detox and physical activity on adolescents' health habits, focusing on gender differences and sociocultural implications. Methods: In February 2025, a self-reported survey was conducted among...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of Posttraumatic Stress Disorder Symptoms in Life Adaptation of Toxic Humidifier Disinfectant Survivors: A Multi-Group Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The Republic of Korean humidifier disinfectant disaster, involving toxic chemical exposure, constitutes a major social disaster causing severe trauma. While physical and psychological difficulties are documented, this study investigated the relationship between posttraumatic stress disorder (PTSD) symptoms and survivors' daily life adaptation across children, adolescents, and adults, examining PTSD's mediating role. Methods: The sample included 834 participants (417 exposed survivors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychosocial Predictors of Anxiety and Depression in Community-Dwelling Older Adults During a Prolonged Infectious Disease Crisis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Infectious-disease-related stress is multidimensional, extending beyond fear of infection to include social-participation disruption and relational strain. Findings highlight that different types of social support exert distinct protective effects through function-specific mechanisms, reinforcing the importance of targeted intervention design. Practical implications include strengthening emotional-support infrastructure, implementing hybrid digital-offline outreach models, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of Self-Compassion, Burden of BPSD, Communication Behavior, and Nursing Work Environment on Person-Centered Care for Patients with Dementia Among Long-Term Care Hospital Nurses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: This study aimed to identify the factors influencing person-centered care (PCC) among nurses working at long-term care hospitals for patients with dementia and to propose strategies for strengthening their capacity to provide PCC. Methods: Guided by the ecological model, this descriptive study examined the effects of personal factors (self-compassion and the burden of behavioral and psychological symptoms of dementia [BPSD]), interpersonal factors (communication behavior), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PLA-Based Biodegradable Polymer from Synthesis to the Application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Poly(lactic acid) (PLA) has emerged as a leading bio-based polymer due to its renewability, processability, and biodegradability, yet its broader adoption remains constrained by limitations in thermal stability, mechanical performance, and end-of-life control. This review provides a comparative and application-oriented overview of recent advances in PLA from synthesis and catalyst landscapes to structure-property-biodegradation relationships and practical applications. Representative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Fabrication of a 3D-Printed Nerve Guidance Conduit Using Heterogeneous Composite Materials and Its Effectiveness on Sciatic Nerve Defects of a Rabbit Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peripheral nerve repair remains a major clinical challenge, and novel strategies such as conduit-assisted repair have been developed to improve outcomes. In this study, we fabricated a 3D-printed nerve guidance conduit (NGC) composed of polycaprolactone (PCL), a biocompatible and biodegradable polymer, combined with acellular dermal matrix (ADM) derived from porcine dermis, in order to create a multilayered PCL-ADM NGC with both favorable mechanical properties and biological activity. Twenty...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-Driven Polymeric Coatings: Strategies for Material Selection and Performance Evaluation in Structural Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymeric coatings play a pivotal role in enhancing the durability, functionality, and sustainability of structural materials exposed to harsh environmental conditions. Recent advances in artificial intelligence (AI) have transformed the development, optimization, and evaluation of these coatings by enabling data-driven material discovery, predictive performance modeling, and autonomous inspection. This review aims to provide a comprehensive overview on AI-driven polymeric coating strategies for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Fluorescence-Based COVID-19 Diagnosis Using a Lightweight Deep Learning System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The coronavirus is highly contagious, making rapid early diagnosis essential. Although deep learning-based diagnostic methods using CT or X-ray images have advanced significantly, they still face limitations in cost, processing time, and radiation exposure. In addition, for the possibility of real-time COVID-19 diagnosis, model lightweighting is required. This study proposes a lightweight deep learning model for COVID-19 diagnosis based on fluorescence images and demonstrates its applicability...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-Light Image Segmentation on Edge Computing System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Segmenting low-light images, such as images showing cracks on tunnel walls, is challenging due to limited visibility. Hence, we need to combine image brightness enhancement and a segmentation algorithm. We introduce essential preliminaries, specifically highlighting deep learning-based low-light image enhancement methods and the pixel-level image segmentation algorithm. After that, we provide a three-step low-light image segmentation algorithm. The proposed algorithm begins with brightness and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Evaluation of Bandit-Style Heuristic Policies for Moving Target Detection in a Linear Grid Environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Moving-target detection under strict sensing constraints is a recurring subproblem in surveillance, search-and-rescue, and autonomous robotics. We study a canonical one-dimensional finite grid in which a sensor probes one location per time step with binary observations while the target follows reflecting random-walk dynamics. The objective is to minimize the expected time to detection using transparent, training-free decision rules defined on the belief state of the target location. We compare...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Controllers to Multimodal Input: A Chronological Review of XR Interaction Across Device Generations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study provides a chronological analysis of how Extended Reality (XR) interaction techniques have evolved from early controller-centered interfaces to natural hand- and gaze-based input and, more recently, to multimodal input, with a particular focus on the role of XR devices. We collected 46 user study-based XR interaction papers published between 2016 and 2024, including only studies that explicitly defined their interaction techniques and reported quantitative and/or qualitative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lightweight Deep Learning Model for Classification of Normal and Abnormal Vasculature in Organoid Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human organoids are 3D cell culture models that precisely replicate the microenvironment of real organs. In organoid-based experiments, assessing whether the internal vasculature has formed normally is essential for ensuring the reliability of experimental results. However, conventional vasculature assessment relies on manual inspection by researchers, which is time-consuming and prone to variability caused by subjective judgment. This study proposes a lightweight deep learning model for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Source-Free Domain-Adaptive Semi-Supervised Learning for Object Detection in CCTV Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current object detection methods deployed in closed-circuit television (CCTV) systems experience substantial performance degradation due to domain gaps between training datasets and real-world environments. At the same time, increasing privacy concerns and stricter personal data regulations limit the reuse or distribution of source-domain data, highlighting the need for source-free learning. To address these challenges, we propose a stable and effective source-free semi-supervised domain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Necrotic Cells Alter IRE1α-XBP1 Signaling and Induce Transcriptional Changes in Glioblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Necrosis is a characteristic feature of glioblastoma multiforme (GBM) and is closely associated with tumor-associated inflammation and poor clinical outcomes. However, the molecular consequences of necrotic cell death on endoplasmic reticulum (ER) stress signaling in GBM cells remain unclear. In this study, we examined the effects of necrotic cells on the ER stress signaling and unfolded protein response (UPR) in human glioblastoma cell lines. Exposure to necrotic cells reduced IRE1α...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protective Effects of miR-16-5p and miR-142-3p on Inflammation and Autophagy in Human Corneal Epithelial Cells Under Hyperosmotic Stress In Vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To investigate the regulatory effects of miR-16-5p and miR-142-3p on inflammation and autophagy in human corneal epithelial cells (HCEpiCs) exposed to hyperosmotic stress, a key pathogenic condition in dry eye disease, HCEpiCs were cultured under NaCl-induced hyperosmotic conditions (450 mOsm, 24 h) and transfected with miR-16-5p or miR-142-3p mimics. Expression of inflammatory cytokines (IL-1β, IL-6, TNF-α, IRAK1), autophagy-related genes (ATG5, Beclin-1, ATG16L1, p62), and apoptotic markers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-Driven Digital Pathology: Deep Learning and Multimodal Integration for Precision Oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pathology is fundamental to precision oncology, offering molecular and morphologic insights that enable personalized diagnosis and treatment. Recently, deep learning has demonstrated substantial potential in digital pathology, effectively addressing a wide range of diagnostic, prognostic, and biomarker-prediction tasks. Although early approaches based on convolutional neural networks had limited capacity to generalize across tasks and datasets, transformer-based foundation models have...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41516254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JULGI coordinates vascular development and leaf patterning through non-cell-autonomous regulation of miR165/166]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The interplay between vascular development and leaf development is central to the evolutionary success of vascular plants, yet the underlying mechanisms remain poorly understood. Here, we identify the RNA-binding protein JULGI1 (JUL1) as a key integrator of vascular and leaf development in Arabidopsis. JUL1 is transcribed in leaf veins, while the protein distributes throughout the leaf, where it binds G-rich regions of pri-MIR165a transcripts on the abaxial side. This interaction disrupts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors for Returning to Work for Patients with Physical Disabilities and Brain Damage After Industrial Accidents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Return to work (RTW) after an industrial accident is crucial for an individual's well-being and socioeconomic recovery. This study investigated factors influencing RTW among workers who sustained physical or brain lesion-related disabilities following industrial accidents. Methods: Using five-year panel data (2018-2022) from the Panel Study of Workers' Compensation Insurance of South Korea, we analyzed 340 individuals with physical or brain lesion-related disabilities...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41517005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implant‑position reproducibility of wired and wireless intraoral scanners and the effects of Wi‑Fi distance and upload speed: an in vitro study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of preparation dimensions and material choice on stress distribution in MOD inlays: a 3D finite element study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical features of pulmonary nocardiosis: a descriptive research study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Given that many patients have underlying lung diseases and that mixed infections (particularly with NTM and P. aeruginosa) are frequently observed both at diagnosis and during follow-up, it is crucial to always consider the possibility of pulmonary nocardiosis when symptoms or imaging findings worsen.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiology of herpes zoster and postherpetic neuralgia in Japan: analysis of a large-scale claims database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and virological impacts of human parvovirus B19 epidemics on fulminant myocarditis in childhood]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Access to licenced vaccines for high-threat infectious diseases: a scoping review and interpretive analysis of Ebola virus disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apilactobacillus kunkeei as a promising fermentation candidate for reducing free sugars in fruit juices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that FLAB, especially A. kunkeei, are capable of efficiently reducing free sugars, i.e. glucose, fructose, and sucrose, in apple and orange juices. The sugar-reducing activity of A. kunkeei remains effective even under acidic conditions and high osmotic pressure. These characteristics suggest that fermentation with A. kunkeei is a promising approach for reducing the free sugar content in fruit juices.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Removal of submandibular hilar stones using a sialendoscope and a high-definition endoscope: Our experience and outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sialendoscopy is an effective method for removing submandibular hilar stones, with a low incidence of postoperative complications. Using an HDE during transoral surgery enhances its efficacy by aiding precise localisation of the stone, facilitating its removal and detecting residual fragments or stones.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epithelial tumors of the lacrimal drainage system: A narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this review, we aimed to provide a comprehensive and up-to-date overview of epithelial tumors of the lacrimal drainage system (LDS)-rare but clinically significant entities that are often misdiagnosed as benign obstructions-by integrating recent evidence regarding epidemiology, clinical manifestations, diagnostic approaches, histopathological and molecular diversity as well as warning signs and imaging and biopsy strategies. According to the available data, squamous cell carcinoma is the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sensitization in Organ Transplantation: Assessment of Risk (STAR) 2025 Meeting Group Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Sensitization in Transplantation: Assessment of Risk (STAR) initiative aims to translate HLA laboratory data into clinical practice and identify key knowledge gaps to guide future research. The STAR working group has held three consensus meetings and published reports that have influenced clinical care. In 2025, the group focused on five evolving areas: donor-derived cell-free DNA (dd-cfDNA) tests, innate immunity in allograft rejection, immunogenicity and antigenicity, HLA antibody...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell body area expansion is a key factor determining connectivity and diameter of on-chip vascular networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to identify the key determinants of vascular networks (VN) morphology, with a particular focus on the role of endothelial cell body area expansion. We introduced a quantitative metric, the cell body area expansion (CBE) score, to assess endothelial cell (EC) enlargement during the early stage of self-organizing vascular network formation. The CBE score positively correlated with both VN connectivity and vessel diameter. Notably, VNs formed in the absence of growth factors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical significance of detecting asbestos bodies in bronchoalveolar lavage fluid in diffuse lung disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The presence of ≥1 AB/mL in the BALF reflects substantial asbestos exposure and is associated with pleural plaques on CT imaging but not with BAL cellular patterns or the rate of decline in respiratory function. These findings suggest that AB detection in BALF has limited predictive value for respiratory function decline but could be valuable for identifying unrecognized asbestos exposure in patients with diffuse lung disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global glucagon-like peptide-2 receptor activation linked to increased obesity risk in the UK Biobank]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings suggest that global GLP-2R activation, encompassing the effects across all tissues, is associated with increased risk of obesity. This study highlights the role of the GLP-2R in metabolic diseases, guiding the future development of biased GLP-2R ligands and the potential adverse effects of GLP-2R modulation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation between permeability of pectin-ethylcellulose films and drug release from coatings under variable processing conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pectin (PEC) and ethylcellulose (EC) are widely employed as colon-targeted coating materials due to their complementary properties, namely enzymatic degradability of pectin in the colonic environment and hydrophobicity of ethylcellulose. Beyond polymer selection, processing parameters critically influence the mass transfer characteristics of pharmaceutical coatings. This study investigated the relationship between the permeability of PEC-EC isolated films and drug release profiles of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A mouse circadian proteome atlas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The circadian clock drives daily rhythms of gene expression and physiology. Advances in next-generation DNA sequencing have provided extensive insights into RNA expression, but more functional information at the protein level with sufficient depth has been limited by technical challenges. In this study, we generated a comprehensive mouse circadian proteome atlas (https://chronoproteinology.org/circadian_atlas) by analyzing 32 tissues, including the suprachiasmatic nucleus (SCN), using the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In silico design of stable single-domain antibodies with high affinity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Designing antibodies is complex and resource intensive. While deep learning and generative approaches have shown promise in the design of protein binders, achieving high affinity and stability remains challenging. We introduce EvolveX, a structure-based antibody design pipeline leveraging the empirical force field FoldX to design complementarity-determining regions (CDRs) of single-domain antibodies (VHHs). We demonstrate the ability of EvolveX to redesign a VHH targeting mouse Vsig4 (mVsig4) to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of total daily working hours encompassing unpaid care and domestic work with nonrestorative sleep and mental health in middle-aged Japanese men and women: A cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Total daily working hours encompassing unpaid care and domestic work represent an important factor influencing sleep and mental health outcomes, with notable associations observed in women. These findings underscore the importance of incorporating unpaid care and domestic work into time burden assessments and support the development of gender-equitable strategies that account for total working hours in health and social policies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of brensocatib in Japanese patients with non-cystic fibrosis bronchiectasis: Analysis of the ASPEN trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Consistent with overall ASPEN results, brensocatib 10 mg and 25 mg reduced exacerbation frequency vs placebo in Japanese patients with bronchiectasis. Lung function, patient-reported symptoms, and safety data were consistent with overall ASPEN trial results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[All-case post-marketing surveillance of delamanid for treating multidrug-resistant pulmonary tuberculosis in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This surveillance showed the effectiveness of ≥6 months of delamanid treatment among patients with MDR-TB in real-world settings in Japan, with no new safety issues identified.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41519017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Osteoporosis prediction from Frontal Lumbar Spine X-rays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study evaluated the performance of Deep Xray™ Spina in predicting osteoporosis from FLS-X. The software is a practical and reliable tool for predicting osteoporosis, with high performance and robustness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shielding design to mitigate neutron-induced single event upsets in space]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We evaluated charged particle and neutron environments in space modules constructed from various structural materials using Monte Carlo simulations. Error rates due to single event upsets (SEU) in silicon devices were also assessed. Charged particle environments in modules constructed from organic composite materials closely resemble those in conventional aluminum structures, whereas neutron environments showed notable differences. Compared to aluminum, organic composites reduced SEU rates by up...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacological management of insomnia with a focus on GABA<sub>A</sub> receptor positive allosteric modulators and orexin receptor antagonists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The scientific literature regarding the effectiveness of two insomnia treatments: GABA(A) receptor positive allosteric modulators, and orexin receptor antagonists is reviewed. In this review, we define insomnia, present epidemiological statistics on insomnia, and provide a rationale for use of medications targeting GABA(A) and orexin receptors for management of insomnia. Following this, we present results of a PRISM guideline-based literature search spanning multiple databases, including PubMed,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergency Nurses' Comprehensive process of surrogate decision Support: Reanalysis of qualitative data Using a grounded theory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mass mortalities caused by different genotypes of HPAIV H5N1 clade 2.3.4.4b in colony breeding Black-headed Gulls and Sandwich Terns in Denmark 2022 and 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unprecedented seabird mass mortality events (MMEs) were reported in multiple European countries in 2022 and 2023. These events were attributed to Clade 2.3.4.4b H5N1 high pathogenicity avian influenza viruses (HPAIVs). In Denmark, populations of Sandwich Terns (Thalasseus sandvicensis) and Black-headed Gulls (Chroicocephalus ridibundus) were significantly impacted. Sandwich Tern mortality occurred primarily between May and June of 2022 and was caused by the HPAIV genotype EA-AB. From 2022 to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal trends of transcatheter aortic valve implantation in a single Belgian centre over 15 years: 30-day and 1-year outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Over 15 years we observed a shift from very high-risk towards predominantly intermediate- to high-risk patients, together with substantial procedural simplification and a marked reduction in in-hospital complications and length of stay. These improvements translated into a significant increase in 30-day and 1-year survival.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unilateral eye occlusion (patching) in Sunflower syndrome: Promise, limitations, and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol for generating protoplasts from the leafcutter ant symbiotic fungus Leucoagaricus gongylophorus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a protocol to isolate viable protoplasted cells of the basidiomycete fungal mutualist (Leucoagaricus gongylophorus) obligately farmed by leafcutter ants. We describe steps for culturing actively growing mycelia, enzymatic digestion of fungal cell walls under osmotic stabilization, and purification of protoplasts (plasma membrane enclosing cytoplasm and organelles). We then detail procedures for assessing viability and wall removal using microscopy and fluorescent staining.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The poorly differentiated component in endoscopic biopsy predicts submucosal invasion in superficial Barrett's esophageal adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We showed biopsy-PDC, tumor diameter greater than 20 mm, and complex macroscopic type independently predict submucosal invasion in Barrett's esophageal adenocarcinoma. Biopsy-PDC may predict submucosal cancer and submucosal invasion at the biopsy site more reliably, independent of endoscopic findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mother-Adolescent Discrepancies in Reports of Relationship Quality and Early Adolescent Internalizing Symptoms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This 3-wave longitudinal study examined the bidirectional associations between adolescents' and mothers' perceptions of the mother-adolescent relationship quality (i.e., warmth and hostility) and internalizing symptoms (i.e., depressive symptoms and loneliness). The focus was on the direction of effects between internalizing symptoms and both the levels of and discrepancies in mothers' and adolescents' perceptions of mother-adolescent relationship quality and potential differential associations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41518453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260111142145&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>