<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:02:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Prognostic Impact of Multiple Adverse Events on Long-Term Mortality Following Acute Myocardial Infarction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Multiple adverse events after AMI confer substantially higher mortality risk than single events, with the greatest impact in the first 30 days. These findings support the need for an immediate and tailored approach and sustained surveillance to prevent further ischemic or bleeding complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerebellar tonic inhibition orchestrates the maturation of information processing and motor coordination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tonic inhibition in cerebellar granule cells is crucial for maintaining information coding fidelity during motor coordination. It arises through both activity-dependent and activity-independent mechanisms, and the interplay between these mechanisms changes with age. However, specific molecular and cellular mechanisms and how their change affects network-level computation and motor behavior remain unclear. Here we show that, while net tonic inhibitory current remains unchanged, the main source of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two codes of RNA editing by deamination in human diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA editing is a post-transcriptional modification that expands transcriptomic and proteomic diversity. Advances in high-throughput sequencing across a broad range of biological and pathological contexts have enabled systematic identification of editing events driven by two major RNA deaminase families: ADAR and APOBEC, which catalyze adenosine-to-inosine (A-to-I) and cytidine-to-uridine (C-to-U) substitution, respectively. Genome-wide profiling of RNA editing has uncovered a substantial number...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cold-injection synthesis of highly emissive perovskite nanocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colloidal perovskite nanocrystal (PeNC) has long been synthesized using the hot-injection method and room-temperature ligand-assisted reprecipitation as the prominent techniques^(1,2). However, both methods have challenges for industrial-scale production^(3-5): the hot-injection method requires high temperatures, an inert gas environment and rapid cooling, which raise safety concerns, whereas ligand-assisted reprecipitation can exhibit limited productivity on scale-up. Here we present a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Passive sampling and molecular networking for surveillance of lipophilic marine biotoxins along the south coast of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipophilic marine biotoxins (LMTs) are increasingly reported in coastal ecosystems, posing risks to seafood safety and public health. This study investigated the spatial and seasonal distributions of LMTs along the south coast of Korea in 2022 by integrating phytoplankton and mussel sampling with passive solid-phase adsorption toxin tracking (SPATT) and molecular networking-based high-resolution mass spectrometry. Diatoms dominated the phytoplankton community, but toxin-producing dinoflagellates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic engineering of Escherichia coli for the production of two-carbon primary amines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary amines are the industrially important chemicals widely used in the manufacture of dyes, pharmaceuticals, and agrochemicals. In this study, we developed metabolically engineered Escherichia coli strains for the efficient production of two-carbon primary amines, ethylamine and ethanolamine. For ethylamine production, metabolic pathways were optimized by enhancing flux toward the precursor l-alanine and by increasing the expression of a valine decarboxylase variant, VlmD^(V94I). Subsequent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive evaluation of Chokyungjongok-tang, a traditional herbal prescription: HPLC-based quality assessment, genotoxicity, anti-inflammatory efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings indicate that CKJOT showed no evidence of genotoxicity in OECD/MFDS guideline-compliant in vitro and in vivo assays under the tested conditions, and that it modulated selected inflammatory mediators in LPS-stimulated RAW264.7 macrophages in vitro.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The mast cell-stabilizing effects of inotodiol and lanosterol result from ubiquitin-mediated degradation of HMG-CoA reductase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inotodiol, a C22-hydroxy lanosterol uniquely found in chaga mushroom, possesses potent anti-anaphylactic and mast cell-stabilizing activities; however, its underlying mechanism remains poorly understood. Given its structural similarity to lanosterol and the established role of lanosterol in regulating HMG-CoA reductase (HMGCR) expression, we investigated whether inotodiol exerts its mast cell-stabilizing effects by blocking the mevalonate pathway through downregulation of HMGCR. Both inotodiol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of an induced pluripotent stem cell line (cmESF-iPSC-C3) from cynomolgus monkey ear fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Induced pluripotent stem cells (iPSCs) derived from cynomolgus monkey (crab-eating macaque) ear fibroblasts offer a minimally invasive and ethically acceptable source of cells for autologous therapies and preclinical research. Owing to close genetic and physiological similarities to humans, these iPSCs represent a relevant and versatile alternative to human-based models. Here, iPSCs exhibited trilineage differentiation and were directly differentiated into neurons in vitro, confirming...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural Basis of Action Simulation in Architectural Perception: A Multi-voxel Pattern Analysis Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A growing body of neuroscience evidence indicates that perceiving everyday objects and environments triggers mental simulations of potential actions, preparing the brain for movement even before any motion occurs. Although previous research on navigation has demonstrated how the spatial configuration of corridors and doorways guide locomotion, it remains unclear whether architectural elements (e.g., doors, windows, stairs) that require direct interaction evoke distinct, action-specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accurate conformational ensembles of intrinsically disordered proteins using reweighting based on NMR chemical shifts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intrinsically disordered proteins and protein regions (IDRs) underpin a wide range of vital biological processes but exhibit dynamic and heterogeneous conformations. Currently, many computational efforts seek to elucidate the conformational ensembles of these disordered proteins, yet most methods still struggle to fully capture their structural diversity. Here, we integrate structural libraries of various IDRs-derived from coarse-grained molecular dynamics (MD) simulations and machine learning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metal-organic framework/graphene nanoribbon/polyimide mixed-matrix membranes for high-temperature H<sub>2</sub>/N<sub>2</sub> separation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the application of mixed-matrix membranes for high-temperature hydrogen separation. To enhance hydrogen selectivity, graphene nanoribbons (GNRs) were incorporated into ZIF-8 fillers, forming a physically confined structure conducive to hydrogen transport. The metal-organic framework (MOF)/GNR filler embedded into a polyimide (PI) matrix yielded a much higher H(2) permeability (298 Barrer, +40%) and H(2)/N(2) selectivity (15, +25%) than the neat PI membrane. In particular, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Millimeters to Microns: A Hybrid Strategy for Reconfigurable Liquid-Crystal Patterning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Programmable patterning of nematic liquid crystals (LCs) enables spatially encoded optical functionality, but existing approaches often face trade-offs between patterned area, feature fidelity, dimensionality, and device integration. Many methods rely on surface alignment, electrode patterning, or global illumination, limiting local addressability, depth control, or scalability. Field-assisted polymerization of reactive mesogens offers a means to capture designed LC director configurations as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemo-Mechanical Failure and Reinforcement of Solid Electrolyte Films for Practical All-Solid-State Li Metal Pouch Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All-solid-state Li metal batteries (ASLMBs) are the key to achieving high energy densities; however, studies on practically relevant pouch-type cells remain scarce. A critical challenge lies in integrating thin solid electrolyte films, particularly under the high pressures required for cell assembly, which has been largely overlooked. Here, we reveal the inherent incompatibility of conventional sulfide solid electrolyte films with Li metal during pouch cell assembly. To address this challenge,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preclinical and clinical evaluation of vancomycin plus delpazolid combination therapy for MRSA bacteremia: a multicenter, double-blinded, randomized, parallel design, phase IIa clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA) bacteremia is a serious clinical challenge due to limited treatments and high mortality. We conducted both preclinical and clinical studies to assess the potential role of delpazolid in combination with vancomycin. Synergistic effects of delpazolid with vancomycin or daptomycin were evaluated in vitro using checkerboard and time-kill assays, and in vivo using a Galleria mellonella model. A multicenter, double-blind, randomized, Phase IIa trial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Dosage-Dependent Dominant-Negative Mechanism of SLC45A2(W74R) in Autosomal Dominant Oculocutaneous Albinism Revealed by Zebrafish Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrated that a heterozygous c.220T>C:p.(W74R) variant in SLC45A2 causes variable expressivity of OCA in a dominant inherited manner, and this variant interferes with melanogenesis in zebrafish.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroinflammatory and transcriptional dynamics during SARS-CoV-2 infection in KRT18-hACE2 mouse brain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Neurological complications are increasingly recognized as a significant consequence of COVID-19; however, time-resolved, brain-specific characterization of transcriptional alterations underlying SARS-CoV-2-associated neuroinflammation and neuronal injury remain limited. We hypothesized that brain transcriptional responses evolve dynamically during acute SARS-CoV-2 infection, resulting in temporal transcriptional programs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding the brain's ATG8 paralog code: LC3-GABARAP specialization at synapses and the astrocyte-neuron interface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macroautophagy is essential for the long-term health of neurons and astrocytes in the central nervous system (CNS). The six mammalian ATG8 paralogs (LC3A/B/C and GABARAP/GABARAPL1/L2) exhibit an emerging "ATG8 code"-a division of labor among these proteins that assigns specialized roles in the autophagy pathway to each paralog, enabling fine-tuned proteostasis at synapses and the astrocyte-neuron interface. This review synthesizes how LC3 versus GABARAP mediate distinct steps of autophagy (LC3...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational identification of natural inhibitors targeting GroEL in <em>Leptospira interrogans</em>: an integrative virtual screening and molecular dynamics approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Leptospirosis is a zoonotic disease caused by Leptospira interrogans and represents a major public health and veterinary concern. The persistence of the pathogen is closely associated with biofilm formation, yet targeted therapeutics are currently unavailable. The GroEL chaperonin, a conserved protein involved in biofilm formation and immunogenicity, was investigated as a potential therapeutic target.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and Future Challenges in Monolithic 3D Integrated Logic, Power, and Optoelectronics Technologies for Tightly Interconnected Intelligent Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of ultralarge-scale hardware systems for artificial intelligence is driving demand for high-performance heterogeneous integration. At the heart of these systems lies the maximization of computational capability through high data bandwidth, necessitating interconnects that either increase the number of links between tiers and chips or enhance the data transfer rate of each link. Monolithic three-dimensional (M3D) integration, particularly with two-dimensional (2D) materials, offers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, KIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Astragalus membranaceus sprouts and their unique constituents regulate reactive oxygen species production, inflammation-related senescence-associated secretory phenotype components, and extracellular matrix in fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging involves a gradual decline in physiological functions and increased susceptibility to damage and disease. Suppressing reactive oxygen species (ROS) production and inflammatory responses is critical for delaying age-related cellular decline. Astragalus membranaceus is one of the important health functional foods worldwide due to its health benefits, including antioxidant and immunomodulatory properties. While the root is the most commonly utilized part, other plant parts remain largely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrophobic Polymer-Coated and Uncoated ZIF-67/Alumina Membrane for Volatile Organic Compound Degradation and CO<sub>2</sub> Adsorption Capture]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A major obstacle to the commercial application of metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) is that their powder form hinders scalable membrane fabrication and significantly compromises stability under humid conditions. To address these limitations, this study presents a novel, humidity-resistant zeolitic imidazolate framework ZIF-67/alumina composite membrane (MMF) that combines visible-light volatile organic compound (VOC) degradation and CO(2) adsorption in a single, scalable platform. Using an in situ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The integrated stress response promotes immune evasion through lipocalin 2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer cells activate the integrated stress response (ISR) to adapt to stress and resist therapy¹. ISR signals converge on activating transcription factor 4 (ATF4), which controls cell-intrinsic transcriptional programs that are involved in metabolic adaptation, survival and growth^(2,3). However, whether the ISR-ATF4 axis influences anti-tumour immune responses remains mostly unknown. Here we show that loss of ATF4 decreases tumour progression considerably in immunocompetent mice, but not in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hardware-independent control for partial gravity simulation using a 2-DOF robotic device]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A variety of physiological changes in the human body have been observed to occur under the microgravity conditions of space. 3D clinostat devices capable of implementing time-averaged simulated microgravity (taSMG) have been widely used to predict these changes on Earth and to identify their underlying mechanisms. Recently, the concept of time-averaged simulated partial gravity (taSPG), which mimics the gravitational environments of the Moon (0.17 g) and Mars (0.38 g), has been proposed as an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing drinking and irrigation water quality in a highly altered subtropical river in India using hydro-chemical indices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[River water pollution and the subsequent degradation of water quality for irrigation and drinking are reported worldwide, especially in tropical regions with excess population pressure. The present study intends to investigate irrigation and drinking water quality and assess their suitability in the subtropical Damodar River in India using hydrochemical indices during pre-monsoon (PRM), monsoon (MON), and post-monsoon (POM) periods. The water quality index (WQI) results reveal that the river's...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apoptosis and Metabolic Reprogramming by RHART in Hepatocellular Carcinoma Through the CPSF6/MCT4/c-Myc Signaling In Vitro and In Vivo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Though Rhus verniciflua and Artemisia capillaris have been traditionally prescribed for liver ailments, the molecular antitumor mechanism of their ethanol extract (RHART) remains undefined in hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC). Thus, this study aimed to elucidate the apoptotic mechanisms of RHART, focusing on its regulation of oncogenic drivers-cleavage and polyadenylation specificity factor 6 (CPSF6), monocarboxylate transporter 4 (MCT4), and c-Myc-and glycolysis-related pathways. RHART quality was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How AI tools can enhance generalizability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of preoperative comorbidity and intraoperative hypotension on postoperative acute kidney injury after non-cardiac surgery: a structural equation modeling-based mediation analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: High ASA-PS scores increase AKI risk after non-cardiac surgery, a relationship partially mediated by statistically significant pathways involving IOH and hypoalbuminemia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The decline of child stunting in 122 countries: a systematic review of child growth studies since the 19th century]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The global child stunting rate was substantially higher in the early 20th century than in 1985, and the reduction of child stunting was a central feature of the health transition. The high stunting rates and subsequent reduction of stunting in HICs suggest that current HICs provide lessons for eradicating child stunting and that all LMICs can eliminate stunting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708137/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cellulose nanofiber-based active packaging film enhanced with carbon dots and hydrochar derived from nettle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbon dots (CD) and hydrochar (HC) derived from nettle were synthesized using a zero-waste synthesis method, and their effectiveness was elucidated as active packaging fillers. Cellulose nanofiber (CNF)-based films were produced by blending CD (CNF/CD) and HC (CNF/HC), resulting in improved preservability of pork sausages. The CNF/CD and CNF/HC films enhanced the UV blocking performance, reducing UV-B transmittance by 91.7% and 83.3% and UV-A transmittance by 85.2% and 58.9%, respectively. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraperitoneal injection of Chaetomorpha aerea extract boosted immunocompetence, antioxidant status and disease resistance against Aeromonas hydrophila in grey mullet, Mugil cephalus juveniles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The current research was conducted to examine the effects of intraperitoneal injection (IP) of hot water extract of Chaetomorpha aerea (HWECA) on some physiological responses and disease resistance against Aeromonas hydrophila infection in flathead grey mullet, Mugil cephalus (initial body mass 25 ± 0.5 g) juveniles. Six experimental groups, each containing triplicates (n=30 fish/tank) were designed. A positive control and a negative control group received an injection of phosphate buffered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Future temperature-related labour loss due to premature deaths: a multi-country study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ongoing climate change is expected to lead to a significant increase in the frequency and intensity of climate extremes. However, the impact of cold and hot temperatures on labour loss, through causing premature deaths in the future, remains largely unknown. We collected historic daily all-cause mortality data during 1986-2019 from 1066 locations in seven countries. A two-stage time-series approach was applied to estimate associations between non-optimum temperatures and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cryo-CLEM-guided workflow for quantitative assessment and optimization of cryo-ET specimen quality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cryo-correlative light and electron microscopy (cryo-CLEM) is an essential technique for precisely targeting regions of interest in vitrified biological specimens for in situ cellular cryo-electron tomography (cryo-ET). Despite its widespread use, the potential of cryo-CLEM remains underexploited because its imaging performance under cryogenic conditions has not been characterized. Here, we evaluated the imaging capabilities of two commercially available cryo-CLEM systems-a stand-alone Leica EM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Irregular meal frequency and depressive symptoms: Moderating roles of dietary diversity and breakfast skipping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Irregular main-meal consumption frequency was associated with depressive symptoms, moderated by dietary diversity and breakfast habits, highlighting meal pattern regularity as a modifiable nutritional target for prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic changes to the tibiofemoral joint line with increasing osteoarthritis severity and its relationship to constitutional alignment : a radiological analysis of 3,320 knees]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The tibiofemoral joint line angle changes dynamically with OA progression, while the constitutional aJLO remains stable until advanced disease occurs. Understanding this distinction between constitutional and dynamic joint line orientation is important when communicating and studying outcomes related to knee alignment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Late distant recurrence prediction model in premenopausal women with ER-positive/HER 2-negative breast cancer: A multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The machine-learning model effectively stratified patients into distinct DR risk groups and highlighted the benefit of extended ET in high-risk patients. This model supports tailored decision-making regarding extended ET in premenopausal patients with ER-positive/HER2-negative breast cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recurrent pyuria is associated with shorter progression-free survival in dogs with bladder urothelial carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dogs with pyuria at initial diagnosis and frequent pyuria (≥ 3 episodes) during the entire treatment period had shorter PFS than dogs without pyuria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental activation assessment of metallic components from medical cyclotron operations in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyclotron-based medical radionuclide production inevitably generates secondary neutrons, which can induce activation in surrounding materials. Despite the growing clinical use of medical cyclotrons, systematic measurements of neutron-induced activation products in the cyclotron components remain scarce. Therefore, this study aimed to perform quantitative measurements of activation in metallic components exposed to secondary neutrons during cyclotron operation. Representative metallic subsamples,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative Enfortumab Vedotin and Pembrolizumab in Bladder Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative enfortumab vedotin plus pembrolizumab and surgery led to significantly better event-free and overall survival outcomes and a greater percentage of participants with pathological complete response than surgery alone in a predominantly cisplatin-ineligible population with muscle-invasive bladder cancer. Safety was also assessed. (Funded by Merck Sharp and Dohme, a subsidiary of Merck [Rahway, NJ]; KEYNOTE-905 ClinicalTrials.gov number, NCT03924895.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dental-Medical Data Interoperability and Mutual Workforce Training: Insights of Enhancing the Benefits of SDF Treatment Among Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnosis of Primary Open-Angle Glaucoma Using Spectral Profiling of Aqueous Humor-Derived Exosomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary open-angle glaucoma (POAG) is one of the most common neurodegenerative diseases that cause irreversible optic nerve damage. POAG diagnosis requires multimodal assessments; however, current methods like intraocular pressure (IOP) and optical coherence tomography (OCT) imaging suffer from low sensitivity and inter-patient variability, respectively. Liquid biopsy provides objective molecular signatures, offering a robust alternative to overcome limitations of conventional clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Living-donor liver transplantation in hepatocellular carcinoma with portal-vein tumor thrombosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In carefully selected patients with HCC and PVTT who achieved successful downstaging, even including Vp4 cases, LDLT may confer acceptable survival; These findings highlight the importance of preoperative assessment of tumor biology and treatment response in selecting candidates and stratifying risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoparticle-Mediated Interface Engineering for Uniform, Reproducible Electron Transport Layers in Scalable Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As lab-scale perovskite solar cells (PSCs) approach their efficiency limits, reproducing this performance in large-area, manufacturable devices remains challenging. Here, we show that printing interlayers of metal oxide nanoparticles, specifically Al(2)O(3) and SnO(2), can systematically control the morphology and interfacial energetics of solution-processed PC(61)BM electron transport layers (ETLs) in flexible roll-to-roll printed PSCs. These nanoparticle interlayers enhance ETL uniformity,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preoperative Circulating Tumor DNA Detection and Risk Stratification in Esophageal Squamous Cell Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Preoperative ctDNA detection was significantly associated with occult nodal metastasis and recurrence risk in clinical N0 early-stage ESCC in this study. Among patients with T2N0 ESCC, ctDNA may serve as a complementary biomarker to inform neoadjuvant treatment escalation and support more personalized therapeutic strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcome and efficacy of nusinersen in Korean adult patients with 5q spinal muscular atrophy: Nationwide multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our multicenter real-world study demonstrates the sustained efficacy and manageable safety profile of nusinersen in adult SMA patients, supporting the long-term use in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pan-cancer multi-omics characterization of CDK12 and virtual screening of Vietnamese natural products for novel inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyclin-dependent kinase 12 (CDK12), a key regulator of cell-cycle-linked transcriptional programs, has gained increasing attention as a driver of tumorigenesis and a promising therapeutic vulnerability across diverse malignancies. In this study, we combined pan-cancer multi-omics profiling with a computational screen of a Vietnamese medicinal herbs compound library to identify candidate inhibitors targeting both wild-type CDK12 and its drug-resistant C1039F variant. Transcriptomic and proteomic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systematic review of current evidence on metabolites associated with gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Previous studies have reported associations between metabolites and GC, as well as progression of precancerous lesions, providing insights into gastric carcinogenesis. However, substantial heterogeneity across studies highlights the need for standardized methodological approaches and adjustment for key confounders followed by independent validation and replication in large, well-designed, multi-population studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of CEUS LI-RADS v2017 major feature combinations: individual patient data meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CEUS LI-RADS demonstrated progressively higher PPVs from LR-3 to LR-5, supporting its ability to stratify risk across HCC categories. Major feature combinations performed similarly within each category, indicating internal consistency of the system. Although only PPVs were assessed, the results align with trends seen in CT/MRI LI-RADS, with wider confidence intervals in CEUS reflecting smaller sample sizes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent ultratrace per- and polyfluoroalkyl substance (PFAS) detectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in per- and polyfluoroalkyl substance (PFAS) detection exploit engineered fluorophilic interfaces, conjugated polymers, molecular imprinting, and nanoscale transduction to deliver rapid, selective, and field-compatible sensors with ppt to ppq level sensitivity. This minireview discusses advances made over the last five years in five material classes-organic molecules and assemblies, polymers, nanoparticles, carbon nanotubes, and metal-organic frameworks-highlighting how tailored...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vacancy Cluster-Mediated Epitaxial Layer-by-Layer Growth of van der Waals Heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two-dimensional transition metal dichalcogenide heterostructures offer a versatile platform for tailoring quantum and optoelectronic properties, yet their scalable synthesis remains challenging due to the inert nature of van der Waals (vdW) basal planes, which lack nucleation sites for epitaxy. Here, we report a vacancy cluster-mediated epitaxial layer-by-layer growth strategy that enables the deterministic construction of vdW heterostructures with atomic precision. Hydrogen plasma treatment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The longitudinal trajectory of learned helplessness among adolescent students: The role of parental autonomy support and control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the longitudinal trajectory of learned helplessness in academic settings during adolescence, examined the generalizability of this trajectory across students' demographic and academic backgrounds, and assessed the role of parental autonomy support and psychological control in predicting learned helplessness at each time point. We analyzed five waves of large-scale panel data following Korean adolescent students (N = 2590) from Grade 7 to Grade 11. Our second-order latent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Collagenase-Functionalized Liposomes Overcome Stromal Barriers in Pancreatic Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC) features a dense desmoplastic stroma dominated by type I collagen, which forms a physical barrier that limits vascular perfusion and drug penetration, resulting in poor therapeutic outcomes. Here, we report gemcitabine-loaded collagenase-conjugated liposomes (GLCLs) that enzymatically remodel the collagen-rich extracellular matrix (ECM) while delivering a cytotoxic payload. GLCL retained enzymatic activity and stability, exhibited prolonged circulation,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On-scene machine learning prediction model for massive transfusion in trauma and its association with in-hospital mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A prehospital ensemble learning model to predict MT was developed and validated, and its predictions were significantly associated with in-hospital mortality. However, this study is limited by the inclusion of a single ethnicity, and future research needs to integrate data from multiple populations to enhance generalizability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Situ Transmission Electron Microscopy Visualization of Electric-Field-Induced Phase Transitions at the Morphotropic Phase Boundary in Hf<sub>0.5</sub>Zr<sub>0.5</sub>O<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding electric-field-induced phase transitions is crucial for optimizing the ferroelectric and antiferroelectric properties of hafnium zirconium oxide (Hf(0.5)Zr(0.5)O(2), HZO) thin films. Here, we use in situ transmission electron microscopy (TEM) to uncover the nanoscale mechanism of field-induced phase evolution in ultrathin HZO films at the morphotropic phase boundary (MPB), directly visualizing oxygen vacancy migration and its correlation with the transformation from the nonpolar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>ERJ Open Research</em> in 2026: progress and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As we enter our 11th year, ERJ Open Research celebrates record interest. We are dedicated to becoming the best-open access respiratory journal, balancing high-quality research with inclusivity and speed to serve the community. https://bit.ly/4bqyvLh.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From coordination to function: Inorganic insights into metalloproteins and metallopeptides in biosystems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deubiquitinase USP2 promotes hepatic stellate cell activation via p300 stabilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatic stellate cell (HSC) activation is a central mechanism in liver fibrosis, with histone acetyltransferase p300 acting as a pivotal transcriptional cofactor. To define upstream regulators of p300 stability during HSC activation, we performed a deubiquitinase inhibitor screen in activated HSCs and identified ubiquitin carboxyl-terminal hydrolase 2 (USP2) as a p300 deubiquitinase. Single-cell RNA sequencing of fibrotic human liver tissues revealed USP2 as the most specifically expressed USP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plant-based oil composition modulates saltiness and bitterness in sodium-reduced double emulsions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the effects of plant-based oil composition on the physicochemical properties, sensory perception, and digestive stability of sodium-reduced emulsions. Four edible oils (perilla, sesame, canola, and olive) were evaluated in both oil-in-water (O/W) and high internal phase double emulsion (HIPDE) systems. O/W emulsions contained either NaCl or KCl, whereas HIPDEs encapsulated KCl in the internal aqueous phase (W₁) and NaCl in the external phase (W₂). In O/W emulsions, oils...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma-driven oxidative modification of quercetin and its antibacterial application on cherry tomato]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quercetin, a widely distributed natural flavonol, is well known for its antioxidant properties, but can act as a pro-oxidant under certain conditions, promoting oxidative stress and generating reactive oxygen species (ROS). This transition to a pro-oxidant state enables quercetin to exert potent antibacterial activities. In this study, cold plasma treatment was employed to induce the pro-oxidant conversion of quercetin, and the antibacterial efficacy, underlying antibacterial mechanisms of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations Between Information and Communication Technology Use and Depression in Community-Dwelling Older Adults: The Potential Role of Social Participation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ICT use was associated with depression among older adults, with formal and informal social participation potentially being relevant factors, and associations varied by ICT use type.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Evaluation of Machine Learning Models for Spatio-Temporal Groundwater Quality Prediction and Classification in the Muvattupuzha River Basin, India]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Groundwater contamination has increased significantly due to population growth, land-use change, and unsustainable resource exploitation, necessitating advanced predictive tools for effective water governance. This study presents a multi-temporal, comparative machine learning (ML) to evaluate groundwater quality in the Muvattupuzha River Basin, Kerala, India, using datasets from 2003, 2013, and 2023. A total of five supervised ML models (i.e., decision tree [DT], logistic regression, support...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of musculoskeletal pain in relation to joint hypermobility among health science students in Kuwait: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Chronic and acute musculoskeletal pain is common among HSC students and may be related to the presence of JHM. Female students appear to be at a higher risk of developing musculoskeletal pain related to JHM than male students. However, the indicated correlation between JHM and musculoskeletal chronic/acute pain needs to be affirmed in further studies with validated quantitative outcome measures and longitudinal designs. Key Points • Chronic and acute musculoskeletal pain is common...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Contrast X-Ray Computed Tomography for Quantifying Amorphous Content in Melt-Quenched Acetaminophen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[X-ray computed tomography (XRCT) allows for non-destructive three-dimensional observation and volumetric quantification of samples. It also allows for structural changes monitoring, such as the amorphous-to-crystalline transition in pharmaceuticals, over time. Despite past applications of XRCT to characterize amorphous pharmaceuticals, its quantitative validity has not been systematically verified against established thermal methods. Here, we evaluated laboratory XRCT for monitoring the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic value of rising smoke sign on MRI: a characteristic finding of odontogenic maxillary sinusitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiofrequency Ablation for Early Stage Breast Cancer as a Potential Alternative to Partial Mastectomy: 5-Year Results from the Multiple-Center, Single-Arm, Phase 3 RAFAELO Study (NCCH1409)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RFA was shown to be a safe and minimally invasive treatment for early stage breast cancer, comparable in efficacy to partial mastectomy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deciphering the etiology of the 2024 outbreak of undiagnosed febrile illness in Panzi, Democratic Republic of the Congo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In late 2024, an outbreak of over 400 cases of undiagnosed febrile illness, predominantly presenting as fever and cough, was reported in Panzi Health Zone, southwestern Democratic Republic of the Congo. Here we conducted an epidemiological and laboratory investigation to determine the etiology of the outbreak. Clinical data and specimens were prospectively collected from 108 individuals, of whom 59/108 (54.6%) were female. Children aged <5 years were the most affected (47/108, 43.5%); 14/32...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation and fine mapping of qVmunBr6.2 locus reveal a gene encoding hevamine-A, a defense protein with chitinase activity, is associated with bruchid (Callosobruchus maculatus) resistance in black gram (Vigna mungo)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Callosobruchus maculatus (cowpea weevil) is an insect pest that causes significant yield loss in cultivated black gram (Vigna mungo var. mungo) during storage. A previous study showed that seed resistance to C. maculatus in wild black gram (V. mungo var. silvestris) accession 'TC2210' is controlled by two linked QTLs, qVmunBr6.1 and qVmunBr6.2. However, none of these QTL have been validated, and the molecular basis of these QTLs is not yet known. The objectives of this study are to validate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and evaluation of recombinant dense granule 14 for serological diagnosis of Toxoplasma gondii infection in domestic cats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LUMIN: an automated graphical analysis toolbox for high-throughput calcium imaging ofin vitro neuronal cultures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conformational biosensors delineate endosomal G protein regulation by GPCRs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many GPCRs trigger a second phase of G protein-coupled signaling from endosomes after signaling from the plasma membrane, necessitating GPCRs to increase the concentration of active-state G proteins on the endosome membrane. How this is achieved remains unclear. Here, we show that three G(s)-coupled GPCRs-the β2-adrenergic receptor, VIP-1 receptor, and adenosine 2B receptor-each trigger a net redistribution of Gα(s) from the plasma membrane to endosomes at native expression levels and without...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemistry-driven autonomous nanopore membranes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fabrication of pores at the atomic scale remains a significant challenge in modern nanotechnology, hindering the study of ion transport and molecular dynamics in confined spaces. Here, we introduce a chemically controllable break-membrane approach that enables the repeated formation and closure of nanoscale pores in SiN(x) membranes through manipulating the in-pore electrochemical reaction conditions by transmembrane voltage. Ionic current measurements reveal distinct conductance features that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune endotypes and treatment response in psoriatic arthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating in-depth interpretive qualitative research with social pharmacy research: Opening the dialogue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This commentary invites readers to explore the possibilities that emerge when in-depth interpretive qualitative research is brought into closer dialogue with social pharmacy. Drawing on the analytical concepts of temporality, socio-materiality, and morality, the authors show how patient-centered perspectives can enrich and expand adherence research. Through a fictional patient case, they illustrate how everyday medication practices are shaped not only by clinical decisions but also by shifting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of pulmonary arterial hypertension in systemic sclerosis: from classical treatments to new horizons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pulmonary arterial hypertension (PAH) is a severe disease characterised by a progressive thickening and obliteration of pulmonary vessels, resulting in increased vascular resistance, elevated pulmonary artery pressures, and right heart failure. Among the various conditions associated with PAH, systemic sclerosis (SSc) is the most common in Western countries. Compared to other forms of PAH, SSc-PAH presents with a more aggressive clinical course, poorer response to conventional therapies and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mirror-Image D-Core Streptavidin Exhibits Reduced Immunogenicity and Comparable Biodistribution to Natural Core Streptavidin in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The clinical application of natural core streptavidin remains unrealized owing to its immunogenicity and interference from endogenous D-biotin. These limitations could be addressed using D-core streptavidin, the mirror-image form. Here, we evaluated the immunogenicity and biodistribution of D-core streptavidin in mice. Intraperitoneal administration of natural core streptavidin induced antibodies against streptavidin, whereas no antibody production was observed for D-core streptavidin. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alteration of Fatty Acid Composition of Phospholipids in EA.hy926 Endothelial Cells Is Reflected in Microvesicles during TNF-α Stimulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fatty acid composition of phospholipids in the plasma membrane affects cell function; however, these findings have primarily been observed in vitro because there are no suitable tools for monitoring phospholipid fatty acid composition of the plasma membrane in vivo. In this study, we used elaidate as a trigger for altering fatty acid composition in phospholipids and determined whether such changes are reflected in microvesicles (MVs) released from the plasma membrane. Persistent exposure of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dripping-based microencapsulation using a novel Omani gum/alginate system: Formulation, characterization, and encapsulation efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the potential of Omani gum (OG)/alginate composite beads for in vitro oral delivery of the model protein bovine serum albumin (BSA). Novel biopolymeric beads were fabricated using Boswellia sacra (OG) as the primary matrix component through an ionic gelation dripping technique, enabling efficient protein encapsulation and controlled release. BSA release profiles were assessed under varying pH conditions to simulate gastrointestinal environments. The physicochemical properties...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acetic acid induces proteasome storage granule formation and inhibits proteasomal proteolysis: Comparison with other induction conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proteasomes are primarily located within the nuclei of proliferating cells; however, their localization changes dynamically in response to environmental conditions. Saccharomyces cerevisiae forms proteasome storage granules (PSGs) in the cytoplasm upon glucose depletion, mitochondrial stress, or transition to quiescence. Although intracellular acidification drives PSG formation, the detailed mechanisms underlying this process are unclear. As the established PSG induction conditions are limited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary fucoxanthin alleviates skin aging and modulates systemic aging markers in naturally aged C57BL/6J mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fucoxanthin, a well-known xanthophyll obtained from marine algae, has been documented to exhibit multiple physiological and health-promoting effects. In this study, we investigated the impact of dietary administration with fucoxanthin (0.01% and 0.1%) on skin aging in 80-week-old C57BL/6J mice and examined its effects on age-related alterations in other organs. The findings revealed that both concentrations of fucoxanthin attenuated the age-dependent elevation of trans-epidermal water loss...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of N-glycosylation on the transport kinetics of organic anion transporting polypeptide (OATP) 1B1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic anion transporting polypeptide (OATP) 1B1 is crucial for hepatic drug uptake. Three N-glycosylation sites, Asn134, Asn503, and Asn516, have been identified, and substituting the amino acid at these sites with glutamine reduces the expression of the OATP1B1 protein on the plasma membrane. However, the effects of disrupted N-glycosylation on the transport kinetics of OATP1B1 molecule remained uninvestigated. This study quantitatively analyzed the impact of N-glycosylation modifications on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of baloxavir/marboxil treatment and treatment with other anti-influenza agents in adult patients hospitalized for influenza: An internet-based, prospective, multicenter, cohort study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: BXM was used for patients with secondary bacterial pneumonia, although their general conditions were better, and antibiotic use was similar, although more anti-influenza agents were used than in non-BXM-treated patients. BXM might be one of the treatment options for severe influenza patients requiring hospitalization in the real world.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing multimodal large language models for localizing dental implant fixtures on panoramic radiographs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Reasoning-focused multimodal LLMs outperformed GPT-4o in zero-shot implant fixture localization and reduced false positives, but moderate sensitivity, restoration-driven errors, and run-to-run variability limit autonomous clinical use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone-targeting β-cyclodextrin phosphate has anti-resorptive activity and thereby prevents osteoporosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoporosis is a common bone disease that weakens and fragilizes the bones. A wide variety of osteoporosis medicines are available; however, the long-term use of such medicines is not recommended because of major adverse effects. Therefore, the development of effective and safe therapeutic drugs is urgently required. Here, we developed a bone-targeting drug delivery system with anti-resorptive activity for potential osteoporosis treatment. A phosphate-functionalized β-Cyclodextrin (β-CDP)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endothelial cystathionine-γ-lyase (CTH) regulates body weight and insulin resistance in mice fed a high-fat diet]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen sulfide (H(2)S) has been reported to play a critical role in vascular function and metabolism, yet specific molecular mechanisms remain largely unknown. Given this importance and the role of endothelium in metabolic health, we hypothesized that endothelial cystathionine-γ-lyase deficiency (ecCTH-KO) could modulate metabolic function influencing insulin sensitivity and weight gain. To test this, we examined body weight, adipose tissue inflammation, glucose metabolism, and insulin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancement in cell and gene therapy research: A 35-year bibliometric perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results provide a data-driven foundation for guiding research policies and strategic cooperation in this evolving field.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated generation of image-based subject-specific spine models for adult spinal deformity: Development and kinematic evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Adult spinal deformity (ASD) involves complex three-dimensional (3D) spinal malalignments that impair mobility and stability. Current clinical assessments rely on static, two-dimensional (2D) radiographs, which fail to capture the 3D dynamics essential for comprehensive evaluations. While musculoskeletal models with marker-based motion analysis offer insights into kinematics, generic models fail to replicate the 3D deformities in ASD. This study introduces an automated workflow to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The understandability and actionability of AI-generated information for patients with chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The AI responses showed comparable understandability to expert information, but outperformed expert information in terms of text readability. However, challenges have arisen regarding the actionability, flow, and comprehensiveness of AI responses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-related disease or disease-related age? Perspectives for paleopathological research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Diseases and pathological lesions influence the ability to estimate skeletal age at death, whilst our inability to accurately estimate age and death affects our ability to understand past disease. By incorporating consideration of age-related disease and disease-related age into paleopathological research, alongside adopting specific methodological approaches, we will significantly improve our understanding of both past disease and past demography.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bisphenol P triggers hepatic injury via gut microbiota dysbiosis-Induced intestinal barrier disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bisphenol P (BPP), a structural analog of bisphenol A (BPA), is increasingly found in industrial and consumer products. Despite its prevalence in food and biological samples, its health risks are largely uncharacterized. This study aimed to investigate whether BPP exposure induce liver injury through a disrupted gut-liver axis, specifically via gut microbiota dysbiosis and intestinal barrier damage in mice. Mice received an oral dose of 30 μg/kg bw/day of BPP for five weeks to simulate typical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The AMPK activator A769662 promotes ferroptosis and suppresses disulfidptosis by inhibiting SLC7A11]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AMP-activated protein kinase (AMPK) plays a critical role in maintaining cellular energy homeostasis. Activation of AMPK negatively regulates ferroptosis, a form of cell death caused by iron-dependent accumulation of lipid peroxides. In the present study, we unexpectedly found that A769662, widely used as a selective AMPK activator, inhibited SLC7A11-mediated cystine uptake, thereby decreasing intracellular reduced glutathione (GSH) levels and promoting ferroptosis in glioblastoma cells....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial distributions and structural effects of endogenous and exogenous α-glucosidase enzymes in rice grains during cooking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endogenous and exogenous enzymes influence the sensory properties of cooked rice by acting on starch during gelatinization. This study elucidated the distinct spatial distributions of endogenous α-glucosidase (E-AG) and an exogenous version derived from Aspergillus niger (A-AG) during cooking. The E-AG, A-AG, and water distributions in rice grains were visualized. E-AG was distributed throughout the raw grain, whereas A-AG was localized around starch granules, amyloplasts, and cell walls,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41707261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Propagation of the Madden-Julian oscillation as a deterministic chaotic phenomenon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Madden-Julian oscillation (MJO) is a planetary-scale tropical weather disturbance marked by eastward-propagating cumulus cloud clusters over the Indo-Pacific region, causing severe weather and climate events worldwide. The mechanism and predictability of MJO propagation remain elusive, partly because relevant multiscale processes are poorly understood. Here, we reveal chaotic MJO propagation arising from cross-scale nonlinear interactions, based on 4000-member ensemble simulations of two MJO...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ocular manifestations of Clade Ib mpox in four South-Kivu health zones, Democratic Republic of the Congo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With several international outbreaks ongoing, mpox-related eye disease is increasingly detected, yet data on its prevalence remain limited. We conducted a descriptive cross-sectional study in four health zones in South-Kivu Province, Democratic Republic of the Congo, between November 1, 2024 and January 31, 2025, to describe the clinical features of mpox-related ophthalmic disease in hospitalized patients during the ongoing clade Ib outbreak. Routine ophthalmic examination was performed in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coherence evaluation and first demonstration of multi-contrast X-ray computed tomography on NanoTerasu BL09W with an X-ray Talbot interferometer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report on the coherence evaluation of the beamline BL09W at NanoTerasu (Tohoku University, Japan) and demonstrate X-ray multi-contrast imaging using an X-ray Talbot interferometer. Fringe visibility was measured in both the horizontal and vertical directions and analyzed to estimate the effective source size of the X-ray beam. The estimated source size in the horizontal direction was consistent with the design specification, confirming the validity of the measurements. In the vertical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-uniform interval-pulse X-ray photon correlation spectroscopy for reduced exposure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[X-ray photon correlation spectroscopy (XPCS) is a powerful technique for evaluating microscopic dynamics using coherent X-rays. Detecting fast or small-scale dynamics typically requires strong illumination and wide-angle scattering detection; however, such conditions can cause non-negligible sample damage. This study presents a non-uniform pulse-interval XPCS approach that enables quantitative dynamical analysis with substantially reduced X-ray exposure. In conventional XPCS, continuous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling β-sheet breaker peptides across multiple resolutions: from neurological targets to liposomal membranes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[β-Sheet-breaker peptides can destabilize protein aggregates associated with neurological disorders, thereby interfering with fibril formation. Given the pivotal role of misfolded protein oligomers such as amyloid-β and α-synuclein in Alzheimer's and Parkinson's diseases, respectively, strategies that block β-sheet formation or perturb β-sheet-rich interactions are promising therapeutic approaches to mitigate neurotoxicity and slow disease progression. However, cross-applicability of inhibitor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inducible kidney-selective knockdown of Cyp27b1 does not compromise calcium and bone homeostasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking crossover and recovery in eating disorders through a dynamic and value-sensitive framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptomic insights into the role of CmLec4 in infection and development of Cordyceps militaris]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Entomopathogenic fungi are a diverse group of ascomycetes that infect insects and form fruiting bodies, with over 1,000 species reported globally. Among them, Cordyceps militaris has long been valued in East Asia as a traditional medicinal resource, reflecting its recognized pharmacological potential. However, the molecular basis of host recognition and infection in this species remains poorly understood. Our previous work identified a novel chitin-binding lectin, CmLec4, in C. militaris, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preoperative albumin grip index as a novel biomarker predicting prognosis and postoperative complications after gastrectomy for gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metagenomic analysis of the intragastric and oral microbiome associated with gastric carcinogenesis after Helicobacter pylori eradication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Involvement of Membranous S100A10 Expression in the Tumor Budding of Colorectal Cancer: An Immunohistochemical Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing surgical strategies for ruptured vertebral artery dissecting aneurysms: experience with perforator bypass and hyperacute management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ruptured vertebral artery dissecting aneurysms (rVADAs) are life-threatening lesions with a high risk of rebleeding and brainstem infarction. This study describes our institutional experience with open surgical management of rVADAs, with a focus on perforator bypass strategies. We retrospectively analyzed 17 patients with rVADAs treated surgically between 2012 and 2025. Clinical data, imaging characteristics, surgical details, and outcomes were reviewed. Special attention was given to cases with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Midbrain length by the one-line method predicts motor outcome after deep brain stimulation in Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We showed that midbrain size evaluated using the One-Line Method was a good predictor of the motor outcome after STN-DBS, but volume measured using FreeSurfer was not. The One-Line Method was considered to detect changes in size specifically in the midbrain tegmentum, which is associated with PD motor symptoms. Thus, we present a simple and useful method for predicting poor outcomes after STN-DBS treatment in patients with PD with disease progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can single reference density functional theory methods describe spin state crossing for 3d transition metal carbon monoxide association?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The bonding between a transition metal (TM) and carbon monoxide is found in many chemical complexes that are important in biological and catalytic processes. Density functional theory (DFT) methods have been widely used for many calculations; however, the validity of such calculations for complex spin state coupling induced by TM-CO bond formation remains unclear. Interestingly, binding between a 3d TM atom and carbon monoxide induces a spin state change, making it a good benchmark system for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative pleurodesis using OK-432 for pulmonary air leak in lung cancer patients with idiopathic interstitial pneumonia: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: There were no treatment-related deaths following OK-432 pleurodesis in IIP patients; however, IIP remained a significant risk factor for pleurodesis-related complications, particularly pneumonia. Early intervention and elevated WBC levels may increase the complication risk. Delaying pleurodesis until the WBC count normalizes is advisable to reduce adverse events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aqueous dispersion of carbon nanotubes by chlorine dioxide oxidation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The poor solubility and dispersibility of single-walled carbon nanotubes (SWCNTs) in aqueous media remain critical limitations for their practical application because conventional oxidative treatments typically require harsh conditions that degrade the nanotube structure. Here, we report a simple and scalable method for dispersing SWCNTs in water via chlorine dioxide (ClO(2)˙)-mediated oxidation under ambient conditions. The treatment selectively introduced oxygenated functionalities-including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Metabolic Bariatric Surgery on Weight Loss and Glycemic Control in Adults With Type 1 Diabetes: A Multicenter Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MBS was associated with substantial metabolic improvement in people with T1D and obesity, in particular in those with high HbA1c and insulin need at baseline.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational investigation of acetylene hydrogenation to ethylene over transition metal-exchanged chabazite zeolites: mechanistic insights and descriptor-based predictions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The selective hydrogenation of acetylene to ethylene is a key reaction for producing polymer-grade ethylene in industrial processes. We study the efficiency of transition metals (Fe, Co, Ni, Cu, and Zn) confined in a chabazite (CHA) zeolite for the selective hydrogenation of acetylene to ethylene using density functional theory (DFT) calculations with the M06-L functional. The proposed reaction mechanism involves H(2) dissociation, followed by the formation of an ethenyl intermediate and its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41706020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A reprogrammed genetic code consisting of 32 distinct amino acids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sense codon reassignment enables ribosomal incorporation of nonproteinogenic amino acids (npAAs) at any of the 61 sense codons. Because npAAs replace proteinogenic amino acids (pAAs), the total number of available building blocks usually remains limited to 20. To overcome this, we previously introduced "artificial codon box division", where four-codon boxes (e.g. Val GUN) are split into distinct sets (e.g. GUY and GUG) using in vitro transcribed transfer RNAs (tRNAs) lacking nucleotide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suppressed Photoluminescence Blinking and Enhanced Stability in Ligand-Engineered Pure Blue-Emitting Perovskite Nanocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-halide perovskites have emerged as a promising light-emitting material, yet achieving efficient and stable blue emission remains a challenge. Moreover, colloidal nanocrystals (CNCs) synthesized via the hot-injection method lose much of their emission quality upon film formation. In this work, we present a one-step spin-coating strategy to grow blue-emitting cube-like CsPb(Cl/Br)(3) nanocrystals (NCs) directly on a substrate. We achieve this by synergistically integrating sterically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of p16-positive stromal cells in age-related cardiac disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The heart undergoes structural alterations, including fibrosis and cardiomyocyte hypertrophy with age. These alterations are accompanied by functional decline, resulting in heart failure. Although cardiac stromal cells such as fibroblasts and macrophages are known to play a role in age-related cardiac changes, specific subsets of these cells may have a more pronounced effect on the development of these alterations. In this study, we analyzed p16, a marker of senescence,-positive (p16+) cells in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concentration-QTc Analysis as an Alternative to TQT Studies: Findings From QT Evaluation and Safety Labeling Decisions in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thorough QT (TQT) studies have long been the regulatory gold standard for evaluating QT prolongation risk. With the implementation of the ICH E14 Q&A updates, various alternatives to TQT studies, referred to as QT pathways, have gained attention. However, it remains unclear whether concentration-QTc (C-QTc) analysis or other QT pathways carry the same regulatory weight as TQT studies, particularly when making safety labeling decisions. To address this issue, we investigated the relationship...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Förster resonance energy transfer-based anion-responsive nanoemulsion optodes: the importance of fluorescent dye liquid lipophilicity and ionophore-dye interaction for stable and background-free anion response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we fabricated and evaluated a highly sensitive Förster Resonance Energy Transfer (FRET)-based anion-responsive nanoemulsion optode (FRET-NE optode) using an originally developed lipophilic fluorescent dye liquid. When the donor (D) dye liquid, designed and synthesized for a previously developed poly(vinyl) chloride (PVC) film optode, was directly applied to the NE optode, it was found that the D dye liquid leaked into the aqueous phase upon anion response due to insufficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unravelling Voriconazole's Hepatic Metabolism: A Narrative Review on Factors Impacting Voriconazole-N-Oxide Exposure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: VRC dose, CRP, age and CYP2C19 genotype are the primary covariates affecting NOX or MR, and renal and liver function should also be considered in future population pharmacokinetic models and TDM protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colorless and Transparent Semialicyclic Polyimide Aerogels with Mechanical Durability for Thermal Insulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Visible-light transparency, low thermal conductivity, and high mechanical resistance are important properties for aerogel insulators. Achieving these properties in a single aerogel, however, is a significant challenge. While aromatic polyimide aerogels are known to demonstrate high mechanical resistance, improving both visible-light transparency and thermal insulation remains a challenge. Herein, we present colorless and transparent aerogels with low thermal conductivity and high mechanical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction and inter-species transmission dynamics of high pathogenicity avian influenza H5N1 viruses in Japan 2021-25]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High pathogenicity avian influenza virus impacts poultry and wild birds worldwide. Since the introduction of clade 2.3.4.4b H5N1 isolates in Japan in late 2021, new cases have been reported in domestic birds and poultry each winter. To understand the role of wild birds in introducing these viruses in Japan, a phylodynamic analysis based on geography and host species was conducted using H5N1 isolates in Japan from 2021 to 2025. A total of 892 hemagglutinin gene sequences of H5N1 viruses,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Machine Learning Applications in Lung Transplantation: A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lung transplantation (LTx) offers life-saving therapy for patients with end-stage lung disease but remains limited by donor shortages, complex postoperative management and graft failure. Machine learning (ML) enables opportunities to address these challenges by identifying patterns in complex, high-dimensional data, thereby providing novel insights and improving outcomes. This review outlines ML studies in LTx and explains the methodologies. ML has demonstrated promising results in organ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case report of J wave syndrome with abnormal potentials in both right and left ventricles and reversed J wave in lead V1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Abnormal epicardial potentials in J wave syndrome predominantly involve the right ventricular outflow tract (RVOT), while left ventricular (LV) involvement remains less characterized and associates with increased ventricular fibrillation (VF) risk. We report a case demonstrating an inverted J wave in lead V1, suggesting LV posterior wall substrate rather than typical RVOT involvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety, immunogenicity, and optimal dosing of VLPCOV-02, a SARS-CoV-2 saRNA vaccine with modified 5-methylcytosine base]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Variant-adapted vaccines are becoming increasingly important for continued COVID-19 prevention. Part 1 of the phase 1/2 study with VLPCOV-02, a lipid nanoparticle-encapsulated, self-amplifying RNA (saRNA) vaccine with a modified 5-methylcytosine (5 mC) base, demonstrated lower reactogenicity and incidence of adverse events, and induction of antibody responses. We report results of part 2 with an expanded number of participants (N = 323 [3 μg VLPCOV-02: 53 non-elderly and 54 elderly; 7.5 μg...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary intake characteristics in older adults: A systematic review of physical, social, psychological, and behavioral limitations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Older individuals generally have decreased food intake owing to physical, social, psychological, and behavioral limitations. However, the characteristics of food and nutrient intake resulting from these limitations are poorly organized. Organizing knowledge for practical application in older adults is necessary when considering nutrition care strategies. This review aimed to characterize food and nutrient intake according to these exposure factors in older individuals. This systematic review...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Voice Conversion System from Electrolarynx Speech to Preoperative Patient's Speech for Total Laryngectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Laryngectomy is a life-changing procedure typically performed as a surgical treatment for patients with head and neck cancer. Voice conversion (VC) is a technology that converts one voice into another without changing the linguistic information. Recently, "Save the Voice Project" for patients planning to undergo laryngectomy using our VC technique has been initiated. This study evaluated the speech converted from EL speech using the VC technique in a patient with head and neck cancer who had...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enthalpy-Entropy Trade-Off Underlies Geometric Isomer Selectivity in Histamine H<sub>1</sub> Receptor-Doxepin Interaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the thermodynamic basis of ligand recognition by G-protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs) is crucial for rational drug design. Here, we directly characterized the binding thermodynamics of the histamine H(1) receptor (H(1)R) interacting with the geometric isomers of doxepin using isothermal titration calorimetry combined with molecular dynamics (MD) simulations. The Z-isomer binding to H(1)R_WT exhibited a larger enthalpic gain but a greater entropic loss than the E-isomer, whereas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of the particle size of wheat bran inclusions in feed on the precaecal gastrointestinal tract fibre particle size distribution, caecal digesta particle size and caecal fibre fermentation in young and growing broilers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Including additional dietary fibre fractions in broiler feed has gained renewed interest due to its potential for stimulating (gut) health and performance. The beneficial effects of fibre are mainly due to its fermentation in the caecal lobes, but the influx of digesta into these lobes seems restricted to small particles and solubles. To boost caecal fermentation via fibre inclusions, more knowledge on how fibre particle size in feed can affect the fibre particle size distribution along the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between climate change awareness-related psychological distress and mental health in people with psychiatric diagnoses or subclinical symptoms: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of arginine-enriched enteral nutrition on clinical outcomes with infectious events and muscle volume in critically ill patients: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Arginine-enriched EN may not exert beneficial effects on the incidence of infection or other outcomes. However, because no studies have examined the administration of arginine alone and few RCTs investigated physical outcomes, such as muscle volume and physical function, further research is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revealing the biological and genomic characteristics of Escherichia coli phages and their application in reducing biofilm formation and bacterial counts in contaminated meat]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The meat industry is often confronted with bacterial contamination, particularly Escherichia coli (E. coli), which compromises food safety and poses significant public health risks. Conventional treatments for bacterial contamination can lead to undesirable outcomes, highlighting the need for alternative strategies. In this study, we characterized E. coli phages, including their genomic features to evaluate their safety, and assessed their potential as biocontrol agents for controlling E. coli...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does compassion affect shame emotions and mental health in individuals with ASD traits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The continuous net benefit: assessing the clinical utility of prediction models when informing a continuum of decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The magnitude of multimorbidity in childhood: a global systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Childhood multimorbidity poses significant health and social challenges, necessitating integrated care approaches and standardized definitions for cross-study comparability. Preventive strategies targeting social determinants and early-life interventions are crucial to mitigate its long-term burden. Future research should focus on longitudinal studies to explore progression and inform targeted interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comment on 'Muscle-Specific Strength Better Predicts Physical Performance Decline Than Conventional Metrics: The I-Lan Longitudinal Aging Study' by Chien et al.-The Authors Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporally Defined Brain Network Activation Associated With Slowed Information Processing Speed in Multiple Sclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Information processing speed (IPS) is a core cognitive deficit in people with multiple sclerosis (PwMS). Previous efforts have associated IPS performance to frontal regions, but were constrained by limited temporal resolution. In this work, we employed a data-driven method, the time delay embedded-hidden Markov model (TDE-HMM), to identify task-specific states that are spectrally defined with distinct temporal and spatial profiles. We used magnetoencephalographic (MEG) data recorded while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Loop electrosurgical excision procedure and perinatal outcomes post-human papillomavirus cervical screening: A longitudinal cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among HPV-screened women, the risks of PTB and LBW were not statistically significantly associated with LEEP. HPV-based screening might lead to more treatments than cytology-based screening, yet the overall risks of PTB and LBW remained similar across groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Growing Physician Shortage: The Role of Non-US Citizen International Medical Graduates in the Physician Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revealing actinobacterial diversity inhabiting Malaysian Beach Ridges Interspersed with Swales (BRIS) soil : insights from culture-dependent and metagenomic approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure and mechanism of antiphage retron Eco2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retrons are prokaryotic reverse transcriptase systems that produce multicopy single-stranded DNA (msDNA), yet the principles by which they mediate antiviral defense remain largely unresolved. Here we investigate the mechanism of Escherichia coli Eco2, a minimal retron composed of a single reverse transcriptase-nuclease fusion protein. Cryogenic electron microscopy and hydrogen/deuterium exchange mass spectrometry reveal the structures and dynamics of a trimeric nucleoprotein complex assembled...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasonic, Clinical, and Pathological Characteristics of Malignant Ovarian Tumors in Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Childhood malignant ovarian tumors are predominantly germ cell tumors, manifesting as large, solid-predominant, calcified lesions with high-risk ultrasound features. Ultrasonic, clinical, and laboratory features vary significantly by pathological type. Integrating these characteristics (including O-RADS and tumor markers) enables preoperative pathological diagnosis, supporting early multi-dimensional and personalized management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generalist vs. specialist: cognition and behavioral flexibility in Gambusia across habitats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The International Scientific Association for Probiotics and Prebiotics (ISAPP) consensus statement on the definition and scope of gut health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The term 'gut health' is increasingly used as a catch-all phrase by many stakeholders, including scientists, health-care professionals, industry and the general public, to describe a wide range of health-related concepts. Despite its widespread use, particularly in relation to studies on diet, fermented foods, biotics and the gut microbiome, it remains unclear what the term gut health means. Therefore, an expert panel was convened by the International Scientific Association for Probiotics and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing intermediate-scale bioreactors for next-generation macrophage production and application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macrophages are crucial in immune responses, tissue repair and homeostasis, making them prime candidates for translational applications. Induced pluripotent stem cell (iPS cell)-derived macrophages hold considerable promise for regenerative medicine, cancer therapy, inflammatory disease treatment and in vitro bioassays. However, cost-effective, standardized intermediate-scale bioreactor systems tailored for early-stage research and drug discovery in academia remain limited. Here, we present an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41709011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex-dependent developmental changes in behavior, brain structure, functional connectivity, and sensory perception following exposure to psilocybin during adolescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Psilocybin is a hallucinogen with complex neurobiological and behavioral effects. Underlying these effects are changes in brain neuroplasticity. We hypothesized psilocybin given during adolescence, a time of heightened neuroplasticity, particularly in the forebrain, would affect emotional behavior and the associated underlying neuroanatomy, neurocircuitry, and epigenetics. Female and male mice were given vehicle or 3.0 mg/kg psilocybin every other day by oral gavage from postnatal days 40-50 for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative multi-omics defines melanoma drug response networks and ARID1A-dependent resistance mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Resistance to BRAF/MAPK inhibitors is a significant challenge in melanoma treatment, driven by adaptive and acquired mechanisms allowing tumor cells to evade therapy. We explored early signaling responses to BRAF and MAPK inhibition in a BRAFV600E-sensitive melanoma cell line and a drug-resistant ARID1A-knockout (KO) derivative. ARID1A, frequently mutated in melanoma, is linked to resistance and immune evasion. Through an innovative systems biology approach integrating multi-omics datasets, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Targeting thymine DNA glycosylase induces synthetic lethality in p53-deficient cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNA-peptide-DNA together from the beginning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Body mass index and activities of daily living impairment: systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Both underweight and obesity have been linked to increased risk of disability, yet evidence on the relationship between body mass index (BMI) and activities of daily living (ADL) impairment remains inconsistent. To examine these associations in adults, we conducted this systematic review and meta-analysis following the standard methods and reported according to the Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses (PRISMA) 2020 guidelines. Six databases were searched from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature thresholds of extreme heat-induced yield loss in maize and soybean reveal geographic heterogeneity across the Northern Hemisphere]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exposure to extreme high temperatures is a major constraint on global crop productivity, yet most large-scale assessments rely on fixed temperature thresholds that overlook regional variation in genetics, environment and management. Consequently, the temperature thresholds at which heat exposure begins to cause substantial yield loss and their spatial variability remain unclear. Here we compiled subnational yield census over Northern Hemisphere (20° N-55° N) and analysed the extreme degree days...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primary contact physiotherapy versus standard emergency physician care in the emergency department: a Time-Driven Activity-Based Costing analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study is a first step towards a better understanding of the costs incurred by the Canadian Public Payer for the management of persons presenting with musculoskeletal disorders in the ED using different care models. In EDs, physiotherapists may have the potential to help manage persons presenting with a musculoskeletal disorder without significantly increasing healthcare costs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Keeping kids engaged: the effects of superimposed single-line cartoons on pattern reversal VEPs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The effect of cartoon overlays on the P100 component of adult prVEPs is small, albeit statistically significant. The effects likely reflect subtle influences of attention and adaptation rather than eye movements. These findings support the use of a single-line cartoon in pediatric testing to enhance engagement and response reliability without compromising clinical interpretation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-based semantic matching of cis-regulatory DNA sequences facilitates the prediction of gene function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rich information encoded in cis-regulatory DNA sequences has not been fully exploited for gene function prediction in reverse genetics. Here we show that orthologous cis-regulatory sequences that diverged approximately 160 million years ago share little sequence similarity, yet remarkably retain semantic similarity that can be effectively captured by a deep learning model, PhytoBabel. Although trained solely on orthologous cis-regulatory sequence pairs from 15 angiosperms, PhytoBabel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to: 'Comment on: 'Incidence and prevalence of mucous membrane pemphigoid with ocular involvement: a retrospective analysis using the TriNetX database"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41708913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260219030213&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>