<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:20:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Flatfoot Management with foot orthoses: A Systemic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings strongly support insoles as an effective conservative treatment for flexible flatfoot and underscore the need to incorporate clinical, biomechanical, and radiographic outcomes in future research to optimize management strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermally Drawn Multifunctional All-Hydrogel Fibers for Anti-Fibrotic and Multimodal Neural Interfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogels have emerged as promising materials for anti-fibrotic neural interfaces due to their mechanical and chemical similarity to biological tissue. However, their use in multimodal platforms remains limited, owing to fabrication challenges in microstructuring multiple functional hydrogels into compact architectures. Here, a hydrogel thermal drawing process (HG-TDP) is presented that enables the co-fabrication of multiple thermoplastically deformable hydrogels into a single, compact, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Active Learning-Guided Accelerated Discovery of Ultra-Efficient High-Entropy Thermoelectrics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-entropy alloys are emerging as highly efficient thermoelectrics, but their vast compositional spaces hinder efficient material discovery using conventional heuristics-based and advanced machine learning approaches. Here, this fundamental challenge is addressed by demonstrating an active learning framework that leverages sparse experimental data (80 out of 16206) to efficiently identify three new high-entropy chalcogenides (HECs) with remarkable thermoelectric performance (zT >2). By...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of P-doping on CO<sub>2</sub>-Derived Porous Carbon for the Cathode of Lithium-Sulfur Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To address the sluggish redox kinetics and the polysulfide shuttle effect in lithium-sulfur (Li-S) batteries, phosphorus-doped CO(2)-derived carbon (PCDC) was developed to improve their electrochemical performance. The carbon scaffold was derived from CO(2) reduction through sodium borohydride (NaBH(4)), enabling the simultaneous incorporation of boron and oxygen. This eco-friendly strategy converts CO(2) into a hierarchically porous structure with the phosphoric acid treatment. The resulting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chronic stress impairs autoinhibition in neurons of the locus coeruleus to increase asparagine endopeptidase activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Impairments of locus coeruleus (LC) are implicated in anxiety/depression and Alzheimer's disease (AD). Increases in cytosolic noradrenaline (NA) concentration and monoamine oxidase A (MAO-A) activity initiate the LC impairment through production of NA metabolite, 3,4-dihydroxyphenyl-glycolaldehyde (DOPEGAL), by MAO-A. However, how NA accumulates in soma/dendritic cytosol of LC neurons has never been addressed despite the fact that NA is virtually absent in cytosol while NA is produced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Impact of Early Graft Function on Kidney Transplantation Outcomes According to Donor Types]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The impact of impaired EGF varies by donor type. In living donor KTRs, impaired EGF increased the risks of BPAR and DCGF, particularly in cases of DGF. In deceased donor KTRs, impaired EGF elevated the risks of DCGF and mortality but not BPAR, highlighting the need for tailored strategies to optimize EGF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical perspective on targeted alpha therapy using <sup>225</sup>Ac]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[^(225)Ac targeted alpha therapy is characterized by high linear energy transfer (LET) and short range, which has demonstrated outstanding therapeutic effects and minimal adverse effects in the treatment of prostate cancer and neuroendocrine tumor. This review paper aims to summarize the research conducted to date on ^(225)Ac targeted alpha therapy applied to the treatment of patients with prostate cancer and neuroendocrine tumor. Efforts has been made to improve the therapeutic outcomes of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of cardiac autonomic dysfunction between apnea-predominant and hypopnea-predominant obstructive sleep apnea: a study matched for age, sex, and apnea-hypopnea index : Short running title: cardiovascular risk of apnea vs. hypopnea in OSA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Description of Tateyamaria algicola sp. nov. and Tateyamaria rhodophyticola sp. nov., Isolated from Marine Algae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two aerobic, non-motile, Gram-stain-negative strains, designated SN3-11ᵀ and SN6-1ᵀ, were isolated from marine algae. Both strains were oxidase- and catalase-positive, with rod-shaped morphology. Strain SN3-11ᵀ grew optimally at 25 ℃, pH 7.0-8.0, and 2.0-5.0% (w/v) NaCl, while strain SN6-1ᵀ showed optimal growth at 25 ℃, pH 8.0, and 2.0-3.0% NaCl. Both strains contained ubiquinone-10 as the sole respiratory quinone, and their major fatty acids were summed feature 8 (C(18:1) ω7c and/or C(18:1)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and Characteristics of Psychiatric Disorders in Adolescent and Young Adult Patients with Malignant Brain Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose: Adolescents and young adults (AYAs) with brain tumors are at an increased risk of developing psychiatric disorders. We aimed to investigate the incidence and characteristics of psychiatric disorders in AYA patients with brain tumors. Methods: Using the Korean Classification of Diseases, we identified a cohort of AYA patients (aged 15-34 years) diagnosed with malignant brain neoplasms (C71) between 2003 and 2016 from the Korean National Health Insurance Claims Database. The analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical Differentiation of Presbyopia-Correcting Intraocular Lenses With Improved Intermediate Vision From a Single Manufacturer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although all lenses performed well at distance, differences in intermediate vision, pupil dependency, and photic phenomena highlight the importance of individualized IOL selection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for morbidity in both donor and recipient following minimally invasive donor hepatectomy: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Risk factors for donor and recipient morbidity after MIDH include anatomical, operative, procedural, donor, and recipient factors. Notably, biliary variation of graft is key contributor for both donor and recipient morbidity. Given the limited studies on risk factors, multicenter studies with larger sample sizes are essential to validate these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of robotic liver resection compared with laparoscopic and open liver resection for hepatocellular carcinoma: a network meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This network meta-analysis suggests that RLR is a feasible surgical treatment option for HCC, offering perioperative and long-term outcomes comparable to LLR, with reduced postoperative morbidity and shorter hospital stays compared to OLR. However, further studies are needed to confirm RLR's efficacy due to its limited sample size.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A proof-of-concept study on an injectable artificial ovary using a xenogeneic ECM for fertility restoration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of artificial ovaries presents a promising strategy for patients facing infertility due to chemotherapy or high metastatic potential cancers, where conventional ovarian tissue transplantation poses significant risks. Our study introduces an "injectable artificial ovary" leveraging a xenogeneic extracellular matrix (ECM) hydrogel derived from bovine ovarian tissue. The ECM hydrogel obtained from bovine ovaries and prepared through decellularization, milling, and digestion is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating surface-guided radiation therapy and continuous positive airway pressure for breast cancer: Improving reproducibility and efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SGRT effectively minimized displacement-related uncertainties during breast cancer radiation therapy with and without CPAP. Although CPAP provides additional internal stabilization and its integration with SGRT increased treatment delivery time variability, the total treatment time remained comparable across all groups. These findings underscore the potential of SGRT and CPAP as complementary tools to enhance precision and safety, particularly for techniques requiring high...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tongue-Strengthening Exercise in Older Adults With Sarcopenic Dysphagia: A Randomised Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TSE with an intensity of 80% 1RM was more effective than 50% 1RM in increasing tongue strength and thickness in older adults with sarcopenic dysphagia, but showed a relatively high dropout rate. Thus, it is recommended to select and apply an appropriate exercise intensity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Antiplatelet Therapy After Endovascular Aortic Repair: A Target Trial Emulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients without atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease undergoing standard EVAR, DAPT did not confer cardiovascular or procedural benefit but was associated with increased bleeding. Single antiplatelet therapy may represent a safer and equally effective antiplatelet strategy in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[scHDeepInsight: a hierarchical deep learning framework for precise immune cell annotation in single-cell RNA-seq data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate classification of immune cells is crucial for elucidating their diverse roles in health and disease. However, this task remains very challenging in single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq) data due to the complex and hierarchical relationships of immune cell types. To address this, we introduce scHDeepInsight, a deep learning framework that extends our previous scDeepInsight model by integrating a biologically-informed classification architecture with an adaptive hierarchical focal loss...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Balancing Public Health and Privacy: South Korea's Infectious Disease Laws Post-MERS and COVID-19]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates South Korea's legislative amendments related to infectious disease after the 2015 Middle East respiratory syndrome (MERS) outbreak and how they were applied during the COVID-19 pandemic. A significant legal case after the 2015 MERS outbreak highlighted the government's liability due to inadequate response, which led to amendments in the Infectious Disease Control and Prevention Act. Key revisions included changes to epidemiological investigations, information disclosure, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alpha-relaxation by scattering and medium-range atomic correlation in simple liquids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The relaxation dynamics of liquid and glass can be studied by inelastic x-ray or neutron scattering through the intermediate scattering function F(Q, t), where Q is the momentum transfer of scattering. Because of the time-consuming nature of these measurements, F(Q, t) is usually measured only at the first peak of the structure function S(Q), and its principal decay time is referred to as the α-relaxation time τα. τα is generally considered to describe the relaxation time of the bulk, which is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modular Synthesis of Pyritide-Inspired Macrocycles Featuring Bipyridine Motifs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macrocycles represent a promising class of drug-like scaffolds with unique structural features and the ability to engage challenging targets such as protein-protein interactions. Inspired by structural characteristics of pyritides, we constructed a library of 27 diverse macrocycles via a build/couple/pair approach, enabled by efficient synthesis of bipyridine-based triaryl building blocks through azaindole cleavage. Kinetic and cheminformatic analyses confirmed both reactivity trends and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrochemical Dehydrogenation of Piperazine on Pd-Based Multimetallic Alloy Catalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen, an essential clean energy carrier, poses challenges in terms of efficient and scalable storage. Liquid organic hydrogen carriers (LOHCs) have gained attention as viable chemical media for hydrogen storage and release, providing advantages such as high energy density and compatibility with zero-emission fuel cells. Nevertheless, a critical bottleneck is the development of cost-effective and stable electrocatalysts for LOHC dehydrogenation, particularly using noble metal catalysts such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sorghum crops classification and segmentation using shifted window transformer neural network and localization based on (YOLO)v9-path aggregation network]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The world's population has been increasing continuously, and this requires prompt action to ensure food security. One of the top five cereals produced worldwide, sorghum, is a staple of the diets of many developing nations. For this reason,getting accurate information is crucial to raising cereal productivity. The quantity of crop heads arranged in various branching configurations can be used as an indicator to estimate the yields of sorghum. For various crops, computerized methods...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fascicular Injury in True Neurogenic Thoracic Outlet Syndrome Associated with Manual and Shockwave Therapies: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[True neurogenic thoracic outlet syndrome (nTOS) is a rare condition resulting from brachial plexus compression, frequently associated with congenital anomalies such as cervical ribs or fibrous bands. We report a unique case of nTOS involving both a cervical rib and fibrous band, complicated by an incidental intraoperative finding of a fascicular rupture in the lower part of lower trunk. Notably, the patient had no history of trauma but had undergone multiple sessions of manual therapy and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcome of Rifabutin-based Treatment for Pulmonary Tuberculosis in Solid Organ Transplant Recipients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Rifabutin-based therapy in SOTRs achieved treatment outcomes comparable to rifampin-based regimens in non-SOTRs, supporting its use in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uneasy (Intractable) Head and Neck Defect Coverage With Easy and Reliable Local Flap Techniques: A Retrospective Case-Based Study of Perforator-Plus Peninsular Flap and Modified Keystone Flap]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PPPF and MKF offer reliable solutions for uneasy head and neck defects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of serum complement C3 level with disease severity in primary pterygium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lower serum C3 levels were associated with advanced stromal opacification in pterygium, indicating possible complement activation in severe disease. While ANA was frequently positive, it did not correlate with clinical severity. These findings suggest that complement C3 may serve as a potential biomarker for advanced pterygium.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Efficacy of IL-12/23 and IL-23 Inhibitors for Induction and Maintenance Therapy in Moderate-to-Severe Crohn's Disease: A Systematic Review and Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that guselkumab may be a potential first-line therapy for patients presenting with predominant clinical symptoms, offering the additional benefit of reducing corticosteroid use and its associated long-term risks. Conversely, mirikizumab may be the preferred option for patients with persistent mucosal inflammation, owing to its superior efficacy in achieving endoscopic remission.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serological surveillance of <em>Trypanosoma evansi</em> in Kazakhstani camels by complement fixation and formalin gel tests]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Surra, caused by Trypanosoma evansi (T. evansi), is a significant vector-borne disease of camels that leads to substantial economic losses in affected regions. This study was conducted to determine the seroprevalence of surra among dromedary (Camelus dromedarius) and Bactrian (Camelus bactrianus) camels in Kazakhstan.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential benefits of internet-based behavioral activation (iBA) for adolescents with high vs. low reward probability: a secondary analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Behavioral activation (BA) therapy is effective in treating depression in both adults and adolescents, and internet-based BA (iBA) therapy showed promise during the COVID-19 pandemic. Adolescents with depression often exhibit motivational impairment, which is associated with reduced motivation and engagement in rewarding activities as well as a heightened risk of problematic internet use. This study examined the differential benefits of iBA in alleviating depressive symptoms in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Evolving Role of Imaging in Hepatocellular Carcinoma: From Pathomolecular Profiling to Prognostic Decision-Making]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC), which represents the most common type of primary liver cancer, is increasingly perceived as a complex ecosystem with marked spatial and temporal heterogeneity as well as varied sensitivities to treatment. Recent revolutions in the management of HCC, particularly the introduction of several immune checkpoint inhibitor-based regimens, are placing pressing needs on more tailored imaging-aided prognostic decision-making for individualized treatment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conversion Ability of Immunotherapy in Hepatocellular Carcinoma: Insights from the International Converse Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although patients treated with AB achieved higher OR and PC rates than those treated with LENV, AC remained similarly low, highlighting a potentially worrisome UC phenomenon in real life, also with novel immunotherapy-based combinations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Curative Treatment after Immunotherapy Leads to Excellent Outcomes in Patients with Hepatocellular Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Curative treatment conversion after immunotherapy was infrequent but was associated with significantly improved survival. Care at an academic center increases the probability of receiving subsequent curative treatment and favorable outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors associated with meaning in life of patients with multiple myeloma in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this descriptive survey study, we aimed to identify factors influencing the meaning in life of patients with multiple myeloma. We recruited and analyzed 204 patients with multiple myeloma who visited the outpatient clinic or received treatment in wards at Hospital X. Data were collected from these participants using a structured questionnaire and analyzed using SPSS 21.0 through t-tests, analysis of variance, Scheffé's test, Pearson's correlation coefficient, and multiple regression analyses....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jujuboside B Induces Ferroptosis and Overcomes Radioresistance Through the PPARγ-ATF3-Gpx4 Signaling Pathway in Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Jujuboside B (JJB) is a saponin extracted from the Ziziphus jujuba var. spinose and has been reported to have anticancer effects. However, the detailed mechanism of its anti-cancer effect in non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) remains unclear. New combination therapies may be able to overcome TRAIL resistance. In this study, we found that JJB regulates the activity of PPARγ and investigated whether the combination of JJB and TRAIL had synergistic anti-cancer effects against NSCLC cells....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Independent associations between obesity, glucose metabolism, and breast cancer risk through unrelated pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although BMI and WC are robustly linked to BC risk, FBG plays a negligible mediating role. These findings suggest that obesity and glucose metabolism independently influence breast cancer risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between bioelectrical impedance analysis parameters and metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease relative to handgrip strength in children and adolescents in Korea: A comparative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Combining bioelectrical impedance analyses and handgrip assessments may be beneficial for MASLD screening in youth.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterogeneity in effectiveness of conservative complementary and alternative medicine treatment for lumbar disc herniation: A latent trajectory analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Distinct outcome trajectories highlight the heterogeneity in patient responses to conservative complementary and alternative medicine-based treatments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The influences of antihistamine on liver fibrosis, vasoresponsiveness and portosystemic shunting in bile duct-ligated cirrhotic rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Levocetirizine ameliorated liver fibrosis, portal hypertension and splanchnic hyperdynamic circulation in cirrhotic rats, possibly through the down-regulation of hepatic fibrogenesis factors. Antihistamines may be a therapeutic option to control portal hypertension. However, further investigations are required to clarify its clinical application.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regional disparities and sociodemographic determinants of food insecurity in Somalia: a secondary cross-sectional analysis of a National survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Food insecurity in Somalia operates through complex, intersecting pathways of sociodemographic vulnerability and pronounced geographical inequalities. Food insecurity in Somalia results from a complex, multifaceted crisis spanning social, political, economic, and environmental domains. Effective interventions must simultaneously address educational infrastructure development, provide targeted support for vulnerable demographic groups, and implement place-based strategies that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding contrasting S<sub>2</sub> → S<sub>1</sub> internal conversion rates in boron-dipyrromethene derivatives <em>via</em> multi-configuration time-dependent hartree method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Internal conversion (IC) dynamics from higher-lying to lower electronic states following photoexcitation are often described as ultrafast, occurring in much less than 1 ps. However, IC processes can exhibit a range of time scales, depending critically on the energetic landscape of excited-state manifolds and the strength of vibronic couplings that drive nonadiabatic transitions. These dynamics play a fundamental role in most photochemical and photophysical applications. A previous time-resolved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatiotemporally Resolved Orbital Hall Effect in a Topological Semimetal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orbital angular momentum (OAM), once considered a marginal property in solids, has recently gained importance in various physical phenomena. Although optical probes couple to OAM directly, comparable low-energy electrodynamic methods are still in the early stages of development. To exploit the potential of OAM for information science and technology, angular momentum-resolved transport methods must be established. Here, a principle is presented for an angular momentum-resolved method to observe...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do Surgical Outcomes Differ Between Cervical Spondylotic Myelopathy and Ossification of the Posterior Longitudinal Ligament? A Prospective Multicenter Study of 935 Patients with Degenerative Cervical Myelopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with CSM and OPLL achieved similarly favorable outcomes after cervical spine surgery. These findings support a unified surgical strategy for DCM, emphasizing functional severity rather than pathological subtype in clinical decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of low tidal volume on dynamic arterial elastance in patients undergoing laparoscopic surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The reduction in tidal volume had a clinically negligible effect on Eadyn. Neither Eadyn values at tidal volume of 8 mL/kg PBW and 6 mL/kg PBW could not predict MAP increase after a fluid challenge during laparoscopic surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use of the tracheal bisecting line to differentiate upper pole from lower pole parathyroid adenomas: a PET/MR study using [<sup>18</sup>F]Fluorocholine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The TBL is a reliable and reproducible landmark on [^(18)F]Fluorocholine PET/MR for predicting parathyroid adenoma polarity, particularly in orthotopic and non-intrathyroidal cases. It may enhance surgical planning by improving anatomical clarity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of human histiocytic sarcoma organoids dependent on the SHH/YAP pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Histiocytic sarcoma is an extremely rare and aggressive malignant neoplasm characterized by immunophenotypic features of mature histiocytes. The mechanisms underlying its malignant transformation remain poorly understood; consequently, the development of effective therapies remains limited. Resected histiocytic sarcoma specimens were cultured using a modified air-liquid interface organoid method, serially passaged, and xenografted into NOD-scid IL2Rgnull mice. Tumors formed by xenografted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gyriform infiltration indicates tumor invasion burden of isocitrate dehydrogenase 1/2-wildtype gliomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Few robust radiological markers have been identified for predicting the molecular status of gliomas. Recently, gyriform infiltration (GI) has been identified as an imaging biomarker for molecular glioblastoma (mGBM). This study aimed to validate the diagnostic value of GI in predicting the molecular status of diffuse gliomas. Clinical data were retrospectively collected from patients treated at a single center. Their imaging findings, including GI and the status of molecular markers, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[R-spondin 3 is a myokine that mediates type I fiber determination during skeletal muscle regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This work reveals that Rspo3 as a Type I fiber specific myokine promotes Type I fiber determination during muscle regeneration in vivo.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunosuppressive Therapy for Pulmonary Arterial Hypertension Associated with Connective Tissue Diseases: Insights from Japanese Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our data suggest that early initiation of IST may be associated with hemodynamic improvement; prospective confirmation in international cohorts is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evidence-based Management of Heart Failure in the Systemic Right Ventricle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Explore the clinical progression, diagnostic challenges, and evolving treatments of systemic right ventricular (SRV) failure, highlighting key gaps and advances.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antenatal and postpartum depression among women who conceived after pregnancy loss: a longitudinal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Women who experienced repeated pregnancy loss had an elevated risk of diagnosable perinatal depression. Thus, it is crucial to consider interventions targeting pregnant women who have experienced repeated pregnancy loss to prevent perinatal depression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Membrane lipid-driven thylakoid biogenesis coordinating chlorophyll synthesis and expression of photosynthetic proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chloroplasts in seed plants differentiate from proplastids or, occasionally, from other types of plastids. The development of the thylakoid membrane (TM) is a key process in chloroplast biogenesis, enabling plants to perform photosynthesis. The TM is a lipid bilayer membrane system densely packed with photosynthetic protein-cofactor complexes, and its formation requires the coordinated synthesis of membrane lipids, photosynthetic proteins, and cofactors particularly chlorophyll. During...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High Glucocorticoid Dependency and Limited Therapeutic Response in Japanese Patients with VEXAS Syndrome: A Multicentre Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights the difficulty of treating patients with VEXAS syndrome in Japan. The development of more effective treatments is urgently needed to reduce glucocorticoid dependence and improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Description and Phylogenetic Position of <em>Thermocypris isabella</em> gen. et sp. nov. (Ostracoda: Cyprididae: Cyprinotinae) from a Hot Spring in Peru]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During a faunal survey in Baños del Inca hot spring (40-50°C), Cajamarca, Peru, we collected a cyprinotine ostracod species, the sixth example of a thermophilic ostracod inhabiting freshwater in temperatures above 40°C. Because this could not be assigned to any of nine genera in Cyprinotinae, we established the new genus Thermocypris for it and described it as Thermocypris isabella gen. et sp. nov., defined by the following combination of characters: (1) no dorsal hump on carapace, (2) no...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recurrence risk stratification by station- and zone-based nodal classification in resected non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both station- and zone-based nodal classifications effectively stratify recurrence risk and are good candidates for further N category stratification in NSCLC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Draft genome sequence of three <em>Glaciozyma watsonii</em> strains isolated from near the Syowa station area, East Antarctica]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Three strains of Glaciozyma watsonii were isolated from the Inhovde area, East Antarctica. This yeast is known as having ice-binding proteins and cold-active enzymes that are active, even at subzero temperatures. We report a draft genome sequence of these three Glaciozyma watsonii strains isolated from East Antarctica.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Artificial Intelligence-Assisted Middle Meningeal Artery Embolization Using Liquid Embolic Agents for Chronic Subdural Hematoma: A Preliminary Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: To our knowledge, this is the first study to examine MMA embolization for chronic subdural hematoma with real-time AI assistance. The system demonstrated high notification accuracy, safety, and potential clinical usefulness for liquid embolization procedures. Large-scale prospective studies are warranted to validate the impact on clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hierarchical wrinkle pattern drives tenogenic differentiation from human mesenchymal stem cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stem cells possess the unique abilities to self-renew and differentiate into various cell types, making them invaluable in tissue engineering and regenerative medicine. This study explores the behavior of human bone marrow-derived mesenchymal stem cells (hMSCs) on poly(dimethylsiloxane) (PDMS) substrates with hierarchical wrinkle patterns. These bio-inspired patterns were created using the surface instability of gold-coated elastomer bilayers. The results indicate that the hierarchical wrinkles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Cell Fluorescence Analysis of Lipid Droplet Compositional Dynamics during Triacylglycerol Catabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipid droplets (LDs) are dynamic organelles essential to lipid metabolism and energy homeostasis, yet their compositional heterogeneity in living cells remains poorly understood. Here, we present LipiPB Red, a red-emissive fluorescent probe with exceptional photostability, high polarity sensitivity, and long-term retention within LDs, even under serum-containing conditions. When applied to fluorescence lifetime imaging microscopy (FLIM), LipiPB Red enables discrimination between triacylglycerol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Critical exponents of fluid-fluid interfacial tensions near a critical endpoint in a nonwetting gap]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluid three-phase equilibria, with phases α, β, γ, are studied close to a tricritical point, analytically and numerically, in a mean-field density-functional theory with two densities. Employing Griffiths' scaling for the densities, the interfacial tensions of the wet and nonwet interfaces are analyzed. The mean-field critical exponent is obtained for the vanishing of the critical interfacial tension σβγ as a function of the deviation of the noncritical interfacial tension σαγ from its limiting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Easily Separable Racemic and Meso Isomers of a Salen-Based Cryptophane for Selective Guest Binding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A salen-based cryptophane cage was synthesized via dynamic covalent imine chemistry, affording separable meso and racemic isomers. Single-crystal X-ray analysis confirmed the structure of the racemic form. The isomers exhibited slow interconversion in solution, enabling an individual study of their properties. The racemic isomer bound quaternary ammonium guests with notable size selectivity, highlighting the potential of imine-based cryptophanes as functional hosts for molecular recognition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase Separation of RX Repeat Peptides with Nucleic Acids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biomolecular liquid-liquid phase separation (LLPS) plays a crucial role in organizing membraneless cellular compartments, which regulate a wide variety of cellular processes. A key molecular mechanism underlying LLPS of nucleic acids involves G-quadruplex (G4) structures of DNA and RNA interacting with intrinsically disordered proteins, particularly arginine and glycine (RGG/RG) rich proteins. The role of arginine residues in LLPS has been studied extensively, whereas few studies have focused on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Survey of Patient Satisfaction and Willingness to Pay for Shared Decision-Making Implemented by Pharmacists for Patients with Inflammatory Bowel Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This pilot study is the first to demonstrate that SDM by pharmacists is highly satisfactory for patients with IBD. Furthermore, many patients expressed a WTP for SDM as part of counseling. These findings support the involvement of pharmacists, alongside physicians, in the SDM process for IBD treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acetylation of lysine 49 on Ctnnb1 drives naïve pluripotency in murine stem cells by modulating Nanog function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Naïve pluripotency represents the ground state of mammalian development. A comprehensive understanding of the molecular mechanisms governing its establishment is crucial for elucidating the unique properties of embryonic cells and the regulatory mechanisms controlling cell fate determination. However, the key molecule to robustly achieve naïve pluripotency with minimal manipulation remains unclear. We found that the acetylation status of lysine 49 (K49) of Catenin beta-1 (Ctnnb1) plays a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuronal effects of epicranial current stimulation in macaque cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ECS has been used as a proxy for transcutaneous stimulation in rodent setups. Here we show that as a standalone technique it can be applied to a larger and more complex brain. This makes it a promising neuromodulation approach with clinical applications in patients who do not respond to TES but are not yet candidates for ICS or DBS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of food extraction techniques and impact of nitrogen fertilization on the potential allergenicity of soybean related to birch pollen-food allergy syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings support the feasibility of standardized extraction methods. Varying nitrogen fertilization in soybeans resulted in altered physical, proteomic, and allergenic characteristics in this pilot study. Our results highlight the need for further research on environmental influences on food allergy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tuning i-motif folding and stability with acyclic phosphonate-linked (ZNA) cytidine residues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[i-Motifs (iMs) are non-canonical four-stranded DNA structures stabilized by hemi-protonated (C:H^(+)C) cytosine base pairs. Under non-acidic pH conditions, cytosine deprotonation disrupts these interactions, resulting in structural unfolding. To broaden the environmental conditions that support iM formation for potential biomedical applications, we investigated the effect of substituting 2'-deoxycytidine residues with either the (R) or (S) isomers of an acyclic phosphonate-linked nucleotide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design, synthesis and evaluation of arylpurine-based sinefungin mimetics as zika virus methyltransferase inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Arylpurine derivatives were designed and synthesized to mimic sinefungin by targeting the SAM/SAH binding site of zika virus (ZIKV) methyltransferase (MTase). These compounds incorporate adenine or 6-methyl-7-deazapurine bases, while the ribose of sinefungin has been replaced by an aniline, linked to its amino acid chain via a CO or a CH(2) unit. Compounds 18, 29 and 31 inhibited ZIKV 2'-O-MTase activity. Docking studies showed that compounds 18 and 29 interact with both the purine and amino...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delayed-onset organizing pneumonia following perioperative COVID-19 after lobectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Delayed-onset organizing pneumonia as a manifestation of post-acute coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) syndrome has not been documented in the perioperative setting. Here, a 61-year-old man underwent left lower lobectomy complicated by persistent air leakage requiring seven pleurodesis procedures. He developed COVID-19 on postoperative Day 10 and initially recovered but was readmitted on Day 27 with fever and respiratory failure. Chest computed tomography revealed progressive consolidations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robot-Assisted Simultaneous Distal Pancreatectomy and Sigmoidectomy for Synchronous Pancreatic and Colon Tumors: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case highlights the feasibility and safety of robot-assisted simultaneous distal pancreatectomy and sigmoidectomy. While robotic multivisceral resections offer several advantages, thorough preoperative planning, surgical expertise, and appropriate patient selection remain essential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Unpacking policy developments in marine natural product research: a scientist's guide to DSI and BBNJ]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Correction for 'Unpacking policy developments in marine natural product research: a scientist's guide to DSI and BBNJ' by Federica Casolari et al., Nat. Prod. Rep., 2025, 42, 1063-1070, https://doi.org/10.1039/D4NP00070F.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The current state of our knowledge of the domestication and evolution of the grain amaranths, a critical standpoint]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sauer's hypothesis that the three grain amaranths originated from a single ancestor, and that artificial selection combined with hybridization with wild species resulted in the three grain amaranths, is corroborated by most recent authors. There is consensus that the three grain amaranths originated from Amaranthus hybridus. However, it appears that A. hybridus is polyphyletic. Only seed color is predominantly present in the literature as a symptom of the grain amaranths...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of MRI Examinations Under Sedation: A Nationwide Survey in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: MRI is performed under sedation for patients requiring immobility or for those already sedated for clinical management. Although specialist guidelines advocate for anesthesiologist-led care, non-anesthesiologist-led adult sedation is a common practice worldwide. Furthermore, the increase in risk attributable to sedation has not been quantified.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rationally Designed Solid Sorbent Electrolyte Exhibits Dual CO<sub>2</sub>/ H<sub>2</sub>O Sorption and Enables Full Gas Phase CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient CO(2) electrolysis hinges on high CO(2) availability and controlled water transport toward and away from the catalyst. Traditional methods, such as direct CO(2) supply in the gas form or using CO(2) sorbent liquid electrolytes face significant limitations. In this study, a pioneering approach is presented using a rationally designed CO(2)/H(2)O sorbent composite electrolyte, enabling low-temperature aqueous CO(2) electroreduction without liquid catholyte nor anolyte. The development of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Operando</em> Micro- and Nano-Computed Tomography Reveals Silicon-Electrolyte Interface Dynamics and Anisotropic Contact Loss in All-Solid-State Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All-solid-state batteries (ASSBs) with silicon anodes offer high energy density and mitigate issues such as continuous solid-electrolyte interphase (SEI) formation in lithium-ion batteries with liquid electrolytes. However, the evolution of the mechanical contact interface between silicon (Si) and the rigid solid electrolyte during cycling remains poorly understood. This study utilized operando synchrotron X-ray micro-computed tomography (micro-CT) and nano-computed tomography (nano-CT) to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Safety of Active Hearing Implants in the Ultra-high Field Magnetic Resonance Environment: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings show no adverse effects or performance degradation of the implant within the predefined test conditions. Preliminary outcomes of this feasibility study are positive, yet do not imply implant safety in the 7T MR environment. Formal verification will be required to label a device safe at this field strength.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Telework on Body Composition, Physical Fitness, and Physical Symptoms in Japanese Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the need for interventions to mitigate the negative impacts of telework on workers' physical fitness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Canonical translation factors eIF1A and eIF5B modulate the initiation step of repeat-associated non-AUG translation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nucleotide repeat expansions, such as the GGGGCC repeats in C9orf72, associated with C9-ALS, are linked to neurodegenerative diseases. These repeat sequences undergo a noncanonical translation known as repeat-associated non-AUG (RAN) translation. Unlike canonical translation, RAN translation initiates from non-AUG codons and occurs in all reading frames. To identify potential regulators of RAN translation, we employed a bottom-up approach using a human factor-based reconstituted cell-free...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Toward enhanced nutritional interventions in community pharmacies: personal attitude construct analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251009152048&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Syndromic and etiological classification predicts seizure freedom in childhood and youth onset epilepsy: A population-based study from the Norwegian Mother, Father, and Child Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: This study was undertaken to determine the proportion of individuals with childhood and youth onset epilepsy who attain seizure freedom across seizure types, epilepsy types, etiologies, and syndromes using the latest International League Against Epilepsy (ILAE) classifications. Secondary objectives were to identify predictors of seizure freedom, evaluate time to last seizure among those achieving it, and estimate prevalence of active epilepsy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors for Valvulopathy Among Childhood Cancer Survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION AND RELEVANCE: In this case-control study, heart RT, anthracyclines, and platinum agents were associated with increased VHD risk in childhood cancer survivors. Risks from both RT and anthracyclines were amplified with age and follow-up, underscoring the need for long-term cardiac surveillance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IGF-1R Inhibitor IBI311 for the Treatment of Active Thyroid Eye Disease in Chinese Patients: The RESTORE-1 Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this phase 3 randomized clinical trial, IBI311 demonstrated better and clinically relevant outcomes in proptosis and CAS than placebo with no new safety issues not identified in previous clinical trials. The results suggest that IBI311 represents a viable treatment option for Chinese patients with active TED.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IL-1 Receptor Antagonist Antibodies in Idiopathic Recurrent Pericarditis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chimeric RNA isoforms generated by diverse mechanisms from two C-type lectins modulate innate immunity in arthropods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimeric RNA formation represents a critical mechanism for expanding protein functional diversity, yet its role in invertebrate immune adaptation remains poorly characterized. Here, we report that two C-type lectin genes (MnLec2 and MnLec3) from distinct genomic loci in the oriental river prawn Macrobrachium nipponense undergo positionally flexible chimeric RNA formation via alternative trans-splicing and transcriptional slippage, generating 11 structurally diverse chimeric isoforms (MnLec1,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Platelets engage mast cells in a bilateral IL-33-driven feed-forward loop]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platelets amplify type 2 inflammation (T2I) through incompletely understood mechanisms. Depletion of platelets markedly attenuated mast cell (MC) activation in a model of aspirin exacerbated respiratory disease (AERD) that depends on IL-33 and cysteinyl leukotrienes (cysLTs). We demonstrate an IL-33-driven feed-forward loop between platelets and MCs. IL-33 neutralization prevented increases in cysLTs and CXCL7, a platelet activation marker, in bronchoalveolar lavage (BAL) fluid from AERD-like...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Duffy Null-Associated Absolute Neutrophil Counts and Cancer Clinical Trial Eligibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reevaluation of Enlarged Vestibular Aqueduct]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The results of this cohort study underscore the importance of periodic hearing surveillance and tailored genetic counseling for patients with EVA, offering substantial implications for prevention, management, and future gene therapy approaches. This study provides an extensive phenotypic and genotypic characterization of EVA, potentially advancing an understanding of its molecular underpinnings and clinical heterogeneity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assault on the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention-Budget Cuts, Political Control, and the Erosion of Trust]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Limitations in Quantitative Harm-Benefit Assessment in Immuno-Oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathogenic Variants, Family History, and Cumulative Risk of Breast Cancer in US Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, population-based estimates of cumulative breast cancer risk for established PVs, as informed by the CARRIERS case-control sample, varied by family history and potentially modifiable risk factors. These estimates provide guidance for identifying individuals who will most benefit from enhanced screening and prevention strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Common cold embecovirus imprinting primes broadly neutralizing antibody responses to SARS-CoV-2 S2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The S2 subunit of the severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) spike is highly conserved across coronavirus strains and therefore is a potential pan-coronavirus vaccine target. However, antibodies targeting this region are typically non-neutralizing. We report herein that S2-targeting antibodies from patients who recovered from SARS-CoV-2 infection bound only closely related sarbecovirus subgenus strains and, like most known S2 antibodies, none of these were neutralizing. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Pancreatic Cancer with Acute Pancreatitis: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with AP have a higher likelihood of PC diagnosis, especially within the first two years. Although the association decreases with time, it remains significant long term. Newly diagnosed CP, NOD, idiopathic AP may further elevate the likelihood of PC diagnosis. PC diagnosed after AP tends to occur at a younger age, more often at an earlier stage, typically in the pancreatic head.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing naming and verbal memory in bilingual epilepsy: Challenges and insights for surgical planning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Naming and verbal memory are key components of epilepsy evaluations, as impairments often reflect left temporal dysfunction, and baseline performance helps estimate postsurgical risk. The utility of naming tests in bilingual individuals with epilepsy, however, has been questioned. We examined whether naming and verbal memory performance reflects seizure laterality in bilingual adults, how bilingualism affects baseline scores, and whether bilingual factors moderate the effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between Nightmare Frequency, Nightmare Distress, and Psychopathological Problems among Chinese College Students: a Population-based Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nightmares are associated with psychopathological symptoms. This study aimed to investigate the prevalence of nightmares and heterogeneity of nightmare distress and examine the association between nightmares and mental health problems with a broader sample of Chinese college students. A total of 5,824 college students were assessed in our study. Participants completed a self-reported questionnaire to assess their nightmare frequency, nightmare distress, and a range of psychopathological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduction in anastomotic leakage by fluorescent laparoscopic resection for ultra-low rectal cancer: a propensity-matched analysis with BMI stratification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anastomotic leakage (AL) is a serious complication in colorectal surgery, particularly after laparoscopic intersphincteric resection (LsISR) for ultra-low rectal cancer. This study evaluates the effectiveness of ICG fluorescence laparoscopic (FL) resection in reducing AL and improving recovery, especially in high-BMI patients. A retrospective cohort study was conducted on patients undergoing LsISR for ultra-low rectal adenocarcinoma from January 2012 to July 2023, comparing FL (n = 133) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Disease in the Middle East and North Africa, 1990-2021: Burden, Trends, and Risk Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Cardiovascular disease (CVD) continues to exact a heavy toll across the Middle East and North Africa. We analyzed Global Burden of Disease 2021 data to characterize trends in CVD mortality, disability‑adjusted life‑years (DALYs), and incidence from 1990 to 2021, identify leading risk factors, and highlight country‑level disparities that inform policy action.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catheter Design Matters: Hemolysis and Renal Function after Pulsed Field Ablation with Balloon-in-Basket vs. Pentaspline Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The pentaspline catheter induced more hemolysis and a measurable decline in renal function. Myoglobin increases were similar in both groups and unlikely to explain the renal findings. Catheter design and energy delivery appear to shape the systemic impact profile of PFA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The spatial ventricular gradient is a non-invasive, vectorcardiographic correlate of cardiac fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SVG magnitude is correlated with CMR-derived ECV and native T1. Patients with high SVG magnitude were not observed to have a large burden of diffuse fibrosis or infiltration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Some novel causes and clinical characteristics of reversible splenial lesion syndrome- found in children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This research demonstrates some possible causes of RESLES. Patients with RESLES present with a variety of nonspecific symptoms and most of them had a good prognosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic deuterium metabolic imaging in glioblastoma at 7T]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: This study investigates the dynamic metabolic characteristics of glioblastoma (GBM) using Deuterium Metabolic Imaging (DMI) at 7 T, aiming to dynamically characterize the Warburg effect in vivo.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does public indebtedness matter in the effect of public health expenditure on human longevity in Sub-Saharan Africa countries? Evidence from dynamic panel threshold regression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The third Sustainable Development Goal (SDG) aims to enable everyone to live in good health and to promote the well-being of all. However, despite the various efforts made to achieve this goal, sub-Saharan Africa (SSA) is still characterised by low human longevity. To increase longevity, authors have stressed the importance of public spending on health. However, continuous borrowing and servicing of public debt deprive the SSA of funds that could be devoted to public spending on health. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the impact of various zwitterionic surface modifications on the mucus diffusion and membrane permeability of lipid-based nanocarriers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the effect of structural differences among six zwitterionic surfactants on the performance of lipid-based nanoemulsions. Nanoemulsions were prepared using a standardized formulation approach to minimize compositional variability, thereby isolating the influence of surfactant type. The headgroups of the zwitterionic surfactants, phosphorylcholine, carnitine, amine oxide, betaine, and sulfobetaine, were evaluated for their impact on key parameters including physical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomic and Phosphoproteomic Landscapes of Azole Resistance in Aspergillus fumigatus Biofilm Exposed to Voriconazole]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aspergillus fumigatus, an opportunistic and allergenic pathogenic fungus, is responsible for a range of clinical disorders in humans, including invasive aspergillosis (IA), which can lead to severe infections in immunocompromised individuals. Unfortunately, the emergence of azole resistance has become a significant challenge in combating IA, necessitating further investigations into the underlying mechanisms of resistance. In this study, we conducted an integrated proteomic and phosphoproteomic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ozone therapy for temporomandibular joint osteoarthritis: a comment on the mechanistic insights and clinical translation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AIM2 regulated by JAK3/STAT1 pathway promotes PANoptosis in intestinal barrier dysfunction caused by concomitant radiation and PD-1 Blockade]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intestinal injury is a common and potentially life-threatening complication in patients receiving concurrent radiotherapy (RT) and anti-PD-1 immunotherapy (IO) for pelvic, abdominal, or retroperitoneal malignancies. Despite the therapeutic benefits of RT/IO combinations the mechanisms underlying RT/IO-induced enteritis remain poorly understood. This study investigates the role of Absent in melanoma 2 (AIM2)-mediated PANoptosis in intestinal barrier dysfunction during RT/IO-induced enteritis....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment of transplant-ineligible multiple myeloma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The treatment landscape for patients with multiple myeloma (MM) who are ineligible for transplant has evolved significantly over time. Initially dominated by melphalan-based regimens, treatment options have progressed with the introduction of proteasome inhibitors, immunomodulatory drugs, and more recently, anti-CD38 monoclonal antibodies. These advances have led to the development of doublet, triplet, and quadruple regimens, aiming not only for survival benefits, but also for meaningful...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive Function and Proteomic Changes in Patients with Autoantibody-Positive Neurodegenerative Dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This exploratory study provides preliminary evidence of distinct clinical and molecular signatures in autoantibody-positive neurodegeneration. ARRB1 and CAPN2 may contribute to cognitive resilience in this group, while UGGT1 appears associated with cognitive decline in autoantibody-negative cases. Owing to the limited sample size, these findings should be considered hypothesis-generating and warrant validation in larger, independent cohorts before consideration as biomarkers or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of aortic and mitral valve regurgitation volumes by cardiovascular magnetic resonance in participants without valvular heart disease in the Hamburg City Health Study population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An assessment of currently available cardiovascular magnetic resonance (CMR) methods to quantify aortic (AR) and mitral regurgitation (MR) in a large, population-based setting is lacking. The aim of this study was to evaluate CMR-based AR and MR quantification methods by quantifying AR and MR in participants without valvular heart disease in the population-based Hamburg City Health Study (HCHS). CMR was performed at 3T in the HCHS population. Aortic valve regurgitation volume (CMR-ARV) was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hypophosphatasia and Type 1 Diabetes: A Pilot Study and Review of Literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Hypophosphatasia (HPP) and type 1 diabetes (T1D) are both associated with low bone turnover and increased fracture risk. In this review, our objectives were to (a) discuss results of our pilot study aimed to evaluate prevalence and clinical and radiological characteristics of HPP in adults with T1D and (b) to review literature on the use of electronic medical records (EMR) for HPP case findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trace element signatures and regional differences in kidney stones: insights from a high-prevalence region]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global rise in urolithiasis poses significant health risks. However, the formation mechanisms and environmental influences of kidney stones remain poorly understood. Investigating the elemental composition of kidney stones provides a critical approach to exploring these factors. This study analyzed kidney stones from Yunnan Province, a region with high nephrolithiasis prevalence, classifying them into three types: calcium oxalate (CO), uric acid (UA), and mixed CO and carbonate apatite (CA)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[U.S. Highway 71 and Social Determinants of Health: Long-Term Disparities in Earnings, Economic Mobility, Incarceration, and Teen Birth in Kansas City]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A growing body of research has revisited the social costs of U.S. interstate highways. In Kansas City, U.S. Highway 71 (Bruce R. Watkins Drive) was built through the city's East Side over nearly two decades, displacing residents, destroying community institutions, and raising safety and health concerns. Using Opportunity Atlas data, we compare long-term outcomes-income, economic mobility, incarceration, and teen birth-for the 1978-1983 cohorts by childhood residence: census tracts along the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Self-reported Clinical Outcomes and Quality of Life in Agammaglobulinemia: the Importance of an Early Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Driven Diagnosis and Prognosis Comparison of ChatGPT-4o and DeepSeek-R1 in HIV Negative Talaromycosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates and compares the diagnostic and prognostic capabilities of ChatGPT-4o and DeepSeek-R1 in 56 HIV-negative talaromycosis cases. Clinical case fragments were de-identified and submitted to both models, with diagnostic accuracy and prognostic prediction rates statistically analyzed using chi-square tests, Fisher's exact tests, and logistic regression. Results showed DeepSeek-R1 achieved significantly higher diagnostic accuracy (66.1%) than ChatGPT-4o (3.6%) (χ² = 48.2, p <...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SMAD4 mutation drives gut microbiome shifts toward tumor progression in colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings emphasize the significance of SMAD4 mutation and microbiome modulation, revealing the interaction between host genetics and gut microbiota in driving colorectal cancer aggressiveness and suggesting potential microbial targets.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between lean mass, fat mass, and waist circumference with bone mineral density in Mexican children and adolescents: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To assess the associations of lean mass (LM), fat mass (FM), truncal fat mass (TFM), and waist circumference (WC) with bone mineral density (BMD) in Mexican youth, independently of body weight. We analyzed cross-sectional data from 1,054 children and adolescents from the Health Workers Cohort Study. We measured total and region-specific BMD, LM, and FM, with dual-energy X-ray absorptiometry. To eliminate the effect of body weight on FM, LM, TFM, and WC, weight-adjusted values were generated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local therapy overcomes primary resistance to target-immunotherapy combination in unresectable hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AR normally develops within 2 years after the beginning of treatment. Patients with AR have better characteristics in general, less invasive pattens of progression, and better prognosis compared to those with PR. Subsequent local therapy and changes in ICI treatment showed potential to overcome primary resistance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Testing the <em>JOIN for ME</em> Program in Low-Income Communities: Rhode Island CORD 3.0]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Dissemination of evidence-based intensive health behavior and lifestyle treatments (IHBLTs) to families from low-income communities was the primary objective of the CDC Childhood Obesity Research Demonstration (CORD) 3.0 projects. The goal of RI CORD 3.0 was to adapt and test the effectiveness and context for remote implementation of an IHBLT, JOIN for ME. Methods: Children aged 6-12 years with body mass index (BMI) >85th percentile and a caregiver (N = 111) were recruited through a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primary age-related tauopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary age-related tauopathy (PART) was proposed in 2014 as a neuropathological term to describe patients with Alzheimer's-type medial temporal lobe neurofibrillary degeneration in the absence of significant β-amyloid pathology. Over the past decade, this designation has gained widespread adoption, helping to clarify the interpretation of biomarker profiles, delineate early-stage tauopathy in aging, and differentiate non-Alzheimer tauopathies from aging and classical Alzheimer disease. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the malignancy rate of adrenal nodules in patients with a history of cancer: factors associated with adrenal metastases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In a cohort of patients with a history of any type of malignancy, almost 90% of isolated adrenal nodules were benign. However, a history of lung cancer, melanoma, or lesion size ≥ 2 cm significantly increased the risk of adrenal metastases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum concentrations of selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors and atypical antipsychotics in children and adolescents: data from routine clinical care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Therapeutic reference ranges (TRRs) for selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors (SSRIs) and atypical antipsychotics are established for adults. In children and adolescents, however, knowledge on TRRs of psychotropic drugs is scarce. The aim of this study was to determine serum concentrations in children and adolescents to provide guidance for the definition of therapeutic reference ranges in this age group. Within the routine therapeutic drug monitoring service of a German child and adolescent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal trends, patient characteristics and hospital volume outcomes after transcoronary ablation of septal hypertrophy and septal myectomy for treatment of obstructive hypertrophic cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SM was performed in older, more comorbid patiens and frequently included concomitant valve surgery. Higher in-hospital mortality at low-volume centers may partially reflect surgical complexity or case mix rather than volume alone. Our findings underscore the need for individualized referral strategies to experienced centers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estrogen-Related Receptor Alpha Promotes Skeletal Muscle Regeneration and Mitigates Muscular Dystrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skeletal muscle regeneration in chronic muscle diseases such as Duchenne Muscular Dystrophy (DMD) has remained clinically unsurmountable. Estrogen-related receptor alpha (ERRα) plays a critical role in adult skeletal muscle metabolism and exercise fitness. Whether ERRα activation can drive muscle regeneration and mitigate dystrophy in DMD is not known. We have investigated ERRα signaling in pre-clinical models of acute muscle injury and DMD. ERRα is induced in differentiating C2C12 myoblast and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the oncogenic role of lncRNA PIG13-DT in hepatocellular carcinoma progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study identifies a novel PIG13-DT/YBX3/USP15 axis driving HCC progression, suggesting PIG13-DT as a potential biomarker and therapeutic target. This work provides new insights into HCC molecular mechanisms and offers potential diagnostic and therapeutic implications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role for NF-κB in herpes encephalitis pathology in mice genocopying an inborn error of IRF3-IFN immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herpes simplex encephalitis (HSE) is a devastating disease with high mortality and serious sequelae. Genetic defects in the IFN-I pathway predispose individuals to HSE, but underlying mechanisms remain unclear. Using transgenic mice with the IRF3 R278Q mutation, ortholog to HSE-associated IRF3 R285Q, and iPSC-derived CNS cells from a pediatric patient carrying the variant, we investigated mechanisms in HSE. IRF3 R278Q transgenic mice exhibited aggravated HSV-1 brain disease and elevated CNS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Posterior Corneal Astigmatism Measured With Different Biometers on Toric IOL Power Calculation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The IOLMaster 700 exhibited the highest prediction accuracy for toric IOL compared to the CASIA2 and Pentacam AXL. When compared with Barrett-MPCA, Barrett-PPCA yielded comparable prediction accuracy for the IOLMaster 700 and improved accuracy for the CASIA2 and Pentacam AXL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomechanical Comparison of PRK, LASIK, and KLEx Using Personalized Finite Element Simulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although the same volume of tissue was removed in all procedures, corneal biomechanics influence refractive surgery outcomes, with PRK offering advantages in terms of reduced undercorrection and more favorable stress distribution. PRK's conservative approach offers a greater biomechanical safety margin, making it the recommended option for suspiciously weak corneas.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated Quantification of Lens Cortex and Nuclear Opacity Based on Swept-Source Anterior Segment Optical Coherence Tomography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The AI model is capable of accurately and objectively quantifying the opacity of both the lens cortex and nucleus based on swept-source AS-OCT images, thereby offering a method that is more precise, objective, and rapid for quantification in both clinical practice and research settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor: Combined fluorescent tags and multiplex CRISPR/Cas9 assembly for gene functional research in plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Related to the Prognosis of Chronic Low Back Pain in Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Factors affecting the intractability of CLBP were the intensity of pain, RDW, and atrophy of the LM muscles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nickelaelectro-Catalyzed Glycosyl-Donor Activation Enabling α-<em>C</em>-Alkenyl Glycoside Assembly]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[C-alkenyl glycosides represent an important class of carbohydrates that includes numerous biologically active compounds. We developed a stereoselective and sustainable strategy using anomeric glycosyl halides as radical precursors for reductive alkenylation. This enables efficient anomeric functionalization with excellent α-selectivity through ligand control. Electrochemical halogen-atom transfer (e-XAT) activates the glycosyl donors, avoiding stoichiometric metal reductants and expensive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of Pleiotropic Genetic Factors and Critical Brain Cell Types Linking Insomnia with Psychiatric Disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Insomnia and psychiatric disorders exhibit frequent comorbidity and heritability, yet their shared genetic architecture and neurobiological mechanisms remain unclear. This study investigated genetic overlap, pathways, and brain cell types linking insomnia with 12 psychiatric disorders using genome-wide association study (GWAS) data (insomnia: Neff = 314,149; psychiatric disorders: Neff = 12,783 - 449,855). Significant genetic correlations were identified between insomnia and seven psychiatric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Greater adherence to healthful dietary patterns is associated with lower insomnia risk in the Women's health initiative observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Better diet quality predicts lower insomnia risk in postmenopausal women. Clinical trials are needed to determine whether strategies to enhance diet quality improve insomnia symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[General anesthesia and systemic hyperosmolality modulate lumbar intrathecal drug distribution in female rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Anesthesia modulates the distribution of intrathecally administered drugs at the spinal and intracranial levels. Systemic HTS increased the intracranial availability of spinally administered drugs under K/DEX and prolonged the CNS availability of spinal drugs in the awake state. These interventions should be taken to clinical trials to improve efficacy and to reduce side effects of spinally administered drugs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards oral insulin-controlled release nanomedicine: A review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Frequent insulin injections remain the primary method for regulating blood glucose levels in individuals with diabetes mellitus; however, patient compliance is often poor. Due to its non-invasive nature, oral insulin delivery, exploring nanomedicine strategies, is considered a highly desirable alternative as an affordable and accessible medicine. However, the physical intestinal barriers and the harsh gastrointestinal environment provide major obstacles to reaching the best possible...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Viable Schistosoma mansoni infection 41 years after last exposure - a case report of a loyal parasite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Schistosoma species may show extraordinary longevity, despite not replicating in human hosts. We present a case of active S. mansoni infection in a Swiss patient 41 years after her one and only possible exposure (swimming in Lake Kivu, Rwanda).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From locus to lipase: LIPA as a paradigm for post-GWAS mechanistic and translational research in CAD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Continuous Monitoring of New-Onset Atrial Fibrillation After Coronary Artery Bypass Grafting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Although the incidence of new-onset AF after CABG in this study was higher than previously reported, the AF burden in these patients was very low, especially after 30 days. The very low AF burden questions the current guideline recommendations that long-term oral anticoagulation should be considered in patients with new-onset AF after CABG.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of State Gatekeeper Training Laws on Suicide Prevention Training for School Staff]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: To evaluate the impact of gatekeeper training laws (GTLs) on the prevalence of suicide prevention training (SPT) among school staff.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opioid Dispensing Trends Among Children and Adolescents Aged ≤ 19 Years in the United States: 2018-2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Since 2019, adolescent overdose deaths have more than doubled, primarily due to illegally-made fentanyl. Prescription opioid misuse during adolescence increases the risk of substance use disorders and overdose. This analysis examines opioid dispensing trends among individuals aged ≤19 years to support safer prescribing practices.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engaging Latinx Youth in PhotoVoice to Inform Message Development to Improve COVID-19 Vaccine Uptake]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: The COVID-19 pandemic exacerbated health care disparities with higher infection rates and lower vaccination rates among Latinx communities. Caregivers are often responsible for vaccine decisions, but evidence shows teens want involvement in decision-making. Therefore, it is crucial to refine vaccine advocacy, messaging, and communication to effectively target teens. We aim to (1) understand Latinx teen experiences during the COVID-19 pandemic and perspectives on vaccination and (2)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photon-Counting Computed Tomography in Cardiac Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coronary computed tomography (CT) angiography plays a pivotal role in the diagnosis, risk stratification, and treatment of patients with known or suspected coronary artery disease. However, conventional CT technologies are limited by spatial resolution, artifact susceptibility, and radiation exposure. Photon-counting computed tomography (PCCT) introduces substantial technological improvements over conventional CT. This includes improved spatial and contrast resolution, energy discrimination, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The SCAI Is Not the Limit: Refining Dynamic Shock Trajectories With Machine Learning-Based Phenotyping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mono- and dinuclear β-oxo-δ-diiminate (BODDI) based catalysts for the ring-opening polymerization of L-lactide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyesters such as polylactic acid belong to the most useful biodegradable polymers being able to substitute polyolefins in many applications. In search for potent catalysts based on bio-compatible and non-critical raw materials bimetallic cooperativity has emerged as a powerful approach, but one that is still in its infancy. Here, we report a comparative study on the catalytic activity of overall 13 mono- and dinuclear β-oxo-δ-diiminate (BODDI) complexes in the ring-opening polymerization (ROP)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking Polyanion-Type Materials through High-Entropy Effect for Aqueous Potassium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exploration of electrode materials for aqueous batteries has predominantly followed the established principles and design strategies derived from organic electrolyte-based systems. However, this conventional approach faces inherent limitations. Although V-based polyanion materials (e.g., Na(3)V(2)(PO(4))(3)) are compelling for organic electrolyte-based alkali metal ion batteries, their applications in aqueous K-ion batteries remain untapped, probably due to the limited cation electroactivity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shaping the Glycan Landscape: Hidden Relationships between Linkage and Ring Distortions Induced by Carbohydrate-Active Enzymes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbohydrate-active enzymes (CAZymes) catalyze glycan remodeling by forming and cleaving glycosidic bonds. An often-observed aspect of their catalytic mechanisms, particularly in glycosidases, is monosaccharide ring distortion that brings the substrate from a stable solution conformation to a reactive state. To what extent this distortion is promoted by steric constraints in the enzyme's binding pocket or by more elusive dynamical effects associated with the glycan conformational flexibility is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A theoretical study of the thermoelectric properties of two-dimensional surface-functionalized MXene materials ScYCTT' (T = OH, H; T' = H, F)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MXenes are a novel family of two-dimensional layered materials consisting of transition metal carbides, nitrides, or carbon-nitrides, and great interest has been shown in these materials because of their distinctive structural configurations. In this study, the electronic structures of functionalized ScYC(OH)H, ScYC(OH)F, and ScYCHF were initially evaluated through density-functional theory (DFT) to judge their stability in the two-dimensional state. Subsequently, based on the Boltzmann...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbon dots meet artificial intelligence: applications in biomedical engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbon dots (CDs) are fluorescent carbon nanomaterials typically less than 10 nm in size with excellent water solubility, low toxicity, high biocompatibility, favorable optical properties, and modifiable surface. CDs have great promise in various fields, including bioimaging, sensing, and drug delivery. With the emergence of artificial intelligence (AI) technologies, particularly machine learning (ML) and deep learning (DL) algorithms, new avenues for synthesis optimization, performance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population Health Surveys in Spain: description of methodologies and contents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PHS are fundamental for public health decision-making. Enhancing methodological and content harmonization, incorporating longitudinal designs, and linking with administrative records could significantly improve their utility. Additionally, promoting open access to PHS data and expanding result dissemination are recommended to maximize their impact on Public Health policies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Japanese Radiology 2025 Updates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review provides a comprehensive overview of recent transformative advancements in diagnostic imaging that position Japan at the forefront of radiological innovation. We highlight pivotal innovations that enhance diagnostic capabilities and redefine clinical workflows. The article begins with upright multidetector computed tomography (MDCT), a groundbreaking technology offering novel insights into posture-dependent anatomical and physiological changes. We then explore significant progress in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomimetic synthesis of a benzobisthiazole-based conjugated polymer for pH-responsive drug delivery and synergistic tumor therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A benzodithiophene-based conjugated polymer (termed as DPDMP) with high water-dispersibility, biocompatibility, and superior photothermal conversion efficiency was synthesized using a biomimetic click reaction. DPDMP can establish pH-responsive boronate ester bonds with bortezomib, enabling an integrated approach to tumor photothermal and chemotherapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251009152047&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>