<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 07:38:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does experience translate? A multicenter evaluation of the learning curve in single-port robotic prostatectomy based on prior multiport proficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-port robot-assisted radical prostatectomy (SP-RARP) offers potential benefits over multiport RARP (MP-RARP), including fewer incisions and reduced postoperative pain. However, the influence of prior MP-RARP experience on early SP-RARP learning curves remains unclear. We retrospectively analyzed 622 consecutive SP-RARP cases performed by four surgeons with differing MP-RARP caseloads (> 1,000, > 400, > 200, and > 100) across multiple centers. The primary endpoint of this study was the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sealing stretchable electronics through a viscoplastic surface effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Machine Learning-Empowered Quantitative Structure-Activity Relationship Model for Predicting the Plasma Half-life of Drugs in Dogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding a drug's plasma half-life is essential in guiding dosage regimens and optimizing therapeutic outcomes, particularly in the early stages of drug development. By using published pharmacokinetic data from Food Animal Residue Avoidance Databank, we collected 560 data points of plasma half-lives for different drugs in dogs following intravenous administration. The dataset was then preprocessed and the mean elimination half-life for each drug was selected in the final clean dataset for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of radiative cooling materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiative cooling is a renewable cooling mechanism with diverse applications. Many radiative cooling materials have been developed (e.g., fabrics, paints and building materials). It is, however, difficult to compare their properties because of a lack of standardized and transparent performance-evaluation systems. Here, we present procedures for assessing the optical and thermal properties of radiative cooling materials that can be applied to various forms such as films, coatings and fabrics. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LGBQ+ Veteran and Service Member Health and Health Care: A Scoping Review of Research from 1994 to 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: People who are lesbian, gay, bisexual, queer, and other minoritized sexual orientations (LGBQ+) have served in the US military for generations. Despite well-documented health disparities between LGBQ+ and heterosexual individuals, research addressing the health of LGBQ+ veterans remains limited. This scoping review provides a map of the literature on LGBQ+ veteran health and health care from 1994 to 2023, identifying trends, gaps, and future directions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local strain tuning for scalable quantum photonics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brownian spin-locking effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brownian systems are characterized by spatiotemporal disorder, which arises from the erratic motion of particles driven by thermal fluctuations. When light interacts with such systems, it typically produces unpolarized and uncorrelated fields. Here we report the observation of a large-scale spin-locking effect of light within a Brownian medium. In an observation direction perpendicular to the incident wave's momentum, scattering naturally divides into two diffusion regions, each associated with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eye Opening Primes Synaptic Maturation by Enhancing AMPA Receptor-Mediated Transmission and Spinogenesis in the Developing Superior Colliculus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eye opening represents a critical milestone in postnatal visual development, triggering experience-dependent plasticity that refines neural circuits across visual pathways. While synaptic maturation in the thalamocortical system has been extensively studied, how eye opening shapes synaptic development in the superior colliculus (SC) - a major subcortical hub mediating rapid orienting and motion detection - remains poorly understood. Here, we combine electrophysiological, biochemical, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aligning brains into a shared space improves their alignment with large language models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent research demonstrates that large language models can predict neural activity recorded via electrocorticography during natural language processing. To predict word-by-word neural activity, most prior work evaluates encoding models within individual electrodes and participants, limiting generalizability. Here we analyze electrocorticography data from eight participants listening to the same 30-min podcast. Using a shared response model, we estimate a common information space across...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Guidelines for T cell nomenclature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advances in T cell biology have revealed heterogeneity among T cell populations that is not captured by existing general nomenclature. This issue has caused an ad hoc broadening of core T cell subset definitions and the invention of new subset designations that have not been uniformly delineated. To address this issue, in this Consensus Statement, we propose guidelines that serve three goals. First, they advocate that primary research reports define the experimental basis by which relevant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering PVX vectors harboring heterologous VSRs to enhance Recombinant vaccine protein expression in plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant-based systems offer a sustainable platform for production of recombinant proteins, but their utility remains limited by host RNA silencing and low yields. Potato virus X (PVX)-derived vectors have shown promise in transient expression systems; however, their efficiency can be further improved by incorporating viral suppressors of RNA silencing (VSRs). Here, we engineered optimized PVX-based expression vectors harboring heterologous VSRs (P19, P38, and NSs) from distinct plant viruses,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing clinical utility of STANDARD M10 rapid rtRT-PCR assay with pooled testing for SARS-CoV-2 screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pre-admission screening for severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus-2 (SARS-CoV-2) was essential during the COVID-19 pandemic in Korea. The pooled real-time reverse transcription (rtRT)-PCR test, recommended for optimizing testing capacity, had long turnaround times, limiting its use for same-day hospitalizations. This study evaluated the performance and clinical utility of a rapid rtRT-PCR test as an alternative screening tool for same-day admissions, compared to pooled testing with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-quality phased genome assemblies of line-bred Korean Hanwoo cattle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Korean cattle breed, Hanwoo, has been selected as a meat cattle breed since the late 1980s in Korea, but has suffered from reduced genetic diversity due to repeated selection within a single population. In this study, we generated high-fidelity long-read sequencing data (~Q30, 98-146 Gb) for three Hanwoo Research Center (HRC) Hanwoo individuals from early, intermediate, and current breeding generations of the genetically distinct HRC population. These datasets yielded four partially phased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standardized rice bran supplement ameliorates depressive behaviors via FKBP5 mediated glucocorticoid receptor signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic stress-induced dysregulation of the hypothalamic-pituitary-adrenal (HPA) axis and glucocorticoid receptor (GR) signaling is central to the development of depression. This study investigated the antidepressant effects of a standardized rice bran supplement (RBS) in a corticosterone (CORT)-induced mouse model and explored the underlying molecular mechanisms, with a focus on GR regulation. Male ICR mice were administered CORT (40 mg/kg, intraperitoneally) for 6 weeks to induce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolation of <em>Orientia tsutsugamushi</em> from Human Blood and Factors Effect <em>In Vitro</em> Isolation in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction: Orientia tsutsugamushi, the causative agent of scrub typhus, is endemic to South Korea. While diagnostics such as PCR and immunochromatographic tests (ICT) are widely used, pathogen isolation remains essential for antimicrobial resistance and genetic studies. Methods: In this study, 444 blood samples were collected from febrile patients across 13 hospitals. Among 263 samples identified as scrub typhus-positive by at least one diagnostic method, 99 isolates were successfully...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Markovnikov-Selective Hydroboration of Aryl Alkenes Catalyzed by Quaternary Ammonium Salts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of catalytic Markovnikov-selective hydroboration of alkenes has seen significant progress; however, achieving this transformation under metal-free conditions has remained a longstanding challenge. Here, we present an organocatalytic method for the Markovnikov-selective hydroboration of aryl alkenes using a readily available quaternary ammonium catalyst. This approach is operationally simple, scalable, and demonstrates broad substrate compatibility. Furthermore, the method enables...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Letter:</em> Author's Reply to: "Refining Atomoxetine Research for Adolescent NSSI"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging or Direct Thrombectomy in Posterior Circulation Large-Vessel Occlusion Stroke: Analysis of Binational Registries and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: The role of IV thrombolysis before endovascular thrombectomy (bridging thrombectomy, BT) in posterior circulation large-vessel occlusion stroke remains uncertain. This study evaluated the effectiveness and safety of BT compared with direct thrombectomy (DT) using data from 2 nationwide registries and an updated meta-analysis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In silico design of a multi-epitope vaccine against Cryptosporidium parvum using structural and immunoinformatics approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The MESV construct demonstrated strong immunogenicity, structural stability, and broad population coverage, underscoring its potential as a promising vaccine candidate against C. parvum. Furthermore, experimental validation is warranted to confirm its safety and efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic Transformation of CuI Nanoparticles Into Oxidation-Resistant 2D Copper Nanoplates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unconventional phase transformations reveal new crystallization mechanisms, yet direct observation of such pathways during nanoscale solution-phase synthesis remains challenging. This study uncovers an atypical growth process in which thermodynamically stable CuI nanoparticles (NPs) transform into high-energy 2D Cu plates. Using a combination of in situ transmission electron microscopy, ex situ structural analysis, and density functional theory calculations shows that the formation of structural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decellularized Extracellular Matrix (dECM) in Tendon Regeneration: A Comprehensive Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tendon injuries pose significant clinical challenges due to complex structure and limited healing capacity. Decellularized Extracellular Matrix (dECM) offers a promising solution by replicating the native tendon microenvironment and promoting regeneration. This review summarizes the role of Extracellular Matrix (ECM), ongoing trends in the decellularization methods, as well as their integration with emerging technologies such as 3D printing, hybrid composite scaffold and hydrogels. Preclinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dissipation in fermionic two-body continuous-time quantum walk under the steepest entropy ascent formalism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum walks play a crucial role in quantum algorithms and computational problems. Many-body quantum walks can reveal and exploit quantum correlations that are unavailable for single-walker cases. Studying quantum walks under noise and dissipation, particularly in multiwalker systems, has significant implications. In this context, we use a thermodynamically consistent formalism of dissipation modeling, namely the steepest entropy ascent (SEA) formalism. We analyze two spinless fermionic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastward transients in the dayside ionosphere. II. A parallel-plate capacitorlike effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During the 23 April 2023 geospace storm, we observed chorus-wave-driven, energetic particle precipitation on closed magnetic field lines in the dayside magnetosphere. Simultaneously and in the ionosphere's bottom side, we observed signatures of impact ionization and strong enhancements in the ionospheric electric field, via radar detection of meter-scale turbulence, and with temporal characteristics matching those of the magnetospheric observations. We detail this in another work [M. F. Ivarsen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastward transients in the dayside ionosphere. I. Electrodynamics on closed field lines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[At night in Earth's polar regions, energetic aurorae frequently penetrate into the atmosphere, with the peculiar effect of driving turbulent electrojet currents in the bottomside ionosphere. During the day, however, Earth's plasma environment becomes highly conductive, owing to the constant flux of extreme ultraviolet radiation emitted from the Sun. The high-conductivity plasma in the dayside ionosphere can effectively short out plasma turbulence around aurorae, and so electrojet turbulence is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of on-site potentials on q breathers in nonlinear chains]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[On-site potentials are ubiquitous in physical systems and strongly influence their heat transport and energy localization. These potentials will inevitably affect the dynamical properties of q breathers (QBs), defined as periodic orbits exponentially localized in normal mode space. By integrating on-site terms into the Fermi-Pasta-Ulam-Tsingou-β system, this work utilizes numerical simulations and Floquet analysis to systematically explore the influence of on-site potentials on QB stability. For...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CK2α Regulates Endoplasmic Reticulum Stress-Mediated Mitophagy via the PERK/ATF4/CHOP Pathway in Rotenone-Treated SH-SY5Y Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitophagy refers to selective mitochondrial autophagy to remove damaged mitochondria and plays a critical role in maintaining mitochondria homeostasis. Casein kinase 2α (CK2α) is involved in mitophagy regulation in dopaminergic neurons. Endoplasmic reticulum (ER) stress releases calcium into mitochondria, leading to mitochondrial dysfunction and contributing to various diseases. However, it is not clear whether CK2α regulates ER-mediated mitochondrial dysfunction and mitophagy in response to ER...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PYCR1 drives lung cancer progression through functional interactions with EGFR and TLR signaling pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lung cancer, particularly non-small-cell lung cancer (NSCLC), remains a leading cause of cancer-related mortality worldwide. Recent studies have implicated pyrroline-5-carboxylate reductase 1 (PYCR1), a key enzyme in proline biosynthesis, in cancer progression, yet its specific role in lung cancer remains unclear. Here we demonstrate that PYCR1 plays a critical role in NSCLC progression through its functional association with the epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR) and Toll-like receptor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Failure of lysosomal acidification and endomembrane network in neurodegeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lysosomes have emerged as central hubs in the regulation of the endomembrane system, extending beyond degradation to coordinate organelle communication. Central to this regulatory role is vacuolar-type H^(+)-ATPase (V-ATPase), a proton pump that acidifies the lysosomal lumen to enable hydrolase activity and support proteostasis. In addition to its lysosomal functions, V-ATPase influences the physiology of other organelles, including the endoplasmic reticulum (ER), Golgi apparatus and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Putative multiple myeloma susceptibility genes identified by exome sequencing of 347 familial and early-onset cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiple myeloma (MM) is the second most common blood malignancy, with several lines of evidence supporting an inherited genetic component. Here, we sequenced 177 affected individuals from 128 families, and 170 early-onset MM cases diagnosed before 55 years of age. Samples were identified and collected through nationwide efforts in France, Sweden, and Greece. We focused on rare germline protein truncating and likely deleterious missense variants in genes harboring variants in at least two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing ChatGPT-3.5, Gemini 2.0, and DeepSeek V3 for pediatric pneumonia learning in medical students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pediatric pneumonia (PP) remains an important topic in undergraduate medical education and offers a suitable framework for evaluating large language models (LLMs) in AI-assisted learning. We developed a 27 open-ended survey including five core domains of PP, such as diagnosis, etiology, diagnostics, treatment, and prevention. DeepSeek V3, Gemini 2.0, and ChatGPT-3.5, were each provided with identical reference materials. Two pediatric infectious disease specialists independently assessed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[iWAX: interpretable Wav2vec-AASIST-XGBoost framework for voice spoofing detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep learning have led to the widespread use of pre-trained large-scale speech models, such as wav2vec 2.0 (w2v2), in voice spoofing detection. However, the interpretability of such models remains a critical challenge due to their complex internal representations. In this paper, we propose iWAX, an interpretable voice spoofing countermeasure that combines a fine-tuned w2v2 front-end with the AASIST back-end, and an XGBoost classifier. iWAX leverages the feature importance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cross-sectional study on schistosomiasis prevalence, intensity and risk factors in Kassala State, Sudan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite decade-long global efforts, schistosomiasis remains a significant concern in Sudan. In 2017, a nationwide survey on schistosomiasis raised concerns about the existence of persistent "hot spot" areas that require more focused interventions and resources. The Sudanese Federal Ministry of Health (FMOH) and the Kassala State Ministry of Health have continued to implement school-based MDA. This study aimed to assess the prevalence and intensity of Schistosoma mansoni and S. haematobium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Salivary kynurenine pathway metabolites as potential non-invasive markers of glandular dysfunction in Sjögren's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sjögren's disease (SjD) is an autoimmune disorder characterized by salivary gland dysfunction and systemic manifestations. This study aimed to evaluate kynurenine (Kyn) pathway metabolites in saliva and investigate their clinical relevance in SjD. Saliva samples were collected from 39 SjD patients and 32 healthy controls (HCs). Concentrations of tryptophan, Kyn, quinolinic acid (QA), and kynurenic acid (KA), as well as inferred enzyme activities, were measured using ELISA. Receiver operating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physical frailty and MRI markers of structural brain integrity in the community-dwelling late middle-aged and old adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Physical frailty may weaken structural brain integrity (SBI), which may lead to cognitive impairments. In this cross-sectional study, the number of final study participants was 2057 (700 men, 1357 women). The proportion of the frail men was 5.3% (n = 37), and the proportion of the frail women was 6.6% (n = 90). We used the Fried Frailty Phenotypes (FFP) to assess the physical frailty associated with SBI regarding cognitive impairments by sex. We performed multivariate linear and logistic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trauma center level and postoperative mortality: a nationwide cohort study from South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trauma center designation may influence surgical outcomes, but evidence from Asian trauma systems remains limited. This study examined the association between trauma center level and postoperative mortality following trauma surgery in South Korea. We conducted a nationwide cohort study using 2021 data from the Korean National Health Insurance Service. Adults (≥ 18 years) who underwent trauma surgery under general anesthesia at one of 17 designated trauma centers were included. Centers were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mortality and suicide risk in glaucoma patients with or without vision impairment: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate the mortality and suicide risk in glaucoma patients with or without vision impairment. Data were retrieved from the Korean National Health Insurance Service for 4,056,650 individuals aged ≥ 20 years and assessed for all-cause and cause-specific mortality for glaucoma from 2009 to 2020. Subjects were classified into 3 groups: healthy control subjects, glaucoma without vision impairment, and glaucoma with vision impairment. Hazard ratios (HR) were calculated under...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of rs3802177 G/A polymorphism on SLC30A8 mRNA and hsa-miR-183-5p in Malay women with gestational diabetes mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gestational diabetes mellitus (GDM) is characterized by the initial presentation of impaired glucose tolerance identified during pregnancy. Numerous investigations have explored the associations between single nucleotide polymorphisms (SNPs) and microRNAs in relation to the susceptibility to GDM across diverse populations. This study aimed to investigate the interplay among rs3802177 G/A 3' UTR polymorphism, SLC30A8 mRNA expression, and hsa-miR-183-5p in Malay women with GDM. TargetScanHuman,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Affecting Perfectionistic Self-Presentation Among ICU Nurses, Focusing on Pride and Impostor Phenomenon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to explore perfectionistic self-presentation among ICU nurses in South Korea and investigate factors affecting perfectionistic self-presentation, focusing on authentic pride, hubristic pride, and the impostor phenomenon. In this secondary analysis, data from 239 participants who met the eligibility criteria of the parent study conducted in July 2022 were used. Authentic and hubristic pride, the impostor phenomenon, and perfectionistic self-presentation were assessed using the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported Outcomes for Men with Metastatic Castration-resistant Prostate Cancer Who Received Olaparib plus Abiraterone Versus Placebo plus Abiraterone in the Phase 3 PROpel Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND CLINICAL IMPLICATIONS: In PROpel, there were no differences in HRQoL or pain scores reported by patients with mCRPC receiving olaparib + abiraterone versus placebo + abiraterone, suggesting that patients can derive a clinical benefit from olaparib + abiraterone while maintaining similar HRQoL in comparison with current standard-of-care treatment. The PROpel trial is registered on ClinicalTrials.gov as NCT03732820.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing a Reference Interval for Flow Cytometric Analysis of Red Blood Cell Osmotic Fragility in a Healthy Korean Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We established reference intervals for the flow cytometric OFT at the midpoint and endpoint time/forward scatter plot regions in a Korean population for the first time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[T cell immune dysfunction and progression to severe COVID-19 in asthma revealed by single-cell RNA sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study provides new insights into the mechanisms underlying the progression of COVID-19 infection in patients with asthma. A reduction in the proportion of T cells while expanding cytotoxic CD8+ T cell proportion was associated with severe COVID-19 presentation in asthma.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cage design-centric glider approach to full-endoscopic lumbar fusion: optimizing nerve root protection in facet-sparing and facet-resecting techniques]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endoscopic transforaminal lumbar interbody fusion (TLIF) offers substantial advantages in the management of degenerative spinal diseases, including accelerated postoperative recovery. However, its technical complexity and steep learning curve pose risks for nerve root injury. Optimizing nerve root protection in full-endoscopic facet-sparing TLIF (FE fs-TLIF) and full-endoscopic facet-resecting TLIF (FE fr-TLIF) is essential for enhancing surgical safety. This study aimed to improve the nerve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mimotopes of calcitonin gene-related peptide (CGRP) screened from Fv-antibody library: antagonists to CGRP receptor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Calcitonin gene-related peptide (CGRP) is a neuropeptide synthesized in the trigeminal ganglion and it has been identified as a key mediator in the pathophysiology of migraine. The monoclonal antibodies and small-molecule antagonists for calcitonin receptor-like receptor (CLR) have been developed for therapeutics for migraine. In this study, the previously screened CGRP mimotopes sequences from Fv-antibody library were prepared as CDR3 peptides, Fv-antibodies, and heavy chains of immunoglobulin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refining IOL Power Calculations with PMOD: A Multi-Formula Analysis in High-Power Lenses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PMOD is a simple diopter-specific adjustment applied to the formula-predicted spherical equivalent. It effectively improved refractive prediction accuracy and reduced residual systematic errors that persisted in high-power IOLs across formulas, even after applying constants optimized in the central power group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frequent De Novo Mutations in Korean Patients With Charcot-Marie-Tooth Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND AIMS: De novo mutations provide a fundamental source of gene pool changes, driving genomic microevolution. Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease (CMT), which is a group of genetically and clinically heterogeneous peripheral neuropathic disorders, is characterized by progressive muscle weakness, hand and foot deformities, and occasional involvement of other organs. This study conducted the first cohort study of de novo mutations in CMT patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutational study-based identification of high activity O-methyltransferase for the regioselective methylation of epigallocatechin gallate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The site-specific methylation of (-)-epigallocatechin-3-O-gallate (EGCG), especially 3`` hydroxyl group in D-ring, significantly enhances its stability and bioavailability in human body. Therefore, the methylation is the way to make EGCG more orally active and potent nutraceutical agents. In this study, for the effective synthesis of the methylated EGCG, S-adenosyl-L-methionine dependent O-methyltransferase (OMT) was studied to synthesize the methylated EGCG. OMT from Bacillus licheniformis and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of blue-green-grey drainage systems for urban flooding based on resilience components]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a practical evaluation framework to assess the pre-flood defense performance of urban drainage systems. This framework integrates the four components of resilience (rapidity, redundancy, resourcefulness, and robustness) with a Flood Defense Index (FDI), a metric designed to quantify the system's hydraulic capacity utilization. The proposed framework was applied to two urban watersheds in Seoul, South Korea, i.e., the Gunja and Banpocheon watersheds, under three...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Airborne emissions and corrosion of stainless bellows under simulated semiconductor halide environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stainless steel bellows in semiconductor pump-scrubber systems are prone to halide-induced corrosion, releasing airborne fine particles and transition metals. This study examined the emissions and surface degradation of AISI 316Ti and Alloy 926 under simulated halide-rich conditions over 72 h. Particle size distributions were measured using a Scanning Mobility Particle Sizer and Optical Particle Sizer; surface morphology and pit depth were analyzed via stereo microscopy and SEM-EDS. Airborne...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stability-preserving post-processing of mRNA-lipid nanoparticles utilizing a scalable ion concentration polarization platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipid nanoparticles (LNPs) have emerged as key vehicles for mRNA delivery. However, their physicochemical fragility during post-processing remains a critical bottleneck for clinical translation. In this paper, we present an ion concentration polarization (ICP)-based concentration strategy that enables the rapid, gentle, and selective enrichment of mRNA-LNPs. This process preserves essential physicochemical properties, including particle size (<80 nm), low polydispersity (PDI <0.2), and high...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tailoring flexible aliphatic covalent organic frameworks with hydroxyl sites: A novel platform for efficient extraction and rapid detection of bisphenols]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of advanced adsorbents enabling rapid and sensitive detection of endocrine-disrupting bisphenols (BPs) is essential for safeguarding ecosystems and human health. Covalent organic frameworks (COFs) hold great promise for the adsorption of BPs, but conventional rigid aromatic architectures suffer from limited molecular recognition capability. Herein, we design a hydroxyl-functionalized flexible aliphatic COF (TFT-TAH COF) via the polymerization of 2,3-dihydroxydicarbohydrazid (TAH)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increasing equity to mental health treatment by adapting churches as alternative facilities: a location-allocation analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quality of life and care burden of people living with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis who need home-based medical care in Korea and their family caregivers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: Advanced neurodegenerative diseases (NDDs) lead to severe mobility limitations, creating significant challenges for patients and caregivers at home. We aimed to investigate the quality of life (QOL) and care burden of people living with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS, pALS) and other NDDs and their family caregivers in Korea. Methods: This prospective survey study included people living with NDDs with mobility restrictions and their caregiver enrolled in a home-based medical care...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct spatially resolved tumor microenvironment trajectories define benefit from ramucirumab plus pembrolizumab in refractory PD-L1+ gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The activity of bispecific antibodies against vascular endothelial growth factor (VEGF) and programmed death ligand-1 (PD-1) have reinvigorated interest in dual VEGF and PD-1 targeting across solid tumors. However, the tumor and immune features influencing tumor response remain largely unknown. We conducted a single arm phase II trial evaluating dual VEGFR2 and PD-1 targeting with ramucirumab and pembrolizumab in pre-treated PD-L1+ gastric cancer. Twenty-six patients were enrolled between June...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of damage accrual by organ domain in systemic lupus erythematosus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Risk factors for individual organ system damage accrual were highly varied in patients with SLE. Not all factors associated with domain-specific damage accrual were captured by the risk factors analysed for overall organ damage accrual.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes of surgical resection for thymic epithelial tumor with intrathoracic dissemination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Surgical resection for metastatic TET with intrathoracic dissemination demonstrated favourable OS; however, high progression rates necessitated repeated treatments. Factors including the number of metastases, WHO cell type, and the presence of MG were identified as significant determinants influencing PFS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased Risk of Early-onset Kidney Cancer in Individuals with Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease Aged 20-39: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: NAFLD may serve as an independent risk factor for early-onset kidney cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of dopamine depletion and cholinergic basal forebrain atrophy with brain metabolism and cognition in Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundCognitive dysfunction is one of the most debilitating non-motor symptoms of Parkinson's disease (PD). This study aimed to explore the interplay between altered neurotransmitter activities, including dopamine and acetylcholine, and brain metabolism in cognitive decline in PD.MethodsWe enrolled 172 PD patients (mean ± SD age 69.8 ± 8.6 years; 93 females) who underwent brain magnetic resonance imaging, N-(3-[^(18)F]fluoropropyl)-2β-carbomethoxy-3β-(4-iodophenyl) nortropane (^(18)F-FP-CIT)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between relative handgrip strength and metabolic syndrome in Korean postmenopausal women by time since menopause]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lower RHGS is independently and dose-dependently associated with increased odds of MetS, particularly among women beyond 10 years postmenopause. RHGS may serve as a simple, low-cost tool for identifying women at elevated cardiometabolic risk in later life.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[User-Centered Formative Evaluation of Cognitive Rehabilitation Software: Cognitive Walkthrough and System Usability Scale Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The combined use of CW and the SUS enabled the identification of both objective and perceived usability challenges in the cognitive rehabilitation software. Findings emphasize the importance of user-centered design and formative evaluation in the early stages of software development. Recommendations such as improving information visibility, reducing unnecessary steps, and enhancing system feedback may contribute to safer and more effective digital cognitive interventions. However,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Outcomes Following Endoscopic Papillectomy for Ampullary Neuroendocrine Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: EP is a safe and effective option for small, well-differentiated Amp-NETs without radiologic evidence of LN metastasis. Although the incomplete resection rate is concerning, the absence of recurrence in margin-negative patients supports EP as a viable treatment option in carefully selected cases. Patients with positive margins warrant close surveillance and consideration of additional surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tislelizumab + Chemotherapy in Gastric Cancer: Long-Term RATIONALE-305 Randomized Trial Follow-up]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Results from RATIONALE-305 continued to show durable and improved efficacy outcomes with tislelizumab + chemotherapy versus placebo + chemotherapy at 3 years in advanced GC/GEJC, supporting PD-L1 as a potential prognostic biomarker.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of congenital heart disease on somatic growth: a monozygotic twin study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Children with congenital heart disease (CHD) often experience growth faltering. However, somatic growth is significantly influenced by genetic and environmental factors. Given the unique genetic and environmental similarities of monozygotic twins, this study aims to evaluate the relationship between CHD and growth faltering, while minimizing the influence of these factors. We retrospectively reviewed data from 41 pairs of twins, where one had CHD and the other did not. Anthropometric measures...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison between single and dual antiplatelet therapy in patients on oral anticoagulants undergoing coil embolization for unruptured intracranial aneurysms: a retrospective multicenter cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: With respect to SAPT, DAPT was not associated with a reduction in thromboembolic complications in patients taking OACs who underwent coil embolization, but it was associated with an increase in all bleeding events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abnormal Doppler and perinatal outcomes according to the placental lesions of maternal and fetal vascular malperfusion in preterm fetal growth restriction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We identified key findings among placental MVM and FVM associated with abnormal UA and MCA Doppler as well as neonatal mortality in preterm FGR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Contrast Black-and-White Switching via Reversible Copper Electrodeposition for Reflective Monotone Displays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite their low power consumption, commercial black-and-white reflective displays based on electrophoretic technology (i.e., electronic paper) suffer from limited brightness, contrast, and temperature tolerance. Here, this study presents an electrochemical display mechanism that addresses these limitations by integrating a light-scattering layer beneath a roughened indium tin oxide (ITO) electrode supporting reversible metal electrodeposition (RME). The scattering layer is composed of an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delayed post-polypectomy perforation: A case report of a 65-year-old man at 54 days post-procedure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RATIONALE: Post-polypectomy perforation (PPP) is an uncommon complication, usually occurring within 24 hours of colonoscopic polypectomy. Delayed perforation beyond several days is extremely rare.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural and dynamic roles of tandem acyl carrier proteins in aryl polyene biosynthesis in carbapenem-resistant Acinetobacter baumannii]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aryl polyenes (APEs) are critical secondary metabolites in gram-negative pathogens, synthesized by polyketide synthases that rely on acyl carrier proteins (ACPs) as essential cofactors. Despite their importance, the structural and functional dynamics of tandem ACPs-ApeE and ApeF-have remained largely uncharacterized. In this study, we elucidate the molecular mechanisms underlying these ACPs within the APE biosynthetic gene cluster of carbapenem-resistant Acinetobacter baumannii (CRAB), a major...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of Interlayer Excitons in Mixed-Dimensional MoS<sub>2</sub> and InGaN/GaN Quantum Well Heterojunctions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mixed-dimensional heterojunctions (HJs) between compound semiconductors and transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDCs) provide a versatile platform for modulating interfacial exciton dynamics. While compound semiconductors offer precise compositional control for bandgap tuning across wide spectral ranges, they exhibit weak exciton binding energies that limit exciton stability at room temperature. Mixed-dimensional HJs address this limitation by integrating compound semiconductors with TMDCs, whose...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[eVLP-Mediated Cas9 Delivery for Preventing IBMIR in Islet Transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Islet transplantation is a promising strategy for effective β-cell replacement in patients with type 1 diabetes. However, its success is hindered significantly by instant blood-mediated inflammatory reaction (IBMIR), which leads to rapid graft loss. IBMIR is triggered when the transplanted islets come in contact with blood, activating the coagulation cascade, complement pathways, and innate immune responses. Tissue factor (TF), abundantly expressed on the islet surface, initiates the coagulation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251053/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GLP-1RA and Liver Fibrosis Progression in MASLD and Type 2 Diabetes: Target Trial Emulation Using Propensity Score Matching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: GLP-1RA use significantly reduced the risk of liver fibrosis progression in patients with MASLD and T2DM, supporting its potential role in early disease modification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catalyst-Free Collagen Filament Crosslinking for Engineering Anisotropic and Mechanically Robust Tissue Scaffolds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Engineering mechanically resilient hydrogels from naturally derived proteins, such as collagen and gelatin, remains a key challenge in tissue regeneration, particularly when cell compatibility and structural integrity are simultaneously required. Here, a bioorthogonal crosslinking strategy using rhodamine and polyethylene glycol (PEG) is reported to fabricate dense, mechanically reinforced collagen hydrogels. PEG-mediated dehydration induces spontaneous peptide bond formation between rhodamine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevated Serum Bile Acids Predict Poor Liver Outcomes in Children With Alagille Syndrome: Results From the GALA Study Group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lower SBA in children with ALGS liver disease predicts improved NLS and EFS. SBA is also associated with NLS in children with ALGS who clear their bilirubin, that is, those with anicteric cholestasis. Although the patients studied here did not receive IBAT inhibition, these data suggest that lowering SBA may improve important clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between sudden work recall and psychological health issues: a cross-sectional analysis of the 6th Korean Working Conditions Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The relationship between sudden work recall and psychological health may not be a simple linear one. The results suggest that only a high frequency of sudden work recall is associated with an increased risk of anxiety and fatigue. Therefore, it is necessary to establish appropriate measures and to conduct additional research in this area.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health effects of weekend work on Korean workers: based on the 6th Korean Working Conditions Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Weekend work was found to increase the risk of both physical and mental health problems of Korean workers, and the effect varied according to employment status. There is a need to design a comprehensive occupational health policy that reflects the characteristics of different employment statuses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cathode Interface Layer-Free Sequential-Deposited Nonfullerene Acceptor Organic Solar Cells Via a 3-(<em>N</em>,<em>N</em>-Dimethylamino)propyloxy-Flanked Benzo[1,2-b; 4,5-b']dithiophene Electron-Extracting Additive]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cathode interface layers (CILs), which are often built between the active layer and the metal cathode to facilitate electron collection and extraction, are highly necessary to develop stable and efficient organic solar cells (OSCs). However, most CILs are usually very sensitive to film thickness and work only in ultrathin films. In this study, 4,8-bis((N,N-dimethylamino)propyloxy)benzo[1,2-b,4,5-b']dithiophene (BDT-N) is utilized as an electron-attracting additive for sequential-deposited (SD)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward personalized therapeutic drug monitoring of ustekinumab in Crohn's disease: influence of previous exposure to biologics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ustekinumab TLs in patients may differ according to their prior exposure to biologic agents and disease activity. Accordingly, rather than applying a uniform threshold, ustekinumab levels should be interpreted using individualized, patient-specific strategies in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Strategy for Enhanced Delivery of Anti-Fibrotic miR-150 via PDGFR-Targeted Exosomes for Fibrosis Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings highlight the potential of PDGFR-tEx for efficient miR-150 delivery, demonstrating improved therapeutic efficacy with reduced systemic toxicity. This targeted approach may offer a more precise and effective treatment for liver fibrosis, surpassing conventional methods.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Intravascular Fluid Resuscitation on Whole Blood Viscosity During Endovascular Detachable Coiling Procedure for Unruptured Intracranial Aneurysm: A Prospective Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study showed that HES infusion provided significantly lower WBV than crystalloid infusion during the EDC procedure. Further study is warranted to determine whether the lower WBV after HES infusion would enhance clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Varicella Vaccine Effectiveness and Duration of Protection: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The two-dose vaccination demonstrated superior clinical efficacy compared to the one-dose vaccination, with protection slightly diminishing over time. These findings highlight the importance of implementing universal two-dose varicella vaccination programs in countries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exercise-induced modulation of IGF-1 in healthy, obese, and cancer populations: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Chronic exercise exerts health status-dependent effects on circulating IGF-1, supporting metabolic benefits in healthy and obese individuals and potentially contributing to cancer care by reducing IGF-1 in cancer patients or survivors. These findings demonstrate the complex endocrine response to exercise and support the therapeutic potential of tailored exercise prescriptions. .]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between changes in systolic blood pressure and the incidence of diabetes mellitus: a retrospective study based on the Korean National Health Screening Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: As the global prevalence of diabetes mellitus continues to increase, it is important to identify its risk factors and implement preventive approaches. This study aimed to investigate the association between changes in systolic blood pressure (SBP) and the incidence of diabetes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subcritical pitchfork bifurcation transition of a single nanoparticle in strong confinement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Confinement often influences the properties of fluids. Using molecular dynamics simulations with explicit solvents, we show that strong slit confinement induces a first-order transition between solvation states, where a nanoparticle either resides at the slit center or binds to the confining surfaces. We find that the stability transition of this bistable state follows a subcritical pitchfork bifurcation. Furthermore, along with the transition, the nanoparticle's lateral diffusion, which is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental observation of enhanced electron cyclotron resonance heating and nonlocal electron kinetics induced by Ramsauer-Townsend effect in ultralow electron temperature plasmas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The effect of the Ramsauer-Townsend effect, a quantum mechanical phenomenon, is investigated by generating an ultralow electron temperature plasma (T_{e}<1 eV) in a weakly magnetized inductively coupled argon plasma using a dc-biased grid. In the ultralow electron energy regime, the Ramsauer-Townsend effect is maximized, significantly reducing electron-neutral collisions. Consequently, electron cyclotron resonance (ECR) heating remains effective even at high pressures (ω_{c}≪ν), where it is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microscopic heat engines with hydrodynamic flow]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrodynamic flows are often generated in colloidal suspensions. Since colloidal particles are frequently used to construct stochastic heat engines, we study how the hydrodynamic flows influence the output parameters of the engine. We study a single colloidal particle confined in a harmonic trap with time-periodic stiffness that provides the engine protocol, in the presence of an externally applied steady linear shear flow. The nature of the flow (circular, elliptic, or hyperbolic) is externally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Speed limits for discrete-time Markov chains]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As a fundamental thermodynamic principle, speed limits reveal the lower bound of entropy production (EP) required for a system to transition from a given initial state to a final state. While various speed limits have been developed for continuous-time Markov processes, their application to discrete-time Markov chains remains unexplored. In this study, we investigate the speed limits in discrete-time Markov chains, focusing on two types of EP commonly used to measure the irreversibility of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knowledge and Self-Reported Practices in Central Line-Associated Bloodstream Infection Prevention Among Nurses: The Mediating Effect of Perceived Barriers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perceived barriers play a crucial role in the adherence of ICU nurses to self-reported CLABSI prevention practices.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeepCOI: a large language model-driven framework for fast and accurate taxonomic assignment in animal metabarcoding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabarcoding remains challenging due to incomplete taxonomic annotations and computationally intensive processes. We present DeepCOI, a large language model-based classifier pre-trained on seven million cytochrome c oxidase I gene sequences. DeepCOI enables fast and accurate taxonomic assignment across eight major phyla, achieving an AU-ROC of 0.958 and AU-PR of 0.897-outperforming existing methods while significantly reducing inference time. Additionally, DeepCOI demonstrates interpretability...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reliability and validity of virtual reality box &amp; block test in healthy adults and patients with stroke: a prospective, multi-center, exploratory, cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The VR-BBT demonstrated strong reliability and validity despite differences in performance counts compared to BBT. The affected hand showed greater movement distance but lower speed, indicating inefficient motor control. These parameters were significantly associated with FMA-UE, suggesting their potential as objective markers of upper limb motor impairment. These findings suggest that the VR-BBT could serve as a complementary tool for motor function assessment, with potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and predictors of self-medication with antibiotics among adults in Santo Domingo and the National District, Dominican Republic: an online cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patterns and trends in infection control nursing research: text network analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study confirmed that keywords revealed through text network analysis were medical workers, vaccines, and gloves. Vaccine was closely related to terms such as influenza, hepatitis, and healthcare provider, while the term gloves was closely related to respiratory protection, injury and needles, and healthcare provider. Infection control for healthcare providers is based on evidence-based knowledge and practices, and quality evaluation of the evidence and verification of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skeletal muscle loss and associated clinical outcomes in patients with small-cell lung cancer receiving concurrent chemoradiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41249994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Skeletal muscle loss during CCRT, particularly a decrease in L3 SMI, was associated with inferior overall survival in LD-SCLC patients. Monitoring and mitigating skeletal muscle loss may improve patient prognosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41249994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of deep learning models for real-time neural tissue segmentation in spinal endoscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41249940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41249940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating Causal Treatment Effects in the Sequential Parallel Comparison Design (SPCD)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41249861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The high placebo responses observed in many placebo-controlled randomized clinical trials, particularly in psychiatric research, have hindered the demonstration of treatment efficacy. To address this issue, Fava proposed the Sequential Parallel Comparison Design (SPCD) in 2003, which aims to mitigate the placebo response by estimating a pooled treatment effect (denoted by Δ SPCD $$ {\Delta}_{\mathrm{SPCD}} $$ ). This is achieved by combining the treatment effect observed in the first stage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41249861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Genetically Encoded and Potent PDE6D Inhibitor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PDE6D is a trafficking chaperone of prenylated proteins, such as small GTPases. Several small molecule inhibitors have been developed against it, given that the oncogene K-Ras is one of the cargo proteins. Inhibitor development suffers from the fact that inhibitors against the hydrophobic pocket of PDE6D are typically poorly water-soluble. Herein, the development of genetically encoded inhibitors that are inspired by high-affinity natural cargo of PDE6D is described. The most potent inhibitor,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Molecular Size on Ocular Drug Distribution After Intravitreal Injection Using Computed Tomography and Mathematical Spatial Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Using computational spatial modeling based on CT images, we identified the effect of molecular size on ocular drug distribution after intravitreal injection in humans. These findings are expected to aid the establishment of appropriate times to maintain the supine position to ensure targeted exposure in accordance with modality size, as well as the estimation of optimal clinical doses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence prediction of age from echocardiography as a marker for cardiovascular disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While chronological age is a universal risk predictor across most populations and diseases, distinguishing between biologically older from younger individuals may identify individuals with accelerated or delayed cardiovascular aging. This study presents a deep learning model to predict age from echocardiogram videos, leveraging 2,610,266 videos from 166,508 studies from 90,738 patients. Leveraging multi-view echocardiography, our model achieved a mean absolute error (MAE) of 6.76 (6.65-6.87)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progression-free survival for unresectable non-metastatic locally advanced pancreatic cancer after surgical microwave ablation plus durvalumab and tremelimumab: phase-2 non-randomized prospective clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that CD8-Temra cells may serve as potential biomarkers and therapeutic targets for immunotherapy efficacy in pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma, pending validation in larger cohorts. We hypothesize that local tumor ablation may enhance tumor immunogenicity and systemic anti-tumor responses, supporting their integration into future treatment strategies. Future studies with larger cohorts are needed to validate these findings and optimize treatment protocols for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disentangling the architectural and non-architectural functions of CTCF and cohesin in gene regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cohesin- and CTCF-mediated chromatin loops facilitate enhancer-promoter and promoter-promoter interactions, but their impact on global gene regulation remains debated. Here we show that acute removal of cohesin or CTCF in mouse cells dysregulates hundreds of genes. Cohesin depletion primarily downregulates CBP/p300-dependent putative enhancer targets, whereas CTCF loss both up- and downregulates enhancer targets. Beyond loop anchoring, CTCF directly modulates transcription, acting as an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long intervals between repetitive concussions reduce risk of cognitive impairment and limit microglial activation, astrogliosis, and tauopathy in adolescent rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although previous studies have demonstrated the effects of concussions do not accumulate as the time interval between injuries increases, little is known about the relationship between this interval and the effects of repetitive concussions. The objective of this study is to explore the relationship between the time interval and changes in behavior and histology following repetitive concussions. Male adolescent rats received concussions by weight drop and were randomly assigned to one of five...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MAFB regulates hematopoietic stem cell proliferation and maintenance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MAFB, a transcription factor of the large Maf family, is expressed in both fetal liver (FL) and bone marrow (BM) hematopoietic stem cells (HSCs). However, its stage-specific roles remain elusive. Here, we reveal that MAFB plays distinct roles in FL and BM HSCs. Using Mafb-deficient and Mafb-GFP knock-in mouse models, we demonstrate that Mafb deletion enhances proliferation, cell cycle entry, and myeloid differentiation of FL HSCs, leading to enhanced chimerism rate in transplantation assays....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41254014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Taking the eye-tracker out to dinner: characterizing spatial attention biases during an everyday behavior using computer vision]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Visual exploration during everyday tasks reveals attentional processes and offers promising avenues for clinical assessment. In this study, we examined whether the spatial attention bias induced by the presence of a mobile phone during a routine activity, eating dinner, can be effectively captured using wearable sensors that record gaze and body orientation. In a within-subject design, participants ate spaghetti while their mobile phone was either absent or placed on the left or right side of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between gestational age and child health and neurodevelopment in twins from a nationwide longitudinal survey in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite previous research, evidence on the relationship between gestational age and long-term health and neurodevelopmental outcomes among twins remains limited. Using data from the Longitudinal Survey of Babies in the 21st Century, we analyzed 549 twins born in Japan in 2010. The twins were grouped by gestational age: <32 weeks (very preterm), 32-36 weeks (moderately and late preterm), and 37-38 weeks (early term). The health status was evaluated by hospitalization between 0.5 and 5.5 years,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional and genomic characterization of polyethylene degrading yeast Meyerozyma carpophila M6.0.2 isolated from marine plastic debris in East Java Indonesia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyethylene (PE) is a primary contributor to environmental plastic pollution, posing a critical risk to ecosystems and living organisms. This study screened six yeast strains (BI.4.1.1, K3.1.2, M.5.0.1, M.5.0.3, M.6.0.1, and M.6.0.2) isolated from marine plastic debris in East Java, Indonesia, for their ability to degrade PE. Among these, Meyerozyma carpophila M6.0.2 demonstrated functional characteristics with the highest polyethylene-degrading activity in liquid medium after a 10-day...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of convolutional neural networks for automated brain-wide histopathological analysis in mouse models of synucleinopathies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preclinical animal models are indispensable for uncovering disease mechanisms and developing novel therapeutic interventions in synucleinopathies. Key readouts including neuronal cell death, neuroinflammation and alpha-synuclein protein aggregation, are routinely assessed by histological methods. However, traditional characterization of histological samples is labor-intensive and time-consuming. There is a growing need for reproducible and high-throughput tools to capture region- and cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural basis of vilazodone dual binding mode to the serotonin transporter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The serotonin transporter (SERT) plays a pivotal role in regulating serotonin (5-HT) signaling and is a key target in the treatment of psychiatric disorders. SERT has a binding site (S1) for 5-HT that also serves as a high-affinity binding site for antidepressants. The antidepressant vilazodone has been shown to inhibit SERT by binding to an allosteric site. Here, we present the cryo-EM structure of SERT with vilazodone bound to the S1 site and extending towards the allosteric site. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sub-400 nanometer-thick skin and environment adaptable organohydrogel nanofilm epidermal electrode]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogels are crucial for soft bioelectronics in long-term health monitoring; however, reconciling skin comfort with environmental resilience remains a major challenge. We present a 392 nm-thick organohydrogel nanofilm electrode that mimics skin deformation, offers high gas/water vapor/sweat permeability and heat transfer, and remains functional under various extreme conditions. The electrode comprises a genipin-crosslinked gelatin matrix, reinforced by polyurethane nanomeshes and plasticized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multistimuli-Responsive Porous Organic Polymers for Drug-Gas Anticancer Combination Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Combination therapies can significantly aid in the treatment of biologically complex diseases, including cancer. These powerful therapies, such as combination nitric oxide (NO) gas and chemotherapy, are able to simultaneously target different biological targets, thereby overcoming or reducing drug resistance and decreasing dose-related toxicity. However, in nearly all existing carriers, gases and drugs compete for loading in the same physical space of the carrier and can thus interfere with each...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Energetic profiling reveals thermodynamic principles underlying amyloid fibril maturation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amyloid fibrils adopt diverse structural polymorphs linked to disease-specific phenotypes, but the thermodynamic principles guiding their formation and maturation remain unclear. Here, we apply energetic profiling to structural time series from cryo-EM datasets of IAPP, tau, and α-synuclein to decode the principles governing fibril maturation and polymorphic divergence. By mapping residue-level free energy contributions across experimentally resolved assembly pathways, we reconstruct their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxidative Generation of Isobenzofurans for Intermolecular Cycloadditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A tandem oxidation/Diels-Alder reaction of phthalans was investigated. It was found that phthalans can be oxidized with DDQ to provide isobenzofurans, which immediately undergo Diels-Alder reaction with dienophiles such as benzoquinone, affording oxygen-bridged polycycles in modest to good yields. The reaction was rendered catalytic by the use of Mn(OAc)(3) as a co-oxidant. A portionwise addition of DDQ proved to be effective when using reactive phthalans as IBF precursors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Finger motion required for Auslan: A biomechanical analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Effective Auslan communication requires greater finger ROM on the dominant hand, particularly for the index, middle, and ring fingers. Rehabilitation strategies should prioritize motion preservation in these joints. Conversely, lower ROM demands on the non-dominant hand suggest motion-sacrificing interventions may be more viable and appropriate for certain joints without compromising function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeted Protein Interactions Driven by Hybrid Vanadium-Oxo Clusters in Solution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-oxo clusters, specifically polyoxometalates (POMs), have garnered significant attention due to their potential as powerful bioinorganic catalysts capable of modulating protein functions through targeted interactions. Herein, we investigate the solution-based interactions between the hybrid vanadium-oxo cluster [V(6)O(13){(OCH(2))(3)CCH(2)OH}(2)]^(2-) (V(6)-OH) and hen egg white lysozyme (HEWL), utilizing a combination of ^(51)V NMR spectroscopy, cyclic voltammetry (CV), fluorescence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intestinal blood vessel-associated macrophages and gut-vascular barrier dysfunction in cirrhosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study emphasises the critical role of intestinal macrophages in preventing the dissemination of luminal bacteria and highlights the multifaceted breakdown of the intestinal barrier in cirrhosis and the importance of the gut-vascular barrier.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mucosal viral infection elicits long-lived IgA responses via type 1 follicular helper T cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although immunoglobulin A (IgA)^(+) long-lived plasma cells (LLPCs) generated following mucosal viral infection provide durable protection against reinfection, little is known about their generation. Here, we show that rotavirus (RV) infection induces gut-resident LLPCs that produce highly mutated, protective IgA. Unlike RV-specific immunoglobulin G (IgG)^(+) LLPCs, IgA^(+) LLPCs were generated independently of major histocompatibility complex class II (MHC class II) expression by dendritic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship Between Shoulder External Rotation and Glenohumeral Joint Alignment Changes in Baseball Players]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clarification of glenohumeral joint alignment changes during the late cocking phase may reveal the mechanisms of throwing injuries. This study aimed to determine the effect of shoulder external rotation on humeral head center deviation relative to the scapular glenoid. Twenty-eight baseball players participated. The anteroposterior deviation of the humeral head center relative to the glenoid (humeral head translation) and the distance between the humeral head and posterior glenoid rim...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Socially parasitic ant queens chemically induce queen-matricide in host workers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Matricide - the killing of a mother by her own genetic offspring - is rarely observed in nature, but not unheard-of. Among animal species in which offspring remain with their mothers, the benefits gained from maternal care are so substantial¹ that eliminating the mother almost never pays, making matricide vastly rarer than infanticide. Here, we report matricidal behavior in two ant species, Lasius flavus and Lasius japonicus, where workers kill resident queens (their mothers) after the latter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical characteristics and healthcare resource utilization among patients hospitalized for pulmonary tuberculosis: A national inpatient database study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Early discharge may be feasible for a subset of hospitalized pulmonary tuberculosis patients in Japan and could contribute toward optimizing healthcare resource utilization by reducing hospitalization costs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dispersibility criteria based on Hansen solubility parameters for perovskite nanocrystals via ligand-assisted reprecipitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lead halide perovskite nanocrystals (PeNCs) are in high demand for industrial applications. Among the numerous synthetic routes, the ligand-assisted reprecipitation method has emerged as a promising approach owing to its low energy requirements and feasibility under ambient conditions at room temperature, which is advantageous from an industrial standpoint. Controlling the dispersibility of PeNCs during the fabrication process is crucial for enhancing the product yield. However, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41253037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydroxylation and dechlorination of chlorinated paraffins by human cytochrome P450 monooxygenases and prediction of its metabolic sites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chlorinated paraffins (CPs) are a mixture of chlorine-substituted n-alkanes detected in the environment, wildlife, and humans and toxic to organisms. CPs are metabolized by cytochrome P450 (CYP, P450) monooxygenases contained in human hepatic microsomes. However, studies on the metabolism of CPs by human P450s and in silico analyses to reveal the structural basis of CP metabolism are limited. Therefore, this study showed that enzymes in human hepatic microsomes hydroxylated and dechlorinated CPs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of microcalcification cluster detection in wide-angle flying focal spot digital breast tomosynthesis and synthetic mammography: A virtual imaging study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Increasing the dose to the central projections or reducing the angular range from 50° to 40° did not significantly affect calcification detection in DBT or SM compared to the standard AEC setup for an FFS system.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationships between single-leg hop for distances of four types at 6 Months after anterior cruciate ligament reconstruction and knee joint function, disturbed body perception, and movement-specific fear]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the need to integrate not only muscle strengthening but also assessments addressing disturbed body perception and movement-specific fear into rehabilitation programs aimed at facilitating return-to-sport after ACLR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimal social co-presence modulates heartbeat evoked potentials and EEG dynamics during a parallel crafting task]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Minimal social context alters the brain's processing of cardiac signals and its autonomic relationship in healthy young adults, establishing a neurophysiological benchmark for brain-body-society interactions. As this study used a non-clinical sample, the findings are not direct evidence of HEP's clinical utility. This work provides a foundational baseline for future comparative studies needed to determine its potential as a clinical biomarker.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two strategies to improve stability in a precision-based task: Insights from the badminton short serve]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The badminton short serve is a highly precise task requiring accurate control of racquet face orientation, which directly influences shuttlecock trajectory and limits an opponent's ability to attack. Previous studies on motor redundancy have emphasized covariation among elemental variables as the primary mechanism for stabilizing performance. However, when the sensitivities of elemental variables differ, performance can also be stabilized by unevenly distributing individual variances without...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A critical review of cushion gas in underground hydrogen storage: Thermophysical properties, interfacial interactions, and numerical perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Underground hydrogen storage (UHS) represents a large-scale energy storage system, aiming to ensure a consistent supply by storing hydrogen generated from surplus energy. In the practice of UHS, cushion gas is typically injected into the formation to maintain reservoir pressure for efficient hydrogen withdrawal. This paper reviews the impact of cushion gas on the performance of UHS from both experimental and numerical simulation perspectives. The thermophysical (e.g., density, viscosity,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanding lung volume reduction surgery indications: Outcomes in patients beyond conventional NETT criteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Beyond-criteria patients can be considered for LVRS when guided by careful multidisciplinary evaluation, with meaningful improvement in experienced centers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valuing Quality in Aged Care: A Cost-Benefit Framework for interRAI Implementation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Improving aged care quality is a global priority. Effective monitoring and evaluation systems are the mechanism through which this priority can be realized. The interRAI consortium offers an integrated clinical information system that spans multiple care settings to support quality improvement in clinical care, meeting policy, industry, and recipient needs. However, the economic value of implementing these systems remains unknown, complicated by challenges in monetizing relevant costs and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding of Authorship Guidelines and the Frequency of Authorship Misuse: A Descriptive Cross-Sectional Study in the State of Qatar]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ethical authorship practices ensure both accountability and credibility. In this study, we estimated the frequency of encountering honorary and ghost authorship at least once among researchers at Hamad Medical Corporation (HMC) in Qatar. Additionally, we evaluated researchers' familiarity with standard authorship guidelines. Using a cross-sectional design, we administered a pre-developed anonymous online survey to 4043 researchers. Descriptive statistics in the form of percentages and frequences...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cyclometalated Iron(II) Thiolate Complexes Featuring Diazine Rings: π-Acceptor Character of the C,N-Chelate Moiety]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The combination of electron-donating and π-accepting groups is a compelling strategy in the development of polydentate ligands. A series of thiolate iron(II) complexes featuring N,C,S-tridentate ligands (L(N,C,S)), formulated as trans-[Fe(L(N,C,S))(CO)(PMe(3))(2)], was synthesized from dibenzothiophene derivatives containing a diazine ring (pyridazine, pyrimidine, or pyrazine) via C-S bond cleavage. The π-acceptor character of the N-donor site in L(N,C,S) was demonstrated by comparing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into the G-protein subtype selectivity revealed by human sphingosine-1-phosphate receptor 3-G<sub>q</sub> complexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sphingosine-1-phosphate (S1P) is one of the most extensively studied bioactive lipids that transduces signals via the S1P receptor (S1PR) family (S1PR1-5), a class of G-protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs), to regulate immune cell migration, vascular permeability, and pain modulation. However, the mechanism for achieving specificity in downstream signaling remains poorly understood. Here, we present cryogenic electron microscopic structures of the S1PR3-G(αq) complex bound to endogenous agonists:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diabetic Ketoacidosis and Severe Hypoglycemia Risks with Ipragliflozin/Insulin Versus Insulin in Type 1 Diabetes: A Japanese Real-World Database Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ipragliflozin/insulin combination therapy showed no difference in the incidence of DKA, but a lower incidence of SH, versus insulin therapy in patients with T1D in Japan. These results suggest that ipragliflozin treatment is not associated with increased incidences of initial DKA or SH; however, its use should be accompanied by appropriate monitoring, education, and risk mitigation strategies to minimize the occurrence of these events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breast reconstruction-related complications from postmastectomy radiation therapy in stage II-III breast cancer: sub-analysis of a multi-institutional observational study (Reborn-03)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PMRT was associated with an increased incidence of BR-related complications in prosthetic BR, but not with reoperation, irrespective of the reconstruction method.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41252041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of encapsulating peritoneal sclerosis associated with tuberculous peritonitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a case of encapsulating peritoneal sclerosis (EPS) associated with tuberculous peritonitis. A man in his 50s presented with fever, anorexia, and abdominal distension and was urgently hospitalized because computed tomography (CT) revealed ascites. Despite hospitalization for 1 month, the diagnosis remained unclear and his condition worsened; therefore, the patient was transferred to our hospital. At our hospital, his fever reached approximately 38 °C and an upper abdominal mass was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are weight control and food waste a trade-off?: A clustering of pre-meal portion planning and plate-clearing behaviors among Japanese adult consumers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results support the possibility of a trade-off between food waste and weight gain if PPP-O is not implemented.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinicopathological features and prognosis of metastatic tumors in the small bowel: a large multicenter analysis of the JSCCR database in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The lung cancer is the most frequent primary tumor of metastatic tumors in the small bowel. Surgical intervention was associated with improved survival outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Goddard score for emphysema predicts the postoperative prognosis in pancreatic cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The GS, a simple radiological index of emphysema, may serve as a novel preoperative prognostic indicator in patients undergoing pancreatic cancer surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A LAT1-selective PET tracer, 5-[¹⁸F]F-αMe-3BPA, as a companion to its structurally matched ¹⁰B analog in boron neutron capture therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The 5-[¹⁸F]F-αMe-3BPA/5F-αMe-3[¹⁰B]BPA theranostic pair demonstrates high LAT1 specificity, low normal tissue uptake, and strong pharmacokinetic alignment, enabling accurate prediction of therapeutic boron delivery for BNCT. Furthermore, 5-[¹⁸F]F-αMe-3BPA shows promise as a dedicated LAT1 imaging probe for advancing LAT1-targeted therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Localization of parvovirus B19 in the renal allografts of healthy donors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence of hyponatremia with different postoperative intravenous maintenance fluids: a single-center, prospective, randomized trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The use of postoperative fluids with a sodium concentration of 140 mmol/L significantly reduced the incidence of hyponatremia. There was no significant difference in the incidence of postoperative delirium.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing hydrogen adsorption on SnS<sub>2</sub> and SnSe<sub>2</sub> monolayers: alkali and alkaline earth metal decoration under external electric fields]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient hydrogen storage is essential for advancing clean energy technologies. In this study, based on density functional theory (DFT), we report the hydrogen storage functionality of the post-transition metal dichalcogenides including SnS(2) and SnSe(2) monolayers modified by decoration with alkali (Li, Na, K) and alkaline-earth (Mg, Ca) metals. We reveal that Ca-decorated SnS(2) and SnSe(2) offer the most favorable hydrogen adsorption, with binding energies of approximately -0.15 eV per...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microcondensate-Mediated Intracellular Infusion of mRNA Across the Plasma Membrane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a strategy for developing micrometer-sized coacervates comprised of cationic intracellular delivery peptide FcB(L17E)(3) and nucleic acids (termed "microcondensates") as a lipid nanoparticle (LNP)-free platform for intracellular messenger RNA (mRNA) delivery. The feasibility of this approach is demonstrated both in vitro and in vivo. This approach is based on our previous finding that FcB(L17E)(3) forms a microcondensate through interactions with IgG labeled with a negatively...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ongoing independent evolution of linezolid and vancomycin-resistance pELF-type linear plasmids across the One Health spectrum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vancomycin and linezolid are crucial for treating enterococcal infections. The global emergence of linezolid- and vancomycin-resistant enterococci is a growing concern. Enterococcal pELF-type linear plasmids, which confer both types of resistance, have been identified worldwide from clinical and environmental sources. Phylogenetic and structural analyses of pELF-type linear plasmids revealed that they diverged into two distinct lineages and evolved through the integration of circular plasmids....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obesity-induced leptin resistance is directly involved in skin fragility by decreasing type I collagen synthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The relationship between obesity-induced leptin resistance and skin function remains unclear. In this study, we examined the effects of leptin signaling on collagen production in mouse skin. Mice were divided into three groups: control diet, high-fat diet, and switching diet [from the high-fat diet to the control diet]. We measured the expression of leptin signaling-related genes and type I tropocollagen levels in the skin. In an additional experiment, leptin was administered to leptin-deficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a spore-based confrontation assay to screen for biocontrol organisms with antagonistic activity against oomycete and fungal pathogens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study showcases a versatile and robust spore-based screening that outperforms conventional screening methods. Through the use of the SBCA, two promising biocontrol strains with antagonistic activity against P. cactorum in strawberry were identified.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41251323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of total neoadjuvant therapy regimens on radiation-induced lymphopenia in locally advanced rectal cancer: a retrospective analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Total neoadjuvant therapy (TNT) improves oncological outcomes in locally advanced rectal cancer (LARC); however, treatment-induced lymphopenia remains a concern. We analyzed 74 patients undergoing three TNT regimens: long-course chemoradiotherapy with consolidation chemotherapy (LCCRT-CNCT), short-course radiotherapy with CNCT (SCRT-CNCT), and induction chemotherapy with LCCRT (INCT-LCCRT). Severe radiation-induced lymphopenia (RIL, Grade ≥ 3) occurred in 48%, 24%, and 54%, respectively (P =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single Inhalation of Peppermint Essential Oil Alleviates Acute Restraint Stress-Exacerbated Itch in Oxazolone-Induced Mild Dermatitis: Correlations With Brain Neuronal Activity in Female BALB/c Mouse]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Acute restraint stress exacerbates itch, and PEO inhalation alleviates the stress-associated aggravation of pruritus caused by OXA-induced dermatitis, which is associated with the modulation of neuronal activity in itch-related brain regions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature chaos as a logical consequence of the reentrant transition in spin glasses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Temperature chaos is a striking phenomenon in spin glasses, where even slight changes in temperature lead to a complete reconfiguration of the spin state. Another intriguing effect is the reentrant transition, in which lowering the temperature drives the system from a ferromagnetic phase into a less ordered spin-glass or paramagnetic phase. In the present paper, we reveal an unexpected connection between these seemingly unrelated phenomena in the finite-dimensional Edwards-Anderson model of spin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiple Notch ligands in the synchronization of the segmentation clock]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Notch signaling is a ubiquitous and versatile intercellular signaling system that drives collective behaviors and pattern formation in biological tissues. During embryonic development, Notch is involved in generation of collective biochemical oscillations that form the vertebrate body segments, and its failure results in embryonic defects. Notch ligands of the Delta family are key components of this collective rhythm, but it is unclear how different Delta ligands with distinct properties...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coupling an elastic string to an active bath: The emergence of inverse damping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We consider a slow elastic string with Klein-Gordon dynamics coupled to a bath of run-and-tumble particles. We derive and solve the induced Langevin-Klein-Gordon string dynamics with explicit expressions for the streaming term, friction coefficient, and noise variance. These parameters are computed exactly in a weak-coupling expansion. The induced friction is a sum of two terms: one entropic, proportional to the noise variance as in the Einstein relation for a thermal equilibrium bath, and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Passive objects in a chiral active bath: From microscopic to macroscopic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a detailed derivation of the Langevin dynamics obeyed by a massive rigid body immersed in a chiral active bath. We show how the antisymmetric nature of the noise leads to an unusual relationship between the Langevin equation describing stochastic trajectories and the Fokker-Planck equation governing the time evolution of the probability density. The chirality of the bath endows the object dynamics with odd diffusivity, odd mobility, and rotational ratchet effects that depend on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synchronization in bus systems with partially overlapping routes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In an increasingly interconnected world, understanding congestion-related phenomena in transportation and their underlying mechanisms is crucial for improving efficiency. As the transportation system becomes denser, different modes of transportation have more opportunities to interact with each other, giving rise to emergent dynamics that simple models cannot explain. In this study, we investigate the synchronized motion of indirectly coupled transportation modes. We develop a numerical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Universal trade-off between irreversibility and intrinsic timescale in thermal relaxation with applications to thermodynamic inference]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We establish a general lower bound for the entropy production rate (EPR) based on the Kullback-Leibler divergence and the logarithmic-Sobolev constant that characterizes the timescale of relaxation. This bound can be considered as an enhanced second law of thermodynamics. When applied to thermal relaxation, it reveals a universal trade-off relation between the dissipation rate and the intrinsic relaxation timescale. From this relation, a thermodynamic upper bound on the relaxation time between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41250408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251119023807&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>