<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 07:38:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Limosilactobacillus reuteri</em> ATG-F4 Improves the Muscle Strength and Muscle Mass of Mice with Immobilization-Induced Muscular Atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Probiotics offer a promising avenue for combating muscle atrophy, which is a debilitating condition associated with muscle disuse, aging, and disease. This study investigated the anti-atrophic potential of Limosilactobacillus reuteri ATG-F4, a human gut-derived bacterium, in a mouse model of staple-induced immobilization. ATG-F4 administration significantly preserved muscle mass and improved grip strength and endurance. Mechanistically, ATG-F4 activated mTOR signaling and promoted protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Anti-Inflammatory Potential of Isoembigenin: A Flavonoid Glycoside from <em>Piper aduncum</em> L. - A Case Exploration through <em>In Vitro</em>, <em>In Vivo</em>, and In Silico Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Piper aduncum L. has long been used in traditional medicine for its notable antimicrobial, anti-diarrheal, and anti-inflammatory properties. Flavonoids are recognized as the principal bioactive constituents of this plant, among which isoembigenin (IEGN) has been shown to inhibit dendritic cell-mediated inflammatory responses. However, its effects on other immune cell types involved in inflammation remain unclear. In this study, we examined whether IEGN pre-treatment could attenuate macrophage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TF-343 Recovered Cyclophosphamide-Induced Compromised Immune Status in a Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyclophosphamide (CP) exerts potent cytostatic and immunosuppressive effects by inhibiting the proliferation and function of tumor and immune cells, thereby being widely used for therapeutic approaches and molecular mechanism studies in immunocompromised models and autoimmune disease models. TF-343 is a mixed extract derived from medicinal plants with anti-inflammatory and antioxidant properties and exhibits anti-inflammatory activity by modulating signaling pathways associated with immune...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiomics Integration Reveals Microbial Gene Interactions Shaping Host Responses in a DSS-Induced Colitis Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) has been studied with a multi-omics approach to identify key contributors and unravel the biological complexity of its pathogenesis, aiding in the development of early diagnostic markers and therapeutic targets. The dextran sulfate sodium (DSS)-induced colitis mouse model, a widely used system for studying IBD, induces gut barrier disruption and proinflammatory responses, making it an ideal model for investigating host-microbiome interactions. This study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pt Nanoparticle Disintegration at Oxide Interfaces Enhances CO Oxidation Catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding how supported metal nanoparticles dynamically evolve under reaction conditions is critical for controlling their catalytic function. Here, the mechanism behind the dynamic disintegration of Pt nanoparticles (NPs) supported on CeO(x)-TiO(2) (CT) during CO oxidation is elucidated, leading to the formation of single atoms (SAs) and/or sub-nanometer clusters. Density functional theory (DFT) calculations reveal that strong Pt-CO interactions weaken Pt─Pt cohesion, while electronic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Most Two-Dimensional Bosonic Topological Orders Forbid Sign-Problem-Free Quantum Monte Carlo Simulation: Nonpositive Gauss Sum as an Indicator]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum Monte Carlo is a powerful tool for studying quantum many-body physics, yet its efficacy is often curtailed by the notorious sign problem. In this Letter, we introduce a novel criterion for the "intrinsic" sign problem in two-dimensional bosonic topological orders, which cannot be resolved by local basis transformations or adiabatic deformations of the Hamiltonian. Specifically, we find that the positivity of higher Gauss sums is a necessary condition for a two-dimensional bosonic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251020033759&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomic Force Microscopy Analysis of Bridging-Induced Phase Separation Mediated by SMC Proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structural maintenance of chromosome (SMC) protein is essential for chromosomal architecture and genome stability across all domains of life. SMC proteins, including cohesin, condensin, and the Smc5/6 complex, are known to organize chromosomes through DNA loop extrusion. However, recent atomic force microscopy (AFM) studies showed ATP-independent DNA-bridging-dependent cohesin/DNA condensate formation, suggesting bridging-induced phase separation (BIPS) for genome organization. Here, we present...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Benefit of Adjuvant Capecitabine According To Residual Cancer Burden in Patients With Triple-Negative Breast Cancer With Residual Disease Following Neoadjuvant Chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adjuvant capecitabine was most beneficial in patients with RCB-III disease, primarily through a reduction in distant metastasis. These findings support its selective use in high-risk TNBC populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of ultrasound-detected and undetected hepatocellular carcinomas: a post-hoc, subgroup analysis from the MAGNUS-HCC surveillance trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: US is less effective in detecting HCCs in patients with a higher BMI and tumors located in the blind spots or left hemiliver. These limitations should be considered in planning and interpreting surveillance strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Interactions between the Gut Microbiome, Health, and Metabolic Disorders in Preterm Infants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preterm birth, which occurs before the entire gestation is completed, causes serious health challenges for newborns. The gastrointestinal tract often shows delayed development and poor function in nutrient utilization and immune response. Preterm neonates are faced with difficulties in growth, are more vulnerable to infections, and have a higher risk of developing inflammatory diseases. One key factor in these outcomes is the abnormal development of intestinal microbiota. In premature neonates,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MMPP Attenuates the Inflammatory Response by Suppressing ROS and Proinflammatory Cytokine and Chemokine Production in TNF-α/IFN-γ-Stimulated Human Keratinocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Keratinocytes play a significant role in regulating skin immune homeostasis, and their dysregulation is central to chronic inflammatory disorders such as atopic dermatitis and psoriasis. Inflammatory mediators such as tumor necrosis factor alpha (TNF-α) and interferon-gamma (IFN-γ) can disrupt this balance, inducing abnormal cytokine and chemokine expression that promotes immune cell infiltration and chronic inflammation in the skin. While (E)-2,4-bis(p-hydroxyphenyl)-2-butenal (BHPB) has shown...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Similar Microbial Carbon Limitation with Soil Depth despite Decreasing Carbon Availability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbon availability regulates the rate of microbial soil organic matter decay and respiration. However, it remains unclear how much carbon is available to microbes, and if soil organic carbon content influences microbial carbon limitation. Here, the Michaelis-Menten parameters (V(max) and k(m)) were employed to estimate available carbon and the degree of carbon limitation along soil depth profiles (0-60 cm) at two study sites with varying soil organic carbon content. Available carbon as well as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Lactiplantibacillus plantarum</em> WB3801 and <em>Lactiplantibacillus plantarum</em> WB3808 Showed Antioxidant Effect and Anti-Apoptosis through Activation of the Keap1/Nrf2/HO-1 Pathway in H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub>-Induced HT-29 Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oxidative stress, primarily triggered by elevated levels of reactive oxygen species (ROS) contributes to intestinal epithelial injury and apoptosis, and is closely associated with gastrointestinal disorders. In this study, we evaluated the cytoprotective effects of three Lactiplantibacillus plantarum strains (WB3801, WB3804, and WB3808) isolated from Korean kimchi against H(2)O(2)-induced oxidative stress in HT-29 cells. The strains exhibited markedly strong acid and bile tolerance, as well as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overall Survival with Abemaciclib in Early Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Adjuvant abemaciclib-ET resulted in a statistically significant and clinically meaningful improvement in OS compared to ET in patients with HR+, HER2-, node-positive, high-risk EBC. At 7 years, abemaciclib-ET continued to demonstrate a sustained IDFS and DRFS benefit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adjuvant nivolumab versus placebo for high-risk muscle-invasive urothelial carcinoma: 5-year efficacy and ctDNA results from CheckMate 274]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Five-year results confirm durable DFS benefit and consistent safety profile for adjuvant nivolumab in high-risk MIUC. Post-hoc exploratory ctDNA assessment identified patients at highest risk of recurrence and may inform tailored adjuvant therapy strategies, pending further validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[\zaAlectinib versus crizotinib in previously untreated ALK-positive advanced non-small cell lung cancer: Final overall survival analysis of the Phase III ALEX study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These final OS data show the sustained long-term systemic and intracranial efficacy of alectinib in the first-line treatment of ALK-positive NSCLC and confirm alectinib as a standard of care in this setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International consensuses and guidelines on diagnosing and managing Coats' disease by the Academia Retina Internationalis (ARI), Asia-Pacific Vitreo-retina Society (APVRS) and the Asia-Pacific Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coats' disease is a rare, retinal vascular disorder characterized by telangiectasias, aneurysmal dilations, and progressive exudative retinal detachment. Limited understanding of the disease warranted the need to identify controversial issues in through extensive literature search and debate discussion of the international panel of experts. Extensive literature search was done on multiple aspects of the disease-classification patterns, disease, Coats plus and Coats-like response. Other key...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural-Functional Brain Network Modulation using Transcranial Focused Ultrasound Stimulation: Implications on the Default Mode Network in Humans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transcranial focused ultrasound (tFUS) has emerged as a promising noninvasive technique for brain stimulation due to its precise focusing and deep penetration capabilities. However, its potential to modulate brain networks beyond the stimulation site and optimal sonication parameters required for such modulation remain unclear. In light of this knowledge gap, this study investigates the effects of tFUS targeted at the medial prefrontal cortex (mPFC), a key component of the default mode network...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiological and Clinical Outcomes of Monoaxial Versus Polyaxial Screw Constructs in C1 Jefferson Fracture Osteosynthesis: A Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Monoaxial screws provided superior anterior arch reduction, lateral mass realignment, and shorter operative time without compromising motion or clinical outcomes. Both constructs yielded similar improvements in pain and function. Screw selection has significant implications for radiological correction in motion-preserving surgery for unstable C1 fractures; however, larger prospective studies are warranted to determine the long-term outcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to comments by Kong et al]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population health impacts of national health insurance coverage for neonatal intensive care unit admission in South Korea: evidence from regression discontinuity analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: NICU coverage showed no mortality benefit for the most vulnerable infants and may have led to overuse near full-coverage thresholds. Targeted policies and rigorous evaluation are needed to maximize benefits and avoid harm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermal processing effects on phytochemical profiles, antioxidant activity, and anti-inflammatory potential of extracts from dried rhizomes of Curcuma longa L. evaluated by UHPLC-MS/MS and in vitro assays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study developed and validated UHPLC-MS/MS methods for quantifying seven phytochemicals-five major bioactives (curcuminoids, sesquiterpenoids) and two thermal degradation products (vanillin, dehydrozingerone)-in Curcuma longa L. extracts. Samples were heat-treated (180 °C) in four matrices (dry, water, olive oil, corn oil), and antioxidant and anti-inflammatory activities were evaluated. While curcuminoids degraded significantly under aqueous heating (up to 71.3 % loss), ar-turmerone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of brigatinib after alectinib in patients with ALK-positive NSCLC: Integrated analysis of the ALTA-2 and J-ALTA studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This integrated analysis showed that brigatinib has clinically meaningful activity after disease progression on alectinib.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking carbon lock-in: How data factor marketization propels low-carbon transformation in heavy-polluting enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In modern economies, data factors have become crucial catalysts for the revolutionary advancement of heavily polluting sectors. The market-driven distribution of these data assets not only generates significant economic benefits but also provides essential assistance for establishing a sustainable development framework. This paper selects the creation of China's data trading platforms as a quasi-natural experiment, analyzing data from A-share listed companies in heavily polluting industries from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of maximal handgrip strength and handgrip strength asymmetry with suicidal behaviors: Evidence from a nationally representative sample of Korean adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epilepsy in children and adolescents with B-cell acute lymphoblastic leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Most seizures in patients with B-ALL were provoked and resolved without the need for long-term antiseizure medication treatment. Acute or subacute MTX neurotoxicity accounted for the majority of provoked seizures. However, these rarely progressed to epilepsy. Long-term neurological surveillance is important in B-ALL survivors, especially those with delayed seizure onset or magnetic resonance imaging evidence of leukoencephalopathy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asymmetric Mechano-Electrochemical Energy Harvesting System with Surface Charge-Modified Carbon Nanotube Yarn for Wearable Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mechano-electrochemical harvesters are being explored for various applications, including wearable and implantable devices. However, their application in practical devices still requires the development of a structurally optimized two-electrode system to avoid mutual voltage cancellation. Herein, the two-electrode system is improved by enhancing individual electrode performance and resolving voltage cancellation through polarity-controlled electrode design via asymmetric surface charge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision Measurement of Net-Proton-Number Fluctuations in Au+Au Collisions at RHIC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report precision measurements on cumulants (C_{n}) and factorial cumulants (κ_{n}) of (net) proton number distributions up to fourth order in Au+Au collisions over center-of-mass energies sqrt[s_{NN}]=7.7-27 GeV from phase II of the Beam Energy Scan program at RHIC. (Anti)protons are selected at midrapidity (|y|<0.5) within a transverse momentum range of 0.4<p_{T}<2.0 GeV/c. Relative to various noncritical-point model calculations and peripheral collision 70%-80% data, the net proton...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision CP Symmetry Test and Polarization Analysis in Σ^{+} Decays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A stringent test of CP symmetry in hyperon decays is performed using 1.0×10^{10} J/ψ events and 2.7×10^{9} ψ(3686) events collected by the BESIII experiment. The CP asymmetry in the two-body nonleptonic weak decays Σ^{+}→pπ^{0} and Σ[over ¯]^{-}→p[over ¯]π^{0} is determined to be A_{CP}=-0.0118±0.0083(stat)±0.0028(syst), consistent with CP conservation. The average decay parameter ⟨α_{0}⟩=-0.9869±0.0011(stat)±0.0016(syst) represents the most precise measurement in the baryon sector to date. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical impact of gastrectomy in surgically proven stage IV gastric cancers: retrospective analysis from Korean multicenter dataset (PASS-META)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that gastrectomy offers a significant survival benefit to patients with surgically proven stage IV gastric cancer and limited peritoneal metastasis (P1/P2), distant lymph node (dLN1), or hepatic metastases (H1). Furthermore, specific surgical procedures such as extended lymph node dissection or minimally invasive surgery may be considered for patients undergoing gastrectomy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of candidate genes associated with resistance to Heterodera sojae in soybean]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We identified QTLs and candidate genes associated with resistance to Heterodera sojae and then designed KASP markers from candidate genes on chromosomes 1 and 18 for marker-assisted selection. Heterodera sojae is a recently discovered cyst nematode species that parasitizes soybean roots, reducing soybean growth and yield. However, genes associated with resistance to H. sojae in soybean remain unknown. A genome-wide association study of genes related to resistance to H. sojae was performed with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative Pembrolizumab for Locally Advanced Thymic Epithelial Tumors: A Single-Arm, Phase 2 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative pembrolizumab demonstrated promising rates of MPR, R0 resection, and long-term DFS in stage III to IV TETs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Updated Overall Survival Analysis From the Phase 2 PHAROS Study of Encorafenib Plus Binimetinib in Patients With BRAF V600E-Mutant Metastatic Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The phase 2 PHAROS study previously showed that encorafenib plus binimetinib has antitumor activity in patients with BRAF V600E-mutant metastatic non-small cell lung cancer (mNSCLC). In PHAROS, 98 patients (59 treatment naïve; 39 previously treated) received encorafenib 450 mg once daily and binimetinib 45 mg twice daily. We report updated results from data cutoff of March 14, 2025. The median duration of treatment with both encorafenib and binimetinib was 16.3 months in treatment-naïve and 5.5...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020033830&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Single- and Multiple-Dose Study to Characterize the Pharmacokinetics and Safety of Dotinurad in Healthy Chinese Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Single- and multiple-dose PK of dotinurad in healthy Chinese adults showed rapid absorption, rapid elimination, linear PK, and no accumulation with once-daily dosing. Dotinurad was well-tolerated during the 7-day treatment course.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Purification and In Vitro Analysis of Escherichia coli RecN]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The RecN protein, a member of the SMC (structural maintenance of chromosomes) family, is highly conserved among bacteria and plays a critical role in the repair of DNA double-strand breaks (DSBs). Like other SMC proteins, RecN forms a ringlike structure and exhibits topological DNA-binding activity, enabling it to encircle DNA molecules. This activity is thought to be essential for maintaining nucleoid integrity at DSB sites and facilitating RecA-mediated recombination reactions. Here, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Involvement of HYBID in the Regulation of Intraocular Pressure and Extracellular Matrix Accumulation in the Trabecular Meshwork]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Increased accumulation of extracellular matrix (ECM) in the trabecular meshwork (TM) causes a rise in intraocular pressure (IOP), which is a primary risk factor for glaucoma. Hyaluronan (HA) is essential for forming the ECM network, but it is unclear whether HA metabolism plays a role in IOP control. In this study, we focused on the hyaluronan-binding protein involved in hyaluronan depolymerization (HYBID, also referred to as cell migration inducing hyaluronidase 1 (CEMIP)/KIAA1199), which is an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TFOS DEWS III]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[(Dry eye disease, DED), ,, . (Tear Film & Ocular Surface Society, TFOS) (Dry Eye Workshop, DEWS III) 2017, :",, /, ,." :, ., .OSDI-6, ≥4. (non-invasive breakup time, NIBUT) <10, (≥308 mOsm/L>8 mOsm/L) , ., , >5;/>9;/≥2mm≥25%, . (,/) (,/,,,//) , , .]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between lumbosacral transitional vertebrae and adjacent segment disease after L4-5 lumbar interbody fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although LSTV did not increase the overall risk of ASD, type IIb LSTV required reoperation earlier, necessitating diligent postoperative monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Taxonomic and thematic generalization of safety behaviors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fear generalization refers to the spread of fear to novel stimuli. Recent evidence suggests that fear generalization is linked with inductive reasoning. In the inductive reasoning literature, inferences are stronger to taxonomically related stimuli that share conceptual features with the target stimulus (e.g., duck and swan), compared to thematically related stimuli that often co-occur with the target stimulus (e.g., duck and pond). Preliminary evidence also shows greater fear generalization to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Objective vs perceived sleep in Belgian occupational drivers: A field study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although SE was adequate, chronic sleep restriction was common. Group differences were minimal, suggesting that individual and environmental factors may outweigh driver type in influencing sleep. Subjective assessments only partially aligned with objective measures, reflecting a discrepancy between perceived and objective sleep.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraoperative symptom-guided plug size selection in sitting position Kobayashi plug surgery for patulous eustachian tube]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: KPS under local anesthesia in the sitting position allows for intraoperative symptom-based plug size selection, which may help reduce the need for revision surgery, especially in patients with active symptoms at the time of surgery. While the overall revision rate was 10.3%, it was markedly lower (2.4%) among symptomatic cases. Although the findings should be interpreted with caution due to the small sample size and retrospective design, this technique represents a promising approach...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refractory myoclonic epilepsy and progressive movement disorder arising from recurrent DHDDS variants in Japanese patients: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DHDDS-related disorders should be considered in patients with intellectual disability, epilepsy with early-onset eyelid myoclonia and myoclonic or myoclonic-atonic seizures, and movement disorders, including myoclonus and tremor, with slow progression. We identified polymicrogyria as a novel finding in DHDDS patients. For drug-resistant epilepsy in these patients, corpus callosotomy and fenfluramine may represent promising treatment options, with this report providing specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeted alpha therapy of ovarian cancer with <sup>212</sup>Pb-labeled anti-PTK7 antibody: On-site <sup>212</sup>Pb production and preclinical insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: [^(212)Pb]Pb-TCMC-chOI-1 was efficiently produced and demonstrated PTK7 specificity and potent cytotoxic efficacy, confirmed through both in vitro and in vivo studies. This highlights the therapeutic potential of [^(212)Pb]Pb-TCMC-chOI-1 for the treatment of metastatic HGSOC following IP administration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Swimming abnormalities and cognitive disruption in Japanese medaka (Oryzias latipes) from antiepileptic drug exposure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antiepileptic drugs (AEDs) exhibit pharmacological activity in the central nervous system, which is highly conserved across vertebrates; however, there is growing concern regarding their potential ecological impact on aquatic organisms. In this study, Japanese medaka (Oryzias latipes) were exposed to six different AEDs to assess the effects of these agents on swimming behavior and cognitive function. Of the six drugs tested, phenytoin, phenobarbital sodium, and levetiracetam induced significant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brace yourself: neural and computational insights into the experience of mental effort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The subjective experience of mental effort is critical for adaptive cognitive control, yet its neural and computational underpinnings remain elusive. Here, we combine hierarchical drift-diffusion modeling and EEG to investigate how trial-by-trial fluctuations in both preparatory and task-related neural activity shape subjective effort ratings. Participants performed an arithmetic task of variable difficulty, choosing task difficulty in advance, which allowed us to isolate neural signatures of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic impact of lung metastasis in patients treated with androgen receptor signaling inhibitors for castration-sensitive prostate cancer: data from the ULTRA-Japan Consortium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LM does not appear to be related to OS or TTCR in mCSPC patients treated with ARSI-based doublet therapy, indicating that its prognostic value may need to be reevaluated.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of FOLFOX for Japanese patients with advanced biliary tract cancer as second-line or later chemotherapy (JON2107-B study)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggested the efficacy and safety of FOLFOX as a second-line or later treatment option also for Japanese patients with advanced BTC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peri-procedural and 6-month outcomes of rotational atherectomy for highly calcified femoropopliteal lesions from Japanese postmarketing surveillance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Jetstream atherectomy system demonstrated high procedural and lesion success with acceptable complication rates in complex, calcified femoropopliteal lesions. These findings support its use in combination with drug-coated balloons in real-world Japanese clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251020033803&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Imaging Analysis of Internal Structural Complexity in Mouse Heart Organoids; Comparison to Mouse Embryonic Hearts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We have established mouse heart organoids (mHOs) that are characterized by the presence of atrium- and ventricle-like structures that mimic entire embryonic hearts. However, maturation was not uniform, and little is known about their trabeculation status. Given the essential role of the trabeculae in cardiac morphogenesis, a new method that combines imaging analysis with a machine learning model was developed for quantifying the internal complexity in developing mHOs in a timely manner. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Autopsy Case of Senile Dementia of the Neurofibrillary Tangle Type Presenting With Behavioural and Psychological Symptoms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["It's the only way i could honestly survive the pandemic": student involvement in sex work amid the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: In a campus-representative survey of students, the aims were: 1) describe participation in sex work among students in the U.S., 2) describe demographic and psychosocial characteristics of students involved in sex work, 3) understand student involvement in sex work amid the COVID-19 pandemic. Participants: 4,231 undergraduate and graduate students at a large public university in the U.S. Methods: A 136-item confidential online survey about health and relationships. Results: 3.2% (n =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral nicotine pouches have arrived at U.S. college campuses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: Examine trends in the prevalence of oral nicotine pouch (ONP) use among U.S. college students. Participants: During the Spring 2025 semester (January-early May), we enrolled 578 undergraduate and 888 graduate students from a large Midwestern University. Methods: Students completed an online survey assessing ONP use and their reasons for use/nonuse. Their history of using other substances and sociodemographic characteristics were also assessed. Results: For the undergraduate and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who participates in collegiate recovery programs? A survey of students in the US and Canada]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To characterize the demographics, recovery pathways, and support needs of students enrolled in Collegiate Recovery Programs (CRPs) across the U.S. and Canada. Participants: 246 students from 77 institutions who were currently enrolled in CRPs during the 2023-2024 academic year. Methods: Students completed an online survey assessing demographics, recovery history, mental health diagnoses, academic status, and use of on- and off-campus recovery supports. Results: Only 54.1% reported...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary carotenoids and acute respiratory infection in the general US population: NHANES 2003 - 2018]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this US national general population, our findings indicated that higher dietary carotenoid intake was inversely associated with ARI risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Third Annual Workshop on Fetal Alcohol Spectrum Disorders Prevention and Clinical Guidelines Research: Supports, Interventions, and Therapies for the Family and Child]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Entropy Amorphous Catalysts for Water Electrolysis: A New Frontier]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-entropy amorphous catalysts (HEACs) integrate multielement synergy with structural disorder, making them promising candidates for water splitting. Their distinctive features-including flexible coordination environments, tunable electronic structures, abundant unsaturated active sites, and dynamic structural reassembly-collectively enhance electrochemical activity and durability under operating conditions. This review summarizes recent advances in HEACs for hydrogen evolution, oxygen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111133/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Effect of age stratification on the association between carotid intima-media thickness and cognitive impairment in Chinese hypertensive patients: new insight from the secondary analysis of the China Stroke Primary Prevention Trial (CSPPT)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of office and home blood pressure control on cardiovascular events in relation to KDIGO risk categories: findings from the J-HOP study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic kidney disease (CKD) is a major risk factor for cardiovascular events, and controlling blood pressure (BP) is essential for reducing this risk in CKD patients. Although office BP is the standard for BP control in CKD, home BP monitoring more precisely predicts cardiovascular outcomes, especially across Kidney Disease: Improving Global Outcomes (KDIGO) risk categories. This study evaluated the differential impact of office and home BP control on cardiovascular event rates across KDIGO...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pak4-mediated crosstalk between necroptotic macrophages and tendon stem/progenitor cells contributes to traumatic heterotopic ossification formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The formation of traumatic heterotopic ossification (HO) is an abnormal repair process after soft tissue injury. Recent studies establish the involvement of immune cells and cellular metabolism in the tissue healing process; however, their role in HO remains unknown. Here, by using murine burn/tenotomy model in vivo and tendon stem/progenitor cells (TSPCs) osteogenic differentiation model in vitro, together with techniques including transgenic knockout, gene knockdown, transcriptome and proteome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antithrombotic Function of Dahuang Zhechong Pill and Its Active Ingredients: A Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decades' progress and prospects on maize functional genomics and molecular breeding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maize (Zea mays L.) is not only an important cereal crop, but also a model plant species for genetic, cytologic, genomic, and molecular studies. Maize possesses tremendous phenotypic and genetic diversity. During the past few decades, researchers have made significant advances in multiple areas, including the genomic compositions and variations of maize and its ancestors, the genetic and genomic bases of maize domestication and evolution, the genetic architecture of various agronomic traits...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell atlas of the esophageal squamous cell carcinoma immune ecosystem to predict immunotherapy response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Esophageal squamous cell carcinoma (ESCC) evolves within a highly interactive tumor microenvironment (TME) that shapes therapeutic response. We utilized mass cytometry to analyze over 10 million cells from 25 ESCC tumors, 24 adjacent nontumor tissues, and 23 peripheral blood samples, employing an extensive panel of 42 immune markers. The resulting atlas reveals a compartmentalized landscape with a reproducible paucity of CD4⁺ and CD8⁺ central memory T cells (TCM) in tumor sites. Reintroduction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacterial Metabolite-Derived NDM-1 Inhibitors: A Computational Strategy to Overcome β-Lactam Resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of New Delhi metallo-β-lactamase-1 (NDM-1) poses a major challenge to antibiotic therapy. This study addresses the urgent need for effective NDM-1 inhibitors by investigating bacterial-derived natural metabolites as potential therapeutic agents. A total of 300 bacterial secondary metabolites were screened using an induced-fit docking model, targeting key active site residues essential for NDM-1 enzymatic activity. Among them, 21 metabolites showed stronger binding affinities (- 6.8...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Biochemical Characterization of Fabry Disease Associated GLA Gene Variants: Data From a Large Cohort of 469 Thousand Genotyped Subjects of the UK Biobank Database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fabry disease (FD) is a lysosomal storage disease due to genetic variants in the GLA gene located on the X chromosome. Males are hemizygous, while many females are genetic mosaics due to the random inactivation of the X chromosome. While most of the identified variants are deleterious for GLA, in some cases, less rare gene variants have been considered responsible for some FD features. GLA variants were selected from the database of 469 thousand genotyped subjects of the UK Biobank database....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Posttraumatic Stress Symptoms, Functioning, and Suicidal Ideation in Older U.S. Veterans: A Network Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A dual-focus approach that addresses PTSD symptoms highly interconnected within the disorder and those most strongly linked to functional difficulties and suicide risk may help promote recovery among older veterans with full or subthreshold PTSD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESMO guidance on the use of Large Language Models in Clinical Practice (ELCAP)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ELCAP provides a three-tier framework and basic practical guidance for LLM use in oncology. ESMO supports efforts to use this framework to improve patient care, but warns against unsupervised or unvalidated use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<sup>177</sup>Lu-Dotatate versus high-dose long-acting octreotide for the treatment of patients with advanced, grade 1-2, well-differentiated gastroenteropancreatic neuroendocrine tumours (XT-XTR008-3-01): an open-label, randomised, phase III trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: XTR008 monotherapy showed superior efficacy versus high-dose long-acting repeatable (LAR) octreotide monotherapy in advanced GEP-NET tumours of all origins in a later-line treatment setting, with manageable safety, supporting its use as a new treatment option.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "E3 ubiquitin ligase RNF128 attenuates colitis and colorectal tumorigenesis by triggering the degradation of IL-6 receptors" [J. Adv. Res. 72 (2025) 107-120]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Entering a new era for exercise countermeasures in human spaceflight]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Framework for Sensory-to-Memory Weighting During Navigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Navigation operates on the weighting of different sources of information to guide path selection. Although navigational strategies are commonly categorized as either sensory-driven or memory-based, real-world navigation typically involves dynamic interactions between immediate sensory information and stored spatial knowledge. Here, we propose a theoretical framework that conceptualizes navigation along a dynamic continuum between sensory and memory reliance, with working memory serving as the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Hypoxia on Shikonin Biosynthesis of Arnebia euchroma Roots and Its Transcriptome Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shikonin derivatives from Arnebia euchroma (Royle) Johnst. roots possess significant economic value as pharmaceutical agents, natural dyes, and cosmetic additives. To investigate hypoxia's impact on shikonin biosynthesis and its mechanisms, we subjected A. euchroma roots to hypoxic stress (1% O(2)). Hypoxic roots remained white with minimal shikonin accumulation. Upon reoxygenation (≈20% O(2)), rapid shikonin synthesis occurred within 4 h. qRT-PCR revealed suppressed expression of shikonin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VasoTracker 2: Open-source software and hardware for tracking blood vessel diameter and assessing vascular function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[VasoTracker 2 is a collection of open-source tools for blood vessel diameter measurement and vascular physiology research, featuring automated diameter tracking software and low-cost myography hardware components. This blood vessel analysis platform addresses the need for accessible alternatives to expensive commercial vascular imaging systems by providing comprehensive tools for studying vessel reactivity and endothelial function. The software enables multipoint diameter tracking in branched...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A NATIONWIDE QUESTIONNAIRE SURVEY ON PREVENTION OF PERIOPERATIVE INFECTIONS IN UROLOGY]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[(Background) The purpose of this study was to investigate the current status of urologists regarding the prevention of perioperative infections in preparation for the revision of the Guidelines for the Prevention of Perioperative Infections in Urological Field (2015). (Methods) From January 26 to March 30, 2022, we administered questionnaires to members of the Japanese Urological Association on their adherence to the guidelines and administration methods of antimicrobial prophylaxis for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2 cumulative infection over the pandemic and its associated factors among healthcare workers in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Among healthcare workers in Japan, cumulative SARS-CoV-2 infection markedly increased after the emergence of the Omicron variant, whereas the proportion of undiagnosed cases has decreased throughout the pandemic. Younger people (<50 years), as well as physicians and nurses, have faced a higher risk of infection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retraction notice to "Ultrasound-guided erector spinae plane block improves analgesia after laparoscopic hepatectomy: a randomised controlled trial" [Br J Anaesth 129 (2022) 445-453]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article has been retracted: please see Elsevier Policy on Article Withdrawal (https://www.elsevier.com/about/policies/article-withdrawal). This article has been retracted at the request of the Editor-in-Chief, Professor Hugh C. Hemmings, following an internal review which concluded that the data and the methods presented are flawed and that the validity of the results presented has been affected.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eosinophilic Lung Diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The diagnosis of eosinophilic lung disease usually relies on characteristic clinical-imaging features and the demonstration of alveolar eosinophilia, while lung biopsy is generally not necessary. The etiology has practical implications, including interruption of a medicinal or illicit drugs, treatment of infections with parasites or fungi, or smoking cessation. The diagnosis of idiopathic eosinophilic pneumonia is considered only once all known causes of eosinophilia have been excluded,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary Alveolar Proteinosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pulmonary alveolar proteinosis (PAP) is a rare syndrome due to a number of underlying disorders, leading to accumulation of surfactant proteins in the alveoli and respiratory insufficiency. The diagnostic workup is aimed at identifying the underlying cause. Detection of GM-CSF neutralizing autoantibodies in serum confirms autoimmune PAP and rules out other causes. Whole lung lavage can effectively restore the alveolar function, but not cure the disease. Inhalational GM-CSF has shown to improve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary Langerhans Cell Histiocytosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pulmonary Langerhans cell histiocytosis (PLCH) is a rare cystic lung disease that affects young adults with exposure to cigarette smoke. PLCH granulomas infiltrate and destroy the wall of distal bronchioles. In adults, PLCH is usually isolated. The demonstration of constant activation of the mitogen-activated kinase pathway in all Langerhans cell histiocytosis (LCH) lesions has been a breakthrough in the understanding of the pathogenesis of LCH. Somatic mutations in RAS-RAF-MEK cascade...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Artificial Intelligence in Medical Education and Continuing Medical Education]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this article, we explore the transformative potential of artificial intelligence (AI) in medical education and continuing medical education. We discuss the rapid evolution of AI technology, particularly generative AI and large language models, and their implications for teaching and learning. We emphasize the importance of AI literacy, ethical considerations, and evidence-based approaches to integrating AI into medical education. We also highlight the evolving roles of educators and learners...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethical and Legal Considerations of Medical Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has the capacity to improve patient care through increasing clinical decision-making accuracy and reducing administrative burdens for clinicians. However, AI poses challenges in medical ethics due to its opaque nature, potential for bias, and ties to large amounts of patient data. This article provides a general overview of medical AI ethics and legal regulations at the time of writing. It includes a description of prominent bioethics principles applied to AI,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[γδ T cells and head and neck squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Head and neck squamous cell carcinoma (HNSCC) is a prevalent and aggressive malignant tumor with poor clinical prognosis. The immune system plays a critical role in tumor surveillance and response to therapy. Among various immune cell populations, γδ T (γδ T) cells, a unique subset of lymphocytes, have emerged as significant participants in the anti-tumor immune response and have attracted extensive attention in recent studies. This chapter discusses the unique properties of γδ T cells, their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gamma delta T cells: Multifaceted mediators in pregnancy and the pathogenesis of miscarriage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pregnancy represents a unique physiological process characterized by a delicate balance between immune tolerance and immune surveillance. Gamma delta (γδ) T cells, serving as a bridge between adaptive and innate immunity, play crucial roles in the maintenance and progression of pregnancy. Alteration in the proportion, subset and function of γδT cells can contribute to miscarriage. This review provides an insightful overview of the physiological roles of γδT cells during normal pregnancy,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[γδ T cells in prostate cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[γδ T cells are a distinct subset of T lymphocytes that recognize and attack cancer cells without needing major histocompatibility complex molecules, making them particularly useful against tumors that evade conventional immune detection. This chapter examines the role of γδ T cells in prostate cancer, especially their potential application in treating metastatic castration-resistant prostate cancer. γδ T cells exert cytotoxic effects through the recognition of stress-induced ligands and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of ageing on neural onset and offset responses in core and belt auditory cortex of alert macaque monkeys]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Age-related hearing loss is a ubiquitous malady in the geriatric population, yet the underlying neural mechanisms remain incompletely understood. We compared onset and offset responses of single neurons in the primary (A1), rostral (R) and caudolateral (CL) areas of the auditory cortex using spectral, spatial and temporal stimuli in a younger macaque monkey with normal-hearing and an aged macaque monkey with high frequency hearing loss. In the younger monkey, core areas exhibited a significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fentanyl blockade of K<sup>+</sup> channels contributes to wooden chest syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fentanyl is widely used perioperatively and illicitly as a drug of abuse. As a potent μ-opioid receptor agonist, fentanyl canonically inhibits excitability through Gα(i/o) intracellular signalling pathways resulting in analgesia and respiratory depression. However, fentanyl also paradoxically activates respiratory muscles causing a potentially lethal effect termed wooden chest syndrome. Here we show that fentanyl, but not morphine, causes a persistent tonic component of diaphragmatic muscle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dabrafenib plus trametinib vs encorafenib plus binimetinib in BRAF-mutant metastatic melanoma: a real-world propensity score-matched survival analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We found no evidence that encorafenib plus binimetinib is superior to dabrafenib plus trametinib in metastatic melanoma. These findings suggest that the choice between these combinations should be guided by tolerability profiles and economic considerations rather than efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Heart Rate on Biomechanical Characteristics of Aortic Aneurysm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reducing heart rate has been advocated as a pivotal therapeutic approach for patients with aortic aneurysm (AA), aiming to mitigate the risk of rupture. This study aims to investigate the effect of heart rate on the biomechanical characteristics of aneurysms. A patient-specific thoracic aortic aneurysm (TAA) model has been built, and the biomechanical characteristics of the aortic wall under different heart rate conditions, including atrial fibrillation (AF) condition, have been simulated by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra processed food consumption by urbanization level among US youth and adults: Cross-Sectional Analysis of NHANES 2013-March 2020]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Adults in rural areas consumed more UPF and less MPF than those in urban areas in terms of both energy and grams. There were few significant differences by urbanization among youth.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Natural History of Atrial versus Ventricular Secondary Tricuspid Regurgitation: Insights from the Bronx-Valve Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atrial secondary tricuspid regurgitation (A-STR) and ventricular secondary tricuspid regurgitation (V-STR) have unique physiological and anatomical differences, but long-term outcomes based on TR etiology remain poorly understood. This study aimed to assess the characteristics and outcomes of severe A-S and V-STR. Adults diagnosed with severe secondary TR between January 2017 and December 2019 in a quaternary-care health system were included. TR was classified into left-sided V-STR (left-sided...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between maternal serum metals mixtures and adverse birth outcomes: A prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maternal exposure to heavy metals is linked to adverse birth outcomes, but combined effects remain understudied. Examine associations between mid-pregnancy serum metals (Iron [Fe], Selenium [Se], Rubidium [Rb], Thallium [Tl], Antimony [Sb], and Iodine [I]) and preterm birth (PTB), congenital anomalies, low birth weight (LBW), macrosomia, SGA, and LGA. Prospective cohort (n = 429 mother-infant pairs). Serum metals quantified via ICP-MS. Bayesian kernel machine regression (BKMR) and weighted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of an in vitro release test (IVRT) method for a locally acting mesalamine suppository]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rectal suppositories are a common FDA-approved dosage form that are administered via the rectal route. Currently, there is limited information in the literature related to in vitrorelease test (IVRT) methods for rectal suppositories that may be utilized to support a demonstration of bioequivalence (BE).To facilitate a comparison of in vitrorelease rates between a reference listed drug (RLD) product and a prospective generic suppository product as a component of a BE approach, it is essential to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of a custom 3D-printed microfluidic aerosolizer for enhanced nose-to-brain delivery of nanoemulsion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nose to brain (N2B) delivery offers a potential means of bypassing challenges associated with drug delivery across the blood brain barrier. The goal of this study was to evaluate the in vivo efficacy of a rat-sized, 3D-printed nasal aerosol delivery system. Aerosolizer design and delivery parameters were assessed for their impact on aerosol droplet size. Additionally, the impact of nanoemulsion vehicle formulation on fluorophore retention and nasal tissue penetration was evaluated. Intranasal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the impact of changes in home location on adolescent lung function: an exposome-wide natural experiment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prenatal Exposure to Environmental Metal Mixtures and Social Development in Early Childhood: Evidence from a Birth Cohort and Mechanistic Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prenatal exposure to heavy metal mixtures may compromise early neurodevelopment via PPAR-mediated lipid metabolic dysregulation. These findings provide mechanistic evidence, highlight the vulnerability of early life to combined exposures, and support translational, mixture-informed frameworks for risk assessment and prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of children's urinary metals with blood RNA N<sup>6</sup>-methyladenosine and 2'-O-methyladenosine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Exposure to nonessential metals may be related to global Am levels in children. Further research is warranted to evaluate potential roles of Am and m⁶A in metal-induced toxicity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current global trends in meningococcal disease control, risk groups and vaccination: Consensus of the Global Meningococcal Initiative]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review outlines recent trends on invasive meningococcal disease (IMD) discussed at the latest meeting of the Global Meningococcal Initiative (GMI). There has been a re-emergence of the Hajj strain sublineage (serogroup W; ST-11 clonal complex), with travel to the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia being a critical factor in transmission. The epidemiology of IMD has also changed following the COVID-19 pandemic, with annual IMD cases increasing in many countries. For example, the highest number of IMD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The diet-derived gut microbial metabolite 3-phenylpropionic acid reverses insulin resistance and obesity-associated metabolic dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity-associated metabolic disorders, including type 2 diabetes and metabolic dysfunction associated fatty liver disease (MAFLD), are major global health burdens. While dietary polyphenols have shown promise in ameliorating these conditions, their efficacy is dependent on specialized gut microbial metabolism, and the underlying molecular mechanisms remain mostly elusive. Here, we demonstrate that dietary supplementation with polyphenol-rich elderberry (Eld) extract abrogates the effects of an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harmonization of reporting for detection of ALK genetic alterations in neuroblastoma - a SIOPEN Biology study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In high-risk neuroblastoma, identification of ALK activating genetic alterations is considered for clinical decision-making in relapse or more recently frontline treatment. The accurate diagnosis of genetic alterations requires harmonization of molecular techniques and reporting especially when these are considered as inclusion criteria for clinical trials. Analysis and validation was preformed across the 21 SIOPEN (International Society of Paediatric Oncology Europe Neuroblastoma) molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of colony size on activity rhythms of ants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thirty years of research into activity rhythms of ant colonies have contributed an improved understanding of this fascinating form of collective behavior. Yet, little is known about how the colony size influences the intensity and tempo of the rhythms. Here, we address this knowledge gap through a two-pronged approach, combining the re-evaluation of published experimental observations on California ant, Temnothorax rudis, with the formulation of a novel mathematical model. From the analysis of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of siramesine, β-Lapachone, and palbociclib as novel maintenance therapies after chemotherapy in small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Small cell lung cancer (SCLC) represents approximately 15% of all lung cancer cases and is characterized by rapid proliferation and a high metastatic potential. In the search for new treatments, drug repurposing has gained increasing attention, particularly with FDA-approved agents such as palbociclib (PB). Other compounds with reported antitumor activity, including siramesine (SR) and β-Lapachone (LP), are also under investigation, although they remain unapproved for clinical use. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applying Spectral Analysis to the Arterial Pulse to Discriminate Cardiovascular Side Effects Following Administration of Moderna's mRNA-1273 Vaccine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vaccines against severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) have demonstrated strong efficacy in preventing symptomatic disease, but adverse cardiovascular side effects have been reported. This study investigated whether noninvasive arterial pulse waveform analysis could help identify cardiovascular responses following administration of Moderna's mRNA-1273 vaccine. Radial blood pressure waveforms were recorded for one minute in 203 individuals who received the vaccine at a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circulating microRNAs in cord blood to predict attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We show that expression levels of circulating miRNAs at birth may be used to predict increased risk of ADHD diagnosis, and our 19-miRNA set should be included in future efforts to develop a biomarker panel.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A non-interactive Online Medical Pre-Diagnosis system on encrypted vertically partitioned data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PPNLR achieves data protection through cryptographic primitives, maintaining high diagnostic accuracy while ensuring the security of medical data and model parameters. Its single-communication architecture significantly reduces the deployment threshold in resource-constrained scenarios, providing a practical framework for building the privacy-friendly OMPD systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards a Biological Evaluation Framework for Oversampling (BEFO) gene expression data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) techniques are progressively being used in biomedical research to improve diagnostic and prognostic accuracy when used in conjunction with a clinician as a decision support system. However, many datasets used in biomedical research often suffer from severe class imbalance due to small population sizes, which causes machine learning models to become biased to majority class samples. Current oversampling methods primarily focus on balancing datasets without adequately...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The mechanisms and therapeutic potential of Atractylodes macrocephala Koidz in chronic liver disease management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AMK could be classified as a novel candidate for the treatment and prevention of CLD, and its natural active compounds may represent new sources for the development of new drugs or dietary supplements against CLD. Future researches should seek to potential new agents by thorough preclinical and clinical studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revealing Fire-Dependent Chemical Transformations in Selaginellae Herba via Integrated Metabolomics and Multimodal Sensory Profiling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SH-Ca achieved an optimal balance between flavonoid transformation and desirable sensory outcomes, supporting the traditional use of carbonization to enhance the properties of Selaginellae Herba. These findings provide a scientific basis for optimizing processing parameters to ensure quality and efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbial-electrochemical driven simultaneous biogas upgrading and high-value medium-chain carboxylic acid production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biological biogas upgrading is often limited by inefficient hydrogen (H(2)) gas-liquid mass transfer and low economic returns. To address this, this study developed an innovative microbial-electrochemical system that integrates enhanced H(2) delivery in a microbial electrochemical cell with ethanol- and acetate-driven chain elongation by a co-culture of Sporomusa ovata and Clostridium kluyveri, enabling simultaneous biogas upgrading and carbon dioxide (CO(2))-to-high-value medium-chain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cyanobacterial biochar and cyanobacteria-bamboo growth elicitors for establishing a self-sustaining nitrogen cycle in soybean]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To address waste valorization and the urgency of decarbonization, bamboo powder was integrated with cyanobacteria to prepare a cyanobacterial growth elicitor (CGE) and cyanobacterial-bamboo growth elicitor (CBGE) through acid-hydrolysis technology. Pot experiments with four treatments (a control, CK; cyanobacterial biochar [CB], BF; CGE-modified CB, LBF; and CBGE-modified CB, LZBF) were conducted to examine the synergistic effects of CB on soil-crop systems. Multiple analytical approaches were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide external quality assessment of serum glycated albumin measurement in China during 2024-2025: current situation, challenges and prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The nationwide GA EQA program scheme has substantially improved analytical performance and cultivated a robust quality assurance culture across participating laboratories. Persistent challenges to further elevating detection quality through EQA include sample commutability, procedure for target value assignment, and replicate samples. Moving forward, fostering collaborative engagement among all stakeholders are essential to overcome these limitations and establish a harmonized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of a single packed red blood cell unit on recipient phosphatidylethanol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phosphatidylethanol (PEth) is a marker of alcohol consumption present on erythrocytes. Consensus guidelines suggest that PEth concentrations ≥20 ng/mL and ≥ 200 ng/mL are consistent with alcohol consumption or chronic excessive consumption, respectively. However, packed red blood cell (pRBC) transfusion is a potential source of PEth in transfusion recipients. Currently, the prevalence of this phenomenon and the magnitude of PEth elevation after transfusion of a single pRBC unit remain uncertain....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110682/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and organizational determinants of a frequently delayed diagnosis of ocular syphilis in a French Referral Center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ophthalmologists in private practice are often the first clinicians that patients consult, and since ocular manifestations often lead to the diagnosis of syphilis, they play a crucial role in its detection. These findings highlight the importance of raising awareness among front-line physicians, routinely prescribing syphilis serology in the presence of unexplained uveitis or vision loss, systematically questioning patients about their sexual history and systemic symptoms, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Periostin promotes inflammation and neovascularization in atopic keratoconjunctivitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Periostin plays an important role in corneal neovascularization and in type 2 and non-type 2 inflammation in AKC-like ocular lesions of FADS mice. Targeting the periostin/α(V)β(3) integrin pathway is a promising therapeutic strategy for treating AKC patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glymphatic dysfunction mediates altered regional neural abilities in night-shift nurses: A multimodal neuroimaging and transcriptomic study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We concluded that the impaired glymphatic function and disrupted regional neural activity may be the neural substrates underlying the poor sleep qualities and cognitive declines in night-shift nurses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection and rehabilitation of age-related motor skills impairment: neurophysiological biomarkers and perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Age-related decline in motor control, manifesting as impaired posture, gait, and slowed movement execution, significantly diminishes the quality of life in older adults. These functional deficits are associated with alterations in neurophysiological data, which are analyzed using advanced techniques including spectral analysis, complexity measures, and functional connectivity network analysis. These methodologies provide valuable insights into the neurobiological mechanisms underpinning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitigating Choice Overload: The Interactive Effects of Set Size and Overall Preference Revealed by Hierarchical Drift Diffusion Modeling and Electroencephalography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Excessive choice can overwhelm cognitive resources and trigger choice overload, yet its neurophysiological basis-particularly the moderating role of overall preference level-remains underexplored. This study employed a two-stage experimental paradigm manipulating choice set size (large vs. small) and overall preference level (high vs. low). We integrated event-related potentials (ERPs), multivariate pattern analysis (MVPA), and hierarchical drift diffusion modeling (HDDM) to investigate how...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERP-based Interbrain Causal Model Reveals Closed-loop Information Interaction in Interpersonal Negotiations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Uncovering the interbrain neural mechanisms underlying interpersonal negotiation offers insight into social decision-making dynamics in resource allocation. In this study, we used EEG hyperscanning alongside an iterated ultimatum game to investigate interbrain coupling and dyadic exchange behavior during negotiation. Frontal cortex event-related potentials (ERPs) revealed the distinct neural responses driven by partners' behavioral cues: the proposer's N200 differed significantly for fair versus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antenatal Exposure to Medication for Opioid Use Disorder and Infant Outcomes in the ESC-NOW Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Use of the ESC care approach was associated with a decrease in pharmacologic treatment for NOWS and a shorter hospital stay for infants with antenatal MOUD exposure. Methadone exposure was associated with a shorter length of pharmacologic treatment for infants cared for with ESC when compared with usual care, whereas such an association was not seen for buprenorphine exposed infants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Influenza Vaccination With Acute Kidney Injury: A Prospective Target Trial Emulation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this prospective population-based study of older adults within the UK Biobank, FluVac was significantly associated with a lower risk of incident AKI. These findings support use of influenza vaccination in older adults to reduce influenza and its kidney-related complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The diagnostic value of hepatitis B core-related antigen in occult HBV infection and its related hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: HBcrAg is a promising serum marker for the diagnosis of OBI in HBsAg-negative population. HBcrAg is related to OBI-related HCC and is valuable in evaluating recurrence after radical resection surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HIV status is not associated with SARS-CoV-2 viral load and longer duration of infection among people with well-controlled HIV and high COVID-19 vaccine coverage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In a setting with well-controlled HIV and high COVID-19 vaccine coverage, HIV status was not associated with SARS-CoV-2 viral load or infection duration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cream-colored lignin nanoflowers via ethanol/water fractionation: Sustainable UV-blocking additives for sunscreen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lignin possesses intrinsic ultraviolet (UV) shielding properties, making it one of the most promising natural materials for eco-friendly sunscreen development. However, the wide molecular weight distribution, complex structure, dark color, and poor dispersibility of industrial sulfonated lignin (LS) have hindered its commercial application in cosmetic formulations. In this study, a green and efficient antisolvent approach using ethanol was developed to simultaneously fractionate LS and fabricate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research progress on the role of oxidative stress in the pathogenesis of vascular dementia and its treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The central role of oxidative stress in VaD provides new targets for treatment, but a shift from single-target antioxidant therapy to multi-level intervention is required. Future research should focus on developing targeted antioxidant therapies, exploring combination treatment regimens, and validating biomarkers applicable for early detection and therapeutic efficacy assessment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The single nucleotide polymorphism rs155787 on the autophagy gene of SQSTM1 is associated with silicosis susceptibility: a multi-stage study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The rs155787 locus on the SQSTM1 may be associated with silicosis susceptibility, and the mutant G allele may serve as a potential risk factor. Furthermore, the A>G variation at this locus was observed to upregulate SQSTM1 gene expression. Additional large-scale studies are necessary to further validate our findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Embryo-Fetal Developmental Toxicity and Toxicokinetics Studies of YWS20045 Orally Administered to Pregnant Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to explore the embryo-fetal developmental toxicity and concurrent toxicokinetic characteristics of YWS20045 in rats. Pregnant rats were divided into a solvent control group, three YWS20045 dose groups (4, 16 and 32mg/kg), and a positive control group (3.5mg/kg cyclophosphamide). Oral administration was conducted from gestation day (GD) 6 to 17. Results showed that all dose groups exhibited loose stools, with the high dose group experiencing significant maternal toxicity,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive phytochemical mapping and biomedical evaluation of Lawsonia inermis L: a potential natural treatment for diabetic foot ulcers with wound healing and antimicrobial effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic foot ulcers (DFUs) are diagnosed in several million patients annually. The risk of death and amputation increases with the prevalence of associated multidrug-resistant infections. Lawsonia inermis L., commonly known as henna, is a plant species belonging to the family Lythraceae J.St.-Hil. For decades, it has been used to treat foot wounds and for other medical and cosmetic purposes. Various henna plant extracts were prepared, and 107 pus samples were collected to isolate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Craving Induction and Treatment Response in Transcranial Magnetic Stimulation for Tobacco Use Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Craving induction reliably increased craving, although the magnitude of cue-induced craving was not associated with end-of-trial smoking cessation. This finding suggests that greater craving induction does not predict greater therapeutic effect of rTMS. Further research is needed to understand the mechanisms and clinical implications of rTMS and brain-state in TUD, including potential improvements in related domains such as inhibitory control.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical profile and long-term outcomes of chest pain patients with coronary microvascular dysfunction from the emergency department - results from the Yale-CMD registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with contemporary phenotypes of ischemia (CMD and CAD/CALC) had higher adverse events than controls, positing ED encounters as an opportunity for early identification and treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obstetric risks from ART: clarifying the forest to identify the right trees (Reply to Letter-to-the-Editor)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Considerations for Contraceptive Counseling Among Women Prescribed Psychotropic Medications (Reply to Letter-to-the-Editor)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the brain: a computational MRI-derived neurophysiological framework for robotic conscious capacity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Explaining when neural activity supports conscious processing remains an unresolved question in neuroscience. Current frameworks describe correlates of consciousness but rarely provide thresholds to predict its emergence or recovery. We introduce the Attribution Consciousness Index (ACI), a metric that estimates the generative potential of consciousness by balancing measures of dynamic information (Φ) and complexity (κ) expressed as a normalized odds ratio. Using the empirically validated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the context-dependent role of miR-744 as a prognostic, diagnostic, and therapeutic biomarker across different cancer types]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MicroRNAs are small non-coding RNAs that regulate gene expression and play crucial roles in cancer development and progression. Among them, microRNA-744 (miR-744) has attracted increasing attention due to its complex, context-dependent functions across various cancer types. Evidence indicates that miR-744 can serve either as an oncogene or a tumor suppressor, depending on the tumor type and cellular environment. This dual role is mediated through regulation of multiple target genes involved in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxidative stress in schizophrenia and bipolar disorders, results from a 2-year follow-up study of two prospective studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110518/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Overall, we found persistently increased RNA damage over time in patients with severe mental illness compared with HC, most pronounced in SCZ but also present in BD, supporting oxidative stress generated nucleoside damage as a potential driver of accelerated aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110518/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hypoalbuminemia Increases Fibrin Clot Density and Impairs Fibrinolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These data show that albumin directly increases fibrin network porosity and enhances fibrinolysis. Hypoalbuminemia may mechanistically contribute to nephrotic syndrome thrombotic complications and may similarly increase thrombotic risk in other hypoalbuminemic conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health-related quality of life in adults with hemophilia B after gene therapy with fidanacogene elaparvovec: Results from the BENEGENE-2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Fidanacogene elaparvovec improved health-related quality of life and health and functional status in adults with hemophilia B.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Angiopoietin-like protein 8 mediates inflammation and fibrosis of tubular cells in diabetic kidney disease progression by interacting with Akt2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings demonstrate for the first time that elevated tubular ANGPTL8 promotes tubular inflammation and fibrosis during DKD by interacting with Akt2, highlighting the ANGPTL8-Akt2 axis as a promising target to prevent DKD progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[β-adrenergic regulation of circadian locomotor activity and anesthetic emergence in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[β2-adrenergic receptors (β2-ARs) are target of catecholamines such as noradrenaline and belong to the family of G protein-coupled receptors. They are distributed in many organs, including the central nervous system. Genetic and pharmacological tools targeting β2-ARs indicate that they mediate a variety of physiological responses. However, their role in the central nervous system remains elusive. Here, we employed β2-adrenergic receptor-deficient (β2-AR KO) mice to elucidate β2-AR role in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Dapagliflozin on insulin signaling and neuronal survival in stretch-induced traumatic brain injury model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traumatic brain injury (TBI) is a major global health issue, affecting millions of people worldwide and contributing to high levels of disability and death. However, post-mortem human studies on brain injury tissue showed a significant increase in SGLT1 and SGLT2, but data in cerebral ischemia are limited. Thus, we aimed to investigate the effect of Dapagliflozin, an SGLT2 inhibitor, reduced ROS-induced neuronal death and increased the expression of the insulin pathway in a stretching-induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment and application of efficient protoplast isolation and transformation system from leaves of multi-genotype poplars]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seven widely cultivated, representative populus varieties across four taxonomic sections were employed to establish a multi-genotype protoplast isolation and transformation system, with systematic evaluation of differences in protoplast dissociation, purification, and transformation efficiency. As representatives, Populus alba (P. davidiana × P. simonii) × P. tomentosa '741' from the Sect. Leuce, Populus euramericana from the Sect. Aigeiros, Populus deltoides × P. cathayana 'Senhai 4' from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multivalent nanoparticle vaccine elicits potent neutralizing antibody response against monkeypox virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global spread of monkeypox virus (MPXV), coupled with the high mortality rates of new clade Ib variants, continues to be a major public health burden worldwide. To achieve global eradication of mpox, there is an urgent need for a safe and more effective MPXV-specific vaccine, particularly for use in high-incidence countries in Africa. Herein, we observed that antibodies targeting the MPXV surface proteins, particularly A29 and M1 antigen, were the principal components in convalescent plasma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Single- Versus Multicomponent Neuromuscular Training on Balance Performance in Recreational Athletes: A Systematic Review and Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: While no overall difference was found between single- and multicomponent NMT, age and injury status influenced the outcomes. Tailored NMT protocols may optimize balance and prevent injuries in recreational athletes. PROSPERO (CRD42023391531).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community-acquired pneumonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Community-acquired pneumonia is a major global health challenge that disproportionately affects vulnerable populations, including older people, immunocompromised people, those with chronic conditions, and young children. Once considered solely an acute illness, community-acquired pneumonia is now recognised as a disease with long-term complications, including cardiovascular events, respiratory impairment, and cognitive decline. Advances, such as nucleic acid amplification tests (NAATs) and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of an uncommon sequence type of serotype b Haemophilus influenzae causing an increase in invasive disease in British Columbia, Canada]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study documented an increase of Hib cases in adults due to an uncommon ST, which was very different from other Hib found in the PubMLST databsae. ST-231 Hib cases were initially found in only two Health Regions, subsequent cases spread to cover four Health Regions suggesting community spread and endemicity in the province.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applying simulation with pharmacokinetic/pharmacodynamic considerations to optimize drug dosing in critically ill patients receiving renal replacement therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110430/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251020033804&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Propagation of infra-slow and slow brain activities in electroencephalogram related to behavioral information processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The brain-wide propagation of neural excitability manifested in fast (>1 Hz) electroencephalogram (EEG) oscillations is known to play an important role in behavioral information processing. While fluctuations in EEG infra-slow and slow activity (ISA, 0.01-0.1 Hz; SA, 0.1-1 Hz) are also considered to reflect changes in neural excitability, it remains uncertain whether EEG ISA and SA propagate over the brain and whether such propagation relates to behavioral information processing. To investigate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Ionomer on CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction at Atomically Dispersed Ni─N─C Catalyst]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionomers play an important role in carbon dioxide (CO(2)) electrolyzers by affecting CO(2) reduction reaction (CO(2)RR) at the cathode. In this study, we systematically examines the impact that different ionomers have on CO(2)RR at atomically dispersed nickel-nitrogen-carbon (Ni─N─C) catalyst. We compare the effects of two acidic cation exchange ionomers, perfluorosulfonic acid (Nafion) and sulfonated poly(aryl ether sulfone), and two alkaline anion exchange ionomers: quaternary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Walks in Rotation Spaces Return Home when Doubled and Scaled]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The dynamics of numerous physical systems, such as spins and qubits, can be described as a series of rotation operations, i.e., walks in the manifold of the rotation group. A basic question with practical applications is how likely and under what conditions such walks return to the origin (the identity rotation), which means that the physical system returns to its initial state. In three dimensions, we show that almost every walk in SO(3) or SU(2), even a very complicated one, will...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prenatal Phthalate Exposure, Leptin in Early Childhood, and Mediating Role of DNA Methylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251020033831&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Currently, research on the association of prenatal phthalate exposure with leptin, as well as the mediating role of DNA methylation, is insufficient. A birth cohort in China was conducted, followed by pregnancy to early childhood. During the follow-up period, measurements were conducted for 160 mother-child pairs, including maternal urinary phthalate concentrations in three trimesters, DNA methylation in cord blood, and leptin levels in children's plasma. The present study found that maternal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251020033831&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Resolution Characterization of the Bacterial Microbiome in Chili Pepper Powder Using SMRT Sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chili pepper powder is an essential ingredient of Korean cuisine and kimchi products. As such, ensuring its microbiological safety is crucial from a public health perspective. In this study, the bacterial microbiomes of Korean and Chinese chili pepper powder samples were compared using high-resolution single-molecule real-time sequencing. Nine samples each from Korea and China were analyzed, yielding high-quality sequencing data with N50 values exceeding 1,460 bp and quality scores greater than...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linking riverine discharge to shifts in temperate estuarine planktonic food web dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Riverine discharge plays a crucial role in shaping planktonic food web dynamics in coastal systems, though its effects can vary across estuaries. This study investigated the influence of riverine discharge on key biological variables-primary productivity, nitrogen uptake (nitrate and ammonium), biomass, community composition, and mesozooplankton feeding rates-across estuarine gradients in Gwangyang Bay, a low-turbidity temperate estuary in Korea. Principal component analysis identified riverine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020033805&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>