<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 07:42:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-aqueous leaching of critical metals from black mass of spent lithium-ion batteries using a reusable acidic organophosphorus extractant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recycling critical metals from the black mass of spent lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) is essential for supply security and waste management. Conventional hydrometallurgical acid leaching is effective but generates large volumes of wastewater. In this study, a non-aqueous leaching system has been developed using an acidic organophosphorus extractant, di-(2-ethylhexyl)phosphoric acid (D2EHPA), as the lixiviant, consolidating leaching and solvent extraction (SX) into a single stage. Metallic copper...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual PI3Kδ/γ inhibition enhances radiotherapy-induced antitumor immunity via macrophage-dependent cGAS-STING-type I interferon signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiotherapy (RT) promotes antitumor immunity by activating the cyclic GMP-AMP synthase-stimulator of interferon genes (cGAS-STING) pathway and inducing type I interferon (IFN-I); however, its efficacy is often limited by the immunosuppressive tumor microenvironment. Herein, we investigated whether dual inhibition of phosphoinositide 3-kinase (PI3K)δ and PI3Kγ could enhance RT-induced innate immune activation in colorectal cancer. In the syngeneic CT26 model, dual PI3Kδ/γ inhibition (BR101801 or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic behavior of molecular Pd-acetate trimers and dimers in heterogeneous vinyl acetate synthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vinyl acetate monomer (VAM) is a crucial intermediate in the production of various polymers. While molecular Pd-acetate trimers and dimers, such as Pd(3)(OAc)(6) and K(2)Pd(2)(OAc)(6), are known to form on potassium acetate (KOAc)-promoted PdAu catalysts during heterogeneous VAM synthesis, their mechanistic role remains unclear. Here, we study the dynamics of different Pd-acetate species by utilizing in situ and operando crystallographic and spectroscopic characterizations combined with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical utility of genome sequencing in rare diseases: lessons from a single-center study of 1,452 Korean families]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genome sequencing (GS) was applied to 3317 individuals from 1452 Korean families with suspected rare genetic disorders to assess diagnostic yield and clinical utility. Patients were categorized into 16 clinical subgroups with curated phenotypes, and variant interpretation was refined by post-analytic phenotype matching. A molecular diagnosis was achieved in 46.2% of families, influencing clinical management in 18.5% of diagnosed cases. Family-based GS had a higher yield than singleton testing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic insights into PPARγ's role in suppressing collagen-driven platelet activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AIMS: Platelets, despite being anucleate, express peroxisome proliferator-activated receptor γ (PPARγ), a nuclear receptor implicated in regulating platelet activation. While previous studies suggested that PPARγ ligands inhibit collagen-induced platelet activation by modulating downstream glycoprotein VI (GPVI) signaling without affecting Syk, the upstream regulatory mechanisms remain unclear. This study aimed to determine whether PPARγ ligands modulate Src family kinase (SFK)-dependent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomic Insights into Inflammatory and Angiogenic Pathways Distinguishing Uveitic and Neovascular Glaucoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Uveitic glaucoma and neovascular glaucoma (NVG) exhibit distinct clinical characteristics, yet the specific molecular alterations in the aqueous humor (AH) associated with each subtype remain poorly understood. In this study, we performed a proteomic analysis of AH samples from patients with uveitic glaucoma (n = 7), NVG (n = 5), and age-matched cataract patients (controls, n = 8) to identify potential biomarkers and elucidate subtype-specific molecular pathways. We applied advanced statistical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comparative Analysis of SCALE-CTP and RAPID in Determining the Affected Brain Volumes of Patients with Ischemic Stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SCALE-CTP demonstrated strong agreement with RAPID in predicting affected brain volumes and shows potential as a reliable tool for guiding hyperacute ischemic stroke treatment. Further validation is needed to confirm its clinical utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the Physician Global Assessment × Maximum Diameter (PGAMAX) as a Severity Assessment Tool for Pyoderma Gangrenosum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative analysis and toxicological mechanisms of various male infertility inducers: A network meta-analysis and pharmacological approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This first integrated toxicological and mechanistic analysis elucidates how diverse inducers impair male reproductive health. Oxidative stress contributes to toxicity, highlighting potential molecular targets for therapy. Findings support the translational relevance of rodent infertility models and guide risk assessment and mitigation strategies for stressors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of novel imidazo[4,5-b]pyridine derivatives as noncovalent reversible Bruton's tyrosine kinase inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bruton's tyrosine kinase (BTK) has emerged as a validated therapeutic target for B-cell malignancies and autoimmune disorders, and covalent BTK inhibitors have demonstrated remarkable clinical efficacy. However, because of concerns regarding their off-target effects and safety profiles, there is research interest in developing noncovalent, reversible inhibitors. Herein, we report the design, synthesis, and biochemical evaluation of novel imidazo[4,5-b]pyridine derivatives as noncovalent BTK...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Subchronic Cardiac Stress of High Doses of a Novel SARS-CoV-2 mRNA Vaccine Candidate in Streptozotocin-Induced Diabetic Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although mRNA vaccines have been pivotal in combating the COVID-19 pandemic, research on their side effects remains limited. Adverse effects can vary considerably, including cardiac injury, and individuals with diabetes may experience broader reactions. This study compared vehicle (Veh) and streptozotocin (STZ)-induced type 1 diabetes mellitus (T1DM) mouse models following administration of the novel SARS-CoV-2 mRNA vaccine candidate CUK3-1/LNP128 to evaluate its toxicity profile and assess...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354119/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assisted reproductive technology trends in Korea: Annual report for 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nationwide infertility treatment cycle reporting in Korea has enabled detailed monitoring of infertility treatment trends and outcomes. The data show a substantial increase in IVF utilization, a growing preference for frozen-thawed embryo transfer, and broader adoption of single embryo transfer consistent with global practices. Further integration with birth outcome data and longitudinal patient tracking will be essential to evaluate cumulative success rates and overall...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tracing the contrasting fates of terrestrial and marine organic matter in coastal waters using stable carbon isotopes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We measured the concentrations of dissolved oxygen, nutrients, particulate (POC) and dissolved organic carbon (DOC), and their δ^(13)C values in Lake Sihwa, Korea, during spring (May 2024) and summer (August 2023) to determine the fates of terrestrial and marine POC and DOC. NO(3)^(-) mainly originated from freshwater, whereas NH(4)^(+) and PO(4)^(3-) were additionally supplied from bottom sediments in the innermost bay. Although POC and DOC originated primarily from biological production and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coffee beverage sedimentation: From roasting effects to storage stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ready-to-drink (RTD) coffee products often experience sedimentation that compromises product quality and consumer acceptance. This study investigated sedimentation mechanisms in RTD coffee under varying roasting conditions, extraction temperatures, and product formulations through molecular weight and compositional analyses. Two mechanisms were identified: galactomannan crystallization and protein-polyphenol interactions. Low-temperature extraction favored protein-polyphenol aggregation with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pirtobrutinib Versus Ibrutinib in Treatment-Naïve and Relapsed/Refractory Chronic Lymphocytic Leukemia/Small Lymphocytic Lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Pirtobrutinib demonstrated NI of ORR versus ibrutinib, with a favorable early PFS trend, particularly in TN patients, and a favorable safety profile including low rates of atrial fibrillation and hypertension.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cooperative optical response of two-dimensional atomic arrays in solids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We develop a model describing long-range atom-atom interactions in a two-dimensional periodic or a-periodic lattice of optical centers considering spectral and spatial broadening effects. Using both analytical and numerical Green's function techniques, we develop a mathematical framework to describe effective atom-atom interactions and collective behaviors in the presence of disorder. This framework is applicable to a broad range of quantum systems with arbitrary lattice geometries, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FRAX score predicts vertebral compression fractures impairing spinal alignment and hip function after total hip arthroplasty: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this 6.1-year retrospective cohort study, 20% of hips developed new VCFs after THA, which were associated with worsened spinal alignment and hip function. The higher FRAX score, calculated prior to THA surgery, is a useful predictor of VCF risk and may help identify individuals who require closer monitoring or preventive interventions during follow-up after surgery. Video Abstract.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dapagliflozin in acute heart failure: lessons from the DAPA ACT HF-TIMI 68 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal trajectories of health-related quality of life and their predictors among community-dwelling older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The 36-item Short-Form Health Survey (SF-36) is widely used to assess health-related quality of life. However, only few studies have examined longitudinal SF-36 trajectories in general populations, and even fewer have explored their relationships with lifestyle factors, including sleep quality. We conducted a longitudinal analysis of SF-36 subscale trajectories among 910 Japanese individuals aged ≥ 60 years from 2007 to 2018 (4,799 records). Using latent class mixed models, we identified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Posterior decompression and spinous process reconstruction for lumbar spinal stenosis in a pediatric patient with achondroplasia: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case demonstrates that, in patients with achondroplasia, laminotomy with spinous process reconstruction can effectively address lumbar spinal canal stenosis and preserve posterior elements with a minimal risk of complications. Long-term follow-up remains crucial for monitoring the potential development of thoracolumbar kyphosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A pathway to coexistence of electroluminescence and photovoltaic conversion in organic devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving both high electroluminescence (EL) efficiency and power conversion efficiency (PCE) in a single organic device has long been considered difficult, since the design principles optimising one often compromise the other. In this study, we present a strategy employing multiple-resonance thermally activated delayed fluorescence materials with strong absorption and high emission efficiency, enabling coexistence of high EL and photovoltaic (PV) efficiencies. By precisely controlling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful use of methylene blue for severe vasoplegia in a patient with partially-treated portopulmonary hypertension with atrial septal defect undergoing liver transplantation: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MB can be lifesaving for intraoperative vasoplegia even in patients with PoPH on PAH drug therapy with an ASD, though potential drug interactions with anti-PAH drugs warrant caution.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age differences in alcohol and music consumption among Japanese nonproblem drinkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alcohol use and music use were examined in relation to emotion regulation; however, most studies examined these two factors separately. We examined how people of different ages drink alcohol and listen to music within the context of emotion regulation. The following survey data was analyzed among Japanese nonproblem drinkers (20-59 years, N = 1279): How often people drink alcohol and listen to music, Tendencies to use them when experiencing negative emotions, Drinking Motives...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comment on "De Novo Reconstruction of 3D Human Facial Images from DNA Sequence"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The recent article by Jiao et al., presenting the Difface model for reconstructing faces from deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA) and other artificial intelligence (AI)-enabled facial genetics research, has transformative potential for biomedical and forensic applications. Yet such research raises serious ethical, legal, and social challenges, as such applications are rights and safety impacting. Methodological transparency, algorithmic explainability, and contextualization of findings are essential to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of dectin-1-binding peptides targeting dendritic cells for antigen delivery via ribosome display]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dendritic cells (DCs) are professional antigen-presenting cells that play a central role in initiating and shaping adaptive immune responses. Targeting antigens to DCs has emerged as a promising strategy to enhance vaccine efficacy and tailor desired immune responses. While antibodies are well established as targeting molecules for DCs, the use of peptides remains underexplored despite their favorable tissue penetration and their ability to offer design flexibility. Here, we report the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[gem-Difluorocyclopropane Synthesis by Copper-Catalyzed C(sp<sup>3</sup>)-H Addition of 1,3-Dioxolane to Difluorocyclopropenes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report here a synthesis of gem-difluorocyclopropanes via a copper-catalyzed C(sp³)-H addition of dioxolane to difluorocyclopropenes. The combinational use of silane and dibenzoyl peroxide was crucial for promoting the reaction, enabling access to gem-difluorocyclopropanes with an acetal moiety in a cis configuration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhibition of Cell Proliferation by Euphorbia Factors L1 and L3 from Euphorbia lathyris through the ATF4-CHOP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A luciferase reporter gene assay demonstrates that a methanol extract of the aerial parts of Euphorbia lathyris L. activates reporter gene expression mediated by CCAAT-enhancer-binding protein homologous protein (CHOP) transcriptional activity in the human pancreatic cancer cell line MIA PaCa-2. We isolated 2 lathyrane-type diterpenoids, euphorbia factor L1 (EFL1) and L3 (EFL3), from the extracts. This is the first report of their isolation from aerial parts of this plant. Treatment of the MIA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural basis for heme binding by the Shr protein from Streptococcus pyogenes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Streptococcus pyogenes causes a range of infectious diseases. In an era of increasing antibiotic resistance, new antimicrobial strategies targeting virulence factors, rather than essential survival mechanisms, are being explored. A key virulence factor in S. pyogenes is the bacterial iron acquisition system, because iron is essential but limited in the host due to sequestration by proteins like hemoglobin. The bacteria S. pyogenes possesses the Shr protein that acquires heme from host hemoglobin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bidirectional Associations Between End-of-Life Communication and Depressive Symptoms in Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Older adults appear at risk for having depressive symptoms following discussing end-of-life wishes with their physicians. End-of-life communication may reflect an ongoing trajectory of cognitive decline which could result in further functional decline and increased depressive symptoms. A better understanding of how and which elements of end-of-life discussions are associated with the mood of older adults will provide implications for the implementation of ACP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pigment-dispersing factor is not essential for eclosion rhythm and inducing the photoperiodic diapause in the silkworm, Bombyx mori]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The neuropeptide pigment-dispersing factor (PDF) functions as a key circadian clock output that regulates circadian rhythmicity at physiological and behavioral levels in the fruit fly Drosophila melanogaster. Similarly, the involvement of PDF in circadian behavioral rhythmicity and photoperiodism has been demonstrated across a wide range of insect orders. However, in Lepidoptera, the second largest insect order, the function of PDF remains poorly elucidated. The silkworm Bombyx mori, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking (un)blinding in biomedical proposal peer review: A multi-stakeholder qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While there remains a strong preference for double-blinded review within the context of our study, its limitations have become evident-particularly given current funding challenges. These shortcomings highlight the need for greater openness in peer review and increased transparency in fund allocation processes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of gastrointestinal motility trajectory in patients with severe traumatic brain injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with severe TBI demonstrate high and low levels of GI motility. Brain edema following TBI may be associated with reduced GI motility, and the use of potassium supplements and proton pump inhibitors was also associated with lower motility. These findings suggest that attention to factors potentially influencing GI motility, along with early enteral nutrition strategies, may be important in the clinical management of patients with severe TBI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Informal coercion towards discharge: The entanglement of formal and informal coercion in social resource introduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Informal coercion towards discharge was a structurally embedded practice linked to formal coercion. Two forms of informal coercion were identified: extra-legally constructed medical authority and informal legal transplantation. Reducing informal coercion requires limiting formal coercion, clarifying discharge criteria in law, and expanding non-coercive social resources.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seasonality of Sensorineural Hearing Loss and Impact of the Coronavirus Disease 2019 Pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This population-based study in Japan reveals seasonality in the incidence of sudden sensorineural hearing loss and a decrease during the coronavirus disease 2019 pandemic. Despite the observational nature of the study, the findings may be useful in elucidating the etiology of sudden sensorineural hearing loss.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A mitogenomic phylogenetic analysis of the Japanese Plestiodon species (Scincidae, Squamata) clarifies a mito-nuclear discordance caused by a past long distance dispersal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The whole mitochondrial genomes (mitogenomes) excluding the control region were sequenced for 42 samples of the ten species of scincid lizards of the genus Plestiodon occurring in Japan, and the mitochondrial genealogy of the East Asian Plestiodon was reconstructed on the basis of the mitogenomic dataset. A comparison with a species phylogeny based on five nuclear DNA fragments revealed that P. latiscutatus, a species distributed on the Izu Peninsula of the Japanese Main Islands, was a sister to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of mechanical and chemical denture cleaners on soft relining materials: a literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Mechanical cleaning has been indicated as potentially applicable to auto-polymerized acrylic and heat-polymerized silicone types. Chemical cleaning with sodium perborate has been indicated as potentially applicable to auto- and heat-polymerized acrylics and silicones.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nucleotide-Dependent Actin Conformations Revealed by Multiscale Enhanced Sampling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Actin filaments are essential components of the cytoskeleton. Their structural polarity, characterized by distinct 'plus' (barbed) and 'minus' (pointed) ends, is crucial for the directional growth and dynamic behavior of actin filaments during cellular processes such as motility, division, and intracellular transport. Asymmetric and directional filament formation is highly regulated by the bound nucleotide such that ATP-bound G-actin binds on the barbed end, ATP hydrolysis and phosphate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leopard-EM: an extensible 2D template-matching package to accelerate in situ structural biology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41355025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ability to generate high-resolution views of cells with cryogenic electron microscopy (cryo-EM) can reveal the molecular mechanisms of biological processes in their native cellular context. The revolutionary impact of this strategy is limited by the difficulty of accurately annotating structures within these images. 2D template matching (2DTM), in which high-resolution structural models are used as computational probes to locate and orient molecular complexes with high precision, has shown...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41355025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to "A Slippery Slope: Is Benzyl Alcohol a Contact Allergen?"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41355016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41355016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Assessment of In Vivo and In Silico Evaluation of Automated Fluid Resuscitation Controllers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41355000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The ability of the mathematical model to predict PCLC performance metrics demonstrates its value in supporting the development and evaluation of automated fluid resuscitation controllers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41355000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superhydrated Zwitterionic Hydrogel with Dedicated Water Channels Enables Nonfouling Solar Desalination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solar-driven interfacial desalination (SID) offers a sustainable route for freshwater production, yet its long-term performance is compromised by salt crystallization and microbial fouling under complex marine conditions. Zwitterionic polymers offer promising nonfouling capabilities, but current zwitterionic hydrogel-based solar evaporators (HSEs) suffer from inadequate hydration and salt vulnerability. Inspired by the natural marine environmental adaptive characteristics of saltwater fish, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamics of the gut microbiome and resistome in response to prophylactic antibiotic treatment in post-surgical giant pandas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For giant pandas, the ecological impact of prophylactic postoperative antibiotics on their gut microbial communities and resistome is not well characterized. Here, we assessed the impact of intravenous cefotaxime administration by analyzing longitudinal fecal samples from five giant pandas via 16 S rRNA sequencing (n = 304 samples) and shotgun metagenomics (n = 22 samples). 16 S-based analysis revealed that antibiotic exposure significantly altered bacterial community structure, resulting in a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic and functional analysis of ZMIZ1 in neurodevelopmental disorder with dysmorphic facies and distal skeletal anomalies (NEDDFSA): insights from muscle cells and signaling pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study identifies a novel likely pathogenic variant in ZMIZ1 associated with NEDDFSA. These findings provide new insights into the cellular and physiological mechanisms underlying NEDDFSA, highlighting ZMIZ1's role as a regulatory hub in multiple signaling pathways.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of operative hysteroscopy on pregnancy outcomes in patients with suspected uterine cavity lesions prior to the first frozen-thawed embryo transfer: a retrospective propensity-score matching cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study confirmed that in patients with suspected uterine cavity lesions, performing hysteroscopic surgery before the first frozen-thawed embryo transfer can improve both CPR and LBR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary fatty acids and epigenetic aging in US adults: results from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fatty acids are involved in disease risk and aging processes. In the US National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (1999-2002), we tested for associations of total, saturated (SFA), monounsaturated (MUFA), polyunsaturated (PUFA), and subtypes of dietary fatty acids with DNA methylation-based aging biomarkers, adjusting for age, BMI, total energy intake, and sociodemographic and behavioral factors (N = 2260). Higher SFA and MUFA were associated with greater GrimAge2, an aging biomarker of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-pathway nanoengineering: spatiotemporal control of immunogenic apoptosis and macrophage phenotype reprogramming for augmented antitumor immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Damage-associated molecular patterns (DAMPs) are released by cells through immunogenic cell death (ICD), reshaping the tumor microenvironment and demonstrating significant potential in cancer immunotherapy. We report a type of nanoparticle (FeS-IMQ-MnO(2)@HA) in which Hyaluronic acid (HA) targets the CD44 receptor of tumor cells. Under low-temperature photothermal therapy (LTPTT), FeS within the nanoparticles generates Fe²⁺ through chemodynamic therapy (CDT), thereby producing reactive oxygen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiofrequency ablation of persistent atrial fibrillation in a patient with dextrocardia and interruption of inferior vena cava in the fluoroless catheterization laboratory: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results support fluoroless techniques as a viable option for atrial fibrillation ablation in challenging congenital anomalies, minimizing radiation exposure while maintaining procedural success.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stage-specific EMG feature optimization for enhanced post-stroke hand gesture recognition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Brunnstrom stage-specific feature engineering substantially improves EMG gesture-classification accuracy over both healthy-derived and non-stage-stratified patient baselines while reducing computational load. These findings support adaptive, stage-aware designs for wearable rehabilitation systems and motivate larger Low-stage cohorts and models robust to sparse or low-SNR signals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiological characteristics of hepatitis B virus infection in adult patients before, during and after COVID-19 in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings highlight a complex interplay between pandemic conditions and observed positivity rates. The increase likely stemmed from multiple factors, including shifted testing focus, altered healthcare-seeking behavior, and potential viral reactivation. The COVID-19 response offers insights for optimizing future viral hepatitis control strategies during public health emergencies. Future research should expand demographic and geographic scope and investigate behavioral/social...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating rna structure and protein interactions to uncover the mechanisms of viral and cellular ires function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our in silico analysis indicates that mutational tolerance mirrors IRES cofactor dependence: compact viral IRESs are structurally robust, whereas non-viral IRESs are more reliant on protein interactions. By linking structure prediction with interaction profiling, we identify variants that both stabilize IRESs and improve binding to ITAFs or translation factors. This framework provides mechanistic insight into sequence-structure-function relationships and supports the rational design...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PACIFIC-5: a phase III clinical trial of consolidation durvalumab in patients with unresectable stage III NSCLC and no progression after concurrent or sequential chemoradiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PACIFIC-5 met its primary endpoint of improved PFS after either cCRT or sCRT. Follow-up for overall survival is ongoing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of caregiver support intervention outcomes for refugees in Jordan: a three-path mediational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Both common factors (foundational therapeutic competencies among the service providers) and specific factors (active ingredients of the intervention) are relevant in predicting outcomes following CSI-albeit through different pathways. This study provides support for using competency assessments, attendance tracking, and monitoring participant's skill adoption as a framework for the evaluation and improvement of quality of care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endothelial cell-targeting aptamer-empowered exosomes accelerate wound healing by promoting specialized angiogenesis in type 1 diabetic mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Collectively, our findings emphasize the essential role of specialized angiogenesis in wound repair and propose a novel, advanced EXOs modification-based therapeutic approach to enhance wound healing in both normal and diabetes-related pathophysiological conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in nanomedicine-based retinal drug delivery: mechanisms and translational applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retinal diseases like age-related macular degeneration (AMD), diabetic retinopathy (DR), and diabetic macular edema (DME), alongside optic neuropathies such as glaucoma, are primary contributors to irreversible visual impairment and blindness, and not only impact the quality of life but also place considerable socioeconomic pressures on healthcare systems worldwide. Despite the availability of several therapeutic modalities, the clinical management of these conditions remains challenging due to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The nasopharyngeal carcinoma in Xiamen China from 2011 to 2020: a population-based linkage study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Over the recent decade, a consistent decline in the incidence of NPC has been observed, accompanied an insignificant decreasing mortality trend in Xiamen. Future efforts could focus on enhancing prevention, screening, and treatment strategies to potentially reinforcing these positive trends.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of additive manufacturing technology and build angle on surface characteristics and microbial adhesion of 3D-printed dental zirconia: a laboratory study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AM technologies and build angle affected S. gordonii adhesion to zirconia surfaces. DLP printing at 0° and MJ printing at 45° were associated with significantly reduced bacterial counts, presenting a clinically approach to minimize initial plaque formation and support the long-term periodontal success of 3D-printed zirconia restorations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PA28γ-containing tumor-derived exosomes promote T-cell dysfunction in head and neck squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer cell-derived exosomes have been demonstrated to be effective as intercellular signal transmitters. PA28γ is known to be highly upregulated in cancers, but its specific role in the microenvironment remains unclear. Here, we demonstrated that PA28γ is loaded in exosomes released from head and neck squamous cell carcinoma (HNSCC) cells. Exosomal PA28γ is internalized by T cells, subsequently weakening their cytotoxic functions and increasing the expression of CD25 and LAG-3. Using a tumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MST1 bridges LYN and SHP-1 to suppress FcεRI-mediated mast cell activation and allergic responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mammalian sterile-20-like kinase 1 (MST1) is a core component of the Hippo signaling pathway. A previous study of 24 patients with MST1 deficiency revealed that more than half of the patients presented symptoms of airway hyperresponsiveness and atopic dermatitis. We also found significantly reduced MST1 expression in patients with allergies and in mouse models of allergic asthma, suggesting that aberrant MST1 expression may be broadly relevant to allergic diseases. However, the specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lysophosphatidylethanolamine 18:1 drives clear cell renal cell carcinoma by stabilizing SIRT6 to reprogram lipid metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clear cell renal cell carcinoma (ccRCC) is characterized by profound lipid metabolic dysregulation, yet the mechanisms linking peritumoral adipose tissue (PAT)-derived lipid metabolites to tumor aggressiveness remain poorly defined. Here, we identified lysophosphatidylethanolamine 18:1 (LPE18:1), a lipid metabolite enriched in PAT and the arterial blood of ccRCC patients, as a critical driver of tumor growth and lipid deposition. Through multiomics analyses and functional studies, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EPDR1 promotes gastric cancer progression via STAT3-mediated fatty acid metabolic reprogramming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[EPDR1 has been shown to play critical regulatory roles in development of several types of cancer. Nevertheless, the role of EPDR1, a family of glycoproteins involved in cell-cell contact, to gastric cancer (GC) remain unknown. Here, we determined that EPDR1 is significantly upregulated in GC tissues and cell lines, and is associated with poor prognosis. In vitro and in vivo functional assays demonstrate that EPDR1 promotes the proliferation, migration, and invasion of GC cells. Mechanistically,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aberrant adenosine A<sub>2A</sub> receptor signaling in the choroid plexus drives CSF hypersecretion and ventriculomegaly in hydrocephalus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrocephalus is a common and serious neuropathological condition characterized by disrupted cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) circulation, which lacks effective pharmacotherapy. Here, we demonstrate that adenosine A(2A) receptor (A(2A)R) signaling in the choroid plexus (ChP) is a trigger of hydrocephalus. Adenosine levels are increased in the CSF of hydrocephalus patients and mice, together with elevated ChP-A(2A)R density. Accordingly, continued infusion of adenosine for 14 days or transgenic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[N-cadherin-mimetic 3D hydrogels program pro-regenerative and immunomodulatory states in human adipose-derived mesenchymal stem cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mesenchymal stromal cell (MSC) therapies critically depend on culture systems that preserve stem cell identity while appropriately configuring immunomodulatory functions. Here, we investigated how a biomimetic three-dimensional (3D) hydrogel that presents the N-cadherin-derived HAVDI motif shapes the phenotype and inflammatory programming of human adipose-derived MSCs (ADMSCs). Self-assembled HAVDI-functionalized peptide amphiphile hydrogels formed nanofibrous, mechanically stable networks that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human stem cells loaded with visible and near-infrared fluorescent core-shell polymeric nanoparticles and revealing tropism toward inflammatory stimuli: in vitro evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Theranostic approach based on fluorescent nanoparticles (NPs) internalized by stem cells (SCs) injected in the bloodstream allows for reaching cancer or inflammatory foci with tracking and treating purposes. At the same time, the influence of internalized NPs on SCs properties, namely, their homing, migration ability, and functioning, remains scarcely investigated. Here, H1 human embryonic stem cells (hESCs) labeled with visible (Vis) and near-infrared (NIR) fluorescent NPs are studied in vitro,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carboxymethylcytosine is a natural base modification and a handle for bacteriophage DNA hypermodification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacteriophages possess a wide array of DNA modifications, with many acting as molecular camouflage to evade host immune defenses. Sequence databases contain numerous bacteriophage enzymes of unknown function, with some potentially involved in yet to be identified DNA modifications. Here we report the discovery of a DNA cytosine C5-carboxymethyltransferase (CmoX) in Synechococcus phage S-B43, which catalyzes the formation of a 5-carboxymethylcytosine (5cxmC), previously reported as an unnatural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[INSM1 governs a neuronal progenitor state that drives glioblastoma in a human stem cell model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma is a lethal brain cancer marked by functional plasticity driven by tumor cell-intrinsic mutations and their interplay with developmental programs. To investigate how canonical glioblastoma mutations promote functional plasticity, we have developed an isogenic human neural stem cell (NSC) model of glioblastoma by sequential addition of TERT promoter, TP53, and PDGFRA point mutations. TP53 loss-of-function increases TERT expression during serial mutagenesis, but only triple mutant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global floating algae blooms are expanding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the past two decades, both microscopic algae (i.e., phytoplankton) and larger algae (i.e., macroalgae) have increased in certain coastal and open ocean waters, yet a comprehensive picture at the global scale is lacking. Here, we address this challenge by analyzing 1.2 million satellite images with computer artificial intelligence to quantify macroalgal mats and microalgal scums in global oceans between 2003 and 2022. With a total cumulative realized niche area of 43.8 million km², macroalgae...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of cultivated nasal mucosal epithelial cell sheets for ocular surface reconstruction: an in vitro and in vivo study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Following transplantation, the CUNMEC sheet presented a stratified epithelial layer containing GCs but without cilia and expressed progenitor cell markers, which are morphologically similar to those of ocular surface epithelia and may have the potential to function as a surrogate epithelium for ocular surface reconstruction, especially in dry eye conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of pulmonary function in diverse ethnic adults living at low and high altitudes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[USP18 confers protection against allergic asthma by suppressing CCL8 production in alveolar type II epithelial cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overall, these findings reveal a previously unrecognized role for USP18 in regulating CCL8 production during asthma progression, highlighting USP18 and CCL8 as potential therapeutic targets for asthma treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification and validation of microglia-associated genes in ischemic stroke using single-cell and bulk RNA-seq]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ischemic stroke (IS) is an acute cerebrovascular disease characterized by high incidence and mortality. The mechanism of microglia in the pathogenesis of IS remains unclear. This study aimed to explore the key genes related to microglia in IS and their molecular mechanisms in the pathogenesis. In this study, the transcriptome data of IS were retrieved from public databases. Subsequently, candidate genes were identified through the intersection of microglia-related genes (MGGs) obtained via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LncRNA AC116914.2 promotes the progression of oral cancer by targeting METTL3 via miR-1245a/ZNF250]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study shows that lncRNA AC116914.2, as a competing endogenous RNA (ceRNA), regulates the expression of METTL3 by competitively binding to miR-1245a with ZNF250, thus promoting OSCC progression. The discovery of this regulatory axis provides new diagnostic markers and therapeutic targets for OSCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and factors associated with frailty among older adults with and without HIV in Kampala, Uganda]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In our study, older PWH and PWOH had a similar prevalence of frailty and prefrailty. This unexpected result may be attributable to the benefits of ART and may reflect substantial improvements in the clinical management of PWH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[N-terminal insertion peptides produce varied effects over the cleavage and assembly of norovirus major capsid protein VP1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The N-terminal cleavage of the norovirus major capsid protein VP1 during in vitro expression is a widely observed phenomenon, yet the underlying mechanisms remain poorly understood. This study aimed to determine how N-terminal insertion sequences affect the cleavage and assembly of virus-like particles (VLPs). To this end, a series of recombinant GII.6 VP1 proteins with varied N-terminal insertion peptides were constructed and expressed using a baculovirus expression system. The expression,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HMGB1 and metabolic pathways in Acinetobacter baumannii pneumonia: an associative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HMGB1 levels rise sharply in AB pneumonia-especially in patients with MODs-and correlate with inflammatory and hypoxic metabolic shifts. Anti-HMGB1 treatment in SD rats reduced lung inflammation and injury, highlighting HMGB1's potential as a diagnostic biomarker and therapeutic target.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GeDi: simplifying gene set distances for enhanced omics interpretation in R/Bioconductor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fibre orientations in collagen-containing tissues revealed with computational scattered light imaging and polarimetric second harmonic generation microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Collagen forms dense fibre networks in the human body, with the organisation directly influencing tissue mechanics and function in health and disease. A good understanding of this relation requires proper imaging techniques for visualising the dense collagen network. Previously, computational scattered light imaging was employed as a fast and easy-to-implement technique to retrieve the orientations of multi-directional fibres in various tissue samples, but the fibre orientations were not yet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping coastal transformations with a novel Cellular Automata-Markov-Random forest framework for land use change modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coastal areas are dynamic, shaped by natural processes and human activities, making accurate prediction of shoreline and land use changes crucial for sustainable management. This study presents a hybrid modeling framework that combines CA-Markov and machine learning to enhance land use/land cover (LULC) and shoreline change projections in Oman's vulnerable coastal regions. Coastlines were delineated using multi-temporal Landsat images (1997-2006-2015-2024) and the Normalized Difference Water...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Steroid therapy is linked to lower incidence of acute kidney injury in patients with severe alcohol-associated hepatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute kidney injury (AKI) is a common complication in patients with severe alcohol-associated hepatitis (sAH), yet its risk factors and outcomes remain incompletely defined. Corticosteroids are the only established therapy for sAH, but their impact on renal outcomes is unknown. A post-hoc analysis of the prospective multicenter VTL-308 trial including 151 patients with sAH was conducted to evaluate the incidence and predictors of AKI, the association of corticosteroid therapy with AKI risk, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acceptance of preventive therapy for latent tuberculosis infection in Chinese children and adolescents: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis preventive treatment (TPT) is essential for pediatric tuberculosis control in children and adolescents. Evidence indicates most attrition occurs prior to TPT initiation rather than from post-initiation nonadherence. This study systematically evaluated TPT acceptance for latent tuberculosis infection (LTBI) among Chinese children and adolescents and identified key influencing factors through comprehensive database searches (PubMed, Web of Science, Embase, Cochrane, CNKI, Wanfang...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preliminary clinical outcomes and adoption of continuous glucose monitoring following reimbursement implementation in patients with type 1 diabetes in Thailand]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Hybrid Closed-Loop system significantly improved glycemic outcomes, particularly in younger patients. However, CGM adoption remains low, highlighting the need for expanded access, enhanced reimbursement policies, and improved adherence strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enzyme-inspired single-atom photocatalysis for oxygen reduction to hydrogen peroxide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photocatalysis presents a promising route for generating sustainable, high-energy-density fuels. However, conventional photocatalysts based on rigid binary metal compounds face significant limitations, including fixed band gaps, rapid charge recombination, and non-specific reaction pathways - ultimately leading to limited selectivity and yield. Critically, they lack the site-specific selectivity characteristic of enzymatic systems, a feature essential for achieving high efficiency, control, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NSUN2-mediated m5C modification of SOCS3 mRNA modulates macrophage polarization in bladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor-associated macrophages (TAMs) are pivotal in facilitating the progression of cancer cells. M1 and M2 are two polarization states of TAMs with opposite functions in tumor progression. While the regulatory role of N6-adenosine (m6A) methylation in macrophage polarization has been established, the function of 5-methylcytosine (m5C) remains unclear. The presence of M2 macrophages in bladder cancer and adjacent normal tissues was validated using fluorescence-activated cell sorting (FACS) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real time frequency and voltage stabilization in multi area hybrid power systems using hybrid MGOAO optimized PID and FOPID controllers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integrated study of automatic voltage regulation (AVR) and load frequency control (LFC) in a two-area hybrid power system is examined in this research. A new Moss Growth Optimization and Artemisinin Optimization (MGO-AO) algorithm is suggested for the best controller parameter tuning, while a traditional FOPID controller is used as the secondary controller. First, a test system with two-area non-reheat thermal turbines is used to apply the MGO-AO algorithm. The analysis of the joint LFC-AVR...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bulk Phase Dominates Sulfur Dioxide Hydrolysis over Interfacial Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sulfur dioxide (SO(2)) hydrolysis is a critical step in secondary sulfate formation, which significantly affects air quality and climate change. Since the 1980s, debate has persisted over whether this reaction occurs mainly at the air-water interface or in the bulk phase. In this study, we investigate SO(2) hydrolysis in heterogeneous systems using molecular dynamics simulations that are driven by a deep neural network potential with ab initio accuracy. In previous studies, rapid interfacial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flash droughts exacerbate global vegetation loss and delay recovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing incidence of flash droughts globally presents a great challenge to the agriculture sector, ecosystem resilience and water resource systems. Here we introduce a methodology that improves the accuracy of quantifying drought-induced global vegetation loss (using Normalized Difference Vegetation Index (NDVI)-derived metric). Our results reveal that NDVI loss during flash droughts (9.0%) is approximately 1.5 times higher than that during conventional droughts (5.3%), highlighting the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pre-existing and early cellular immune factors correlate with functionally complete protection against primary controlled human SARS-CoV-2 infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Identifying host factors that mediate protection against newly-emergent viruses is needed for improved pandemic preparedness. Here, we analysed pre- and early post-exposure immune factors associated with resisting SARS-CoV-2 infection after human challenge in seronegative individuals, using multiplex protein, cytometric and RNA sequencing approaches in the nasopharynx and circulation. Pre-existing cross-reactive antibodies correlate poorly with clinical outcome. Instead, protection is associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Find-DLB: a naturalistic cohort of patients presenting with clinical features of dementia with Lewy bodies to a specialized cognitive clinic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The differential diagnosis of DLB may be difficult within a clinical context because other cognitive disorders frequently present with core features of DLB. The cognitive profile and frequency of core clinical features in the DLB group were generally in line with previous reports. Probable RBD was lower than in other cohorts, which may reflect challenges in collecting this information in a clinical interview.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic 6-thio-deoxyguanosine inhibits telomere elongation in cancer cells by inducing a non-productive stalled telomerase complex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Most cancers upregulate the telomere lengthening enzyme telomerase to achieve unlimited cell division. How chemotherapeutic nucleoside 6-thio-2'-deoxyguanosine (6-thio-dG) targets telomerase to inhibit telomere maintenance in cancer cells and tumors was unclear. Here, we demonstrate that telomerase insertion of 6-thio-dGTP prevents synthesis of additional telomeric repeats but does not disrupt telomerase binding to telomeres. Specifically, 6-thio-dG inhibits telomere extension after telomerase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RBM8A confers oxaliplatin resistance in gastric cancer by maintaining EGFR mRNA stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA-binding proteins (RBPs) critically regulate post-transcriptional gene expression, yet their roles in chemotherapy resistance remain underexplored. Here, through a targeted siRNA screen of 40 RBM family members, we identified RNA-binding motif protein 8 A (RBM8A) as central orchestrator of oxaliplatin-induced DNA damage in gastric cancer (GC). Functional studies demonstrated that RBM8A promotes tumor proliferation and chemoresistance by recruiting the RNA helicase eIF4A3 to stabilize...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response and therapeutic failure to meglumine antimoniate, the first-line drug for cutaneous leishmaniasis infections in Colombian soldiers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leishmaniasis is a vector-borne disease caused by Leishmania protozoa, transmitted through infected female phlebotomine sandflies. Cutaneous leishmaniasis (CL), its most common form, causes considerable morbidity, particularly among Colombian military personnel in endemic areas. Although meglumine antimoniate (MA) remains the first-line treatment, increasing reports of therapeutic failure (TF) raise concerns about its efficacy and highlight the need to identify associated risk factors. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced adsorptive removal of ammonia nitrogen from wastewater by EDTA-2Na modified vermiculite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the coincidence between the close passage of HD7977 and the Pliocene-Pleistocene transition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Oort Cloud's dynamical evolution is significantly influenced by both the galactic tide and stellar flybys. This study investigates the particular case of HD7977's close encounter 2.47 Myr ago, which likely repopulated the Inner Oort Cloud and potentially triggered a significant comet shower on Earth. Our results demonstrate that the shower's intensity strongly depends on HD7977's impact parameter (b), with possible flyby distances ranging from 2,300 AU to ∼ 13,000 AU. For the closest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enriched Streptococcus alactolyticus in non-cub giant panda gut contributes to the regulation of tryptophan and its neuromodulatory derivatives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite feeding on a high-lignocellulose bamboo diet, the giant panda (Ailuropoda melanoleuca) retains a typical gut microbiome of Carnivora. We conducted shotgun metagenomic sequencing and functional validation of the giant panda's gut microbiome to elucidate its physiological roles and explore its functional adaptation to the species' specialized diet. Our results revealed that Streptococcus alactolyticus significantly increased in the guts of subadult, adult, and elderly individuals versus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Architecture and mechanism of a dual-enzyme retron system in prokaryotic immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retrons are bacterial genetic retroelements encoding a reverse transcriptase (RT) and a non-coding RNA (ncRNA)-multi-copy single-stranded DNA (msDNA) hybrid. Diverse effector proteins or domains are found to associate with retrons, typically forming tripartite toxin-antitoxin systems involved in anti-phage defense. Although retrons have attracted growing interest in genome editing technologies, the mechanisms underlying most retron-mediated immune systems remain poorly understood. Here, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nef stabilizes actin to prevent HIV-1 sensing by RIG-I-like receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sensing of viral pathogens by RIG-I-like receptors (RLRs) requires their priming via dephosphorylation mediated by the protein phosphatase 1 regulatory subunit 12 C (R12C), which is activated upon virus-induced actin rearrangements. Here, we show that the HIV-1 accessory protein Nef prevents R12C-mediated RLR priming, thereby suppressing viral sensing. HIV-1 variants containing single point mutations in Nef (F/R191A) that ablate its ability to bind the actin-modulating kinase PAK2 trigger...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural-guided identification of two modulators of β-1,3-glucan synthase FKS1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[FKS1 is a β-1,3-glucan synthase critical for fungal cell wall formation and a target for antifungal drugs such as echinocandin and ibrexafungerp. However, the mechanisms regulating FKS1 activity remain largely unknown. Here, we reveal that transfer RNA (tRNA) acts as an endogenous inhibitor, whereas GSR1 functions as a stabilizer of FKS1. The cryo-EM structure of FKS1 adopts a tRNA-mediated homodimer configuration, representing a quiescent state of β-1,3-glucan synthase. Unexpectedly, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Egg-laying ChickenGTEx resource deciphers context-specific regulatory effects on fertility traits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Characterization of the genetic and molecular architecture underlying egg production traits in chickens is essential for improving the rate of genetic gain through intensive artificial selection. Here, to explore the dynamic landscape of regulatory effects across egg-laying stages in chickens, we generated 1272 RNA-seq samples of four tissues, i.e., the hypothalamic-pituitary-ovarian axis and liver, and paired whole-genome sequence data from 358 hens. We detected 1008 genes with stage-specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly replicating hepatitis C virus variants emerge in immunosuppressed patients causing severe disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatitis C virus (HCV) exists as a heterogenous quasispecies, but the phenotypic consequences of viral variability are widely unexplored. Here we identify a replication enhancing domain (ReED) in non-structural protein 5A conferring high replication fitness to clinical isolates. Accumulation of mutations in the ReED mediates high genome replication capacity. In a cohort of liver transplant patients, high replicator variants are exclusively found in individuals with severe disease outcome,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electronic Modulation of K⁺-Intercalated Polymeric Carbon Nitride via ─C≡N/─OH Functionalization for Efficient Photocatalytic H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub> Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymeric carbon nitride (PCN) holds great promise for photocatalytic H(2)O(2) production owing to its excellent stability and structural tunability. However, the inferior overall photocatalytic performance of PCN owing to its limited charge separation efficiency is a longstanding challenge. Herein, a K⁺-doped bridge-type PCN featuring ─C≡N and ─OH surface groups is synthesized via thermal polymerization. K-PCN exhibits superior efficiency for photocatalytic H(2)O(2) production (8647.78...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ZIF-67-Confined Pd Single-Atom Catalysts Implanted Into Polydopamine-Modified Bamboo Microchannels for Robust Continuous-Flow Hydrogenation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing efficient catalytic hydrogenation microreactors with minimal catalyst loading yet high active-site density for treating concentrated organic pollutants remains challenging. Herein, a facile room-temperature method is presented to stabilize Pd single-atom catalysts (SACs) within ZIF-67 crystals during their formation, aiming to fabricate an efficient, low-loading hydrogenation catalytic microreactor (Pd@Z-P/b CMR). ZIF-67 is constructed into polydopamine (PDA)-modified bamboo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endothelial-Derived Extracellular Vesicles During Exercise in COPD Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Endothelial-derived EV profiles differed based on smoking and exacerbation history. Iloprost did not affect eEV levels, although maximal exercise induced a delayed increase in a subset of eEVs, possibly through shear stress.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Housing Assistance and Health Care Access Among Older Adults with Alzheimer's Disease and Related Dementias: Evidence from Multisource Linked Survey-Administrative Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this nationally representative study of the older adults with ADRD, those receiving housing assistance tended to maintain a usual source of care, but experience cost-related barriers to necessary care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical features and microbiological analysis of risk factors for mortality among patients with carbapenem-resistant Klebsiella pneumoniae bacteremia: A changing virulence landscape]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Virulence plasmids generally heighten CRKP strain virulence and directly affect the 7-day survival rate. Certain strains carry virulence plasmids without increased virulence. Community-acquired infection, neurology department admission, and stroke are independent risk factors for pV-CRKP strains. The presence of IncFrepB among pV-CRKP may promote the spread of virulence genes in ST11-type CRKP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The overlooked uterine factor: unlocking endometrium potential in premature ovarian insufficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To date, research on premature ovarian insufficiency (POI) primarily centers on ovarian dysfunction and systemic hormonal imbalances, with limited attention given to associated endometrial alterations. Given the critical role of the endometrium in reproductive function and its potential contribution to POI-related infertility, in this review, we bridge the knowledge gap regarding endometrial aspects of POI. We discuss the physiology and pathophysiology alterations in the POI endometrium, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly efficient single-layer color-tunable QLEDs enables by the real-time interface exciplex modulation with AgInZnS QDs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing single-pixel color-tunable electroluminescence technology represents a practical approach to circumvent current limitations in pixel processing and longevity. However, existing single-pixel color-tunable quantum dot light-emitting diodes (QLEDs) devices predominantly employ complex tandem structures. Herein, we demonstrate single-layer color-tunable QLEDs by the real-time interface exciplex modulation with AgInZnS (AIZS) quantum dots (QDs). The dynamically color-tunable QLEDs based on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-based diagnosis of uterine myomas and sarcomas using tumor-educated platelet transcriptomics: a retrospective multicenter study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The earlier onset of Meiyu under global warming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vitro synergy analysis of the combination of Citrus aurantium bergamia (Risso &amp; Poiteau, 1826), ivermectin, and nitroxinil against gastrointestinal nematodes of sheep]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nematodes are diverse parasites affecting humans and animals, with resistance to anthelmintics becoming a major concern due to prolonged drug use. Essential oils (EOs) from plants offer a promising alternative for parasite control. This study evaluated the preclinical efficacy of Citrus aurantium bergamia essential oil (BEO) combined with nitroxynil (NTX) or ivermectin (IVM) against Haemonchus contortus and Trichostrongylus spp., using the larval migration inhibition test (LMIT). Gas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection and molecular characterization of Ursicoptes americanus in Georgia, USA black bears (Ursus americanus): Clinical presentations, prevalence, and phylogenetic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ursicoptes americanus is a follicular mite that can cause ursicoptic mange in bear species; however, its biology, epidemiology, and clinical significance remain poorly understood. First described in the 1970s from a captive American black bear (Ursus americanus) in Kansas, USA, this mite has since been reported sporadically in both captive and free-ranging black bears, predominately in the western United States. This study aimed to detect and characterize U. americanus in Georgia black bears,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming orthotopic liver transplantation: Innovative dry-lab simulation model in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soft tissue reconstruction after total resection of sacral chordoma: Case report and literature review-is flap repair necessary?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revolutionizing small bowel transplantation in mice and rats: A cutting-edge dry-lab simulation model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microsurgical varicocelectomy and revascularization: a novel approach to varicocele treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Spatiotemporal dynamics of neuron differentiation and migration in the developing human spinal cord" [J. Genet. Genom. 52 (2025) 1283-1295]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disrupting Cascades of Co-occurring Mental Health and Substance Use Problems With Social Support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grief-Specific or Domain-General? Integrative Neuroimaging Perspectives for Understanding Long-Term Grief]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-Omics Reveal the Dysregulated Gut-Joint Axis in Knee Synovitis: Data from Two Osteoarthritis Studies in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gut microbiota dysbiosis and associated host immuno-metabolic disorders may play a role in knee synovitis. Herein, integrated multi-omics analyses of stool and blood samples from subjects from Pearl River Osteoarthritis Cohort (PROC, N = 207) are conducted to explore the potential gut-joint axis. Specifically, gut metagenomics, serum metabolomics and plasma proteomics are carried out. Knee synovitis is identified by magnetic resonance imaging. A total of 87 synovitis cases are identified in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene expression changes of homologs of human trained immunity markers in the silkworm (Bombyx mori) upon exposure to an innate immunity-enhancing agent]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trained immunity (TI) is a memory-like response of the mammalian innate immune system. However, a convenient assay system for measuring TI is not yet available. Insects possess only innate immunity and therefore have the potential for evaluating innate immunity-enhancing vaccines or chemicals. In this study, larvae of the silkworm (Bombyx mori) were injected with heat-killed (HK) Escherichia coli to induce immune priming, the insect counterpart of mammalian TI, which was confirmed with reduction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cohort study on cardiovascular diseases in adults with hemophilia: an interim subanalysis on comorbidities and medication from ADVANCE Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This interim analysis reveals distinctive patterns of comorbidity, medication use, and cardiovascular risk among aging Japanese adults with hemophilia, underscoring the need for tailored long-term care strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of Waste Basil Seed for Removal of Methylene Blue from Aqueous Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, waste basil seed (BS) was prepared and evaluated for the removal of methylene blue (MB) dye from aqueous media. BS was characterized using scanning electron microscopy, specific surface area, surface functional groups, and the point of zero charge (pH(pzc)). Spherical particles were observed in virgin BS. The specific surface area and pH(pzc) value were 0.265 m²/g and 5.59, respectively. In addition, acidic and basic surface functional groups were measured as 0.050 and 0.605...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiological Factors Affecting Cage Subsidence after Single-level Anterior Cervical Discectomy and Fusion with Double Titanium Cylindrical Cages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anterior cervical discectomy and fusion has become established as a standard surgical method for degenerative cervical disease. Various materials have been used, and we currently usually use double titanium cylindrical cages. Many investigators have reported on the incidence of subsidence after anterior cervical discectomy and fusion. This study focused on the radiological position of the inserted cages and radiological factors influencing the surgical method and examined their relationship with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiological alchemy in the AI era comes under close scrutiny-but is it entirely without meaning?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Claims data Learning &amp; Enhancing for Algorithm Refinement (CLEAR) Study: Overview of the Study Design and Baseline Profile]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Medical claims data are increasingly used in epidemiological studies, but are inadequately validated to ensure their reliability in identifying diseases. We developed the Claims data Learning & Enhancing for Algorithm Refinement (CLEAR) Study as a database platform to enable the systematic, low-cost implementation of validation studies in Japan. The CLEAR Study links routinely generated medical claims data from hospitals with diagnostic data (e.g., laboratory data and diagnostic imaging reports)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oncolytic Reovirus-Induced Prostaglandin E2 Production in Human Tumor Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oncolytic viruses, which kill tumor cells by tumor cell-specific replication, elicit superior antitumor immunity by efficiently activating the innate immune system. However, innate immunity-mediated inflammation is an undesirable consequence that often induces cellular production of immunosuppressive cellular factors. Among various immunosuppressive cellular factors, much attention has recently been focused on prostaglandin E2 (PGE2). In this study, we examined PGE2 production in human tumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aromatase inhibitors and medication-related osteonecrosis of the jaw: friends, foes, or bystanders?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Since the 1980s, aromatase inhibitors (AI) have been a cornerstone in the management of hormone receptor-positive breast cancer. However, because of their frequent co-prescription with antiresorptive agents, concerns have been raised regarding the potential contribution of AI to medication-related osteonecrosis of the jaw (MRONJ). We conducted a scoping review to investigate the possible association between AI use and MRONJ. Electronic searches were performed across five databases and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neurochemical Changes in GABA+, Glx, and the Excitatory/Inhibitory Ratio in the Calcarine Cortex with Healthy Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging has been associated with widespread alterations in neural structure and function, but the underlying biochemical changes remain less understood despite recent neurophysiological work suggesting age-related alterations in the excitatory/inhibitory (E/I) balance. In the current study, we used ¹H-MRS to quantify levels of excitatory (Glx: glutamate + glutamine) and inhibitory (GABA+: GABA + macromolecules) neurotransmitters in the calcarine cortex in 187 healthy adults (19-79 years-old)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The 'less-is-better' effect in capuchin monkeys (Sapajus sp.): some data and a contrast-like hypothesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given a choice between a simple option offering a preferred-food item (e.g., a grape, G) and a combo option offering the same preferred-food item plus a less-preferred food item (e.g., a grape + a slice of cucumber, GC), animals often behave suboptimally by either being indifferent between the two options or by preferring the simple option-the "less-is-better" effect. To explain indifference, the selective-value hypothesis assumes that, in the choice context, the subjective value (V) of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of polylactic acid aluminized film/cellulosic paper composite paper-based material for herba houttuyniae preservation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Paper-based materials offer a promising alternative to petroleum-based plastics in food packaging fields due to their eco-friendly attributes and abundance. However, the efficient fabrication of paper-based packaging materials with high barrier performance remains challenge. Herein, a facile method was employed to design the functional composite paper composed of cellulosic paper, polyvinylidene chloride/cellulose nanocrystal coatings, and polylactic acid (PLA) aluminized film. Owning to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simultaneous elimination of both toxic heavy metals and hazardous dyes from wastewater bodies by CNC-induced ceramics membranes: A crucial overview on the advanced fabrication and applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crude effluents have been ejected in huge volumes from various large/medium/small-scale industries and discharged directly into the environment. These are looking dangerous due to the loading of several toxic pollutants, which can contaminate the ecological balance/public safety. To protect this serious environmental pollution, production of polyfunctional bionanocomposites/adsorbents by discovering a more economical and eco-friendly technology is unquestionably a crucial issue. Therefore, in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathogenic POLE-Mutated Endometrial Carcinomas with a Non-Ultramutated Genome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endometrial carcinomas can be classified into one of four molecular subtypes, with the POLE-mutant subtype carrying the best prognosis. Pathogenic mutations in POLE are known to disrupt the proofreading function of DNA polymerase epsilon resulting in an ultramutated genome, typically defined as ≥100 mutations per mega-base. Routine Next Generation Sequencing was implemented on all endometrial carcinoma cases at our institution beginning December 2023 to aid in molecular subclassification. During...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The microbial metabolite I3A inhibits ferroptosis and the effectiveness of redox-based cancer therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferroptosis, a lipid peroxidation-driven form of regulated cell death, has emerged as a promising target for cancer therapy. However, the endogenous metabolic checkpoints restraining ferroptosis remain poorly defined. Here, we identify the tryptophan-derived indole metabolite indole-3-aldehyde (I3A), as a potent suppressor of ferroptosis. Mechanistically, I3A activates the aryl hydrocarbon receptor (AHR) to suppress JNK/c-JUN signaling under oxidative stress. This inhibition of c-JUN limits...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene expression analysis and proximity labeling reveal posttranscriptional functions of the yeast RNA Polymerase II regulator Def1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Def1 is a yeast protein that promotes transcription elongation and regulates the degradation of RNA polymerase II during transcription stress. Although Def1 is localized in the cytoplasm, its functions in this cellular compartment are not yet understood. Despite its well-established roles in transcription, a comprehensive genome-wide analysis of its impact on gene expression has not been conducted. Here, we performed RNA sequencing (RNA-seq) analysis on cells lacking DEF1 and surprisingly found...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes of laparoscopic versus robotic cholecystectomy approaches: a systematic review and GRADE assessment meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Laparoscopic cholecystectomy is the standard treatment for symptomatic cholelithiasis, cholycystitis and other gall bladder diseases. The adoption of robotic-assisted surgery has increased, but its comparative clinical outcomes remain debated. This meta-analysis compares the clinical outcomes of robotic versus laparoscopic cholecystectomy. A comprehensive literature search was conducted in PubMed, Cochrane, Scopus and Embase from inception until August 2025 to identify relevant studies. Risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterologous expression of soybean E3 ubiquitin ligase Glycine max Ring Zinc Finger 1-Like 1 (GmRZFL1) negatively responds to osmotic stress by participating in the abscisic acid signaling pathway in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FORT-IDS: a federated, optimized, robust and trustworthy intrusion detection system for IIoT security]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intrusion Detection Systems are essential for securing both IoT and enterprise networks, yet models that appear nearly perfect on in domain tests often collapse under cross domain evaluation. This generalization gap have limited the operational reliability and slowed the adoption. We present FORT-IDS, a Federated, Optimized, Robust and Trustworthy multi phase framework that unifies cross domain assessment, adversarial hardening and explainable artificial intelligence within a single adaptive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Explainable Hybrid CNN-LSTM Framework for Accurate Sequence-Based Classification of RNA N6-Methyladenosine (m6A) Modification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[N6-methyladenosine (m6A) is one of the most prevalent and functionally significant RNA modifications in eukaryotic transcriptomes, playing critical roles in post-transcriptional gene regulation. Accurate identification of m6A sites remains a considerable challenge due to complex sequence dependencies and limited labeled data. To address these issues, this paper proposed a hybrid Convolutional Neural Network and Long Short-Term Memory (CNN-LSTM) framework integrated with Shapley additive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41354216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing theta-gamma coupled brainwaves using ultrasound for spinal astrocyte revitalization and sustained neuropathic pain relief in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound stimulation is a promising non-invasive strategy for neuropathic pain, yet its sustained effects and underlying mechanisms remain poorly understood. We investigated brainwave-patterned low-intensity continuous theta-burst ultrasound stimulation (LI-cTBUS) in a mouse model of partial sciatic nerve crush injury (PCI). LI-cTBUS substantially alleviated mechanical allodynia during and after treatment. Mechanistically, PCI upregulated brain-derived neurotrophic factor (BDNF)/tropomyosin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IFN-γ and IL-17 elicit synergistic anti-mycobacterial responses by inhibiting coronin-1A retention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CD4^(+)IFN-γ^(+)IL-17^(+) T cells and their secreted cytokines play a critical role in the anti-mycobacterial response. However, the underlying synergistic mechanism of IFN-γ and IL-17 is little known. This study demonstrates that the downregulation of coronin-1A retention on the phagosome is a synergistic pathway for IFN-γ and IL-17 that kills Mycobacterium tuberculosis (Mtb) in macrophages. IL-17 alone does not play a role in intracellular Mtb killing but potentiates the anti-mycobactericidal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proton exchange membrane electrolytic enrichment system and tritium residual ratio curve method for analysis of tritium concentration in seawater]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41352936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Tritium monitoring in seawater has become increasingly important for environmental safety assessment, particularly following Japan's radioactive wastewater discharge. However, extremely low tritium concentrations in Korean coastal waters (0.09-0.45 Bq·L^(-1)) are below detection limits of conventional liquid scintillation counting methods. While alkaline electrolysis can concentrate tritium, it requires about 20 days processing time, making it unsuitable for rapid environmental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41352936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intravascular imaging-guided percutaneous coronary intervention for acute myocardial infarction according to ACC/AHA lesion classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41352656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with AMI, IVI-guided PCI was associated with a significantly lower risk of MACE in those with type B2/C lesions, but not in those with type A/B1 lesions. The prognostic benefit of IVI-guided PCI increased with greater lesion complexity in the infarct-related artery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41352656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seizure susceptibility relates to microglial TREM2 expression and morphology in a multiple repeated low-dose kainic acid model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41352235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microglia, the resident immune cells of the brain, play a critical role in maintaining homeostasis. In this study, we investigated changes in microglial phenotype associated with seizure susceptibility. Kainic acid (KA) was injected intraperitoneally, and when seizures reached Racine stage 4/5, administration was stopped, and mice were monitored for 60 min. Only mice that showed behavioral convulsive status epilepsy (SE) in the first experiment received a second KA injection 2 weeks later. Using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41352235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laminaria japonica extract alleviates fine particulate matter-exacerbated allergic rhinitis by inhibiting NLRP3-mediated pyroptosis and restoring epithelial barrier function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41351978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: LJE may have therapeutic potential for AR by regulating NLRP3-mediated pyroptosis and restoring epithelial barrier integrity through NF-κB/MAPK signaling pathway in allergic responses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41351978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoprinting with Crystal Engineering for Perovskite Lasers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41351530/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal halide perovskites are promising laser light sources due to their exceptional optical gain and solution processability. Structuring the cavity that determines lasing mode and performance, however, is mostly limited to chemical synthesis or in-plane multistep lithographic processes, which lead to high shaping rigidity or poor lasing performance. Here, we introduce a direct electrohydrodynamic three-dimensional printing that produces freestanding, high-performance inorganic perovskite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41351530/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Restoring the glioblastoma tumor microenvironment by targeting C5a with the antagonist W54011]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma (GBM) poses a serious challenge due to its aggressive nature and poor prognosis. Tumor mesenchymal stem-like cells (tMSLCs) secrete complement component 5a (C5a), altering the tumor microenvironment (TME) and promoting tumor progression. This study investigated W54011, a C5a antagonist, to counteract C5a-induced malignancy in GBM tumorspheres. We assessed GBM tissues for C5a receptor 1 (C5aR1) expression using gene profiling and survival analysis. GBM tumorspheres were cultured in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-updated FIB-4 index predicts coronary artery calcification progression in individuals with metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) is the most common chronic liver disorder worldwide and is increasingly recognized as a multisystem disease that elevates cardiovascular disease (CVD) risk. Liver fibrosis, rather than steatosis itself, is considered the primary determinant of prognosis in MASLD. The Fibrosis-4 (FIB-4) index, a simple noninvasive fibrosis score, has been linked to adverse hepatic outcomes, but its value for predicting subclinical atherosclerosis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Secular trends in dietary patterns among Korean adults: using data from the 2007-2022 Korea National health and nutrition examination survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353263/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353263/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conflicting entropy-driven zwitterionic dry polymer electrolytes for scalable high-energy all-solid-state batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inorganic electrolytes dominate all-solid-state batteries (ASSBs), but face critical limitations, including interfacial instability, complex manufacturing, and challenges in operating under commercially viable conditions. Here, we present a transformative approach using zwitterionic dry polymer electrolytes (ZPEs) designed via a conflicting entropy strategy to enable scalable energy-dense ASSBs. Guided by Flory-Huggins theory, liquid-state zwitterionic monomers exhibit higher mixing entropy with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinically aligned multi-modal image-text model for pan-cancer prognosis prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exhalation-synchronous robotic abdominal compression for user-centered respiratory assistance and training in neurological patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates that Exo-Abs can enhance respiratory performance in patients with weakened respiratory muscles, even in long-term usage scenarios. Along with the simplifications in the control policy and user interface, Exo-Abs has been shown to provide effective respiratory assistance over various breathing patterns and respiratory training contexts. The contribution of this study extends beyond demonstrating a user-centered system with improved usability and practicality,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conductivity-based choline contrast as a potential imaging biomarker for assessing abnormal choline metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Electrical conductivity imaging can more sensitively detect choline concentrations associated with abnormal metabolism and may serve not only as a complementary imaging method but also as a potential quantitative biomarker for cancer diagnosis and metabolic assessment in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41353122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251208024229&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>